<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-06-28T02:01:33.182Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is the 'resume=' kernel parameter necessary?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmaydz/is_the_resume_kernel_parameter_necessary/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmaydz/is_the_resume_kernel_parameter_necessary/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T01:26:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In arch wiki the following kernel parameter for boot loader is typically listed,
 root=PARTUUID=X resume=PARTUUID=Y rw initrd=\initramfs-linux.img
 and the resume= pointing to a swap partition is used for hibernation. I do have a swap partition, but do not have the resume= parameter, and the machine hibernates/resumes just fine. (However waking up from hibernation takes a looooong time, 10-20s with 16G mem.)
 So is the resume= necessary? Without this parameter, does hibernation by default still saves memory snapshot (roughly speaking) to the swap partition when available?
    submitted by    /u/notnullnone  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How can I enable NVIDIA graphics? Followed the wiki and screenfetch still shows Intel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmaexa/how_can_i_enable_nvidia_graphics_followed_the/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmaexa/how_can_i_enable_nvidia_graphics_followed_the/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T00:59:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://wiki.archlinux.org/title/NVIDIA_Optimus#Use_NVIDIA_graphics_only
 I copied over that configuration blurb into where it said to. Since I'm using the LightDM welcome screen screen locker, I also copied over that blurb.
 I have the nvidia package installed.
 I rebooted, but nothing happened. Screenfetch still shows Intel graphics.
 What's wrong?
    submitted by    /u/Remarkable-River-300  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Facebook Pictures Not Loading? Here Are the Fixes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=post-ideas&amp;p=362094</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/13900599/fix-facebook-pictures-not-loading"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Facebook has become ubiquitous in today’s world. It’s something you expect to always be there working, ready to service your need to snoop on people from your distant past and get involved in whatever strange Facebook groups you’re part of. If pictures are not loading on Facebook, then that defeats a big point of the social site’s appeal. For this reason, we’ve put together a list of reasons your Facebook pictures might not be loading and what you can do about it.
   

Content

1. Check Facebook Server Status
2. Allow Sites to Show Images in Browser
3. Clear Browser Cache
4. Troubleshoot Internet Problems
5. Change DNS Settings
6. Reset Network Configurations
7. Disable Ad Blocker
8. Clear Facebook Cache (Android/iOS)
9. Disable Data Saver (Android)
10. Open Facebook in Your Mobile Browser (Android & iOS)
11. Try Facebook Lite (Android)
12. Reinstall the App
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexandra Arici</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Having issues with USB input devices not being registered by the system.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vm8fbd/having_issues_with_usb_input_devices_not_being/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vm8fbd/having_issues_with_usb_input_devices_not_being/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T23:21:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(A) yes this is in relation to my Steam Deck, I did ask on that Sub and got nothing ... My gut says this is an OS setting issue, not a Steam issue. (B) I haven't used a Linux desktop in over a Decade & a lot has changed, but I am trying to learn. (C) I tried googling this & my issues seems to be unique.
 I can't get my Steam Deck to recognize any USB wired input devices. Bluetooth works fine, but directly connecting a USB device (either through a dock or directly plugging in a single device with a USB-C to USB-C cable). Display out works when connecting a Dock, all devices I plug in directly will light up and start charging from the Deck, but no input devices are detected by the system.
 I have tried two different Docks, two sets of KB+M (my gaming ones off my main PC and a generic Dell Set), an 8BitDo SN30 game pad, and a Rii i8 mini KB+trackpad.
 None of them will show up when connected through USB, but both my Gaming mouse from corsair & the SN30 worked fine when connect through Bluetooth. The only things I have done with Desktop mode is try out Heroic Game Launcher and Lutris, install flat seal, and install ProtonUp-QT ... All done through the discovery application.
 The over all symptoms of this make me think that some kind of permission for USB PnP detection got turned off, but I don't know enough about Linux to start guessing at where to find those: any suggestions for how to fix this?
    submitted by    /u/Xijit  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[qusetion, how do you remove the bottom panel from xfce?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vm828t/qusetion_how_do_you_remove_the_bottom_panel_from/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vm828t/qusetion_how_do_you_remove_the_bottom_panel_from/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T23:03:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[i searched everything and didnt find the solution
 https://imgur.com/a/ekCAAuK
    submitted by    /u/angryteapod  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel Begins Publishing Habana Labs Gaudi2 Linux Driver Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-Gaudi2-Linux-Driver</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-Gaudi2-Linux-Driver"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T22:36:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last month for their Vision conference, Intel announced the Habana Labs Gaudi2 accelerator. Gaudi2 is the second-generation offering from Intel-owned Habana Labs for training and inference.  The open-source Linux kernel driver support for Gaudi2 is now getting underway along with accompanying open-source user-space software stack support...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git 2.37 Released With Sparse Index Feature Now Ready For Widespread Use]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Git-2.37-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Git-2.37-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T22:19:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git 2.37 is out today as the latest feature update to this widely-used, distributed revision control system...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Screen Capture (XSHM)" is no longer there is OBS Studio]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vm6u7u/screen_capture_xshm_is_no_longer_there_is_obs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vm6u7u/screen_capture_xshm_is_no_longer_there_is_obs/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T22:10:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have absolutely no idea how OBS Studio works, but yeah, the option that I use for screen capture on Arch Linux (Screen Capture (XSHM)) is no longer there.
 It started with OBS saying something like it "doesn't exist" (sorry, I didn't take a screenshot nor do I fully remember what it exactly said) and for further investigation, upon removing it, there is now no option altogether.
 After this happening, I also notice Gnome's screen recording utility also isn't working now either. All videos save as a 0 second video.
 Is this a dependency issue? Is anybody else having this issue? Please help!
    submitted by    /u/jaamivstheworld  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come controllare un PC da remoto: guida a Iperius Remote 4 (desktop remoto e assistenza)]]></title>
        <id>1360|20220628000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/controllo-remoto-270/come-controllare-pc-remoto-guida-iperius-remote-4-desktop-remoto-assistenza-1360"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Il lavoro remoto è ormai una prassi consolidata per molti di noi, con tutte le comodità e tutte le problematiche che questo comporta. Fra le criticità introdotte dal lavorare lontano da colleghi e attrezzature aziendali, figura sicuramente la necessità di collegarsi ai computer remoti, magari per interagire con la propria postazione fissa in sede o fornire assistenza ad un altro lavoratore geograficamente lontano da noi. In questa situazione, ci viene in aiuto Iperius Remote 4: una soluzione integrata che risponde a tutte le necessità di controllo e assistenza remoti. Vediamo dunque come utilizzarlo in questa nostra guida a Iperius Remote 4
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fix Mobile Data Not Working on Android]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=165018</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/4557633/fix-cellular-data-not-working-on-android"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cellular data, mobile data, whatever you want to call it, is one of those things that only becomes a life necessity once you acquire your first smartphone. It’s only when you lose connectivity that you realize you don’t know how to get anywhere without Google Maps, don’t have anything to read without Flipboard, and don’t know how to communicate with people through any medium other than WhatsApp.
    
When mobile data stops working on Android, it’s world-shattering, in other words. Here are some tips on how to get it back.
   

Content

1. Reset Your APNs
2. Set APN Protocol to iPv4/IPv6
3. Enter Your APN Settings Manually
4. Wipe Cache Partition from Recovery
5. Reset Your Phone’s Network Connection
6. Enable the Right Network Mode
7. Reset Networks
8. Remove and Reinsert Your SIM Card
9. Do You Have a Mobile Data Limit?
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Crystal Crowder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Play Adobe Flash SWF Files Outside Your Web Browser]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=438141</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/438141/how-to-play-adobe-flash-swf-files-outside-your-web-browser/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web browsers have dropped support for Flash, but what if you have an SWF file to open? Never fear: Adobe offered a hidden Flash Player download for Windows, Mac, and Linux that is still available from the Wayback Machine. You can open an SWF file outside your browser.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Is the Apple TV 4K so Expensive?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/121779/why-is-the-apple-tv-4k-so-expensive/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/121779/why-is-the-apple-tv-4k-so-expensive/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T20:43:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a world of $50 streaming sticks, the $180 Apple TV 4K looks like an outrageous purchase. But even the biggest Android nerds swoon over Apple TV 4K when they see it in person. Its high price comes with premium features, and for some people, it’s the best streaming device available today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to boot into Arch while keeping secure boot on?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vm52ka/how_to_boot_into_arch_while_keeping_secure_boot_on/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vm52ka/how_to_boot_into_arch_while_keeping_secure_boot_on/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T20:28:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I need secure boot to be on to be able to play Valorant on Windows, but turning it on doesn't let me boot into the Arch Linux installation at all. It says 
  
Secure boot violation: Invalid signature detected
  
I can't even install Arch without disabling it
    submitted by    /u/kushal10  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Microsoft 365?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=669400</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/669400/what-is-microsoft-365/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re familiar with Office 365, you already know what Microsoft 365 is. It’s a subscription plan that costs $100 per year of up to six people or $70 per year for one person. Microsoft hasn’t raised the price.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web-Based Apps Are About to Get Better on Windows 10]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=814204</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/814204/web-based-apps-are-about-to-get-better-on-windows-10/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T19:31:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many desktop applications, like Discord and Spotify, are based on web technologies and usually eat up system resources than proper native apps. Microsoft has been working on an alternative to the Electron framework that most web-based apps use, and now it’s rolling out on Windows 10.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can't download hyprland-git]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vm3mp2/cant_download_hyprlandgit/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vm3mp2/cant_download_hyprlandgit/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T19:25:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey guys,
 ​
 I am trying to install hyprland but the PKGBUILD file is not being downloaded. Also shows "error: target not found" for all dependencies. 
 Anyone else having this issue?
 ​
 Thanks!
    submitted by    /u/DecafDicaprio  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save $250 on a Lenovo Flex 5 Ideapad with Windows 11 Home]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=470048</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15123260/lenovo-flex-5-ideapad"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you still looking for an affordable device that will allow you to run Windows 11? This is a great way to jump in. You can get a Lenovo Flex 5 Ideapad with Windows 11 Home built in, along with AMD Radeon graphics, AMD Ryzen 5 5500U, and Alexa.
    
The Ryzen mobile processor provides the power for the Ideapad. It also includes Radeon graphics, 16GB DDR4 RAM, and 256GB NVMe SSD storage. A narrow bezel on all four sides gives you more viewing area and more area to work on the 14″ IPS FHD 1920 x 1080 display. Added to that is Wi-Fi 6, Bluetooth 5, two USB-A ports, one USB-C port with PD, HDMI, a 4-in-1 card reader, and an audio jack.
   
 
   
If you’re the creative type, the Lenovo Flex 5 Ideapad is designed for you. It will keep your creativity flowing wherever you happen to be. It even includes a Lenovo Digital Pen to jot down and expand all of your ideas.
    
The 360º hinge allows you... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Personal Tasks Directly in Google Chat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=811566</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/811566/create-personal-tasks-in-google-chat/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T19:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many times, projects and goals develop out of emails or messaging discussions. If you’re using Google Chat, you can turn a message turn into a task. Then access it like your other Google Tasks or in Google Calendar.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Android malware ‘Revive’ impersonates BBVA bank’s 2FA app]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/android-malware-revive-impersonates-bbva-bank-s-2fa-app/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/android-malware-revive-impersonates-bbva-bank-s-2fa-app/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T18:30:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new Android banking malware named Revive has been discovered that impersonates a 2FA application required to log into BBVA bank accounts in Spain. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GCC-Rust Feedback Sought - Possibly Aiming For Upstream In GCC 13]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=GCC-Rust-Upstream-Talk-Thread</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=GCC-Rust-Upstream-Talk-Thread"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T18:10:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Rust-GCC front-end that allows Rust code to be compiled with the GNU Compiler Collection (GCC) could possibly be upstreamed for next year's GCC 13 compiler release but not necessarily complete at that stage. In any case, it's good seeing progress on Rust-GCC as an alternative to Rust's official LLVM-based compiler...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Send Mobile Push Notifications With PHP and Firebase]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?post_type=devops&amp;p=800731</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/devops/how-to-send-mobile-push-notifications-with-php-and-firebase/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T18:07:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s Firebase Cloud Messaging (FCM) service is a free and convenient way to distribute push notifications to mobile devices. It works with iOS, Android, and web targets, abstracting away the differences between platforms. You send your payload once to Firebase’s API and get real-time delivery to all your users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US, Brazil seize 272 websites used to illegally download music]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-brazil-seize-272-websites-used-to-illegally-download-music/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-brazil-seize-272-websites-used-to-illegally-download-music/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T18:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The domains of six websites that streamed and provided illegal downloads of copyrighted music were seized by U.S. Homeland Security Investigations (HSI) and the Department of Justice. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Access the Boot Menu in Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809906</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809906/how-to-access-the-boot-menu-in-windows-11/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T18:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Advanced Options Menu, sometimes called the Boot Menu, contains tools and configuration options you can use to troubleshoot or repair your PC. Here’s how to use it on Windows 11.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Lewis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mercedes-Benz Tested an EV With a 747-Mile Range]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=814221</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/814221/mercedes-benz-tested-an-ev-with-a-747-mile-range/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T17:49:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Driving range is a critical issue for electric cars, especially since charging stations still aren’t as common as gas stations. Thankfully, the maximum range on EVs is continuing to improve, as proven by a recent test from Mercedes-Benz.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux "RADV" Radeon Driver Gets A Big Speed-Up For 16-bit FidelityFX Super Resolution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=RADV-Faster-16-bit-FSR</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=RADV-Faster-16-bit-FSR"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T17:30:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Merged today to Mesa 22.2 was a four month old merge request for the open-source Radeon Vulkan driver "RADV" that significantly improves the 16-bit FidelityFX Super Resolution (FSR) performance...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SKG V7 Smartwatch Review]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=496767</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15396925/skg-v7-smartwatch"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T17:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smartwatches can be helpful yet also really expensive. If you think you don’t have the funds to put out for a smartwatch, there are some budget models that may do all the necessary functions. This review covers the SKG V7 Smartwatch to see if it covers both of those metrics: budget and necessary functions.
    
This is a sponsored article and was made possible by SKG. The actual contents and opinions are the sole views of the author who maintains editorial independence, even when a post is sponsored.
    
Setting Up the SKG V7 Smartwatch
    
To prove that the SKG V7 Smartwatch includes what’s necessary, it ships with only three items:
   
 
   
Smartwatch
Charging cord
Quick start guide
   
 
   
Before setting up the smartwatch, you need to charge it to 100%. The charging cord fits into a standard USB-A charging brick and magnetically attaches to the back of the... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Hack Apple CarPlay Onto Any Tesla Now]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/121775/you-can-hack-apple-carplay-onto-any-tesla-now/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/121775/you-can-hack-apple-carplay-onto-any-tesla-now/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T17:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier this year, Polish developer Michał Gapiński released a clever hack allowing Android Auto or Apple’s CarPlay to run on select Tesla vehicles. And while the initial version was only a beta, the latest release has new features and works on any Tesla model.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Type an Em Dash on Windows or Mac]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=811997</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/811997/how-to-type-an-em-dash-on-windows-or-mac/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T17:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’d like to type a long dash—called an em dash—on a Windows PC or Mac, you need to take some extra steps because it’s not on your keyboard. Here’s how to get an em dash.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can't delete @.snapshots subvolume (BTRFS)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vm07ae/cant_delete_snapshots_subvolume_btrfs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vm07ae/cant_delete_snapshots_subvolume_btrfs/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T16:58:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Heya! Loving BTRFS so far. Decided to do a new install with the archinstall script and use the default BTRFS subvolume layout. I'm trying to delete my @.snapshots subvolume in order to create a @snaphots subvol due to my OCD. 
 I've tried changing the permissions from RO to RW, deleting the default mount point at /.snapshots and re-mounting the subvol at /mnt/snapshots to no avail. 
 I'm running sudo btrfs subvolume delete /mnt/snapshots/@.snapshots with the error "ERROR: Could not statfs: No such file or directory"
 If I try a different syntax with sudo btrfs subvolume delete /mnt/snapshots/ /@.snapshots I end up getting back
 "Delete subvolume (no-commit): '/mnt/snapshots'
 ERROR: Could not destroy subvolume/snapshot: Invalid argument"
 Any help would be much appreciated.
 Cheers!
    submitted by    /u/Outsideyourboxes  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft will fix Windows RRAS, VPN issues for all users in July]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-will-fix-windows-rras-vpn-issues-for-all-users-in-july/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-will-fix-windows-rras-vpn-issues-for-all-users-in-july/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has finally confirmed Internet connectivity issues affecting servers with Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) enabled after installing Windows updates released as part of this month's Patch Tuesday. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Phishing più furbo con il componente WebView2 di Edge: rischio furti d'identità]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Phishing-piu-furbo-con-il-componente-WebView2-di-Edge-rischio-furti-d-identita_24711</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Phishing-piu-furbo-con-il-componente-WebView2-di-Edge-rischio-furti-d-identita_24711"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WebView2 è un controllo di Microsoft Edge che permette agli sviluppatori di integrare le principali tecnologie per il Web, come ad esempio HTML, CSS e JavaScript, all'interno di applicazioni native.Con WebView2 il programmatore può creare un eseguibile in grado di comunicare con le applicazioni Web in modo simile a quanto fa un browser.Un ricercatore indipendente ha dimostrato che è possibile utilizzare applicazioni basate su WebView2 per sottrarre dati personali come le credenziali di accesso ai principali servizi online e superare i meccanismi di autenticazione a due fattori.Il ricercatore spiega di aver trovato il modo per iniettare codice JavaScript al fine di registrare tutti i tasti premuti dall'utente (keylogger).WebView2 fornisce anche funzionalità integrate per estrarre il contenu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vice Society claims ransomware attack on Med. University of Innsbruck]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/vice-society-claims-ransomware-attack-on-med-university-of-innsbruck/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/vice-society-claims-ransomware-attack-on-med-university-of-innsbruck/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T16:31:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Vice Society ransomware gang has claimed responsibility for last week's cyberattack against the Medical University of Innsbruck, which caused severe IT service disruption and the alleged theft of data. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come stampare da Android su qualsiasi stampante]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2013/06/come-stampare-da-android-su-qualsiasi.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2013/06/come-stampare-da-android-su-qualsiasi.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T16:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Con i moderni smartphone ed i tablet è possibile stampare qualsiasi documento senza bisogno di trasferirlo ogni volta sul PC: questa comodità è sfruttabile in particolare in ufficio, dove potrebbe sicuramente esserci la necessità di stampare improvvisamente un foglio di calcolo o un documento appena ricevuto via email.

 Quando si utilizza un telefono Android abbiamo diversi metodi per aggiungere...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Earth.fm Streams Relaxing Nature Sounds from Around the World]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/121765/earth-fm-streams-relaxing-nature-sounds-from-around-the-world/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/121765/earth-fm-streams-relaxing-nature-sounds-from-around-the-world/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T16:17:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s nothing more relaxing than the sound of nature, especially when you’re stuck at a desk all day. And that’s what makes Earth.fm so interesting—it’s a website that lets you stream the “natural soundscapes” of several locations across the globe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Cheapest Way to Get iMessage on Android (and Windows)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=810209</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/810209/the-cheapest-way-to-get-imessage-on-android-and-windows/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[iMessage on Android—the white whale of many smartphone users. We’ve shown you how to use iMessage on Android and Windows, but there’s a pretty big barrier to entry. Let’s find the cheapest way to do it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recording Academy’s VP of D.E.I. Ryan Butler Tells Us What Brings Him Joy Online]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.mozilla.org/?p=69351</id>
        <link href="https://blog.mozilla.org/en/internet-culture/recording-academys-vp-of-d-e-i-ryan-butler-tells-us-what-brings-him-joy-online/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here at Mozilla, we are the first to admit the internet isn’t perfect, but we are also quick to point out that the internet is pretty darn magical. The internet opens up doors and opportunities, allows for people to connect with others, and lets everyone find where they belong — their corners of the internet. […]
The post Recording Academy’s VP of D.E.I. Ryan Butler Tells Us What Brings Him Joy Online appeared first on The Mozilla Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Damiano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung's Wackiest Monitor Could Go On Sale This Summer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/121759/samsungs-wackiest-monitor-could-go-on-sale-this-summer/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/121759/samsungs-wackiest-monitor-could-go-on-sale-this-summer/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T15:57:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier this year, Samsung unveiled its massive 55-inch curved gaming monitor called the Odyssey Ark. And while we haven’t heard much about it since, new reports suggest Samsung’s wild new monitor will arrive later this summer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Exchange bug abused to hack building automation systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-exchange-bug-abused-to-hack-building-automation-systems/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-exchange-bug-abused-to-hack-building-automation-systems/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T15:39:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Chinese-speaking threat actor has hacked into the building automation systems (used to control HVAC, fire, and security functions) of several Asian organizations to backdoor their networks and gain access to more secured areas in their networks. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Containerize a Legacy Application]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?post_type=devops&amp;p=800745</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/devops/how-to-containerize-a-legacy-application/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T15:36:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Containerization has transformed how new applications are developed and deployed. However many organizations retain a back catalog of older systems that necessitate a different approach. This disconnect between new and old doesn’t have to be perpetuated: you can package older systems as containers too, making it easier to continue evolving them with more modern development methods.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Plans a Slew of Ambitious Products for Late 2022 and Early 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/121756/apple-plans-a-slew-of-ambitious-products-for-late-2022-and-early-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/121756/apple-plans-a-slew-of-ambitious-products-for-late-2022-and-early-2023/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T15:31:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It seems that Apple was holding out during its June WWDC conference. As reported in Mark Gurman’s Power On newsletter, Apple will launch a “deluge” of ambitious new products in late 2022 and early 2023. These new products include a mixed reality headset, new “core” devices,’ and revamped versions of the Apple TV, Apple Watch, AirPods Pro, and HomePod.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 Ways to View Deleted Reddit Posts and Comments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=156639</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/4054948/access-deleted-comments-reddit"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reddit is home to the internet’s anonymous discussions on a variety of topics and interests. With the cloak of anonymity given by Reddit, users are free to say whatever they want, which isn’t always a good thing. 
    
When a post or comment goes against a subreddit’s rules, they’re deleted using bots or human moderators. Reddit users also have the option to delete their own posts and comments. But are those deleted items gone for ever? What if you’re curious to read a deleted post or comment on Reddit? You can, with the help of certain websites and browser extensions, which we discuss here.
   

Content

1. Unddit
2. Reveddit
3. Wayback Machine
4. Resavr
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:8 of the Best Reddit Clients for iOS and Android
    
1. Unddit
    
Unddit is... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Natalie dela Vega</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 10 Might Get a Major Update In 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=814170</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/814170/microsoft-10-might-get-a-major-update-in-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T15:24:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft is preparing to release a ’22H2′ update for Windows 11, the first major update since Windows 11 arrived last year. People still using Windows 10 might get their own 22H2 update, too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LockBit 3.0 introduces the first ransomware bug bounty program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/lockbit-30-introduces-the-first-ransomware-bug-bounty-program/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/lockbit-30-introduces-the-first-ransomware-bug-bounty-program/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T15:09:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LockBit ransomware operation has released 'LockBit 3.0,' introducing the first ransomware bug bounty program and leaking new extortion tactics and Zcash cryptocurrency payment options. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting NVIDIA dGPU recognized under a Wayland session]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlxl2d/getting_nvidia_dgpu_recognized_under_a_wayland/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlxl2d/getting_nvidia_dgpu_recognized_under_a_wayland/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T15:04:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! I wonder how to get NVIDIA dGPU recognized in GNOME/KDE Wayland session system settings. I experiences a lot of stuttering on the external monitor in Wayland and the system settings doesn't show the NVIDIA dGPU.
 Currently I have a gaming laptop with Intel + NVIDIA running on Xorg on an external monitor hooked up to the dGPU. The internal screen is currently disabled. It's buttery smooth, but when I switched to a Wayland session ( GNOME and KDE ), the inner screen is buttery smooth, but the external monitor stutters a lot.
 What I have done so far:
 Install mesa,xorg
 Install nvidia, set nvidia-drm.modeset=1 parameter, added nvidia nvidia_modeset nvidia_uvm nvidia_drm i915 into MODULES section of mkinitcpio.conf
 Run nvidia-xconfig twice, one with the external monitor disabled, one with the external monitor enabled
 I haven't touched any settings related to optimus yet.
    submitted by    /u/hydrocryo01  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Handy Microsoft Excel Features You May Have Missed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=807862</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/807862/handy-excel-features/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T15:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes when you use applications every day, new features can go unnoticed. So that you’re up to speed with useful tools for your spreadsheets, take a look at these Microsoft Excel features you may have missed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Suspending VMware virtual machines on standby, reboot and shutdown]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlx3z6/suspending_vmware_virtual_machines_on_standby/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlx3z6/suspending_vmware_virtual_machines_on_standby/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T14:43:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey,
 I'd like to suspend my VMs e.g. when the powerbutton is pressed, I restart my machine or shut it down. A Systemd service seems reasonable to do this.
 There are several old topics on this issue on Fedora mailing list e.g. but I cannot get it to work.
 https://lists.fedoraproject.org/pipermail/users/2011-December/409819.html
 It also seems this guy used Systemd in the wrong way according to many comments that you find on Google on this topic. Systemd does not wait for the script to be finished. Executing the script manually does exactly what it's intended for.
 Is there a proper way to suspend the machines?On the Arch wiki there is this section https://wiki.archlinux.org/title/VMware#Suspend_virtual_machines_before_host_suspend/hibernatebut the script doesn't get triggered on Sway e.g. when I poweroff the host although I copied it to
 /usr/lib/systemd/system-shutdown/vmware-suspend-all.sh 
 giving it +x execution permissions for any user. 
 Edit: It seems /usr/lib/systemd/system-shutdown/ is also not correct as this happens when the system already is mounted read only.
 Did you figure out how it works reliably?
    submitted by    /u/cmprmsd  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Pixel 6a Appears to Solve the Pixel 6's Biggest Problem]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/121754/the-pixel-6a-appears-to-solve-the-pixel-6s-biggest-problem/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/121754/the-pixel-6a-appears-to-solve-the-pixel-6s-biggest-problem/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T14:38:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Pixel 6 is plagued by bugs and annoyances, most notably a slow fingerprint sensor. And it seems that Google will fix this problem with the Pixel 6a. In an early review video, Malaysian YouTuber Fazli Halim shows the Pixel 6a besting the Pixel 6 in both fingerprint sensor speed and responsiveness.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come liberare spazio in Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/06/come-liberare-spazio-in-windows-11.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/06/come-liberare-spazio-in-windows-11.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T14:35:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 ha portato con sè numerose novità anche dal punto di vista dell'ottimizzazione e della manutenzione del sistema. Se fino a Windows 10 poteva ancora essere utile un programma di pulizia come CClenaer, con Windows 11 questo tipo di programmi è totalmente superfluo, visto che Microsoft ha introdotto degli efficaci strumenti di pulizia all'interno delle impostazioni. 
Nella guida che segue...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[co-dependent package update behavior]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlwujt/codependent_package_update_behavior/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlwujt/codependent_package_update_behavior/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T14:31:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of my only dislikes of arch package management is co-dependent packages. If two packages require a specific version of each other and you update both at the same time it will always fail. As it can only update one package at a time. From an ignorant standpoint it seems ideal to combine the package install success of co-dependant packages, and try them both, failing and reverting only if any package fails.
 Is there currently a more elegant way to handle this rather than remove both packages and reinstall them?
 I know it's the AUR but my annoying example is zfs-utils/zfs-dkms. This comes up each kernel update but I'm pretty sure I've run into before with more supported packages, albeit much less frequently.
    submitted by    /u/habys  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple’s New 13-Inch MacBook Pro Has One Big Downgrade]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=814134</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/814134/apples-new-13-inch-macbook-pro-has-one-big-downgrade/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T14:13:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple revealed a new 13-inch MacBook Pro earlier this month, powered by the company’s new M2 chipset. Now that the laptop is starting to arrive on buyers’ doorsteps, at least one problem has become apparent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft: Recent Windows updates caused Edge freeze issues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-recent-windows-updates-caused-edge-freeze-issues/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-recent-windows-updates-caused-edge-freeze-issues/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T14:08:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft says it addressed a known issue that was causing all Microsoft Edge tabs running IE mode to stop responding if one of the opened sites displayed a modal dialog box after issuing a window.focus call. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Wi-Fi Adapters of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=804785</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/804785/best-wi-fi-adapter/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T14:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Choosing the right Wi-Fi adapter can upgrade a subpar wireless connection to one that rivals an Ethernet connection. Whether you need to upgrade your laptop Wi-Fi or add wireless capabilities to your desktop tower, we’ve picked out the best adapters for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Russ Ware</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I've got 4 GB of unused ram. Is there a way to use it to speed up apps opening time ?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlvse4/ive_got_4_gb_of_unused_ram_is_there_a_way_to_use/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlvse4/ive_got_4_gb_of_unused_ram_is_there_a_way_to_use/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T13:41:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The title is clear enough. I've got an HDD that make apps quite slow to open, and I'm looking for a way to use the 4 GB of ram that's mostly unused (I've got 6 GB in total) to fix this problem. Thanks!
    submitted by    /u/1_7xr  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Performance Cost To A Proposed Fedora 37 CFLAGS/CXXFLAGS Change]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31240</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31240"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T13:30:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coming about last week was a Fedora 37 change proposal to improve the profiling and debugging of Fedora packages but with possible performance costs. That suggested change is about adding "-fno-omit-frame-pointer" to the default CFLAGS/CXXFLAGS when building packages so the frame pointer is always available for improving the debugging/profiling of the stock Fedora packages. Unfortunately, it can come with significant performance costs as these benchmarks show.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel Releases OSPRay Studio v0.11 Visualization / Ray-Tracing App]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-OSPRay-Studio-0.11</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-OSPRay-Studio-0.11"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of Intel's many wonderful open-source projects for creators is OSPRay Studio that is their interactive visualization and ray-tracing application built atop their OSPRay portable ray-tracing engine. OSPRay Studio has been making steady progress since its 2020 debut and out today is their newest update...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Help]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlvcxf/help/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlvcxf/help/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T13:19:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I just bought an rog flow x13, and now I'm trying to optimize it for my new arch install.
 And there's a really github repository explaining, how to do it.
 But I don't understand what to do in "on archlinux install edit boot config and append to cmdline"
    submitted by    /u/64Yoshi64  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Disadvantages of VPN Nobody is Talking About]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/?p=60066</id>
        <link href="https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/vpn-cons/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T13:01:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using a VPN is pretty common these days as it allows you to access region-specific content and blocked websites and enables you to anonymously surf the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hongkiat Lim</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What to Look For in a Good Ergonomic Chair]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=808425</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/808425/what-to-look-for-in-a-good-ergonomic-chair/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T13:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We already spend too much time sitting in front of a computer, but if you also have a bad chair, you’re in real trouble. There are so many “ergonomic” chairs that it’s hard to know what matters when buying one.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sydney Butler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fopo Triple Laptop Screen Extender Review: Efficiency at the Cost of Comfort]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/114348/fopo-triple-laptop-screen-extender-review/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/114348/fopo-triple-laptop-screen-extender-review/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Short on desk space since you started working from home? Need more screens while you travel? The Model S12 Fopo Portable Monitor adds two displays to your laptop with the goal of upping productivity, and it certainly succeeds—but not without flaw. Here’s what you should know before you buy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcus Mears III</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Opinion: Cheaper Media Streaming tiers support by advertisement is a good development]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179386</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/27/opinion-cheaper-media-streaming-tiers-support-by-advertisement-is-a-good-development/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T12:55:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new streaming service is launched every other month it seems. With more and more streaming services competing for customers, it is not only the customers that need to adjust to the […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Opinion: Cheaper Media Streaming tiers support by advertisement is a good development appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox 102 Available With Transform Streams, Geoclue On Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Firefox-102-Download</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Firefox-102-Download"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T12:45:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Firefox 102.0 release is now available for download ahead of its stable release announcement tomorrow...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here's Everything Coming to Netflix the Week of June 27, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lifesavvy.com/134201/heres-everything-coming-to-netflix-the-week-of-june-27-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lifesavvy.com/134201/heres-everything-coming-to-netflix-the-week-of-june-27-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T12:30:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While it’s still June at the moment, July begins at the end of this week. That means two things for Netflix fans. First, your massive beginning of the month drop is here, and second, the final two episodes of Stranger Things Volume Four are here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shea Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PSA: Not All Steam Games Have DRM (Here’s How to Tell)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=813209</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/813209/psa-not-all-steam-games-have-drm-heres-how-to-tell/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s a common misconception that all games purchased through Steam have DRM (Digital Rights Management) enabled by the very nature of being on Steam, but that’s not the case. Here’s why, and how to tell if your game is DRM-free.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Fitzpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[suplicant interface state disconnected,what should I do?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlu7bh/suplicant_interface_state_disconnectedwhat_should/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlu7bh/suplicant_interface_state_disconnectedwhat_should/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T12:19:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EDIT: I did the solution from this thread and it is fixed https://www.linuxquestions.org/questions/linux-newbie-8/wifi-issue-4175648868/
 output of systemctl status NetworkManager
 Loaded: loaded (/usr/lib/systemd/system/NetworkManager.service; enabled; vendor preset: disabled)
 Drop-In: /usr/lib/systemd/system/NetworkManager.service.d
 └─NetworkManager-ovs.conf
 Active: active (running) since Mon 2022-06-27 17:44:53 IST; 1min 46s ago
 Docs: man:NetworkManager(8)
 Main PID: 4642 (NetworkManager)
 Tasks: 3 (limit: 18965)
 Memory: 5.3M
 CPU: 137ms
 CGroup: /system.slice/NetworkManager.service
 └─4642 /usr/bin/NetworkManager --no-daemon
 ​
 Jun 27 17:46:09 archlinux NetworkManager[4642]: <info> [1656332169.8739] dhcp4 (enp0s20f0u4): activation: beginning transaction (timeout in 45 seconds)
 Jun 27 17:46:11 archlinux NetworkManager[4642]: <info> [1656332171.9689] dhcp4 (enp0s20f0u4): state changed new lease, address=192.168.163.163
 Jun 27 17:46:11 archlinux NetworkManager[4642]: <info> [1656332171.9747] device (enp0s20f0u4): state change: ip-config -> ip-check (reason 'none', sys-iface-state: 'managed')
 Jun 27 17:46:11 archlinux NetworkManager[4642]: <info> [1656332171.9815] device (enp0s20f0u4): state change: ip-check -> secondaries (reason 'none', sys-iface-state: 'managed')
 Jun 27 17:46:11 archlinux NetworkManager[4642]: <info> [1656332171.9816] device (enp0s20f0u4): state change: secondaries -> activated (reason 'none', sys-iface-state: 'managed')
 Jun 27 17:46: 
    submitted by    /u/DrWeird31  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come collegarsi al Wi-Fi senza password]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2017/12/collegare-il-pc-al-wifi-senza-password.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2017/12/collegare-il-pc-al-wifi-senza-password.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T12:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Di base per collegare un PC a internet si seleziona la rete Wi-Fi dall'apposito menu e di inserisce la password d'accesso alla rete wireless per iniziare subito a navigare.

 Se si utilizza una password complessa o non ricordiamo la password usata per quella specifica rete possiamo collegare il PC alla rete Wi-Fi con Internet utilizzando WPS, una speciale funzione che non richiede l'inserimento...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can You Recover Data From a Destroyed iPhone?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=805955</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/805955/can-you-recover-data-from-a-destroyed-iphone/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Has your iPhone been damaged to the point of no longer being usable? Is the screen smashed or does it not even turn on? You can buy a new iPhone, but the data on your old device may be irreplaceable. Fortunately, you may be able to recover it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Waterfox G5 will be based on Firefox ESR 102; users will be upgraded from G4 automatically]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179378</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/27/waterfox-g5-will-be-based-on-firefox-esr-102-users-will-be-upgraded-from-g4-automatically/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T11:46:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alex Kontos, the developer of Waterfox, has announced that the browser is being migrated to Firefox ESR 102. The current version of the popular application, Waterfox G4, is based on Firefox ESR […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Waterfox G5 will be based on Firefox ESR 102; users will be upgraded from G4 automatically appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unable to lock gnome desktop]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlt4tx/unable_to_lock_gnome_desktop/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlt4tx/unable_to_lock_gnome_desktop/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T11:16:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A while ago the lock button in my Gnome desktop disappeared at work, Super + L also does nothing. It happened after a GPU driver bug hard-crashed my system, and although I find it rather absurd to correlate the two, I don't really have any other event to relate it to. I've updated the system and reinstalled all Gnome packages, but the issue remains. It's still possible to log out or switch user, but for some reason I am unable to get to the lock screen. This is especially problematic because the computer will suspend after a while if you go to the switch-user menu, and I need to access my workstation remotely some times. 
 Any ideas of what to do, or what the cause could be? I guess there could be an event log where I can see what happens when I press Super + L?
    submitted by    /u/FluxusMagna  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram Desktop: cos'è, come funziona e quali le sue caratteristiche]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Telegram-Desktop-cos-e-come-funziona-e-quali-le-sue-caratteristiche_24710</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Telegram-Desktop-cos-e-come-funziona-e-quali-le-sue-caratteristiche_24710"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T11:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Una delle piattaforme per la messaggistica istantanea più utilizzate al mondo è Telegram. I numeri relativi agli utenti attivi mensilmente sono ancora piuttosto lontani da quelli che WhatsApp può vantare ma Telegram cresce con un buon ritmo tanto che con il lancio della versione Premium a giugno 2022 il fondatore Pavel Durov ha 'certificato' il superamento della soglia dei 700 milioni di utenti.
Cos'è Telegram Desktop
 Lo smartphone è sicuramente il dispositivo che utilizziamo con maggior frequenza per inviare e ricevere messaggi istantanei. Spesso quando si lavora dinanzi al PC, per comodità si preferisce utilizzare un client desktop, ovvero la versione installabile del programma di messaggistica.Telegram Desktop è il client che può essere installato su Windows, macOS e Linux permettendo di accedere all'intero ventaglio di funzionalità della piattaforma.Diversamente rispetto ad altre soluzioni concorrenti, Telegram Desktop è disponibile anche in versione portatile: ciò significa che il programma può essere utilizzato senza avviare alcuna procedura d'installazione sul PC: basta semplicemente estrarre il contenuto dell'archivio compresso e cliccare due volte sul file Telegram.exe.Com'è facile verificare, inoltre, nel caso della versione portatile di Telegram Desktop tutto il contenuto del programma è ospitato in un unico file eseguibile dal peso di circa 120 MB.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to set system wide Proxy when a vpn connection is established?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlsxl5/how_to_set_system_wide_proxy_when_a_vpn/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlsxl5/how_to_set_system_wide_proxy_when_a_vpn/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T11:04:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I want to use a proxy server when I connect with a VPN connection and disable the proxy server when I close the VPN. 
 Current state
 Once I connect with VPN, I can use the browser with auto proxy detect chromium --proxy-auto-detect and use the proxy server. However, all my other applications show a connection error, e.g. Pacman, docker, nextcloud, git, terminal. There is a workaround by setting for each application the proxy server. however, if I am only occasionally in VPN, I need to disable it everywhere again. 
 I also read about setting Environment variables in the wiki with the script. I tested it out, and my terminal has a connection, but all the other applications are still without a connection. 
 Expectation/Wish
 There is a script that enables and disables the proxy when connected to with VPN. 
 System
 Bpm with network-manager
    submitted by    /u/and0ne  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Atari Was Very, Very Hard” Nolan Bushnell on Atari, 50 Years Later]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=812246</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/812246/atari-was-very-very-hard-nolan-bushnell-on-atari-50-years-later/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T11:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s been 50 years since Nolan Bushnell co-founded Atari, which brought video games to the mainstream. To celebrate, we asked Bushnell what he learned during the early years—and what we’ve lost sight of since then.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GDM cannot start x session on my main user]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlslmd/gdm_cannot_start_x_session_on_my_main_user/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlslmd/gdm_cannot_start_x_session_on_my_main_user/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T10:42:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'd like to start using GDM but for some reason it's failing to start gnome or any other DE in xorg, it can start a DE in wayland on nvidia proprietary and AMD open source drivers, but cannot start anything in xorg on either AMD or nvidia drivers. Startx works
 the only way i've managed to get GDM to be able to start xorg is to create a new user and login to that, so i know it's something to do with my user account
 GDM can start itself in xorg mode by changing the config file, it just can't start a desktop in xorg
 Let me know what logs you want to see, i'll reproduce the issue now and post logs in the comments
 EDIT: troubleshooting steps I've tried so far are, 
 creating a new user (worked but not a long term solution)
 deleting all xorg related configs I could find in my home and in the root directory
 purging and reinstalling GDM
 switching GPU
 all of the troubleshooting tips on the arch wiki for gdm and xorg
    submitted by    /u/Turbulent_Basil4934  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Windows Phishing Method gives attackers access to cookies and more]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179376</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/27/new-windows-phishing-method-gives-attackers-access-to-cookies-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T10:40:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rise of two-factor authentication added a new layer of security to the authentication process on the Internet. Attacks designed to steal user credentials are still common, but many fall short because […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post New Windows Phishing Method gives attackers access to cookies and more appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200-x64.msi]]></title>
        <id>https://sourceforge.net/projects/sevenzip/files/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200-x64.msi/download</id>
        <link href="https://sourceforge.net/projects/sevenzip/files/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200-x64.msi/download"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T10:19:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200-x64.msi]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>7-Zip</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200-x64.exe]]></title>
        <id>https://sourceforge.net/projects/sevenzip/files/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200-x64.exe/download</id>
        <link href="https://sourceforge.net/projects/sevenzip/files/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200-x64.exe/download"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T10:19:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200-x64.exe]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>7-Zip</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200-src.tar.xz]]></title>
        <id>https://sourceforge.net/projects/sevenzip/files/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200-src.tar.xz/download</id>
        <link href="https://sourceforge.net/projects/sevenzip/files/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200-src.tar.xz/download"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T10:19:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200-src.tar.xz]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>7-Zip</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200-src.7z]]></title>
        <id>https://sourceforge.net/projects/sevenzip/files/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200-src.7z/download</id>
        <link href="https://sourceforge.net/projects/sevenzip/files/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200-src.7z/download"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T10:18:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200-src.7z]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>7-Zip</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200-linux-x86.tar.xz]]></title>
        <id>https://sourceforge.net/projects/sevenzip/files/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200-linux-x86.tar.xz/download</id>
        <link href="https://sourceforge.net/projects/sevenzip/files/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200-linux-x86.tar.xz/download"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T10:18:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200-linux-x86.tar.xz]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>7-Zip</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200-linux-x64.tar.xz]]></title>
        <id>https://sourceforge.net/projects/sevenzip/files/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200-linux-x64.tar.xz/download</id>
        <link href="https://sourceforge.net/projects/sevenzip/files/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200-linux-x64.tar.xz/download"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T10:18:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200-linux-x64.tar.xz]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>7-Zip</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200-linux-arm64.tar.xz]]></title>
        <id>https://sourceforge.net/projects/sevenzip/files/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200-linux-arm64.tar.xz/download</id>
        <link href="https://sourceforge.net/projects/sevenzip/files/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200-linux-arm64.tar.xz/download"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T10:17:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200-linux-arm64.tar.xz]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>7-Zip</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200-linux-arm.tar.xz]]></title>
        <id>https://sourceforge.net/projects/sevenzip/files/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200-linux-arm.tar.xz/download</id>
        <link href="https://sourceforge.net/projects/sevenzip/files/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200-linux-arm.tar.xz/download"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T10:17:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200-linux-arm.tar.xz]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>7-Zip</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200-extra.7z]]></title>
        <id>https://sourceforge.net/projects/sevenzip/files/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200-extra.7z/download</id>
        <link href="https://sourceforge.net/projects/sevenzip/files/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200-extra.7z/download"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T10:17:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200-extra.7z]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>7-Zip</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200-arm64.exe]]></title>
        <id>https://sourceforge.net/projects/sevenzip/files/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200-arm64.exe/download</id>
        <link href="https://sourceforge.net/projects/sevenzip/files/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200-arm64.exe/download"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T10:16:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200-arm64.exe]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>7-Zip</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200-arm.exe]]></title>
        <id>https://sourceforge.net/projects/sevenzip/files/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200-arm.exe/download</id>
        <link href="https://sourceforge.net/projects/sevenzip/files/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200-arm.exe/download"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T10:16:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200-arm.exe]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>7-Zip</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200.msi]]></title>
        <id>https://sourceforge.net/projects/sevenzip/files/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200.msi/download</id>
        <link href="https://sourceforge.net/projects/sevenzip/files/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200.msi/download"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T10:16:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200.msi]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>7-Zip</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200.exe]]></title>
        <id>https://sourceforge.net/projects/sevenzip/files/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200.exe/download</id>
        <link href="https://sourceforge.net/projects/sevenzip/files/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200.exe/download"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T10:16:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[/7-Zip/22.00/7z2200.exe]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>7-Zip</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux Kernel Modification – Adding New System Calls]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/?p=58521</id>
        <link href="https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/linux-kernal-add-new-system-calls/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T10:01:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When the need arises to create a powerful and reliable Linux-based system (whether it is to maintain a system processes or the web hosting, etc.), then it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikita</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Contestazioni copyright false con ransomware LockBit allegato]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Contestazioni-copyright-false-con-ransomware-LockBit-allegato_24709</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Contestazioni-copyright-false-con-ransomware-LockBit-allegato_24709"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T09:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gli sviluppatori del ransomware LockBit sono tra i più determinati e agguerriti. Da settembre 2019 questo malware ha causato danni incalcolabili crittografando con una chiave tenuta segreta i dati di un gran numero di aziende, spesso di elevato profilo.Con il trascorrere del tempo LockBit si è evoluto confermandosi il ransomware più veloce a cifrare i file e arruolando collaboratori infedeli con la promessa di guadagni ingenti.Adesso le tattiche di ingegneria sociale per diffondere LockBit stanno cambiando ancora e sfruttano l'invio per email di una falsa contestazione di copyright.Parlando di immagini gratis e copyright abbiamo fatto presente che negli ultimi anni si è registrata la nascita di molteplici realtà che effettuano una scansione dei contenuti pubblicati sul Web e inviano contestazioni formali nel caso in cui un contenuto fosse stato utilizzato senza disporre delle necessarie autorizzazioni.Spesso fotografi e agenzie si appoggiano a siti specializzati che con un team di legali operativo nei vari Paesi si occupa di tutelare i diritti degli aventi titolo.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[F2FS File-System Driver Preparing A Low-Memory Mode]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=F2FS-Low-Memory-Mode</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=F2FS-Low-Memory-Mode"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T09:12:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google engineers are working on the notion of "memory modes" for the Flash-Friendly File-System (F2FS) with the intent on introducing a "low memory" mode for storage devices that would alter its behavior. Presumably Google is working on this new F2FS feature for low-end Android devices...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PEC mail interoperabile a livello europeo: cosa significa e cosa cambia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=PEC-mail-interoperabile-a-livello-europeo-cosa-significa-e-cosa-cambia_24708</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=PEC-mail-interoperabile-a-livello-europeo-cosa-significa-e-cosa-cambia_24708"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T08:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Con oltre 13 milioni e 900 mila caselle attive alla fine del 2021, la PEC (posta elettronica certificata) ha ricoperto un ruolo trainante riuscendo a dare vita ad un sistema di comunicazione destinato a cambiare e migliorare le abitudini di un gran numero di utenti. Tra i principali meriti della PEC quello di incentivare il processo di dematerializzazione documentale, l'abbandono della carta, di far risparmiare tempo con la riduzione degli spostamenti e contribuire a ridurre le emissioni di CO2.Abbiamo visto cos'è la PEC e come funziona spiegando che troppo stesso l'attuale implementazione non veniva considerata come un semplice strumento di comunicazione. La PEC, così come utilizzata fino ad oggi, non verifica in modo certo l'identità del richiedente e quindi dei mittenti di ciascun messa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PKGBUILD review]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlqqny/pkgbuild_review/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlqqny/pkgbuild_review/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T08:35:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, I made a PKGBUILD to make a imhex-bin package, I would like to publish it to the AUR, but I'm not sure if I did everything right, could someone please review it ? https://github.com/iTrooz/ImHex/blob/master/dist/Arch/PKGBUILD-aur
 ​
 (The release .pkg.tar.zst is generated by another PKGBUILD during CI)
    submitted by    /u/iTrooz_  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finding out class_g]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlqfs9/finding_out_class_g/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlqfs9/finding_out_class_g/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T08:13:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was wondering how to find out class_g for my i3 config (I want to exclude chromium from opacity)
    submitted by    /u/ZxmonIsBored  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MacBook Pro M2: non è tutto rose e fiori. Le unità SSD sono lente nel modello base]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=MacBook-Pro-M2-non-e-tutto-rose-e-fiori-Le-unita-SSD-sono-lente-nel-modello-base_24707</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=MacBook-Pro-M2-non-e-tutto-rose-e-fiori-Le-unita-SSD-sono-lente-nel-modello-base_24707"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T08:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vi abbiamo parlato nelle scorse settimane dei nuovi MacBook Pro basati su chip Apple M2 di derivazione ARM.Dopo il lancio del nuovo MacBook Pro da 13 pollici è emerso che il modello base con 256 GB di spazio di archiviazione ha velocità di lettura/scrittura significativamente inferiore rispetto al modello equivalente della generazione precedente.L'unità SSD utilizzata da Apple per il nuovo MacBook Pro sarebbe il 50% e il 30% più lenta, rispettivamente, in lettura e scrittura se confrontata con l'analogo dispositivo utilizzato sul sistema dotato di SoC M1.Il modello di SSD da 512 GB sembra evidenziare invece prestazioni molto simili a quelle del predecessore: utilizza due chip di memoria NAND flash da 256 GB.Non è chiaro il motivo per cui il nuovo modello base del MacBook Pro da 13 pollici è dotato di un solo chip NAND: i costi e altri vincoli progettuali potrebbero aver influito direttamente su questo aspetto.Alle prestazioni inferiori dell'unità SSD sono ancora in pochi a fare riferimento.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[obs studio does not have a screen capture option.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlpnwr/obs_studio_does_not_have_a_screen_capture_option/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlpnwr/obs_studio_does_not_have_a_screen_capture_option/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T07:19:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I just need to have the screen capture option, so I can upload bug reproduction in certain programs. I'm having issues with obs not having an available screen capture option. This wasn't an issue when I had dedicated graphics, but for reasons, I am using intel integrated graphics now (12700k). 
 ​
 If no solution is available, what other screen recording software do ya'll recommend?
    submitted by    /u/slohobo  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 98 si aggiorna nello spazio]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-98-si-aggiorna-nello-spazio_24706</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-98-si-aggiorna-nello-spazio_24706"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T07:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 98 è stato rilasciato sul mercato il 25 giugno 1998 e all'epoca fu considerato un buon sistema operativo. Erede dello storico Windows 95, Windows 98 era un sistema monolitico ibrido a 16 e 32 bit che utilizzava MS-DOS per la fase di avvio: solo con Windows 2000 fu ampliata la platea degli utenti che potevano servirsi di un kernel di derivazione NT svincolato da MS-DOS.Windows 98 non è stato installato solamente su computer consumer ma è stato utilizzato per coadiuvare una serie di importanti missioni spaziali, alcune di esse ancora in corso.È il caso della sonda Mars Express lanciata 19 anni fa che da allora è stata impegnata a fornire importanti dettagli su Marte e Phobos (uno dei due satelliti del pianeta rosso), inclusi i dati sulla superficie, sulla struttura del sottosuolo, dell'atmosfera e sulle condizioni ambientali di entrambi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[simple-aur-helper: a bloat-free AUR helper with minimum dependencies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vloo1r/simpleaurhelper_a_bloatfree_aur_helper_with/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vloo1r/simpleaurhelper_a_bloatfree_aur_helper_with/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T06:12:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, i wrote an AUR helper for myself, but maybe someone will find it useful (Yes, i know that there are similar packages already made).
 It can install/remove/upgrade AUR packages, get dependecies from Arch repository and fetch the necessary PGP keys.
 https://github.com/vladkyiashko/simple-aur-helper
    submitted by    /u/twin_v  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Starting login manager fails after making a new user for qtile]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlnw2r/starting_login_manager_fails_after_making_a_new/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlnw2r/starting_login_manager_fails_after_making_a_new/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T05:22:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On my laptop, I have two users running KDE Plasma, which has been working great. I wanted to try qtile, so I made a new user and logged in using qtile for that user.
 ​
 I did some configuration almost all local to the user, except adding some configuration for natural scrolling to /etc/X11/xorg.conf.d/30-touchpad.conf (I had to make the file).
 I rebooted, and now when I boot it hangs here:
 ​
 [ OK ] Started Hostname Service. [ 19.604395] intel-spi 0000:00:1f.5: unrecognized JEDEC id bytes: 20 60 19 20 60 19 [ 85.031670] ucsi_acpi USBC000:00: ucsi_handle_connector_change: GET_CONNECTOR_STATUS failed (-110) 
 I can access another tty with Ctrl+Alt+F2, but I have no idea what to do to solve it from there. Any ideas?
 ​
 EDIT: This probably won't surprise most of you, but removing /etc/X11/xorg.conf.d/30-touchpad.conf fixed the problem. I'm guessing something else was trying to load at slot 30 at the same time and couldn't? I don't really know exactly how the service startup process works. Should I have put it at 99-* ?
    submitted by    /u/LorenWard  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bypass Windows 11 Microsoft Account requirement and deny privacy questions during setup with Rufus]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179372</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/27/bypass-windows-11-microsoft-account-requirement-and-deny-privacy-questions-during-setup-with-rufus/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T04:58:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rufus is an open source application that allows you to create bootable USB media. It is widely used to create bootable Windows 11 or Linux media for installation. The latest version of […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Bypass Windows 11 Microsoft Account requirement and deny privacy questions during setup with Rufus appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Could not detect root" error using archinstall]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlm69b/could_not_detect_root_error_using_archinstall/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlm69b/could_not_detect_root_error_using_archinstall/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T03:44:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So i tried reinstalling arch on my system, and so this is how i set up my manual partitions: 
 For my bootloader I reused the partition I had before, so i set wipe, boot and esp and the mountpoint as /boot/efi as it was before
 For my root partition I set the flag wipe and the mountpoint as / like before. 
 When I go through the installation it installs a bunch of stuff and then calls this Partition method. This is when it errors with "Could not detect root"
 I copied how my previous partitions were set up as before, is the install script bugged?
    submitted by    /u/Prizefighter-Mercury  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Debugging Your AWS Bill With Cost Explorer and Billing Tags]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?post_type=devops&amp;p=800740</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/devops/debugging-your-aws-bill-with-cost-explorer-and-billing-tags/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T01:48:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS’s billing is notoriously complicated, and misconfigurations in your network can lead to excess data or resource use that can pile up unnoticed. AWS provides many solutions for debugging your bill before it hits your wallet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Heddings</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Losing permissions on external disks.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vljpyh/losing_permissions_on_external_disks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vljpyh/losing_permissions_on_external_disks/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T01:33:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the title say, I am consistantly losing permission to write on any external disks, even those formated with the system. Only started doing that about a week ago, and even with sudo I can change permissions.
 Any clue what could be the "root" cause of this ?
 Edit: I have 3 computers all running Archlinux, and an Ipad, I have a suspission that the Ipad has something to do with it since it was only recently added to the house and I have been using my portable drives with it too.
    submitted by    /u/Bender248  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Plex Media Server "target not found" even though Multilib is enabled (Arch 5.18.6-arch1-1)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlgvfj/plex_media_server_target_not_found_even_though/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlgvfj/plex_media_server_target_not_found_even_though/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T23:03:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello!
 I switched to Arch as my 24/7 OS about 2 weeks ago, I've had Plex Media Server installed as a snap package and it was causing issues so I removed it and now im trying to download PMS through the AUR. I know multilib is required so I went into my pacman.conf and enabled them...
 # If you want to run 32 bit applications on your x86_64 system, enable the multilib repositories as required here. [multilib-testing] Include = /etc/pacman.d/mirrorlist [multilib] Include = /etc/pacman.d/mirrorlist 
 Afterward I ran pacman -Syu to update everything, went to do pacman -S plex-media-server and it comes up with...
 error: target not found: plex-media-server 
 Even though its RIGHT HERE in the AUR. https://aur.archlinux.org/packages/plex-media-server
 I am stumped. I can find no other steps people have had to take other than enabling multilib and pacman-ing "plex-media-server". In fact thats exactly how I did it on Manjaro a few months ago.
 Any help would be appreciated.
    submitted by    /u/bactaholic  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Custom ISOs?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlgpym/how_to_build_custom_isos/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlgpym/how_to_build_custom_isos/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T22:56:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I wanted to try building my own ISO to more easily install Arch and my software without using archinstall or doing it manually, but everything I try just keeps failing. I've tried using archiso, tried using some old programs like Linux Live Kit and I even tried building Arcolinux ISOs because they're supposed to be "easier". I also (obviously) read the wiki pages for building ISOs and older Reddit posts on the topic, but it still is extremely confusing and I don't really know what I'm doing wrong, I just followed the wiki and later some tutorial videos on the subject. I consider myself an advanced user and have been using Linux for the past two years as my main OS. 
 I wanted an Arch ISO running Cinnamon with some custom themes, pamac and the Calamares Installer. Do you have any suggestions on where to begin my search, like more documentation, tutorial videos or the like?
    submitted by    /u/AugustBrasilien  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Problem with wifi keeps disconnecting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlftdc/problem_with_wifi_keeps_disconnecting/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlftdc/problem_with_wifi_keeps_disconnecting/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T22:11:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently I have had this issue with wifi, it keeps disconnecting and reconnecting. I tried switching to networkmanager from iwd, but that didn’t help
 this is what journalctl is saying
  Jun 20 11:10:39 nyly-arch kernel: Linux version 5.15.48-1-lts (linux-lts@archlinux) (gcc (GCC) 12.1.0, GNU ld (GNU Binutils) 2.38) #1 SMP Thu, 16 Jun> Jun 20 11:10:39 nyly-arch kernel: Command line: BOOT_IMAGE=/boot/vmlinuz-linux-lts root=UUID=39713201-b74b-4c19-8f53-aace43e5c1c2 rw loglevel=3 quiet Jun 20 11:10:39 nyly-arch kernel: x86/fpu: Supporting XSAVE feature 0x001: 'x87 floating point registers' Jun 20 11:10:39 nyly-arch kernel: x86/fpu: Supporting XSAVE feature 0x002: 'SSE registers' Jun 20 11:10:39 nyly-arch kernel: x86/fpu: Supporting XSAVE feature 0x004: 'AVX registers' Jun 20 11:10:39 nyly-arc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux 5.19-c4 - A Bit Bigger, Also Fixes A Previously Reported Performance Regression]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-rc4-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-rc4-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T22:07:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linus Torvalds just released Linux 5.19-rc4 as the newest weekly test candidate. There are more patches this week than in the prior Linux 5.19-rc versions but nothing too scary as well as having some notable patches in tow...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Connecting to internet during installation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlfmyu/connecting_to_internet_during_installation/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlfmyu/connecting_to_internet_during_installation/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T22:02:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I need some help conecting to the internet during the installation process. I ran the command Iwctl device list but it just showed an empty table. Acording to ip link, the system detects the wlan0 adapter but for some reason i'm not able to connect to it. Any help would be greatly appreciated.
 Ip link:wlan0:
 <NO-CARRIER,BROADCAST,MULTICAST,UP> mtu 1500 qdisc fq_code1 state DOWN mode DEFAULT group default qlen 1000 link/ether brd ff:ff:ff:ff:ff:ff
 lsusb | grep WLAN:
 Realtek Semiconductor Corp. RTL8191SU 802.11n WLAN Adapter
    submitted by    /u/veganbtw6969  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come evitare le tre domande di sicurezza quando create un account locale]]></title>
        <id>3607|20220627000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/password-174/come-evitare-tre-domande-sicurezza-quando-create-account-locale-3607"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quando create un account locale in un computer, e gli mettete una password, siete obbligati a scegliere tre domande e risposte per il recupero della password quando la dimenticate. Il problema è che queste domande/risposte, a meno di scriverle da qualche parte, dopo cinque minuti dal loro inserimento è probabile che le avrete dimenticate se avete inserito dei dati a caso, se invece utilizzate delle risposte vere, fornendo dei dati personali, non va bene perché possono essere recuperati anche da altre persone che hanno accesso a quel computer.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best alternative to MuQSS?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlf5jo/best_alternative_to_muqss/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlf5jo/best_alternative_to_muqss/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T21:39:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello,
 Apologies if similar questions have been asked, but I'm just curious if there is a similar alternative to CK's MuQSS. I still have the last available kernel release in my secondary slot, which I bounce to when suspend issues come up, and have been using graysky's build for the hrtimer tweaks for the up-to-date kernel releases.
 Just checking in to see what the consensus is on the "best" maintained scheduler (or desktop kernel builds in general), and if anything out there plays a similar role. My current laptop is quite the potato, so I'd like to think tailored kernels are the way to go in my use case. Maybe I should just use zen from the official repo?
 Thanks!
    submitted by    /u/entheogenetica  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[how to rename a command]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlew42/how_to_rename_a_command/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlew42/how_to_rename_a_command/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T21:26:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[there is a thing in arch that will rename a command for example instead of me writing ls for the list i can change it to l but i forgot the name of it and how to use it
    submitted by    /u/zarnackreddit  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can't boot into windows 11 after installing arch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlej25/cant_boot_into_windows_11_after_installing_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlej25/cant_boot_into_windows_11_after_installing_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T21:09:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have just installed arch linux taking making sure to not touch the windows install. I also have disabled secure boot etc but now windows isn't being detected by my bios, os-prober or efibootmgr even when mounted. I can see all my files there etc. I'll attach outputs of lsblk and efibootmgr -v below and os-prober returns nothing. Windows is installed in UEFI mode.
 efibootmgr -v
 BootCurrent: 0003 Timeout: 1 seconds BootOrder: 0003 Boot0003* GRUB HD(1,GPT,c5d1c8be-3300-4e7e-bae0-250c0a18c80d,0x800,0x96000)/File(\EFI\GRUB\grubx64.efi) 
 lsblk
 NAME MAJ:MIN RM SIZE RO TYPE MOUNTPOINTS sda 8:0 0 119.2G 0 disk |-sda1 8:1 0 300M 0 part /boot `-sda2 8:2 0 118.9G 0 part /home / sdb 8:16 0 558.9G 0 disk |-sdb1 8:17 0 16M 0 part |-sdb2 8:18 0 558.3G 0 part /run/media/volt/9E8EDE668EDE368D `-sdb3 8:19 0 580M 0 part sdc 8:32 0 1.8T 0 disk `-sdc1 8:33 0 1.8T 0 part sdd 8:48 0 3.6T 0 disk |-sdd1 8:49 0 16M 0 part `-sdd2 8:50 0 3.6T 0 part zram0 253:0 0 8G 0 disk [SWAP] 
 Windows is installed on /dev/sdb and arch is installed on /dev/sda with btrfs etc. sdc and sdd are just large drives for storage.
 Any other information needed just ask and I will provide it. This has been a common theme with installing linux distros with most of them just not letting me boot into windows after installation.
 Any help is appreciated thank you!
    submitted by    /u/voltaf4  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does Your Android Phone Need an Antivirus App?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=793462</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/793462/does-your-android-phone-need-an-antivirus-app/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may be surprised to learn that Android is the most popular operating system on the planet—even bigger than Windows. That makes it a target for malicious attacks. But do you actually need antivirus apps on your Android phone?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google's Pixel 7 Pro Screen Could Be a Lot Better Outdoors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/121686/googles-pixel-7-pro-screen-could-be-a-lot-better-outdoors/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/121686/googles-pixel-7-pro-screen-could-be-a-lot-better-outdoors/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T20:04:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While Google already teased the Pixel 7 and Pixel 7 Pro back in May, the phones won’t arrive until later this year. Still, that hasn’t stopped a slew of leaks and rumors from emerging. Now, the latest leak suggests the Pixel series will finally have a much brighter display.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Silence Unknown Callers to Stop Robocall Spam on iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=772148</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/772148/how-to-silence-unknown-callers-to-stop-robocall-spam-on-iphone/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tired of getting robocalls all day long on your iPhone? Your iPhone lets you silence the harassment by turning on a feature called “Silence Unknown Callers” in Settings. Here’s how to do it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[how do I permanantly disable a virtual core pointer?I want to disable the wacom one as I use opentablerdriver I dont need it]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlcrzq/how_do_i_permanantly_disable_a_virtual_core/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlcrzq/how_do_i_permanantly_disable_a_virtual_core/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T19:47:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://imgur.com/a/TLw7hA5
    submitted by    /u/DrWeird31  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 Ways to Easily Send Text Messages (SMS) from Your PC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=295664</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/11255842/send-sms-from-pc"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Text messaging has become one of the most popular ways to carry on conversations in our world today. The convenience of using SMS is universally known. Sometimes, though, for one reason or another, you may prefer to have access to text messaging on your computer.
    
No matter your reason, if this is something you want to do, follow one of these texting methods that do not require the use of the messaging app on your phone.
   

Content

1. Google Voice
2. Your Email Account
3. Windows App
4. Chrome Extension
5. Free Websites
6. Text Sync Apps
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Use Google Messages on Desktop
    
1. Google Voice
    
Google Voice isn’t talked about much, but this handy service gives you a free virtual phone number that you can use to make calls and send texts.... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Crystal Crowder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unable to connect to a wifi network after installing arch in virtualbox]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlc4rt/unable_to_connect_to_a_wifi_network_after/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlc4rt/unable_to_connect_to_a_wifi_network_after/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T19:16:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(English is not my native language so there might be some errors sorry)
 I finished to install arch on virtualbox and everything seemed to work just fine until I realized I didn't have any internet connection. I use a laptop without any ethernet port so I have to use a wireless connection. The thing I don't understand is that during the install process (logged in as root), I was able to download all the packages I wanted using pacman but after booting the system for the first time, I just couldn't install anything nor ping any website (it returns "Temporary failure in name resolution"). After looking up some forum posts I tried to use iw which didn't work since I didn't install it during the installation process, then I tried to use netctl and wifi-menu but it didn't bring any results either even though I had access to them. I also tried to activate the dhcpcd client with sudo systemctl start dhcpcd since i thought it was the problem but it returns "Unit dhcpcd.service not found.". I am a complete beginner regarding arch linux so I would really really appreciate it if someone took the time to give me some paths that could lead me to a solution.
    submitted by    /u/NoOil3540  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add Gmail to Your iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=810864</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/810864/how-to-add-gmail-to-iphone/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T19:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google makes it super easy to add your Gmail account to your iPhone. This way, you can access your Gmail emails in your iPhone’s Mail app as well as the Gmail app. We’ll show you how to perform this integration on your device.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[error message in local.conf]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlbbme/error_message_in_localconf/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlbbme/error_message_in_localconf/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T18:39:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I can't update any font packages because it shows the same error: Fontconfig error: "/etc/fonts/local.conf", line 1: XML declaration not well-formed.
 ​
 but i haven't changed anything since i installed it yesterday
 ​
 ​
 <?xml version=1.0?>
 <!DOCTYPE fontconfig SYSTEM fonts.dtd>
 <fontconfig>
 <alias>
 <family>sans-serif</family>
 <prefer>
 <family>Noto Sans</family>
 <family>Noto Color Emoji</family>
 <family>Noto Emoji</family>
 <family>DejaVu Sans</family>
 </prefer>
 </alias>
 ​
 <alias>
 <family>serif</family>
 <prefer>
 <family>Noto Serif</family>
 <family>Noto Color Emoji</family>
 <family>Noto Emoji</family>
 <family>DejaVu Serif</family>
 </prefer>
 </alias>
 ​
 <alias>
 <family>monospace</family>
 <prefer>
 <family>Noto Mono</family>
 <family>Noto Color Emoji</family>
 <family>Noto Emoji</family>
 <family>DejaVu Sans Mono</family>
 </prefer>
 </alias>
 </fontconfig>
    submitted by    /u/OmgGass  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I feel in love with pacman!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlamig/i_feel_in_love_with_pacman/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlamig/i_feel_in_love_with_pacman/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T18:06:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Look, I've used other package managers before like dnf, apt, and pkg. Its main pro, though, is that once you've learned it, pacman does exactly what you tell it to do. I feel more in control of my system due to it.
    submitted by    /u/Mr_Foggy_Glasses  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Import Bookmarks From Chrome to Firefox]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=810747</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/810747/import-chrome-bookmarks-to-firefox/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T18:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla Firefox makes it easy to import bookmarks from other web browsers. If you’re switching from Google Chrome to Firefox, this guide will show you how to get all your Chrome bookmarks moved to your Firefox browser.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Overwatch' Will Stop Working When Its Sequel Arrives This October]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/121687/overwatch-will-stop-working-when-its-sequel-arrives-this-october/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/121687/overwatch-will-stop-working-when-its-sequel-arrives-this-october/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T17:13:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It seems that Overwatch 2 is more than just a flashy sequel. Instead, it’s a full on replacement for the seven-year-old Overwatch, which will stop working when Overwatch 2 arrives on October 4th. Given previous news, this isn’t much of a surprise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Check Your Computer’s Specifications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=810321</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/810321/how-to-check-computer-specs/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T17:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using just the built-in tools on Windows 10 and Windows 11, you can check your PC’s specs, like the processor type, RAM, graphics card model, storage type (SSD or HDD), network adapter model, and more. We’ll show you how to find that information on your machine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[flutter set up for arch linux (without installing android studio)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vl87ew/flutter_set_up_for_arch_linux_without_installing/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vl87ew/flutter_set_up_for_arch_linux_without_installing/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T16:15:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I want to install the android sdk and be able to use the android emulator without android studio.
 My current flutter doctor output:
 Doctor summary (to see all details, run flutter doctor -v): [!] Android toolchain - develop for Android devices (Android SDK version 33.0.0) ✗ Android license status unknown. Run `flutter doctor --android-licenses` to accept the SDK licenses. See https://flutter.dev/docs/get-started/install/linux#android-setup for more details. [✓] Chrome - develop for the web [✓] Linux toolchain - develop for Linux desktop [!] Android Studio (not installed) [✓] Connected device (2 available) [✓] HTTP Host Availability ! Doctor found issues in 2 categories. 
 There are several written tutorials online for how to do this such as this one: https://www.rockyourcode.com/how-to-get-flutter-and-android-working-on-arch-linux/
 but I can't tell which ones are up to date, so if you have it all set up on your machine matching the criteria I mentioned above, I would appreciate some step-by-step instructions on how you did it.
 This is what i have in my .bashrc:
 export JAVA_HOME='/usr/lib/jvm/java-18-openjdk' export JAVA_OPTS='-XX:+IgnoreUnrecognizedVMOptions --add-modules java.se.ee' export ANDROID_SDK_ROOT='/opt/android-sdk' export PATH=$JAVA_HOME/bin:$PATH export PATH=$PATH:$ANDROID_SDK_ROOT/platform-tools/ export PATH=$PATH:$ANDROID_SDK_ROOT/tools/bin/ export PATH=$PATH:$ANDROID_SDK_ROOT/tools/emulator export PATH=$PATH:$ANDROID_SDK_ROOT/tools/ 
 I tried to create an emulator with avdmanager create avd -n my_em -k "system-images;android-25;google_apis;x86" but I got this error:
 Error occurred during initialization of boot layer java.lang.module.FindException: Module java.se.ee not found 
 flutter doctor --android-licenses yielded the same error.
 I saw online that it is probably needing to downgrade my java version, so I tried to downgrade my jdk-openjdk package but I couldn't because it would break dependencies.
    submitted by    /u/Righteous_Warrior  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[liburing 2.2 Released For Easier IO_uring Usage On Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=liburing-2.2</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=liburing-2.2"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T16:07:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jens Axboe, Linux storage expert and IO_uring lead developer, released liburing 2.2 this weekend as the newest version of this helper library that makes it easier for user-space software to make use of the Linux kernel's IO_uring support...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multicharacter Glyph has wrong width in terminal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vl7zql/multicharacter_glyph_has_wrong_width_in_terminal/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vl7zql/multicharacter_glyph_has_wrong_width_in_terminal/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T16:05:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am using dwm/alacritty|st and when I copy a icon from nerdfont's cheatsheet online it seems to have a wrong width on paste and causes for example the terminal string to get erased when moving the cursor. I use the Hack patched NerdFont. Xclip pasting works and correctly gets pasted into terminal output. Does anybody have a similar issue?
    submitted by    /u/Narrow_Farmer_6018  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LGBTQ+ community warned of extortionists abusing dating apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/lgbtq-plus-community-warned-of-extortionists-abusing-dating-apps/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/lgbtq-plus-community-warned-of-extortionists-abusing-dating-apps/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T16:04:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Federal Trade Commission (FTC) has warned this week of extortion scammers targeting the LGBTQ+ community by abusing online dating apps like Grindr and Feeld. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything You Need to Know About Your Apple Watch Move Goal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=807795</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/807795/everything-you-need-to-know-about-your-apple-watch-move-goal/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T16:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you don’t fully understand how your Apple Watch Move goal works, what it should be set at, and how to fill your rings, it can be hard to use it as a motivational tool. Here are some tips to help you master your fitness-oriented wearable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spotify Now Uses Your Listening Habits to Find Concert Tickets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/121694/spotify-now-uses-your-listening-habits-to-find-concert-tickets/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/121694/spotify-now-uses-your-listening-habits-to-find-concert-tickets/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T15:23:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spotify has completely revamped its Concerts Hub, turning it into a powerful concert-finding tool called Live Events. This feed, which you can find by searching “Live Events” on Spotify, uses your listening habits to find concert tickets and information on upcoming shows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chroot into Encrypted Btrfs on Luks to repair fstab]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vl6uj2/chroot_into_encrypted_btrfs_on_luks_to_repair/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vl6uj2/chroot_into_encrypted_btrfs_on_luks_to_repair/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T15:12:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[*Obligatory Noob Preface*: I know I probably should've just used snapshots, but I'm a noob have been procrastinating on learning how to properly use BTRFS' features. I'll do so after resolving this.
 ​
 I recently edited my /etc/fstab to try to access an internal hard drive, and after rebooting, when I attempt to decrypt my arch installation, it times out. After this message it attempts to enter emergency mode but I'm unable to do anything in emergency mode because I have no root user set.
 I did make a backup of my fstab, and now I'm trying to chroot into my installation (via live USB) to restore the fstab backup.
 My Disk Layout:
 DEVICE SIZE TYPE /dev/nvme0n1p1 511M EFI System /dev/nvme0n1p2 931G Linux filesystem 
 What I've tried so far:
 cryptsetup luksOpen /dev/nvme0n1p2 arch mkdir -p /mnt/ mount /dev/mapper/arch /mnt mkdir -p /mnt/root/boot mount /dev/nvme0n1p1 /mnt/root bash chroot /mnt/root cp /etc/fstab.bak /etc/fstab 
  
At this point I get the error: "chroot: failed to run command cp: No such file or directory"
  
Any pointers?
    submitted by    /u/TheBlackChamber  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fake copyright infringement emails install LockBit ransomware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fake-copyright-infringement-emails-install-lockbit-ransomware/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fake-copyright-infringement-emails-install-lockbit-ransomware/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T15:05:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LockBit ransomware affiliates are using an interesting trick to get people into infecting their devices by disguising their malware as copyright claims. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Run Multiple Services In One Docker Container]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?post_type=devops&amp;p=800747</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/devops/how-to-run-multiple-services-in-one-docker-container/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T15:03:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Docker is a technology for packaging components of your stack as isolated containers. It’s common practice to run each of your processes in its own container, creating a clean divide between components. This enhances modularity and lets you access the scalability benefits of containerization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What to Look for in a Gaming Monitor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=803895</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/803895/what-to-look-for-in-a-gaming-monitor/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T15:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A good gaming monitor can improve your gameplay right away. They have key features that can help you see and react to your opponents faster, but they’re also useful for any activity. Here are the specs to look for.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Nguyen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clever phishing method bypasses MFA using Microsoft WebView2 apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/clever-phishing-method-bypasses-mfa-using-microsoft-webview2-apps/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/clever-phishing-method-bypasses-mfa-using-microsoft-webview2-apps/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T14:12:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A clever, new phishing technique uses Microsoft Edge WebView2 applications to steal victim's authentication cookies, allowing threat actors to bypass multi-factor authentication when logging into stolen accounts. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>