<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-07-06T02:17:57.885Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Focus Assist Companion Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=493661</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15415007/focus-assist-companion-apps"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No matter which industry you work in, whether it’s in an office or at home, or what your job title is, you can benefit from spending more time in a state of concentration instead of constant distraction. Let’s face it: our computers are powerful tools that allow us to do incredible things, but they can also hijack our attention and prevent us from getting work done. Focus Assist is an integrated Windows option that can help, but there are plenty of other apps that work with the native app to ensure that you’re not distracted by third-party apps or the Internet.
   

Content

What Is Focus Assist?
Robust Focus Assist Companion Apps
Simplistic Focus Assist Companion Apps
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Use Windows 10 Focus Assist to Control Notifications
    
What Is Focus Assist?
    
In short,... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Yoder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Problem with the fonts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vscgx4/problem_with_the_fonts/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vscgx4/problem_with_the_fonts/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T00:19:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I got this problem where the fonts look fuzzy and thin, unlike windows 10 good looking out of the box fonts.
 I tried various things, read various articles, but just cant find the solution.
 Also my gpu is an nvidia card.
 Any ideas of how i could make it look good? Like in windows 10?
 I would also need to reset all the fonts, and xorg conf, since i touched many things there, and dont know how to do that also :/
 Any help would be appreciated :)
    submitted by    /u/Ramaax  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD Makes More RDNA3 GPU Driver Preparations For Linux 5.20]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMDGPU-More-RDNA3-For-5.20</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMDGPU-More-RDNA3-For-5.20"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T23:24:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AMD today sent out "new stuff" concerning their AMDGPU and AMDKFD kernel graphics and compute drivers to DRM-Next in preparation for the Linux 5.20 cycle kicking off in a few weeks...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[`pacman -Fx keyword` doesn't work with `| grep -v anotherword`]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vsah39/pacman_fx_keyword_doesnt_work_with_grep_v/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vsah39/pacman_fx_keyword_doesnt_work_with_grep_v/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T22:45:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So I want to know which package (the file or package may not be installed) owns a file such pacman -Fx /etc/pacman.conf will list  etc/pacman.conf is owned by core/pacman 6.0.1-5 
 but since I got several third party repos in my /etc/pacman.conf such as chaotic-aur, there will be over 50 lines like the following in the result  error: chaotic-aur database is inconsistent: version mismatch on package libshumate-git error: chaotic-aur database is inconsistent: version mismatch on package linux-next-git error: chaotic-aur database is inconsistent: version mismatch on package linux-next-git-headers error: chaotic-aur database is inconsistent: version mismatch on package linux-tt error: chaotic-aur database is inconsistent: version mismatch on package php80 error: chaotic-aur database is inconsistent: version mismatch on package php80-apache error: chaotic-aur database is inconsistent: version mismatch on package php80-bcmath error: chaotic-aur database is inconsistent: version mismatch on package php80-bz2 error: chaotic-aur database is inconsistent: version mismatch on package php80-calendar 
 I don't want to see the long list of ...database is inconsistent... lines from the result of pacman -F keyword, so I use command like pacman -F /etc/pacman.conf | grep -v "database is inconsistent: ", but it seems grep -v command doesn't work in this case.
 The database is inconsistent: issue from some repo in my /etc/pacman.conf occurs to me occasionally, most of the time I cannot get this fixed, and I can't be bothered fixing it any more, what I need is just hide the long lines oferror: from the result of pacman -Fx keyword command, so what can I do?
    submitted by    /u/CodyChan  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[System76 Announces New Alder Lake Laptop With Coreboot Firmware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=System76-ADL-Lemur-Pro</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=System76-ADL-Lemur-Pro"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T22:32:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[System76 has announced a new Lemur Pro laptop model that is now offering 12th Gen "Alder Lake" Intel processors while continuing to feature Coreboot firmware...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New RedAlert Ransomware targets Windows, Linux VMware ESXi servers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-redalert-ransomware-targets-windows-linux-vmware-esxi-servers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-redalert-ransomware-targets-windows-linux-vmware-esxi-servers/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T22:20:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new ransomware operation called RedAlert, or N13V, encrypts both Windows and Linux VMWare ESXi servers in attacks on corporate networks. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What do you use to take snip screenshot?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vs9tab/what_do_you_use_to_take_snip_screenshot/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vs9tab/what_do_you_use_to_take_snip_screenshot/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T22:15:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I hate using third party apps for basic operations such as screenshots. What light weight and simple screenshot tool do you use?
    submitted by    /u/sugmaJIFF  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crea una pendrive avviabile, per installare sistemi operativi e fare diagnostica, con Rufus]]></title>
        <id>667|20220706000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/windows-10/crea-pendrive-avviabile-installare-sistemi-operativi-fare-diagnostica-rufus-667"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sempre più spesso ci troviamo nella necessità di installare dei sistemi operativi in computer privi di lettore CD-Rom, per fortuna ci sono ormai molti programmi che ci permettono di trasferire l’immagine ISO, di un sistema operativo o di un supporto di utility di vario genere, in una pendrive avviabile. In questo articolo volevo parlarvi di Rufus piccolissimo applicativo, disponibile anche in versione portable, che permette di trasferire l’immagine ISO di moltissimi sistemi operativi, Windows e Linux, oltre a numerosi supporti che contengono utility di vario genere. Trovate una lista, non esaustiva, delle ISO supportate in fondo a questa pagina.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Convert HEIC to JPG in Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=279393</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/10771189/convert-heic-jpg-windows10"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most annoying things in computing is having files that cannot be used by applications on your computer. If this happens to you, then you know how frustrating it can be.
    
This is apparently the case with the new HEIF file format. Newer iPhones and iPads currently take pictures in HEIF (High-Efficiency Image Format) and save images with an HEIC extension. This format, with all its advantages, isn’t native to Windows, but you can quite easily convert HEIC files to JPG using Windows’ standard tools, like Photos and Paint (as well as myriad third-party apps).
    
With its ability to occupy very little storage space, it seems like an extension for the long run. If you hit a brick wall viewing HEIC files on Windows, try some of these ways to convert HEIC to JPG.
   

Content

Opening HEIC In Windows
1. Photos App
2. Paint
3. HEICtoJPEG Web App
4. HEIC Converter Free
5. iMazing HEIC Converter
6. iOS "Automatic" Transfer Mode
7. CopyTrans HEIC for Windows
8. iMobie HEIC Converter
9. GIMP
10. CloudConvert
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Megan Glosson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to jump to Microsoft Edge from Internet Explorer]]></title>
        <id>031d416f-bd48-4283-ae87-8eb52f29ea60</id>
        <link href="https://www.zdnet.com/article/how-to-jump-to-microsoft-edge-from-internet-explorer/#ftag=RSSbaffb68"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T21:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Internet Explorer no longer supported by Microsoft, here's how to jump ship to Microsoft Edge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest topics for ZDNet in Windows</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is a Smart Plug?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=730221</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/730221/what-is-a-smart-plug/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smart plugs make any appliance or device smarter by allowing you to control them remotely. You can track energy consumption, schedule when a device turns on and off, and control it with your voice.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Nguyen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Install Minecraft on Ubuntu or Any Other Linux Distribution]]></title>
        <id>http://www.howtogeek.com/?p=198476</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/198476/how-to-install-minecraft-on-ubuntu-or-any-other-linux-distribution/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Minecraft runs just fine on Linux, but it’s probably not available for easy installation in your Linux distribution’s package manager. Here’s how to get your Linux system ready for Minecraft.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Azure now has confidential VMs with ephemeral storage]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-azure-now-has-confidential-vms-with-ephemeral-storage/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-azure-now-has-confidential-vms-with-ephemeral-storage/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T19:40:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has expanded its confidential computing offering and is now allowing Azure cloud computing service customers to create hardware isolated virtual machines (aka confidential VMs) with Ephemeral OS disks. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Pixel's Next Update Is Timely Yet Late]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/122317/google-pixels-next-update-is-timely-yet-late/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/122317/google-pixels-next-update-is-timely-yet-late/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T19:39:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The slow trickle of new At a Glance features are always keeping Pixel owners on the edge of their seat. But an upcoming “Cross Device Timer” could take the smart widget a whole new level—soon, At a Glance will show you a countdown for timers made on Nest Hubs and other Google Assistant devices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Timeshift terminated by signal SIGSEGV (Address boundary error)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vs66p2/timeshift_terminated_by_signal_sigsegv_address/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vs66p2/timeshift_terminated_by_signal_sigsegv_address/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T19:37:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, I just built Timeshift from the AUR and I get this error when trying to execute it:
 [Warning] Deleted invalid lock ** (timeshift-gtk:9177): CRITICAL **: 16:31:14.785: string_strip: assertion 'self != NULL' failed (timeshift-gtk:9177): GLib-CRITICAL **: 16:31:14.785: g_str_has_prefix: assertion 'str != NULL' failed fish: Job 1, 'sudo timeshift-gtk' terminated by signal SIGSEGV (Address boundary error) 
 I've searched the web and found nothing that could help me. Tried rebuilding it and nothing.
 This is a semi-fresh Arch installation cause my previous one broke after an update and I wanna make a backup before I update again.
    submitted by    /u/LongSnakes  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pacman pause on "Reloading system manager configuration..."]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vs635v/pacman_pause_on_reloading_system_manager/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vs635v/pacman_pause_on_reloading_system_manager/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T19:32:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi
 I was wondering if anyone can shed some light as to why pacman pauses (roughly 1-2 minutes) on the step "Reloading system manager configuration..." during an upgrade process? I can't seem to find any clues as to what it's blocking/waiting for.
 Thanks
    submitted by    /u/Zatie12  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get an Amazon Echo Show 5 Kids for Under $39]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=502448</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15414691/amazon-echo-show-5-kids"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are your kids already bored this summer? They don’t have to be. You can get them an Echo Show 5 Kids for just $39.99. And at that price, you can get one for each of your children. They can watch videos, have access to Alexa, make video calls, get homework help, and more.
    
Forget your worries about your children having this type of device, as easy-to-use parental controls are included, allowing you to set bedtimes and time limits, filter for certain content, and review your kids’ activity. Amazon will not sell your personal information to others, and the device has multiple layers of privacy controls. You can even shut off the mic and camera.
   
 
   
Your kids will certainly be entertained on the Echo Show 5 Kids. It includes one year of Amazon Kids+ that gives them thousands of videos, audiobooks, games, music stations, etc. After the first year, your subscription will automatically renew for $4.99 a month plus tax. But you can cancel at any time if you decide it’s too much.
... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Open JAR Files on Windows 10 and 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=812583</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/812583/how-to-open-jar-files-windows/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T19:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Windows 10 and Windows 11, JAR files don’t open by default as there are no built-in apps to handle this file format. But, you can install the free Java utility and access this file format on your PC. We’ll show you the process to do that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Share Notes on iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=811950</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/811950/how-to-share-notes-on-iphone/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T18:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you want to share a copy of your note with someone, or you want to invite someone to collaborate on your notes with you, your iPhone’s Notes app allows you to do both. We’ll show you how to use those Notes’ features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NPM supply-chain attack impacts hundreds of websites and apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/npm-supply-chain-attack-impacts-hundreds-of-websites-and-apps/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/npm-supply-chain-attack-impacts-hundreds-of-websites-and-apps/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T17:55:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An NPM supply-chain attack dating back to December 2021 used dozens of malicious NPM modules containing obfuscated Javascript code to compromise hundreds of downstream desktop apps and websites. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lennart Poettering - systemd + PulseAudio Creator - Departed Red Hat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Lennart-Poettering-Out-Red-Hat</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Lennart-Poettering-Out-Red-Hat"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T17:30:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To much surprise, the lead developer of systemd Lennart Poettering who also led the creation of PulseAudio, Avahi, and has been a prolific free software contributor has reportedly left Red Hat...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Chrome Keyboard Shortcuts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=cheatsheet&amp;p=152827</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15414568/google-chrome-keyboard-shortcuts"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T17:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Chrome is one of the most widely used browser on both PC and mobile. If you’re a Chrome user, you must be familiar with at least the basic keyboard shortcuts like opening a new tab, checking history, and so on. In this cheatsheet, we will cover almost all the available keyboard shortcuts for Google Chrome on Windows and macOS.
    
We have divided the shortcuts into various sections like tabs, display, bookmarks, windows, etc., to make the shortcuts easier to find and remember.
       

WindowsmacOSFunction

Window Shortcuts
Ctrl + NCommand + NOpen a new window.
Ctrl + Shift + NCommand + Shift + NOpen a new window in Incognito mode.
Ctrl + Shift + W or Alt + F4Command + Shift + WClose the current window.
Alt + Space then NCommand + MMinimize the current window.
Alt + Space then XMaximize the current window.
Alt + F then XCommand + QQuit Google Chrome.
Command + HHide Google Chrome.
Tabs
Ctrl + TCommand + TOpen a new tab.
Ctrl + Shift + TCommand + Shift + TReopen previously closed tabs one by one.
Ctrl + Tab or Ctrl + PgDnCommand + Option + Right arrowJump to the next open tab.
Ctrl + Shift... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mehvish Mushtaq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quick Tip: restore system desktop icons on Windows 10 and 11 PCs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179549</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/07/05/quick-tip-restore-system-desktop-icons-on-windows-10-and-11-pcs/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T17:18:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vanilla Windows 10 and 11 PCs display desktop icons by default on the first run after installation. Manufacturers may place custom icons on the desktop, but if you install one of the […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Quick Tip: restore system desktop icons on Windows 10 and 11 PCs appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Freevee's Latest Free Channels Features Cooking, Music, and Nostalgia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/122303/freevees-latest-free-channels-features-cooking-music-and-nostalgia/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/122303/freevees-latest-free-channels-features-cooking-music-and-nostalgia/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T17:12:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Freevee, Amazon’s free streaming service formally known as IMDB TV, has always offered free content to watch with ads. But “free” doesn’t mean much without something actually good watch. Now the service is getting ready to add even more, and there’s a little something for everyone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Hendrickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Check Out This Drag Racing VW Beetle EV]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/122302/check-out-this-drag-racing-vw-beetle-ev/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/122302/check-out-this-drag-racing-vw-beetle-ev/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T17:02:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While it may sound a bit odd, people really like to convert old VW Beetles into electric drag-racers. The practice goes back twenty years, and back in 2011, two brothers shocked the world with their Black Current III electric Beetle. Now they’re back with an even more ridiculous car, the “V8-killing” Black Current IV.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Change the RDP Port on Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=814556</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/814556/how-to-change-the-rdp-port-on-windows-11/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T17:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’d like to access your Windows 11 PC remotely, it’s easy to do thanks to Remote Desktop Protocol (RDP), which comes with Pro and Enterprise versions of Microsoft’s OS. Although the default RDP port is 3389, there are times when you might want to change it. Here’s how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video sorveglianza con WebCam PC e telecamere IP: migliori programmi]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2008/09/video-sorveglianza-con-la-webcam-i.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2008/09/video-sorveglianza-con-la-webcam-i.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T16:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Con le telecamere IP o con le webcam del PC è possibile creare un vero e proprio sistema di sorveglianza low cost, gestito dal computer di casa. I programmi di questa lista, tutti gratuiti, permettono di gestire più telecamere o webcam contemporaneamente e sono in grado anche di registrare video o scattare foto quando vengono rilevati movimenti.

 Diventa quindi possibile creare un sistema di...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft quietly fixes ShadowCoerce Windows NTLM Relay bug]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-quietly-fixes-shadowcoerce-windows-ntlm-relay-bug/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-quietly-fixes-shadowcoerce-windows-ntlm-relay-bug/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T16:17:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has confirmed it fixed a previously disclosed 'ShadowCoerce' vulnerability as part of the June 2022 updates that enabled attackers to target Windows servers in NTLM relay attacks. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ASUS' New Wireless Earbuds Can Convert to Wired Listening]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/122293/asus-new-wireless-earbuds-can-convert-to-wired-listening/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/122293/asus-new-wireless-earbuds-can-convert-to-wired-listening/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T16:06:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wireless headphones are convenient, but they’re rarely the best option for gamers. Even the best Bluetooth audio codecs come with a bit of latency, and if you want to game without laggy audio, you have to deal with a drop in sound quality. The solution, at least in ASUS’ eyes, may be simpler than you expect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Started With firewalld on Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=807545</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/807545/how-to-get-started-with-firewalld-on-linux/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T16:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re looking for a modern, powerful firewall for Linux that is easy to configure on the command line or with its GUI interface, then firewalld is probably what you’re looking for.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKay</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Filesystem type exfat not configured in kernel." error suddenly when trying to mount external drive with udisks2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vs0j4k/filesystem_type_exfat_not_configured_in_kernel/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vs0j4k/filesystem_type_exfat_not_configured_in_kernel/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T15:29:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[it just suddenly gave me this error:
 failed to mount /org/freedesktop/UDisks2/block_devices/sdb1: GDBus.Error:org.freedesktop.UDisks2.Error.Failed: Error mounting /dev/sdb1 at /run/media/user/drive: Filesystem type exfat not configured in kernel. 
 it was working before I updated using sudo pacman -Syu, I'm guessing something changed with the kernel?
    submitted by    /u/ImALoooserOk  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[9 Charging Stands for Your Apple Watch]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=post-ideas&amp;p=481594</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15414326/apple-watch-charging-stands"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you in the market for a docking station or charging stand for your Apple Watch? We came up with a list of options, at various price points, for you to choose from. We’ll tell you what each docking station can do for your Apple Watch and the rest of your (compatible) Apple devices.
   

Content

What Is a Docking Station and When Do You Need One?
1. Lamicall Apple Watch Charging Stand
2. Conido Charging Stand
3. JackCube Design Wooden Charging Stand
4. OLEBR 3-in-1 Charging Station
5. WAITIEE 3-in-1 Wireless Charging Station
6. Belkin Boost Charge Pro Portable Fast Charger
7. Apple Watch Magnetic Charging Dock
8. MagSafe Duo Charger
9. Belkin Boost Charge Pro 3-in-1 Wireless Charger with MagSafe
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:What Is a GaN Charger? 5 of the Best GaN... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Natalie dela Vega</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Error installing Arch into Docker]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vs0cct/error_installing_arch_into_docker/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vs0cct/error_installing_arch_into_docker/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T15:21:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following steps at https://wiki.archlinux.org/title/Install_Arch_Linux_via_Docker I am trying to install Arch into a Docker container. Here's what I've done:
 mkdir /arch_docker docker run \ --env PS1="ADC(\#)[\d \T:\w]\\$ " \ --interactive \ --privileged \ --rm \ --tty \ --volume "/arch_docker:/target" \ "index.docker.io/library/archlinux:latest" /bin/sh # inside ADC: pacman -Sy reflector reflector > /etc/pacman.d/mirrorlist pacman -S arch-install-scripts pacstrap /target base 
 What I am getting from pacstrap command:
 ==> Creating install root at /target mount: /target/dev: permission denied. dmesg(1) may have more information after failed mount system call. ==> ERROR: failed to setup chroot /target 
 Did I miss something or the wiki instructions are incomplete? dmesg did not reveal any additional information.
    submitted by    /u/Revolutionary_Gur583  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ghacks Deals: The Game Design & Development Bundle]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179545</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/07/05/ghacks-deals-the-game-design-development-bundle/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T15:08:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Game Design & Development Bundle includes seven eLearning courses that take you from game design and development beginner to creating your own computer games. Here is the list of the seven […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Ghacks Deals: The Game Design & Development Bundle appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How do I expand my EFI file system to fill the partition?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vs01y9/how_do_i_expand_my_efi_file_system_to_fill_the/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vs01y9/how_do_i_expand_my_efi_file_system_to_fill_the/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T15:08:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm using the Windows EFI partition but I wanted to expand it a bit, so I downloaded the Gparted Live ISO and went ahead and did that. Now the partition is expanded, but the EFI file system hasn't changed size and still only shows as the Windows default of 100MB free. How can I change that?
 Edit: Fixed! Evidently, there's a "bug" with Gparted making it so that small partitions can't be resized properly - https://bugzilla.gnome.org/show_bug.cgi?id=649324.
 I roughly followed the steps in comment 4 of the bug to get the EFI file system expanded.
 My steps:
  
Back up contents of /boot - I did # dd if=/dev/nvme0n1p1 of=/backup/nvme0n1p1.img then # cp -r /boot ~/boot-backup.
 Re-format the EFI partition to EXT4 - # mkfs.ext4 /dev/nvme0n1p1.
 Re-size the newly-created EXT4 partition to the correct size - for my scenario, I opened Gparted and ran the "check" function on the new EXT4 partition. (I'm not sure if this step was necessary but whatever).
 Reformat the partition back to FAT32 - # mkfs.fat -F 32 /dev/nvme0n1p1.
 Restore the EFI partition files from the backup - # cp -r ~/boot-backup/* /boot
  
Possibly required steps in no particular order
  
Modify /etc/fstab for the new PARTUUID of the EFI partition
 Modify bootloader to check the correct partition - I use rEFInd so I had to edit the volumefield in my Arch configuration stanza to the new PARTUUID. 
  
After that, everything seems to be working but I still have the original backup created with dd for now in case I messed something up that I haven't noticed yet.
 If you need to restore the original partition - # dd if=/backup/nvme0n1p1.img of=/dev/nvme0n1p1 which (I think) should restore the entire original partition to how it was.
 I'd probably keep a flash drive with ARCHISO on-hand if you need to do this, but YMMV.
 EDIT2: Evidently, the Arch fatresize package may be able to do the same thing without copying the partition around... so maybe try that first.
    submitted by    /u/NormGreen  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Things You Didn’t Know You Could Do in PowerPoint]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=808441</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/808441/things-you-didnt-know-you-could-do-in-powerpoint/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T15:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some features in Microsoft PowerPoint stand out like creating animations, adding slide transitions, and inserting charts, shapes, and 3D models. But then there are those features that are a bit hidden.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monitorare gli spostamenti dei bambini anche in vacanza con lo smartwatch Xplora X5 Play]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Monitorare-gli-spostamenti-dei-bambini-anche-in-vacanza-con-lo-smartwatch-Xplora-X5-Play_24743</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Monitorare-gli-spostamenti-dei-bambini-anche-in-vacanza-con-lo-smartwatch-Xplora-X5-Play_24743"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T14:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Difficile non preoccuparsi quando non si sa dove sono i propri figli, soprattutto i più piccoli: bastano pochi secondi di distrazione in spiaggia, mentre si fa una gita, durante un'escursione in montagna, mentre giocano al parco o si è in viaggio ed eccoli sparire. Tanti particolari possono incuriosirli, attirare la loro attenzione e spingerli ad allontanarsi. Per monitorare gli spostamenti dei bambini ed essere un po’ più tranquilli, soprattutto durante un periodo di vacanza, è possibile dotarsi di uno smartwatch come Xplora X5 Play, un dispositivo ideato per i bambini che offre solo le funzioni di comunicazione necessarie. È dotato di un chip GPS integrato che consente ai genitori, grazie all'app collegata, di sapere sempre dove sono i propri figli. 

Con al polso lo smartwatch Xplora X5 Play i bambini hanno la possibilità di essere più indipendenti e autonomi senza preoccupare la famiglia: è possibile anche creare delle zone di sicurezza per ricevere una notifica ogni volta che il minore entra o esce dalle aree preimpostate. Xplora X5 Play è uno smartwatch leggerissimo con funzioni di cellulare e connettività dati 4G, in grado di ricevere e inviare messaggi vocali, messaggi di testo pre-salvati, fotografie ed emoji.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Slashes Trade-In Value Ahead of iPhone 14 Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/122290/apple-slashes-trade-in-value-ahead-of-iphone-14-launch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/122290/apple-slashes-trade-in-value-ahead-of-iphone-14-launch/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T14:49:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you were hoping to get a good trade-in value for your old iPhone—tough luck. Apple quietly adjusted the maximum trade-in rates for all of its devices, including the iPhone, iPad, Mac, and Apple Watch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JBL Live Pro 2 TWS Review: All About That Bass]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/122017/jbl-live-pro-2-tws-review/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/122017/jbl-live-pro-2-tws-review/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T14:24:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Incredible bass? Check. Hefty battery life? Check. Noise canceling? Check. When clear, uninterrupted sound matters most, the JBL Live Pro 2 TWS earbuds deliver. These earbuds feature JBL’s Signature Sound, adaptive noise canceling, and wireless charging capabilities among many other features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brenna Miles</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best External Hard Drives of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=749487</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/749487/best-external-hard-drives/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite fast internet and cheap cloud storage, nothing beats a good external hard drive. Whether you’re backing up data or taking your gigs on the go, one of these brilliant storage devices is sure to be perfect for your needs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sydney Butler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Copertura 4G in treno: completata quella sull'Alta Velocità Milano-Bologna]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Copertura-4G-in-treno-completata-quella-sull-Alta-Velocita-Milano-Bologna_24742</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Copertura-4G-in-treno-completata-quella-sull-Alta-Velocita-Milano-Bologna_24742"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T13:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TIM e Gruppo Ferrovie dello Stato avevano siglato a inizio anno un accordo per estendere la copertura del segnale 4G alle gallerie sulla rete ad Alta Velocità.Le due aziende annunciano i primi frutti di quell'intesa: nel tratto tra Milano e Bologna la copertura 4G è stata completata a distanza di circa 6 mesi dalla stipula dell'accordo. Portando le tecnologie di connessione più performanti anche in galleria, TIM e FS hanno ottenuto la completa copertura della tratta Milano-Bologna assicurando un collegamento stabile ed alte prestazioni, utile soprattutto per i tanti professionisti che utilizzano i treni più veloci per lavorare durante il viaggio.La tecnologia 4G consente ai passeggeri di usufruire di una connessione prestazionale anche nelle aree più sfavorevoli come le gallerie ferroviarie sia attraverso il servizio WiFi di bordo treno sia attraverso la copertura diretta di tutti gli operatori di telecomunicazioni che hanno al progetto: TIM come capofila, Iliad, Vodafone e Wind Tre.I lavori di upgrade verso la tecnologia 4G saranno avviati nei prossimi mesi anche sulle tratte ad Alta Velocità tra Bologna e Firenze per poi proseguire nel corso del 2023 da Torino a Milano, da Firenze fino a Napoli e da Bologna a Venezia.L'obiettivo è ottenere una connettività voce e dati sempre più affidabile sulle linee ferroviarie più veloci ma anche sulle linee convenzionali, a partire dalle tratte a maggiore frequentazione così da garantire un servizio di qualità ai passeggeri dei treni AV, Intercity e Regionali e alle imprese ferroviarie del trasporto merci.L'attivazione degli impianti sulla AV Milano-Bologna rappresenta il primo tassello dell'accordo tra FS, tramite il gestore dell'infrastruttura RFI, e TIM.Nell'ambito delle iniziative legate al PNRR, inoltre, sono previsti studi di fattibilità relativi al possibile utilizzo di tecnologie 5G..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Chrome Is Under Attack: Update Right Now]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=815926</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/815926/google-chrome-is-under-attack-update-right-now/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T13:47:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Chrome is under attack on Windows and Android. The latest security hole in WebRTC has an exploit that’s circulating in the wild, so you don’t want to browse without installing the patch. Here’s what you need to know.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come importare dati in Word da Excel, PDF e siti web]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/07/come-importare-dati-in-word-da-excel.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/07/come-importare-dati-in-word-da-excel.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T13:42:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Microsoft Word possiamo importare dati da tantissime fonti diverse, senza dover fare manualmente copia ed incolla del contenuto. Il programma di scrittura di Microsoft supporta nativamente l'importazione dei grafici e delle tabelle da fogli di calcolo Excel, ma possiamo importare dei dati anche dai documenti PDF o dai siti web, così da integrarli in un unico documento Word. 
Nella guida che...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public key revoked [Xorg server/xorg-server-xdmx-dev]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vry1hs/public_key_revoked_xorg_serverxorgserverxdmxdev/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vry1hs/public_key_revoked_xorg_serverxorgserverxdmxdev/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T13:36:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Verify the signatures of source files by using 'gpg'... xorg-server-1.20.10.tar.bz2 ... FAILURE (public key '9C825A6605D40BBE' revoked) ==> ERROR: One or more PGP-signatures cannot be verified! 
 ​
 I entered the command
 gpg --keyserver hkps://keys.openpgp.org --recv-keys 9C825A6605D40BBE gpg: ключ 0FDD682D974CA72A: "Matt Turner <mattst88@gmail.com>" 1 new signature gpg: ключ 0FDD682D974CA72A: "Matt Turner <mattst88@gmail.com>" 1 new signature gpg: Всего обработано: 1 gpg: new sub-connections: 1 gpg: new signature: 1 
 but its not worked. help(
    submitted by    /u/Reged1tFox  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.11 Might Slip To December Due To Outstanding Bugs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Python-3.11-Possible-Delay</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Python-3.11-Possible-Delay"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T13:30:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While Python 3.11 is a big release and bringing significant performance improvements, users and developers may need to wait a little longer for the stable release...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elimina per tutti WhatsApp: dopo quanto tempo si può cancellare un messaggio]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Elimina-per-tutti-WhatsApp-dopo-quanto-tempo-si-puo-cancellare-un-messaggio_24741</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Elimina-per-tutti-WhatsApp-dopo-quanto-tempo-si-puo-cancellare-un-messaggio_24741"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T13:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Una delle funzioni di un client per la messaggistica istantanea come WhatsApp che gli utenti utilizzano con maggiore frequenza è quella che consente l'eliminazione dei messaggi. Tenendo premuto su qualunque messaggio o allegato inviato all'interno di una chat quindi toccando l'icona del cestino è possibile rimuovere tale contenuto.Anche nel caso in cui il messaggio fosse stato recapitato al destinatario oppure agli iscritti a un gruppo, scegliendo Elimina per tutti il contenuto verrà rimosso dai dispositivi degli altri interlocutori (viene comunque mostrato un messaggio di cortesia che conferma la rimozione del contenuto).La funzione Elimina per tutti è utile perché consente di rimuovere un messaggio WhatsApp già spedito, ad esempio nel caso in cui lo si fosse mandato alla persona sbagliat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Archiso doesn't keep file permissions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vrxszk/archiso_doesnt_keep_file_permissions/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vrxszk/archiso_doesnt_keep_file_permissions/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T13:24:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[so i added scripts (.sh files) in /airootfs/etc/skel/Desktop and i set the permissions so that they can be executed, but once the system boots into the live environment they are no longer allowed to be executed as programs, which i need for my usecase. is there something i'm missing?
    submitted by    /u/firelighter487  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trovare dispositivi smarriti con Huawei Tag: ecco come funziona]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Trovare-dispositivi-smarriti-con-Huawei-Tag-ecco-come-funziona_24740</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Trovare-dispositivi-smarriti-con-Huawei-Tag-ecco-come-funziona_24740"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T13:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dopo il successo riscosso dagli Apple AirTag, i dispositivi che possono essere applicati su qualunque oggetto per rilevarne la posizione geografica, la società della Mela ha applicato alcune importanti modifiche sul loro funzionamento.Altri produttori, nel frattempo, hanno cercato di seguire l'esempio Apple con risultati variabili.Huawei, da parte sua, si appresta a dare uno scossone al mercato con un dispositivo economico e compatto che permetterà di geolocalizzare qualunque cosa.Con una forma simile ai plettri per chitarre (non sono quindi completamente tondi) i nuovi Huawei Tag hanno uno spessore minimo di appena 5,6 millimetri e un peso di 6 grammi riducendo entrambe le misure rispetto alla proposta Apple. I 'localizzatori' di Huawei sono quindi ancora più semplici e pratici passando davvero inosservati.Huawei Tag dispone di connettività Bluetooth: in questo modo è possibile sincronizzarli con lo smartphone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything You Need to Know About Hulu]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119218/everything-you-need-to-know-about-hulu/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119218/everything-you-need-to-know-about-hulu/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T13:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone has heard of Hulu—but how many people really know all the benefits it offers? It has advantages and disadvantages like any other streaming platform, but Hulu is one of the most impressive. The service has plenty of cost-effective features that nearly any subscriber is sure to love.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>April Miller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Should You Install an iOS or iPadOS Beta on iPhone or iPad?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=814058</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/814058/should-you-install-an-ios-or-ipados-beta-on-iphone-or-ipad/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T13:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Installing a beta version of iOS or iPadOS on your iPhone or iPad is easy—but just because you can, that doesn’t necessarily mean you should. Here are some things to weigh up before you dip your toe into Apple’s pool of pre-release software.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fresh MGLRU Benchmarks Are Looking Very Promising For Linux Performance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=MGLRU-July-2022-Performance</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=MGLRU-July-2022-Performance"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T13:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MGLRU as the "Multi-Gen LRU" for reworking the Linux kernel's page reclamation code to be less taxing on the CPU and making better choices continues to look very good for the future of Linux performance...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SupRemo Console: il pannello di controllo definitivo per la gestione IT (prova, guida, recensione) (video)]]></title>
        <id>3611|20220705144500</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/controllo-remoto-270/supremo-console-pannello-controllo-definitivo-gestione-it-prova-guida-recensione-video-3611"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T12:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tutti noi (o quasi) siamo in grado di gestire il nostro PC personale: backup, aggiornamenti, manutenzione, controllo remoto e così via. Ma quando i computer sono 10, 100, 1.000, e magari appartengono a persone diverse che lavorano in smart working, tutto diventa enormemente più difficile. Lo sanno bene gli amministratori di sistema e i responsabili IT, che di sovente si trovano a supervisionare e mantenere decine e decine di sistemi eterogenei. Per aiutare i professionisti del settore in questo difficile compito interviene SupRemo Console: un servizio in cloud, accessibile tramite browser web, che semplifica la gestione remota di molteplici sistemi. Vediamo dunque quali funzione offre in questa nostra recensione e guida a SupRemo Console
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenSSH: come installare client e server in Windows 10 e 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=OpenSSH-come-installare-client-e-server-in-Windows-10-e-11_24705</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=OpenSSH-come-installare-client-e-server-in-Windows-10-e-11_24705"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T12:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Il protocollo SSH, acronimo di Secure Shell, permette di stabilire una sessione remota tramite interfaccia a riga di comando con un altro host. Diversamente rispetto ad altri strumenti simili, l'intera comunicazione - compresa l'autenticazione - avviene in forma cifrata.Se dovete amministrare un sistema Linux a distanza con ogni probabilità vi è la necessità di utilizzare un client SSH.La porta standard sulla quale viene posto in ascolto il server SSH è la TCP/UDP 22 ma come nel caso di qualunque altro servizio è possibile utilizzare altre porte di comunicazione.Un server SSH è spesso presente anche su router, access point e dispositivi per il networking in generale, device IoT e dispositivi industriali; a titolo esemplificativo si usa anche per comunicare - almeno per impostazione predefi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Which Amazon Fire Tablet Should You Buy?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=813982</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/813982/which-amazon-fire-tablet-should-you-buy/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T12:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon’s Fire Tablets are incredibly popular, mostly because they are cheap: the entry-level Fire 7 only costs $49.99 with ads. There’s more than just one model, though, so which one should you get?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA: Here's how to apply this key Windows patch without breaking certificate authentication]]></title>
        <id>ac0f7c92-25e6-4467-9164-493ce7e3ac90</id>
        <link href="https://www.zdnet.com/article/cisa-heres-how-to-apply-this-key-windows-patch-without-breaking-certificate-authentication/#ftag=RSSbaffb68"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T12:25:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CISA now urges agencies to apply a patch that broke logins for users connecting to Windows servers that handle authentication.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest topics for ZDNet in Windows</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Print a Document When You Don’t Own a Printer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=812753</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/812753/how-to-print-a-document-when-you-dont-own-a-printer/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Technology has made printing documents a lot less necessary than it used to be, but that doesn’t mean you’ll never need to do it. Still, many people no longer own printers. So what do you do in those situations?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migliori Launcher Android per cambiare aspetto allo smartphone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2011/11/launcher-e-temi-android-gratuiti-per.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2011/11/launcher-e-temi-android-gratuiti-per.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T11:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Una delle caratteristiche migliori di un telefono Android è la possibilità di cambiare e personalizzare la schermata iniziale dello smartphone dell'interfaccia utente, che è governata sempre da un'applicazione chiamata launcher.

 A seconda della marca del telefono comprato, ci sarà un launcher da cui dipende il modo in cui sono organizzate le app e come appare lo schermo iniziale. I launcher...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t Put Your TV Over Your Fireplace]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=812788</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/812788/dont-put-your-tv-over-your-fireplace/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Faced with a small living room, I decided to mount our family TV over the fireplace a few years ago. It saved lots of space, but I deeply regret it. Here’s why. (Don’t make the same mistake I did!)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OnLogic Factor 201 Fits The Raspberry Pi CM4 For Industrial Needs & Other Innovative Uses]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31261</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31261"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in March the folks at OnLogic announced the Factor 201 as a Raspberry Pi CM4 (Compute Module 4) fitted for industrial use-cases like IoT gateways and more. The past few weeks I have been testing out this Raspberry Pi powered device and indeed it opens the door for using the Raspberry Pi within more harsh and demanding environments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RADV Remains Competitive To AMD's Radeon Vulkan Windows Driver, Linux OpenGL Dominates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=RX6800XT-Linux-Windows-Mid-22</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=RX6800XT-Linux-Windows-Mid-22"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T09:50:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm currently working on a fresh comparison of the Windows vs. Linux performance for Intel's Alder Lake hybrid processors due to a number of readers inquiring how the OS support has evolved. In the process of carrying out those tests I also ran some fresh Windows vs. Linux tests with the AMD Radeon RX 6800 XT for how the OpenGL and Vulkan driver performance stands...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LLVM Clang 15.0 Adds Arm Cortex-M85 Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=LLVM-Clang-Cortex-M85</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=LLVM-Clang-Cortex-M85"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T09:48:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Support for Arm's Cortex-M85 based on Armv8.1-M has been added for the LLVM 15.0 compiler release this fall...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wine on Arch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vrtzgw/wine_on_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vrtzgw/wine_on_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T09:34:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi! I decided that I want to download wine, but I can't get it to work.I tried watching tutorials, none of them have worked so far.
 The commands I tried to use were:sudo pacman -S wine-staging winetrickssudo pacman -S giflib lib32-giflib libpng lib32-libpng libldap lib32-libldap gnutls lib32-gnutls mpg123 lib32-mpg123 openal lib32-openal v4l-utils lib32-v4l-utils libpulse lib32-libpulse alsa-plugins lib32-alsa-plugins alsa-lib lib32-alsa-lib libjpeg-turbo lib32-libjpeg-turbo libxcomposite lib32-libxcomposite libxinerama lib32-libxinerama ncurses lib32-ncurses opencl-icd-loader lib32-opencl-icd-loader libxslt lib32-libxslt libva lib32-libva gtk3 lib32-gtk3 gst-plugins-base-libs lib32-gst-plugins-base-libs vulkan-icd-loader lib32-vulkan-icd-loader cups samba dosbox
 And on the first one, it simply said:error: target not found: wine-staging
 error: target not found: winetricks
 And on the second command, it simply said that all of the dependencies were reinstalling?
 So, can someone help me with downloading wine on Arch?
    submitted by    /u/taparion12  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iwctl says that i'm connected to the network, but it's incorrect]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vrtz4k/iwctl_says_that_im_connected_to_the_network_but/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vrtz4k/iwctl_says_that_im_connected_to_the_network_but/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T09:34:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I just installed arch linux, and, after noticing that even though i installed networkmanager, i wasn't connected to the internet, i booted back into the installation medium, chrooted into the system and then installed iwd. i rebooted back into the main system, and, after using "sudo systemctl start iwd", i was able to connect to my network using the iwctl tool, just like on the live system. but i was mistaken, as when i pinged google.com to test my network, i was horrified to see: "ping: google.com: Temporary failure in name resolution" I have searched a bit on google, but i haven't found a solution that works.
 ❗️Important update ❗️ i used nmcli to interact with networkmanager and connect to my wifi, it was really strange, because it looked like the process hung (i was waiting for it to connect for a minute), and then it said something like secret key required but not given, but then, just to test, i pinged google and they responded!! 
 the command i used: "sudo nmcli dev wifi con "network_name" password "network_password"
    submitted by    /u/Gurn00r  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I broke Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vrtn69/i_broke_python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vrtn69/i_broke_python/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T09:09:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was having issues during an upgrade and I deleted the entire /usr/lib/python directory. Yes, I thought "WTF am I doing?" just as I hit enter.
 How do I fix this? So much of the system relies on Python. Simply re-installing Python didn't fix it.Can I avoid doing a complete system re-install? 
 [SOLVED] Thanks to the awesome people on this sub. I installed this system 7 years ago and you've saved it!
    submitted by    /u/FXOjafar  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitwarden to add support for passwordless login to vault, autofill for other desktop apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179542</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/07/05/bitwarden-roadmap-2022-update-passwordless-login/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T08:56:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bitwarden roadmap for 2022 has been updated, the company plans to implement some interesting features in its password manager. Bitwarden to add support for passwordless login One of the upcoming features […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Bitwarden to add support for passwordless login to vault, autofill for other desktop apps appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DNS-over-QUIC, cos'è e come funziona il successore di DoH]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=DNS-over-QUIC-cos-e-e-come-funziona-il-successore-di-DoH_24704</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=DNS-over-QUIC-cos-e-e-come-funziona-il-successore-di-DoH_24704"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T08:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Il tempo delle comunicazioni non crittografate sta volgendo al termine. Anni fa l'IETF (Internet Engineering Task Force), organismo internazionale libero composto da tecnici, specialisti e ricercatori interessati all'evoluzione tecnica e tecnologica della rete Internet, ha approvato l'utilizzo dei protocolli DNS-over-TLS (DoT) prima e DNS-over-HTTPS (DoH) poi per proteggere, grazie alla crittografia, le richieste di risoluzione dei nomi a dominio inviate ai server DNS.A metà maggio 2022 IETF ha adottato le specifiche di DNS-over-QUIC (DoQ), protocollo ormai destinato a diventare uno standard ufficiale e, stando a quanto emerso, a superare i predecessori come DoT e DoH.DNS-over-QUIC è un protocollo DNS che utilizza il protocollo del livello di trasporto QUIC per trasmettere le richieste di risoluzione dei domini.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 problemi rimasti e risolvibili con pochi clic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-11-problemi-rimasti-e-risolvibili-con-pochi-clic_24661</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-11-problemi-rimasti-e-risolvibili-con-pochi-clic_24661"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T07:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Il debutto di Windows 11, distribuito in versione finale a partire dal 5 ottobre 2021, non è stato dei migliori.Tra i vari problemi di Windows 11 segnaliamo quello relativo all'implementazione della funzionalità fTPM di AMD che causava blocchi del sistema, comportamenti 'scattosi' del puntatore, crepitii durante la riproduzione audio, la riduzione delle prestazioni con i processori AMD quantificata in circa il 15% rispetto allo stesso sistema con Windows 10, l'inadeguatezza del sistema operativo a supportare monitor HDR, i cali di performance con le unità SSD.Tutti i problemi sono stati risolti con il rilascio di aggiornamenti correttivi distribuiti attraverso Windows Update tanto che con un annuncio ufficiale, a metà maggio 2022, Microsoft ha dichiarato che 'Windows 11 è designato per la distribuzione generale'.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GRUB lists Linux option as Debian, even though it’s not]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vrrzcf/grub_lists_linux_option_as_debian_even_though_its/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vrrzcf/grub_lists_linux_option_as_debian_even_though_its/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T07:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few days ago I decided to spruce up my GRUB menu by installing PotatoCarafe’s awesome theme, and came across a funny issue: Arch Linux is listed as Debian Linux in the boot menu. Image.
 It’s very, very small and insignificant, but I notice it every time I turn on my PC and it is slowly whittling away at my sanity. Does anyone know how/why this has happened and how to fix it?
    submitted by    /u/woodencupboard  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RAM: la temperatura di lavoro rappresenta il collo di bottiglia più importante]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=RAM-la-temperatura-di-lavoro-rappresenta-il-collo-di-bottiglia-piu-importante_24626</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=RAM-la-temperatura-di-lavoro-rappresenta-il-collo-di-bottiglia-piu-importante_24626"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T07:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[La memoria RAM è uno dei componenti più importanti di qualunque sistema ma com'è noto vi è una marcata disparità tra la sua velocità quella del processore.In un altro articolo abbiamo visto come scegliere la memoria RAM e quando estenderla.Rispetto al processore la RAM introduce un importante collo di bottiglia che viene in parte gestito utilizzando la cache, utile appunto per ridurre il numero di accessi al contenuto della memoria primaria.Perché non vengono create memorie più veloci? Le RAM hanno fatto registrare una continua evoluzione: si pensi al recente supporto per le memorie DDR5 introdotto nelle schede madri per PC notebook e desktop oppure alle LPDDR5X utilizzate sui dispositivi mobili più performanti.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome 103 update fixes 0-Day security issue that is exploited in the wild]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179537</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/07/05/chrome-103-update-fixes-0-day-security-issue-that-is-exploited-in-the-wild/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T04:48:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google published a new security update for the stable channel of the company's Chrome web browser that addresses several security issues. One of the security issues is exploited in the wild, according […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Chrome 103 update fixes 0-Day security issue that is exploited in the wild appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I need a tool that can give me access to an Snapchat account]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vrlpnn/i_need_a_tool_that_can_give_me_access_to_an/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vrlpnn/i_need_a_tool_that_can_give_me_access_to_an/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T00:47:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So a little backstory someone is stalking my little brother 12 and it's pissing me off. Is there a tool that I can use. I'm not really versed in Snapchat hacking. Thanks
    submitted by    /u/Peanut-Sea  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fix ‘Bad System Config Info’ Error in Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=post-ideas&amp;p=293442</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/11212455/fix-bad-system-config-info-error-windows10"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bad System Config Info is a common bug check error on Windows systems, caused mainly by a malfunctioning of the system and registry files or the Boot Configuration Data (BCD) file. Some boot order files in the BCD, or even some older ones, may conflict with newer, stable files. When this happens, the error otherwise known as the Blue Screen of Death (BSoD) occurs.
    
The bug check error can also be caused by:
    
faulty hardware
incorrect system settings
a bad driver
installing an important update
    
However, most error messages will often have a description of what the problem may be. Below are some tried and tested solutions to help you fix a Bad System Config Info error in Windows 10 and 11.
   

Content

1. Try Restarting Your Computer
2. Roll Back Windows Update
3. Check your RAM and Hard Drive
4. Update or Reinstall Drivers
5. bcdedit Command
6. Fix BCD file
7. Fix the Registry
8. System Restore
9. Reset Windows 10/Windows 11
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Megan Glosson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RTL-SDR programs building]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vrklvh/rtlsdr_programs_building/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vrklvh/rtlsdr_programs_building/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-04T23:45:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have anyone tried building these programs on Archlinux?
 libaeroambe
 JFFT
 JAERO
 They have build scripts for Linux but they're made strictly for Debian based distros and I have issues trying to accommodate the changes…
    submitted by    /u/Granat1  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why my kernel compiling fails in Arch?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vrjwm0/why_my_kernel_compiling_fails_in_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vrjwm0/why_my_kernel_compiling_fails_in_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-04T23:08:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've succesfully compiled kernel in Manjaro, Fedora and Ubuntu. I've never had success in Arch. This time I decided to find the reason why it fails.
 I started and lastly tried the wiki guide again: https://wiki.archlinux.org/title/Kernel/Traditional_compilation
 'sudo make modules' prints the following error:GEN kernel/kheaders_data.tar.xz
 make[1]: *** [kernel/Makefile:158: kernel/kheaders_data.tar.xz] Error 127
 make: *** [Makefile:1843: kernel] Error 2
 'mkinitcpio -k' prints I'm missing dm_crypt, dm_intregrity, usbhid and nvme and "no modules were added to the image".(Full print of the commands: https://pastebin.com/72nRueMx )
 I'm out of ideas what I could do. In Manjaro, it creates the arch/x86/boot/bzImage with 'make' command and Arch requires it separately 'make bzImage'. Obviously it won't boot without modules installed..
    submitted by    /u/Lord_Schnitzel  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Remote for Arch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vrivrx/remote_for_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vrivrx/remote_for_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-04T22:17:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is there anything in the Arch repos where I can use my phone as a remote controller for my desktop? I connect my laptop to my tv and watch videos off it but if I could do this all remotely that would be really cool.
    submitted by    /u/StringNo8495  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come esportare e riutilizzare le password memorizzate di Firefox]]></title>
        <id>1731|20220705000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/browser-455/come-esportare-riutilizzare-password-memorizzate-firefox-1731"/>
        <updated>2022-07-04T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quando ci troviamo a dover reinstallare un sistema operativo, o anche a rifare il profilo di Firefox, le principali cose che ci preoccupiamo di salvare, per poi riutilizzare, sono i preferiti e le relative password memorizzate nel browser. Mentre la reimportazione di preferiti e molto semplice, quella delle password è stata nascosta, quindi vediamo come farlo senza dover utilizzare un account Firefox e la sua sincronizzazione.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the Google Password Manager in Chrome]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=post-ideas&amp;p=487738</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15410693/google-chrome-password-manager"/>
        <updated>2022-07-04T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Keeping track of an endless number of passwords as you browse online is enough to give anyone a headache. Luckily, Google Password Manager in Chrome makes life a little easier by remembering your passwords for you. It’s a simple, free tool that’s already built into Chrome and stores all your login credentials in one easy-to-access place.
   

Content

How Google Password Manager Works
What to Do Before Adding Passwords to Google
Add Passwords With Auto-Save
Add Passwords Manually
How to Create Strong Passwords
How to Check Chrome Passwords for Breaches
How to Edit Passwords
How to Import and Export Passwords in Chrome
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to See a Password in Your Browser Instead of Dots
    
How Google Password Manager Works
    
You need only two things to use Google Password Manager – the Chrome... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Crystal Crowder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best AirTag Alternative for Android]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=724198</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/724198/the-best-airtag-alternative-for-android/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-04T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple AirTags offer an easy and cheap way to track tons of everyday objects. The only problem is they’re locked to Apple products. Android users have several options, but there’s one that stands above the rest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[my Bluetooth adapter problem]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vrgrtp/my_bluetooth_adapter_problem/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vrgrtp/my_bluetooth_adapter_problem/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-04T20:38:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[it doesn't matter what distro I use it shows up one boot. like I started my pc if it shows up then in next boot it doesn't shows up. then again after next boot it again shows up. I don't know what or where the problem
    submitted by    /u/SyeedAhmed  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Raspberry Pi-Powered Black and White Tube TV Plays Modern Movies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/122260/this-raspberry-pi-powered-black-and-white-tube-tv-plays-modern-movies/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/122260/this-raspberry-pi-powered-black-and-white-tube-tv-plays-modern-movies/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-04T20:04:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve all seen countless retro-inspired Raspberry Pi projects throughout the years, like that iPod that streams from Spotify and this ZX Spectrum Raspberry Pi cassette tape. But movie fans will love this old black and white tube TV that plays modern movies with retro vibes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Factory Reset a Windows 11 PC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=762169</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/762169/how-to-factory-reset-a-windows-11-pc/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-04T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Resetting your Windows 11 PC will allow you fix some issues or prepare your PC to sell. Doing so erases all your settings and allows you to start again with a clean slate. We’ll show you how to do just that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD Radeon RX 6800 XT not working]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vrflyl/amd_radeon_rx_6800_xt_not_working/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vrflyl/amd_radeon_rx_6800_xt_not_working/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-04T19:44:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm new to Arch Linux, and I have it running on a computer with an AMD Radeon RX 6800 XT graphics card, but I can't get the card to work with Arch. I have tried many tutorials, but I always end up with a black screen and a blinking cursor when trying to boot. I know the card isn't defective because it works just fine with windows. I can also run Arch just fine with on-board graphics.
 Edit: It's the desktop environment that doesn't work. It worked just fine before I installed the desktop environment.
    submitted by    /u/Z3roKelvin  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First installation freeze on login but not when on integrated graphics. No gui installed only terminal ?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vrf82z/first_installation_freeze_on_login_but_not_when/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vrf82z/first_installation_freeze_on_login_but_not_when/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-04T19:26:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone. Graphics card: AMD R9 380 CPU: i3-4170 I'm installing arch for the initiatory time and I am nearly there but I cant quite get the final bit working. While entering passwords in the initial decrypt and then login stage the terminal will freeze on either after the‍ decrypt stage of after the login stage. It seems to be random. Unplugging the graphics card and going on integrated graphics makes everything work fine. What confuses me more is that I haven't installed any gui elements (Xorg etc.) so its strange that the graphics card causes issues. It didn't when booting from usb. I've installed 'mesa' and 'xf86-video-amdgpu' to no avail. I've installed the intel microcode. Anyone got any advice. Cheers! Edit: I've found a reddit posts about my graphics card so it might be an issue with the card.
    submitted by    /u/lovingothers-  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get HAYLOU PurFree BC01 Bone Conduction Headphones for $80]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=502172</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15410537/haylou-purfree-bc01-bone-conduction-headphones"/>
        <updated>2022-07-04T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earbuds are great, but sometimes they just don’t work for everyone. Some people just don’t like to put them inside their ears. If you count yourself in that crowd, consider the HAYLOU PurFree BC01 Bone Conduction Headphones. There’s nothing to go inside your ear, leaving you with the ultimate in comfort, while paying less than $80.
    
The headphones have a tough memory titanium wire built in, making them lighter than other headphones. It’s difficult for them to lose their shape, even after they are repeatedly twisted. Additionally, the ergonomic design and multi-point support keep them on your head, even during sports. The sound is more concentrated yet wide with delicate details because they are airtight.
   
 
   
Dry, non-sticky, skin-friendly silicone covers the HAYLOU PurFree BC01 Bone Conduction Headphones, making them suitable for long-term wear, even for those with allergies. You’ll be more comfortable while wearing them, leaving you to work out even longer. Being that they aren’t in-ear headphones, they lead to safer workouts and a healthy inner ear, reducing hearing loss.
  ... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Change the RDP Port on Windows 10]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=814478</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/814478/how-to-change-the-rdp-port-on-windows-10/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-04T19:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s easy to use your Windows 10 PC remotely thanks to Remote Desktop Protocol (RDP), which is built into Pro or Enterprise versions of Windows 10. By default, the RDP port is 3389, but you might need to change it. Here’s how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD Rembrandt SoC Support For Coreboot In Place - Based Off Existing "Sabrina" Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMD-Rembrandt-Coreboot</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMD-Rembrandt-Coreboot"/>
        <updated>2022-07-04T18:55:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's Coreboot code now has AMD Rembrandt SoC support by splitting it out from the Sabrina SoC support that has been in the works the past several months for this open-source firmware project...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AstraLocker ransomware shuts down and releases decryptors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/astralocker-ransomware-shuts-down-and-releases-decryptors/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/astralocker-ransomware-shuts-down-and-releases-decryptors/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-04T18:15:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat actor behind the lesser-known AstraLocker ransomware told BleepingComputer they're shutting down the operation and plan to switch to cryptojacking. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon's Retail Stores Will Sell Your Every Move to Advertisers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/122236/amazons-retail-stores-will-sell-your-every-move-to-advertisers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/122236/amazons-retail-stores-will-sell-your-every-move-to-advertisers/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-04T18:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new tool will allow companies to access anonymous information about shoppers through the analytics tool. From here, brands sold at Amazon locations can see how often products are taken off shelves and whether it’s purchased or put back. Additionally, if put back on the shelf, Amazon will note if the specific item gets purchased later on Amazon’s website.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Insert Multiple Rows in Google Sheets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=811935</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/811935/how-to-insert-multiple-rows-in-google-sheets/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-04T18:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you need several more rows in your spreadsheet, don’t waste time adding one row at a time. Google Sheets offers a few ways to add multiple rows, even between your existing rows, in your spreadsheets. We’ll show you how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google patches new Chrome zero-day flaw exploited in attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/google-patches-new-chrome-zero-day-flaw-exploited-in-attacks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/google-patches-new-chrome-zero-day-flaw-exploited-in-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-04T17:56:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has released Chrome 103.0.5060.114 for Windows users to address a high-severity zero-day vulnerability exploited by attackers in the wild, the fourth Chrome zero-day patched in 2022. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tronsmart Onyx Ace Pro True Wireless Earbuds Review]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=486757</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15410417/tronsmart-onyx-ace-pro-true-wireless-earbuds"/>
        <updated>2022-07-04T17:25:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to earbuds, there are two must-haves: great audio quality and comfort. Finding that perfect balance that feels good for hours while also helping shut out the world isn’t always easy. The Tronsmart Onyx Ace Pro True Wireless Earbuds seek to offer both with adaptive sound. I had the pleasure of trying these earbuds out to see just how well they worked.
    
Overview of Features
    
The Tronsmart Onyx Ace Pro True Wireless Earbuds are designed to provide exceptional audio quality while reducing background noise for long-lasting music and calls. The ergonomic design fits partially in the ear, giving a more comfortable fit, even when wearing for long periods of time.
   
 
   
As with most earbuds, the Tronsmart have a compact charging case. The earbuds themselves can last up to 6.5 hours on one charge, while the case extends this to up to 27 hours. A short USB cable is provided to charge the case. 
    
They’re perfect for an active lifestyle with an IPX5 rating, making them... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Crystal Crowder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to See Image Size (Resolution) of Photos on iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=811182</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/811182/how-to-see-image-size-resolution-of-photos-on-iphone/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-04T17:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every digital photo on your iPhone has a resolution defined by the number of pixels in the image. The more pixels each images has, the more detail the photo can potentially store. If you’re running iOS 15 or higher, here’s how to see the size of an image (in pixel dimensions) in the Photos app on your iPhone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PACMAN deps check]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vrbsg8/pacman_deps_check/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vrbsg8/pacman_deps_check/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-04T16:51:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have a question about an useful pacman trick. I uninstalled a few packages that were dependencies of other packages. I noted down their names so i can reinstall those packages but, i was wondering...
 Is there a pacman command that scans the entire database of installed packages and ,for each, checks if the correct deps are installed?
    submitted by    /u/nemis16  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Programmi per registrare video dalla webcam del PC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2008/07/registrare-un-video-con-la-webcam.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2008/07/registrare-un-video-con-la-webcam.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-04T16:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Per registrare un video da caricare online in cui esprimere il proprio parere, per creare videomessaggi da inviare a qualcuno o semplicemente per prove di discorsi o una cantata improvvisata, è possibile utilizzare la webcam del PC e relativo microfono, con un programma adatto per registrare tutto quello che viene ripreso dalla piccola telecamera del computer, sia esso un fisso o un notebook.

...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This $15 Million Mansion Gets You The Coolest 'Stars Wars' Home Theater]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/121954/this-15-million-mansion-gets-you-the-coolest-stars-wars-home-theater/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/121954/this-15-million-mansion-gets-you-the-coolest-stars-wars-home-theater/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-04T16:34:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While movie theaters and Disney’s Star Wars Galactic Starcruiser Hotel can be fun, when you have millions of dollars burning a hole in your pocket, you might as well combine the two and make your own. Right? Right!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Google Password Manager on Android]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=814300</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/814300/how-to-use-google-password-manager-on-android/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-04T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A password manager is a great thing to use if you want to keep your passwords secure and easy to remember. Google’s Password Manager built-in to Chrome is a popular option and it works on Android too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacker claims to have stolen data on 1 billion Chinese citizens]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hacker-claims-to-have-stolen-data-on-1-billion-chinese-citizens/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hacker-claims-to-have-stolen-data-on-1-billion-chinese-citizens/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-04T15:29:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An anonymous threat actor is selling several databases they claim to contain more than 22 terabytes of stolen information on roughly 1 billion Chinese citizens for 10 bitcoins (approximately $195,000). [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Resize and Optimize Images From the Linux Terminal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=151213</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/3270449/convert-images-linux-command-line"/>
        <updated>2022-07-04T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are a Linux user and prefer the Terminal to any other graphical applications, then you will be happy to know that you can also resize, convert, and optimize your images directly in the Terminal with ImageMagick. ImageMagick is a suite of tools for Linux which allows you to manipulate images from the command line. It’s also the image processor behind many graphics-related applications. Here we will show you how to resize your images from the Terminal.
   

Content

Installing ImageMagick
View the Image Information
Resizing Images
Change the image format 
Reduce Image Quality
Rotate Images
Create GIF file
Add Watermark to Images
Remove Exif Data From Image

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Batch Resize Images with XnConvert
    
Installing ImageMagick
    
Before we start, we need to first install ImageMagick on our system.
    
On Ubuntu or any Debian-based distro:
  ... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Prateek Jangid</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch Linux and other systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vr9ehh/arch_linux_and_other_systems/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vr9ehh/arch_linux_and_other_systems/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-04T15:03:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello people.
 I have on my PC several partitions on which I usually install other test distributions while keeping one as the main one.
 I have been running Arch Linux Plasma KDE as my main system for a while now without any problems, with several updates a week.
 I also have to say that the installation was very basic, with hardly any programs, so the updates are not very big.
 The thing is that if I install on another partition, for example, openSUSE Tumbleweed, in grub I get the option to go to both Tumbleweed and Arch.
 I can also access Arch files and folders from Dolphin in Tumbleweed Plasma KDE.
 However, from Arch I cannot access Tumbleweed files.
 I see the partition from Dolphin, and I can enter it with its folders and files, but when I enter /home, it is empty, it has nothing.
 Likewise, if I update the grub to Arch, the Tumbleweed option does not appear, even though I see it in Dolphin, as I said.
 Unchecking OS-PROBER doesn't seem to work either.
 It seems clear that Tumbleweed does something for me that Arch doesn't when it comes to recognizing other systems, but I don't know what it could be.
 I currently have Tumbleweed's grub active, as it allows me to switch between the two systems, but I would like to be able to use Arch's grub without problems.
 Any idea what should I add or change in Arch to make it recognize other systems without problems?
 Thank you very much. Regards, Juan.
    submitted by    /u/jbellas  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Lock Your MacBook Keys for Cleaning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=814038</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/814038/how-to-lock-your-macbook-keys-for-cleaning/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-04T15:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Laptops pick up dust, grease, and grime since they’re constantly in contact with your hands. But due to the way modern MacBooks are designed, cleaning them isn’t a simple case of turning the machine off.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Miglior processore AMD del momento]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/07/miglior-processore-amd-del-momento.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/07/miglior-processore-amd-del-momento.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-04T14:51:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I processori AMD vengono considerati da molti utenti solo come l'alternativa economica ai processori Intel, da sceglire solo quando vogliamo risparmiare. Questa considerazione è sbagliata, visto che da anni i processori AMD hanno dimostrato di essere potenti in maniera eguale (o addirittura anche superiore) alle controparti Intel, fornendo dei processori molto potenti nel multitasking, con un...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[Arch] Bluetooth packages, which one(s) are you running?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vr8y2i/arch_bluetooth_packages_which_ones_are_you_running/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vr8y2i/arch_bluetooth_packages_which_ones_are_you_running/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-04T14:42:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm having major issues on both of my machines to get bluetooth working properly. As soon as I get them working as intended the next updates breaks it entirely...
 Are there any kind souls that could tell me what packages or combination of packages that seem to work best for them?
 Thanks in advance
    submitted by    /u/RipeWaow  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open links in the browser of your choice quickly with Velja for macOS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179521</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/07/04/velja-is-a-free-browser-switcher-app-for-macos/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-04T14:16:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you have multiple browsers installed on your computer, but want to open a link in a specific browser, what do you do? Well, you open the browser and paste a link […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Open links in the browser of your choice quickly with Velja for macOS appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>