<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-06-04T01:43:08.889Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apparmor with python-notify2 script]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v4dp85/apparmor_with_pythonnotify2_script/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v4dp85/apparmor_with_pythonnotify2_script/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-04T01:06:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey all,
 I have enable Apparmor and set the kernel parameters.
 Everything working well and apparmor has 50 profiles enforced, however I am setting the notifications on denied actions and not sure if it's working.
 To note I have completed the following:
 groupadd -r audit
 gpasswd -a (my username) audit
 Sudo nano /etc/audit/auditd.conf And added : log_group = audit
 Installed python-notify2 and python-psutil
 Created this:
 [Desktop Entry] Type=Application Name=AppArmor Notify Comment=Receive on screen notifications of AppArmor denials TryExec=aa-notify Exec=aa-notify -p -s 1 -w 60 -f /var/log/audit/audit.log StartupNotify=false NoDisplay=true
 However, I can't write the script to ~/.config/autostart/apparmor-notify.desktop because it does not exist.
 I have saved it to ~/.config/autostart-scripts/apparmor-notify.desktop instead.
 When I run: sudo pgrep -ax aa-notify nothing happens
 Is the directory "/.config/autostart-scripts/" wrong? I don't have just "autostart" and can't save the nano script if I list that directory.
 Any help appreciated
 UPDATE: I have the script now saved under autostart and autostart-scripts, but when running "Sudo pgrep -ax aa-notify" it still does nothing. So I can't confirm if it's working.
    submitted by    /u/AussieAn0n  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nginx package not including mime.types]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v4czhw/nginx_package_not_including_mimetypes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v4czhw/nginx_package_not_including_mimetypes/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-04T00:27:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello! Apologies if this doesn't belong here, but I'm just curious why /etc/nginx/mime.types is not included with the Nginx package in archlinux? Is it suggested that everyone who installs this package writes their own?
    submitted by    /u/ElTortugo  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is the Headphones Driver and How Does It Affect Audio Quality?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=post-ideas&amp;p=263651</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/9649697/what-is-earphones-driver"/>
        <updated>2022-06-04T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re on the hunt for quality headphones, you’ll be surprised at the many different brands and styles available on the market today. This may make it harder for you to choose the right ones. Headphones specs are complex and very technical and can easily get you confused if you’re looking just at them. In this post we cut through the jargon to shed more light on one of the common headphone components, the headphones driver, and how it affects audio quality.
   

Content

Understanding Headphones Driver
The Impact of Driver Size on the Audio Quality
Does Having Multiple Drivers Equate With Better Sound Quality?
Different Types of Headphones Driver Units Explained
1. Dynamic (Moving Coil) Drivers
2. Planar Magnetic Drivers
3. Balanced Armature Drivers
4. Electrostatic Drivers
5. Piezoelectric Drivers
6. Bone Conduction Drivers
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:AirPods Alternatives: 6... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexandra Arici</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Help me to find a minimal terminal that supports full transparency]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v4cdk8/help_me_to_find_a_minimal_terminal_that_supports/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v4cdk8/help_me_to_find_a_minimal_terminal_that_supports/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T23:53:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello ! I know this community doesn't get much of questions like this, but I need some help to find a terminal emulator that supports full transparency. I have a KDE setup and I use a cli music visualizer called CAVA. I usually put it in background, change Konsole profile and set transparency to 100% but as soon as I open another terminal, the one with transparency gets blurred. So I think the only solution to this is to use another terminal that I would only use for this purpose.
 Thanks in advance.
    submitted by    /u/1_7xr  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LoongArch CPU Support Merged For Linux 5.19 - But It Won't Work For A Booting System Yet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=LoongArch-Merged-Linux-5.19</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=LoongArch-Merged-Linux-5.19"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T23:27:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following a mad dash this week to get the LoongArch CPU architecture support readied for Linux 5.19, Linus Torvalds successfully merged this MIPS64-inspired Chinese architecture code today into the mainline kernel. However, due to some of the code not yet passing review, while the CPU architecture code is in place some crucial drivers have yet to land and thus Linux 5.19 cannot boot on said hardware...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finished installation on Virtualbox, rebooted and it went back to the original pre-installation state]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v4ao0p/finished_installation_on_virtualbox_rebooted_and/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v4ao0p/finished_installation_on_virtualbox_rebooted_and/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T22:24:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What I did
  
Set up the virtual machine
 
Booted the machine and ran archinstall
 
Did all the settings and entered install
 
After the installation finished, i selected no chroot and rebooted the machine on the console, not on VM settings
 
After reboot, it seems nothing occured, it just goes back to the point 2., no matter which settings I choose
 
 Sorry for the maybe obvious question and thanks in advance!
    submitted by    /u/Casparov2804  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to get a stable Arch install]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v4ajkf/how_to_get_a_stable_arch_install/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v4ajkf/how_to_get_a_stable_arch_install/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T22:18:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I really like arch and I installed it a few times(and a lot on VM), but what I want is a guide to help me get a stable good system, like a list of things I should probably want to install on a DIY distro like Arch, like: Compositor: Picom, etc Window Manager: AwesomeWM, bspwm, xmonad, etc Notifications: dunstify DEs: Gnome, KDE, xfce, etc There's some things that a beginner like me forgets to install, as I'm used to not installing everything on my OS.
    submitted by    /u/ZacS2  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Questa settimana su TLI (04 giugno 2022)]]></title>
        <id>3595|20220604000001</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/newsletter-turbolab.it-1349/questa-settimana-tli-04-giugno-2022-3595"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T22:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Non hai tempo di leggerci tutti i giorni? nessun problema! ecco a te il riepilogo di quanto proposto da TurboLab.it nel corso della settimana in conclusione.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use WhatsApp on Chromebook]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=473007</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15349007/use-whatsapp-on-chromebook"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chromebooks do not have a dedicated WhatsApp app like on Windows or macOS. However, that doesn’t mean you cannot use WhatsApp on Chrome OS. You can install WhatsApp from Play Store or use the web version on your Chromebook. Let’s check both methods to use WhatsApp on Chromebook.  
   

Content

1. Use WhatsApp on Chromebook Without Phone
2. Use WhatsApp on Chromebook and Phone at the Same Time
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Secure Your Chromebook
    
1. Use WhatsApp on Chromebook Without Phone
    
Many Chromebooks support Google Play Store and if your device is one of them, you can install and use WhatsApp directly from the Play Store on your Chromebook. This method lets you use WhatsApp without being connected to your phone.
    
Please note if you are already using WhatsApp on your phone, this method will deactivate your WhatsApp... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mehvish Mushtaq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Enable Hardware-Accelerated GPU Scheduling in Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=756935</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/756935/how-to-enable-hardware-accelerated-gpu-scheduling-in-windows-11/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 comes with an advanced setting, called hardware-accelerated GPU scheduling, which can boost gaming and video performance using your PC’s GPU. We’ll show you how to enable the feature and thereby potentially get a performance increase.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samir Makwana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Week in Ransomware - June 3rd 2022 - Evading sanctions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/the-week-in-ransomware-june-3rd-2022-evading-sanctions/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/the-week-in-ransomware-june-3rd-2022-evading-sanctions/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T20:41:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ransomware gangs continue to evolve their operations as victims refuse to pay ransoms due to sanctions or other reasons. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MP3 Players]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v483oi/mp3_players/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v483oi/mp3_players/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T20:21:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Does anyone have any recommendations when it comes to working with MP3 players ?
 I do longer run sessions outside and listen to music / podcasts in mp3 file format. 
 Would like to mount a device and simply upload mp3 files to the device and play it.
 Any info would be greatly appreciated.
 Thank you
    submitted by    /u/_polymatrix  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5.18 enabled VRR/Freesync- but how?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v47xmn/518_enabled_vrrfreesync_but_how/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v47xmn/518_enabled_vrrfreesync_but_how/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T20:13:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the biggest things in the changelogs for me is that VRR/Freesync/Adaptive Refresh Rate is now enabled straight from the kernel.
 It quotes:
  
While the support for FreeSync video was good enough, it was a temporary solution to improve the user experience with FreeSync monitors. 
 ILinux Kernel 5.18, the FreeSync video mode is enabled by default (changelog). You do not have to do anything from your side to enable it with supported monitors.
  
Before this, VRR was acquirable on all DEs with a display port and a config file on xorg, and it is enabled out the box on Plasma Wayland and Sway Wayland. Gnome Wayland despite this still doesn't support VRR.
 How do these changes to the 5.18 kernel affect the way that VRR is normally enabled currently on DEs? What method does it enable it from the kernel? Do they interact with eachother? I was hoping to see Freesync on Gnome Wayland with 5.18 but those hopes were too high.
    submitted by    /u/slycoopr3  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Fi Takes a Page From Comcast Xfinity With “W+”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809236</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809236/google-fi-takes-a-page-from-comcast-xfinity-with-w/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T20:12:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Fi is a wireless network operated by Google that originally focused on low data usage, but recently expanded into unlimited plans. Now the carrier has a new “W+” feature to help expand network coverage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Finally Pay for a Driverless Taxi Ride from GM's Cruise]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120025/you-can-finally-pay-for-a-driverless-taxi-ride-from-gms-cruise/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120025/you-can-finally-pay-for-a-driverless-taxi-ride-from-gms-cruise/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T20:05:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The self-driving company Cruise has worked tirelessly to bring its autonomous taxi service to the public, and now it’s finally happening. This week, Cruise received a permit from the California Public Utilities Commission (CPUC) and can charge actual customers for driverless ridesharing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make Your Facebook Post Shareable]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=754269</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/754269/how-to-make-your-facebook-post-shareable/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever made a Facebook post hoping it would your friends and followers would share it, only to find out they don’t even see a share button? That can happen if you don’t set the correct audience on a post.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open Letter Asks Intel To Open-Source The FSP, Google Engineer Details Interesting Plan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Open-Letter-Intel-FSP</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Open-Letter-Intel-FSP"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An open letter started by the Open-Source Firmware Foundation and seeking community support for this letter is calling on Intel to open-source their Firmware Support Package (FSP). The FSP binary blob has been a big limitation to the level of openness around firmware for Intel systems and has been a limiting factor in supporting the likes of Coreboot, LinuxBoot, and other technologies on Intel hardware...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trevor Project’s Kevin Wong Shares What’s In His Corner of the Internet]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.mozilla.org/?p=69069</id>
        <link href="https://blog.mozilla.org/en/internet-culture/pride-month/trevor-projects-kevin-wong-shares-whats-in-his-corner-of-the-internet/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T19:55:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here at Mozilla, we are the first to admit the internet isn’t perfect, but we are also quick to point out that the internet is pretty darn magical. The internet opens up doors and opportunities, allows for people to connect with others, and lets everyone find where they belong — their corners of the internet. […]
The post Trevor Project’s Kevin Wong Shares What’s In His Corner of the Internet appeared first on The Mozilla Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Damiano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Novartis says no sensitive data was compromised in cyberattack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/novartis-says-no-sensitive-data-was-compromised-in-cyberattack/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/novartis-says-no-sensitive-data-was-compromised-in-cyberattack/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T19:30:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pharmaceutical giant Novartis says no sensitive data was compromised in a recent cyberattack by the Industrial Spy data-extortion gang. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is a Vertical Mouse Better For Your Wrist?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120000/is-a-vertical-mouse-better-for-your-wrist/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120000/is-a-vertical-mouse-better-for-your-wrist/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T19:27:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ergonomic mice have a bad reputation, mainly because trackballs and other ergonomic options look ridiculous and come with a steep learning curve. But vertical mice promise to deliver ergonomics and prevent wrist injury without throwing you out of your comfort zone. And yeah, this claim is mostly true.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get a eufy Security Solo IndoorCam C24 for Under $30]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=494900</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15348913/eufy-security-solo-indoorcam-c24"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s always at least one place in your home where a security camera would come in handy: nursery, front door, your pet’s favorite spot, etc. With the eufy Security Solo IndoorCam C24 currently offered for under $30, you could probably stick one up in every one of those spots.
    
The artificial intelligence in the camera can determine whether it sees a human or pet and will only record at the time of an event. Each event is recorded in 2K clarity or 1080P if using HomeKit. Advanced night vision will allow you to still keep an eye on what’s going on, even in low-light settings.
    

    
You’ll be able to hear every detail from the location of the camera so that you can hear if your baby is crying and needs you or whether the dog is barking to go outside. You can also speak through the camera via built-in two-way audio to calm your baby, tell your dog he’s a good boy, let your kids know dinner is ready, etc. Connect... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Start or Join a Google Meet From Docs, Sheets, or Slides]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=806298</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/806298/start-or-join-google-meet-from-docs-sheets-slides/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T19:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wanted to start a quick video meeting while reviewing a document? You can start or join a Google Meet directly from Google Docs, Sheets, or Slides. Then, present your document or simply join and keep working.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD Kernel Driver Enabling Peer-To-Peer Multi-GPU Compute For Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMD-Multi-GPU-Compute-P2P</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMD-Multi-GPU-Compute-P2P"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T18:36:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new patch series posted today by AMD is enabling peer-to-peer support within their AMDKFD kernel compute driver for allowing communication between multiple AMD GPUs over the PCIe bus without needing intermediate copies through system memory. In turn this should help with the multi-GPU compute performance for the Radeon ROCm stack...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Installing Arch Linux on VMware vSphere 7.0 using Packer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v45twi/installing_arch_linux_on_vmware_vsphere_70_using/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v45twi/installing_arch_linux_on_vmware_vsphere_70_using/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T18:34:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have a Packer configuration that connects to my VMware vCenter 7.0 host, creates a virtual machine, partitions the disks, installs Arch Linux using the Live CD, configures GRUB to use EFI, and reboots. Whenever the Packer reboots the virtual machine, it just boots up using the Live CD, not the installed version of Arch Linux.
 After some investigation, it turns out that the boot order for the UEFI always has the CDROM before the boot partition. If I manually select the boot partition, the newly installed Arch Linux boots up without issues. 
 So I updated the install script to use efibootmgr to change the boot order. It's updated from the looks of things, but the CDROM still boots. Even when I use it to delete boot entries, it continues to kick the Live CD. When I change the EFI boot order manually in the vSphere client or disable entries, it will boot the installed Arch Linux. 
 When I manually eject the CDROM after the reboot, then reboot it again, it will boot into Arch Linux. 
 This leaves me with two questions: 
  
Has anyone successfully installed Arch Linux on VMware vSphere in an unattended fashion?
 What's the best way to instruct Arch Linux to eject removable media before reboots?
  
A note about (2): I can't eject the disk after installation since the Live CD is still in use.
    submitted by    /u/bloudraak  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox Can Now Translate Pages Without Sacrificing Privacy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809203</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809203/firefox-can-now-translate-pages-without-sacrificing-privacy/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T18:09:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some web browsers (like Chrome and Edge) can translate web pages, but the feature always requires external services like Google Translate or Bing Translate. Now Firefox can translate pages on your computer without telling Google, Microsoft, or any other translation company what you’re looking at.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the scp Command on Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=804179</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/804179/scp-command-linux/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T18:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The scp command makes copying files between Linux computers easy and secure. It uses SSH security, but best of all, it is simple. If you can use cp, you can use scp.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKay</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WatchDog hacking group launches new Docker cryptojacking campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/watchdog-hacking-group-launches-new-docker-cryptojacking-campaign/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/watchdog-hacking-group-launches-new-docker-cryptojacking-campaign/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T17:50:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[​The WatchDog hacking group is conducting a new cryptojacking campaign with advanced techniques for intrusion, worm-like propagation, and evasion of security software. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Atlassian fixes Confluence zero-day widely exploited in attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/atlassian-fixes-confluence-zero-day-widely-exploited-in-attacks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/atlassian-fixes-confluence-zero-day-widely-exploited-in-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T17:47:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Atlassian has released security updates to address a critical zero-day vulnerability in Confluence Server and Data Center actively exploited in the wild to backdoor Internet-exposed servers. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux 5.19 Adding Support For The PolarBerry RISC-V FPGA Board]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-PolarBerry-RISC-V</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-PolarBerry-RISC-V"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T17:43:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few days ago the RISC-V pull request landed in Linux 5.19 with support for RISC-V 32-bit (RV32) binaries on RV64, enabling the new Svpbmt extension, and other improvements. On Friday a secondary set of RISC-V changes were sent in for Linux 5.19 that includes adding the DeviceTree files for another new RISC-V board...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla Announces Humanoid Robot and Layoffs, Coincidence?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120001/tesla-announces-humanoid-robot-and-layoffs-coincidence/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120001/tesla-announces-humanoid-robot-and-layoffs-coincidence/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T17:30:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk has called on Tesla execs to freeze hiring worldwide and cut about 10% of the staff, according to Reuters. Then, coincidentally, Elon Musk tweeted that he may have a working prototype of Tesla’s previously announced humanoid robot. Coincidence, or just smoke and mirrors?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Americans report losing over $1 billion to cryptocurrency scams]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/americans-report-losing-over-1-billion-to-cryptocurrency-scams/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/americans-report-losing-over-1-billion-to-cryptocurrency-scams/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T17:24:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Federal Trade Commission (FTC) says over 46,000 people Americans have reported losing more than $1 billion worth of cryptocurrency to scams between January 2021 and March 2022. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Games runing through xwayland capped at 60fps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v448ae/games_runing_through_xwayland_capped_at_60fps/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v448ae/games_runing_through_xwayland_capped_at_60fps/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T17:18:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Games such as Minecraft and those running through wine are capped at 60fps (my screen refresh rate). Frames are not capped in an Xorg session.
 How can fix this?
 My previous post on arch forums for more details.
    submitted by    /u/abrattic  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Redshift turing on and off]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v4400c/redshift_turing_on_and_off/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v4400c/redshift_turing_on_and_off/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T17:06:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[​
 When I start Redshift, It will work for few seconds then turn off the filtering and then again it will start it again.
 I run the program from the terminal and there is no sign problem, Seems like the program is working correctly.
 ​
 ─❯ redshift -v Solar elevations: day above 3.0, night below -6.0 Temperatures: 5700K at day, 3500K at night Brightness: 1.00:1.00 Gamma (Daytime): 0.800, 0.800, 0.800 Gamma (Night): 0.800, 0.800, 0.800 Waiting for initial location to become available... Location: 0.00 N, 0.00 E Color temperature: 6500K Brightness: 1.00 Status: Enabled Period: Daytime Color temperature: 5700K 
 I would appreciate any help or suggestion
    submitted by    /u/Eyuman21  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Fiat Currency?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=806279</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/806279/what-is-fiat-currency/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T17:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Currencies with no other commodity backing them are known as fiat currency. The euro, pound, yen, and other major currencies are all considered fiat currencies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>RJ Fulton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[T-Mobile Starts Rolling Out 5G-Powered Phone Calls]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809176</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809176/t-mobile-starts-rolling-out-5g-powered-phone-calls/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T16:56:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re firmly in the 5G era now, but most phones still have to switch back to 4G or LTE to make calls. That’s now changing, as T-Mobile has started rolling out ‘Voice over 5G’ on select phones.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Fi Now Gives You Speedy Wi-Fi Access Outside Your Home]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119995/google-fi-now-gives-you-speedy-wifi-access-outside-your-home/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119995/google-fi-now-gives-you-speedy-wifi-access-outside-your-home/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T16:35:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in 2020, Google’s in-house incubator—Area 120—launched an experimental Wi-Fi platform called Orion Wi-Fi that gave locales a way to sell Wi-Fi capacity to carriers. Now the company is expanding Google Fi coverage using that tech, and calling it the “W+ network.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzanne Humphries</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Error while installing KDE Plasma.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v42rl2/error_while_installing_kde_plasma/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v42rl2/error_while_installing_kde_plasma/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T16:09:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I try to pacman KDE and other stuff it says failed retrieving file xkeyboard-config. Please help. Thanks in advance
    submitted by    /u/frOSystem  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung's Galaxy Watch 5 Could Leave Behind a Fan-Favorite Design]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119992/samsungs-galaxy-watch-5-could-leave-behind-a-fan-favorite-design/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119992/samsungs-galaxy-watch-5-could-leave-behind-a-fan-favorite-design/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T16:07:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re about halfway through 2022, which means that the Samsung Galaxy Watch 5 should launch soon. Naturally, tons of leaks and rumors are floating around, and much of this unverified info focuses on potential design changes—including one that may ruffle a few feathers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Steam not seeing my other drive]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v42lk6/steam_not_seeing_my_other_drive/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v42lk6/steam_not_seeing_my_other_drive/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T16:01:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone!
 I have a bit of an odd storage layout, and I want steam to detect my 500 gb ssd.
 I have a 250GB SSD split up to a few partitions as my system drive and I mounted my other drive under /storage/ssd.
 What should I change so steam can see it?
 Thanks in advance!
 EDIT: I wasn't the owner of /storage, solved
    submitted by    /u/balika0105  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Turn On/Off Silent Mode Without the Switch on iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=806011</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/806011/how-to-turn-on-off-silent-mode-without-the-switch-on-iphone/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T16:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The original iPhone featured a physical Ring/Silent switch on the left side and it has carried over to every iPhone since. This is the only way to switch between ring mode and silent mode—or is it?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Premium Special To Celebrate Phoronix's 18th Birthday]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Phoronix-18-Birthday-Special</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Phoronix-18-Birthday-Special"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This Sunday, 5 June, marks the 18th birthday for Phoronix.com since I started this website to focus on Linux hardware reviews and performance testing. To mark the occasion, there will be a Phoronix Premium special if you wish to go ad-free on the site and enjoy multi-page articles on a single page while helping to hopefully ensure a successful 19th year for Phoronix...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fibra misto rame: sempre attuale per tanti italiani]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Fibra-misto-rame-sempre-attuale-per-tanti-italiani_24600</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Fibra-misto-rame-sempre-attuale-per-tanti-italiani_24600"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T15:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FTTH (Fiber-to-the-Home) è la 'vera fibra' perché il cavo in fibra ottica arriva fino al router dell'utente finale e non si ferma, ad esempio, all'armadio stradale.Abbiamo visto le differenze tra FTTx e in che misura le connessioni FTTH possono offrire prestazioni nettamente migliori grazie all'assenza del problema della diafonia e all'attenuazione praticamente irrilevante rispetto al rame.Basti pensare che l'attenuazione di segnale che si rileva su un collegamento in rame alla distanza di 2-3 chilometri è la stessa che si può misurare su un collegamento in fibra lungo ben 150 chilometri o più.Con il termine fibra misto rame si fa riferimento a uno schema di collegamento che tipicamente utilizza la fibra ottica fino all'armadio stradale. A partire dall'armadio stradale fino all'utenza dell'abbonato (rete secondaria) il collegamento prosegue con il tradizionale doppino telefonico in rame.Nel caso delle connessioni fibra misto rame FTTC (Fiber-to-the-Cabinet) il cavo fibra arriva fino all'armadio in strada ('cabinet') mentre nello schema FTTE (Fiber-to-the-Exchange) la tratta in rame è ancora più lunga.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come utilizzare Windows 10 su PC con Windows 11 (e viceversa)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/06/come-utilizzare-windows-10-su-pc-con.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/06/come-utilizzare-windows-10-su-pc-con.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T15:47:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chi lavora molto con Windows e con i programmi compatibili sa quando sia importante avere sempre a portata di mano una macchina virtuale dove poter fare i test e gli esperimenti senza dover sporcare o danneggiare il sistema su cui lavoriamo. Chi ha installato Windows 11 Pro sul proprio computer può, senza dover scaricare altri programmi, creare una macchina virtuale del precedente sistema...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mercedes Latest EQB EV Arrives With an Affordable Price Tag]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119989/mercedes-latest-eqb-ev-arrives-with-an-affordable-price-tag/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119989/mercedes-latest-eqb-ev-arrives-with-an-affordable-price-tag/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T15:45:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year, Mercedes-Benz unveiled the EQB, a three-row electric crossover SUV similar to its popular gas-powered GLB. And while it’s not quite as luxurious as the new EQS, it’s still a Mercedes, and now we have full pricing ahead of its release this summer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Copy and Paste Text, Files and Folders in Linux Terminal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=post-ideas&amp;p=305454</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/12267309/copy-paste-files-linux-command-line"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Copying and pasting is one of the most used actions on a computer. While it is easy to do so with the Ctrl + C and Ctrl + V keyboard shortcuts, on the Linux terminal it is not so straightforward. You have several options to get the job done. Here is how you can copy and paste text, files and directories in Linux terminal.
   

Content

Copy and Paste Text
Copy and Paste a Single File
Copy and Paste a Folder and Its Contents
Copy and Paste Multiple Files
Copy and Paste All Files of the Same Type
Make Copying More Interactive
Rsync vs CP
Move a File or Folder
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Delete a Directory in Linux
    
Copy and Paste Text
    
If you just want to copy a piece of text in the terminal, all you need to do... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miguel Leiva-Gomez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is there a good way to record the reason for installing a package with pacman? (Like a commit message)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v41sri/is_there_a_good_way_to_record_the_reason_for/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v41sri/is_there_a_good_way_to_record_the_reason_for/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T15:24:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For example, when you try to install A(it doesnt exist. its example pacakge name) from github, you will often find installation instructions in the document.
 Suppose that the installation procedure says something like the following
 pacman -S A B C
 Now back to the question.
 In such a case, I don't think I would know why I installed B and C.
 I am now realizing the detrimental effects of having used pacman for almost 5 years without a solid understanding of it.
    submitted by    /u/ilove-archlinux  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft disrupts Bohrium hackers’ spear-phishing operation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-disrupts-bohrium-hackers-spear-phishing-operation/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-disrupts-bohrium-hackers-spear-phishing-operation/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T15:24:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Microsoft Digital Crimes Unit (DCU) has disrupted a spear-phishing operation linked to an Iranian threat actor tracked as Bohrium that targeted customers in the U.S., Middle East, and India. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Watch iFixit Tear Down Apple's Official Repair Tools In a New Video]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119979/watch-ifixit-tear-down-apples-official-repair-tools-in-a-new-video/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119979/watch-ifixit-tear-down-apples-official-repair-tools-in-a-new-video/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T15:22:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While Apple’s Self Service Repair program is far from practical, the tools that are rented out through this program are pretty interesting. They’re huge and expensive, but they accomplish simple tasks that really don’t require special equipment. So, iFixit spent a few thousand dollars to buy and tear down Apple’s Self Service Repair tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the ARRAYFORMULA Function in Google Sheets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=805792</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/805792/arrayformula-google-sheets/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T15:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How many times have you created a formula and copied it to the adjacent cells in your sheet? In Google Sheets, you can skip this step by using the ARRAYFORMULA function.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch Linux Python not showing output]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v41433/arch_linux_python_not_showing_output/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v41433/arch_linux_python_not_showing_output/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T14:51:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi all, I recently got arch linux set up and am trying to teach myself some Python to use with qtile
 I've had a little bit of experience with Python, but I wanted to start fresh using a book I found at the library, and I'm already seeing issues somehow.
 when running a "hello world" script, I get no output, it just goes to the next line-
 print( 'Hello World' )
 ​
 typing this same command into the python interpreter yields the "Hello World" we all know and love, but running it by using these commands shows nothing on screen
 python2 helloworld.py
 python3 helloworld.py
 ​
 I thought maybe it was my terminal alacritty, but I also installed kitty and the same thing happened there. I was thinking about asking the Python community directly but I wasn't sure if this is an issue with my arch install or python itself. I even tried running as root and it also did not work. I have python 3.10 and 2.7 installed.
 ​
 Thanks in advance for the help, and let me know if I should check with the Python community instead!
    submitted by    /u/c4sc4deb4dge  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HP and System76 Teamed Up to Build a Powerful Linux Laptop]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809033</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809033/hp-and-system76-teamed-up-to-build-a-powerful-linux-laptop/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T14:37:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[System76 has been selling some of the best Linux laptops for years, but now the company is teaming up with HP to sell the ‘HP Dev One’ — a laptop built for developers with System76’s custom flavor of Linux.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Store: migliora il meccanismo di aggiornamento delle app]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Microsoft-Store-migliora-il-meccanismo-di-aggiornamento-delle-app_24599</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Microsoft-Store-migliora-il-meccanismo-di-aggiornamento-delle-app_24599"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T14:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[L'estate scorsa Microsoft ha corretto l'errore ammesso dagli stessi vertici dell'azienda: sbagliata la decisione passata di limitare la possibilità di pubblicare nel Microsoft Store soltanto le applicazioni UWP. Tra l'altro le stesse app UWP sono state ufficialmente accantonate per guardare a Windows App SDK (Project Reunion), kit di sviluppo che torna a strizzare l'occhio agli storici programmi Win32.Così, come abbiamo visto, Microsoft Store è diventato uno strumento pronto ad accogliere anche applicazioni Win32, .NET, Xamarin, Electron, React Native, Java e Progressive Web Apps (PWA), sia in Windows 10 che in Windows 11.Insieme all'arrivo delle applicazioni Win32, nel corso dell'ultimo anno la società di Redmond ha posto in campo diverse novità per rendere il Microsoft Store più attraente sia per gli utenti che per gli sviluppatori.Nel negozio online sono già stati inseriti browser come Firefox e Opera GX, CCleaner e Audacity.Presto Microsoft renderà molto più semplice reinstallare le applicazioni scaricate attraverso lo store, cosa che può essere davvero pratica quando si reinstalla Windows o si passa a un nuovo PC.Il Microsoft Store sarà anche in grado di riconoscere le applicazioni correntemente in esecuzione rimandando il loro aggiornamento a un secondo momento.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Gaming Monitors of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=746224</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/746224/best-gaming-monitors/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is no one-size-fits-all gaming monitor. Some people look for the highest refresh rates for an edge in competitive gaming, others want to bask in high-fidelity visuals. Let’s break down the best monitors for every gamer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitLab security update fixes critical account take over flaw]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/gitlab-security-update-fixes-critical-account-take-over-flaw/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/gitlab-security-update-fixes-critical-account-take-over-flaw/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T13:55:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitLab has released a critical security update for multiple versions of its Community and Enterprise Edition products to address eight vulnerabilities, one of which allows account takeover. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zstd Compressed Firmware Submitted For Linux 5.19, Other Driver Core Changes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-Zstd-Firmware</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-Zstd-Firmware"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T13:50:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Kroah-Hartman has gotten onto submitting his feature pull requests to Linux 5.19 for various areas of the kernel he oversees. With the driver core changes with this new kernel is now the ability to compress firmware files using the popular Zstd...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come proteggersi dalla cyberguerra ed evitare attacchi informatici]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/06/come-proteggersi-dalla-cyberguerra-ed.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/06/come-proteggersi-dalla-cyberguerra-ed.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T13:50:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sentiamo sempre più spesso parlare di cyberwar (o di guerra informatica) come la guerra del futuro; in questa guerra di nuova generazione i proiettili sono i bit che passano tra un computer e l'altro e tra una rete e l'altra, con le due fazioni in guerra che cercano di indebolire l'avversario con attacchi informatici mirati o con strumenti di spionaggio così avanzati da poter spiare qualsiasi...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch 2022.06.01 iso Gnome Install Screen Tearing archinstall]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3zsnm/arch_20220601_iso_gnome_install_screen_tearing/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3zsnm/arch_20220601_iso_gnome_install_screen_tearing/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T13:47:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I usually download the monthly iso releases and share via torrent.
 I also boot them in virt-manager and do an install using archinstall, just to see how things are going.
 This month the install of my desktop of choice (gnome) presented an issue that I have not seen before. After install and login there is severe video tearing. It is somewhat better when using xorg session vs wayland session. I have not seen this before and could not see why it should be an archinstall issue. I reran an install of the 2022.05.01 iso without any issues.
 In the interest of science and not spending too much time, I fired up the new iso and did an install of gnome with another (ahem) unofficial install script. I noticed the same issue. I may try to do a wiki install when I have time, but I found this curious and I was wondering if anyone else has seen this yet?
    submitted by    /u/3grg  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Meet e Duo diventano un'unica applicazione]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Google-Meet-e-Duo-diventano-un-unica-applicazione_24598</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Google-Meet-e-Duo-diventano-un-unica-applicazione_24598"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google si accinge a un'altra novità nel settore delle app per la messaggistica e le videochiamate.A suo tempo avevamo parlato dell'abbandono di Hangouts per guardare a soluzioni come Google Meet e Chat in ambito professionale, Duo per gli utenti privati.Già nel 2019, nello spiegare come si può organizzare una videoconferenza con i servizi Google, avevamo chiarito qual è la visione dell'azienda di Mountain View.Google Duo è l'app per le videochiamate utilizzabile in ambito consumer, non solo dai dispositivi Android e iOS ma anche da browser web.Google ha annunciato che l'azienda si prepara a unire Meet e Duo creando un'unica soluzione per le videochiamate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Somebody know what the hold-up with svt-av1 (extra) is?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3yxum/somebody_know_what_the_holdup_with_svtav1_extra_is/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3yxum/somebody_know_what_the_holdup_with_svtav1_extra_is/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T13:03:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://archlinux.org/packages/extra/x86_64/svt-av1/
 https://gitlab.com/AOMediaCodec/SVT-AV1/-/releases
  
Not complaining, just curious for the reason.
    submitted by    /u/Schlaefer  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lenovo Yoga 9i Laptop Review: The Best 2-in-1 Companion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/116641/lenovo-yoga-9i-laptop-review-the-best-2-in-1-companion/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/116641/lenovo-yoga-9i-laptop-review-the-best-2-in-1-companion/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T13:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lenovo makes some of the best laptops, so my expectations were pretty high with the latest Yoga 9i model. I’m ecstatic to say that this laptop exceeded those expectations so much that I’m tempted to replace my current laptop with this model.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Chaney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Movies on Netflix in 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=732712</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/732712/best-movies-on-netflix/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix is packed with so many movies, from studio releases to the service’s original productions, that it can be daunting to figure out what to watch. Get started with 10 of the best movies you can stream on Netflix.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Bell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Opinion: I love the tab grouping feature of web browsers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178943</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/03/opinion-i-love-the-tab-grouping-feature-of-web-browsers/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T12:52:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many desktop web browsers and some mobile browsers support the grouping of tabs. Implementations may differ depending on the browser and platform, but all have in common that they provide users with […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Opinion: I love the tab grouping feature of web browsers appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do You Need More Than One Graphics Card?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=797067</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/797067/do-you-need-more-than-one-graphics-card/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T12:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may be able to house two GPUs in your computer, but is it an option worth exploring? Can a single graphics card do enough, or is a dual setup necessary for high-end gaming and design work?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Georgie Peru</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SiFive RISC-V Sees Some Performance Improvements On Ubuntu 22.04]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31170</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31170"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T12:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While SiFive has sadly shutdown production on the current HiFive Unmatched development board in order to focus on new products expected later this year, those with a SiFive HiFive Unmatched RISC-V developer board can enjoy seeing continued performance improvements with newer Linux distributions. Here is a look at the SiFive FU740 SoC performance under the recently released Ubuntu 22.04 LTS compared to the prior 21.10 and 20.04 releases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenVPN download e installazione client Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=OpenVPN-download-e-installazione-client-Windows_24597</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=OpenVPN-download-e-installazione-client-Windows_24597"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T11:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ormai buona parte dei router più moderni, compresi quelli non espressamente rivolti a un'utenza professionale, offrono la possibilità di creare un server OpenVPN. Si tratta di uno strumento che consente di collegarsi a distanza con la rete locale dell'azienda, dell'ufficio o di casa: tutti i dati trasferiti da e verso la LAN saranno automaticamente crittografati rendendone impossibile il monitoraggio, la lettura, la modifica e la sottrazione da parte di soggetti terzi.Stabilire un collegamento OpenVPN a distanza con il proprio server permette di proteggere il contenuto dei pacchetti dati usando reti altrui (ad esempio WiFi pubbliche o aperte) e allo stesso tempo dà modo di collegarsi alle risorse condivise in rete locale come se il dispositivo in uso fosse attestato sulla LAN.Il router e il server NAS che permettono la configurazione di un server OpenVPN tipicamente consentono di specificare se il client collegato a distanza possa anche 'navigare' in rete usando l'indirizzo IP pubblico oppure se abbia soltanto la facoltà di accedere alle risorse locali.Cliccando sul pulsante o sul link che permette di esportare il file di configurazione OpenVPN si ottiene un file .ovpn utile per impostare qualunque client e consentirne la connessione remota.Il consiglio è quello di esportare il file .ovpn quindi di aprirlo con un editor di testo (come Notepad++) e verificare l'indirizzo IP riportato nella prima riga.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NTFS3 Kernel Driver Sees Fixes Sent In For Linux 5.19]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-NTFS3-Fixes</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-NTFS3-Fixes"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T11:37:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following the recent concerns around maintenance for the NTFS3 kernel driver and other developers stepping up to maintain the "NTFS3" kernel driver contributed by Paragon Software, there is now a batch of fixes ready to go for Linux 5.19...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How USB Drives Can Be a Danger to Your Computer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=797290</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/797290/how-usb-drives-can-be-a-danger-to-your-computer/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T11:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you find a random USB stick, perhaps at your school or in a parking lot? You may be tempted to plug it into your PC, but you could leave yourself open to attack or, worse still, permanently damage your machine. Here’s why.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cos'è una maschera di sottorete (Subnet Mask) e come trovarla?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/06/cose-una-maschera-di-sottorete-subnet.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/06/cose-una-maschera-di-sottorete-subnet.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T10:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tra i parametri fondamentali per la navigazione su Internet e per l'accesso alle reti LAN troviamo anche la maschera di sottorete (o subnet mask), un parametro spesso ignorato da tutti gli utenti che configurano manualmente l'indirizzo IP sul computer, utilizzando per il parametro in questione sempre 255.255.255.0. Ma perché utilizziamo proprio questo indirizzo per la maschera di sottorete? Cosa...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Axon Wants to Use Armed Drones to Stop School Shootings]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=494859</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15347837/axon-armed-drones-stop-school-shootings"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T10:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The news of yet another school shooting shook much of the U.S. and confused the rest of the world. Ideas to remedy the situation range from arming teachers to limiting access to guns. The CEO of Axon, the company behind Taser stun guns, has another idea. He wants to stop the shootings with armed drones.
   
Also read:ID.me and Facial Recognition Software Probed by Lawmakers
    
The Bold Idea of Using Armed Drones
    
This isn’t a new idea for Axon CEO Rick Smith. He has been considering armed drones for years, even publishing a novel about the idea. He’s now done with watching the senseless violence unfold.
    
Smith announced in a statement that Axon plans to develop “a remotely operated, non-lethal drone system that we believe will be a more effective, immediate, human, and ethical option to protect innocent people.”
    
Image... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenVPN: come recuperare le password in Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=OpenVPN-come-recuperare-le-password-in-Windows_24596</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=OpenVPN-come-recuperare-le-password-in-Windows_24596"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T10:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Uno degli strumenti più utilizzati per creare un server VPN è il protocollo OpenVPN. Insieme con WireGuard, la stella nascente in continua crescita, e lo storico IPSec, OpenVPN è uno dei protocolli più utilizzati in assoluto per connettersi a distanza con la rete locale della propria azienda, dell'ufficio o di casa.La connessione VPN avviene in totale sicurezza ed è possibile accedere da remoto alle risorse condivise come se il dispositivo in uso fosse fisicamente connesso alla LAN via WiFi o cavo Ethernet.In un altro articolo abbiamo visto quanto conta la scelta del protocollo sul funzionamento di una VPN.Il client OpenVPN per Windows mostra in fase di connessione una piccola finestra di dialogo che consente di specificare nome utente e password per l'effettuazione del collegamento. Spuntando la casella Ricorda la password, la password usata per la connessione al server VPN remoto viene memorizzata in locale in forma cifrata.

Se si fosse dimenticato la password associata a un profilo OpenVPN creato lato client, come si potrebbe fare per recuperarla?
Recuperare le password OpenVPN in forma cifrata
 Supponiamo di aver installato il client OpenVPN su un altro PC Windows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ubuntu 22.10 Looking At Replacing WPA With IWD For Linux Wireless]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Ubuntu-22.10-IWD-Wireless</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Ubuntu-22.10-IWD-Wireless"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T10:08:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adding to the list of planned changes for the Ubuntu 22.10 release this October is transitioning from WPA_Supplicant to Intel's IWD daemon for Linux wireless needs...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ghacks Deals: The 2022 Complete Learn Coding & Automation Bundle]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178940</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/03/ghacks-deals-the-2022-complete-learn-coding-automation-bundle/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T09:45:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2022 Complete Learn Coding & Automation Bundle includes 8 eLearning courses that teach you essential coding and automation skills. It includes beginner courses, like C++ for absolute beginners, but also courses […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Ghacks Deals: The 2022 Complete Learn Coding & Automation Bundle appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yay i have installed arch in 30 minutes fully working with all my apps and config]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3vkp9/yay_i_have_installed_arch_in_30_minutes_fully/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3vkp9/yay_i_have_installed_arch_in_30_minutes_fully/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T09:28:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I just wanted to say this here
    submitted by    /u/you_know_the_lines  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD Preparing To Finally  Support Virtual NMI With Their CPUs (VNMI)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMD-Virtual-NMI-VNMI</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMD-Virtual-NMI-VNMI"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T09:21:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It appears that with upcoming AMD Zen 4 processors there will finally be Virtual NMI (VNMI) support for virtualization, a feature Intel CPUs have supported for well more than the past decade...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[passing commands into gdisk?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3v08v/passing_commands_into_gdisk/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3v08v/passing_commands_into_gdisk/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T08:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[so I wanted to learn bash scripting by creating one to install multiple configurations of arch but I've run into a problem 
 I can't pass Enter key presses with this command:
 echo -en "n\n\n\n" | gdisk /dev/sda
 first 'n' is to add a new partition and the \n for enter keypresses 
 I might be doing this incorrectly as I've found by searching online that echo -en "\n" is for newline (on stackoverflow and other blog sites)
    submitted by    /u/GuildMasterJin  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[KDE/NetworkManager] Wired LAN can't get DHCP; WLAN works fine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3uxl3/kdenetworkmanager_wired_lan_cant_get_dhcp_wlan/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3uxl3/kdenetworkmanager_wired_lan_cant_get_dhcp_wlan/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T08:39:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[***EDIT: Turned out to be an OPNSense issue at the other end. Not related to Arch/NetworkManager at all.
  
I recently had QEMU and Virtualbox installed, but both have since been removed.
 
I've tried using dhcpcd instead of the NetworkManager built-in DHCP client, but this just broke DHCP on both interfaces.
 
Physical equipment tests fine, including cables, switches, etc.
  
Output of # journalctl -xeu NetworkManager:
 Jun 03 18:24:24 RYZEN NetworkManager[11248]: <warn> [1654244664.0016] device (eno1): Activation: failed for connection 'Home LAN' Jun 03 18:24:24 RYZEN NetworkManager[11248]: <info> [1654244664.0017] device (eno1): state change: failed -> disconnected (reason 'none', sys-iface-state: 'managed') Jun 03 18:24:24 RYZEN NetworkManager[11248]: <info> [1654244664.0219] dhcp4 (en…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adattatori video da DisplayPort a HDMI: ecco l'offerta Techly]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Adattatori-video-da-DisplayPort-a-HDMI-ecco-l-offerta-Techly_24583</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Adattatori-video-da-DisplayPort-a-HDMI-ecco-l-offerta-Techly_24583"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T08:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Techly, che da sempre offre un'ampia gamma di prodotti e accessori al servizio del settore informatico, presenta i nuovi convertitori da DisplayPort (DP) a HDMI per risolvere le problematiche di compatibilità video tra un notebook o un PC con un'uscita DP e un monitor HDMI e trasmettere il segnale audio-video ad alta definizione con risoluzione fino a 8K Ultra HD.Semplici, compatti e funzionali, i nuovi adattatori video per la conversione DisplayPort-HDMI presentati da Techly godono ognuno di caratteristiche peculiari e si dividono principalmente in due tipi: passivi e attivi. Questi ultimi, oltre a collegare le due diverse interfacce, convertono attivamente il segnale mentre viene trasmesso, indipendentemente dal tipo di segnale emesso o ricevuto.Tra i dispositivi attivi di Techly, vi è il nuovo adattatore IADAP DP-HDMIF8K da DisplayPort 1.4 a HDMI che consente di collegare un DisplayPort 20 pin maschio a un HDMI 19 pin femmina.Questo convertitore supporta una risoluzione video 8K a 30Hz, perfetto anche per lo streaming video e per il trasferimento di sessioni gaming da un computer a un televisore HDTV.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows: attenzione agli indirizzi che aprono finestre di Esplora file contenenti malware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-attenzione-agli-indirizzi-che-aprono-finestre-di-Esplora-file-contenenti-malware_24595</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-attenzione-agli-indirizzi-che-aprono-finestre-di-Esplora-file-contenenti-malware_24595"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T08:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Un URI (Uniform Resource Identifier) è un oggetto che permette di identificare una risorsa fisica o logica. Ne abbiamo parlato nell'articolo in cui abbiamo visto cos'è un URL e come è strutturato.In Windows sono registrati molti URI: un indirizzo che comincia con microsoft-edge:// permette ad esempio di aprire una pagina Web o una qualunque altra risorsa con il browser di Microsoft. Lo abbiamo visto nell'articolo in cui spieghiamo perché Microsoft blocca i tentativi di modifica dell'URI usato da Edge sui sistemi Windows.Provate a digitare App predefinite nella casella di ricerca di Windows quindi cliccare su Scegli app predefinite per protocollo: nella finestra che appare è possibile rendersi conto di quali e quanti URI sono registrati a livello di sistema operativo.Tra i tanti URI in elenco c'è search-ms: esso permette alle applicazioni o a pagine Web di avviare una ricerca personalizzata con la funzione integrata in Windows.Sebbene la maggior parte delle ricerche si concentri sull'utilizzo dell'indice memorizzato nel dispositivo locale (abbiamo visto come funziona la ricerca in Windows), è anche possibile forzare Windows Search ad attingere al contenuto delle risorse condivise in rete con la possibilità di alterare anche il titolo della finestra di ricerca.Gli aggressori possono inserire URI search-ms all'interno di email di phishing e indurre l'utente a cliccare sul link presentando quanto contenuto come aggiornamenti Microsoft non posticipabili.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did anyone try to install Arch on the Dell XPS 13 plus ?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3uigh/did_anyone_try_to_install_arch_on_the_dell_xps_13/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3uigh/did_anyone_try_to_install_arch_on_the_dell_xps_13/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T08:07:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/Techlis  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to keep my system clock at the right time ?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3u9lk/how_to_keep_my_system_clock_at_the_right_time/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3u9lk/how_to_keep_my_system_clock_at_the_right_time/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T07:49:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My computer clock kept being 5 minutes late, so I followed the arch wiki on system time and manually changed the time, and it worked. But then I was having error connecting to HTTPS pages because my system time wasn't correct, I think. So I found the fix on the same wiki page with ntpd -qg, but now I have to run this command every time I reboot, and I can't execute it automatically on startup as it requires an internet connection. So how can I stop having to run this command, have my system clock at the right time and being able to connect to HTTPS webpage ?
    submitted by    /u/Mahkda  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 10 continuerà a essere aggiornato: in arrivo un importante pacchetto correttivo]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-10-continuera-a-essere-aggiornato-in-arrivo-un-importante-pacchetto-correttivo_24552</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-10-continuera-a-essere-aggiornato-in-arrivo-un-importante-pacchetto-correttivo_24552"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T07:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Con la pubblicazione di una nota sul blog dell'azienda, Microsoft ha confermato che lo sviluppo di Windows 10 prosegue. La versione di riferimento del sistema operativo, che sarà supportato fino al 14 ottobre 2025, è al momento Windows 10 21H2 ovvero il feature update rilasciato pubblicamente a metà novembre 2021. In autunno verrà pubblicato l'aggiornamento 22H2.L'importante aggiornamento KB5014023 che era stato distribuito in anteprima, nelle scorse settimane, agli iscritti al programma Windows Insider è ora installabile da parte di tutti gli utenti. Presentato in Windows Update come aggiornamento opzionale, KB5014023 diverrà parte integrante della batteria di patch che saranno distribuite martedì 14 giugno ('patch day').Dopo l'applicazione dell'aggiornamento gli utenti di Windows 10 21H2 vedranno il numero di versione cambiare in 19044.1741: è possibile verificarlo premendo Windows+R quindi digitando winver.L'aggiornamento risolve innanzi tutto un problema nella copia dei file che in alcune situazioni può apparire lenta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wifi connection 'slow' since update linux-5.18.1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3tq6w/wifi_connection_slow_since_update_linux5181/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3tq6w/wifi_connection_slow_since_update_linux5181/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T07:08:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi together,
 I am experiencing some trouble with my wifi connection. The connection generally works and a speedtest shows the expected speed, but for some reason it just takes forever to load websites.
 The problem seems to be the initial step of the connection. After typing an address and hitting enter, it takes like 10-20 seconds until anything loads, but as soon as it is loading, it's fast. E.g. loading a youtube page with a video takes 10s but as soon as the play button is there, the video plays fine.
 The problem does not exist when connecting via ethernet and also does not exist on other devices and it only appeared yesterday after upgrading the kernel to linux 5.18.1. I didn't find any bug reports or forum threads related to that issue tho.
 What I (unsuccessfully) tried so far:
  
rebooting router
 changing DNS server, which didn't help
 connecting via ethernet => works fine, but doesn't fix the problem because I do not have ethernet at my desk
 re-installing linux & linux-firmware
  
If anybody could help me or give me some ideas what to even look for, would be super helpful! Thanks in advance
    submitted by    /u/badumudab  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fedora Server 37 Looking At Providing A KVM-Optimized Image]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Fedora-Server-37-Optimized-KVM</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Fedora-Server-37-Optimized-KVM"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fedora Server working group stakeholders are looking at offering an optimized KVM VM disk image as part of their offerings with the F37 release later this year...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox 102: Query Parameter Stripping improves privacy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178936</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/03/firefox-102-query-parameter-stripping-improves-privacy/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T04:51:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla plans to introduce a new privacy feature in the upcoming Firefox 102 web browser. Called Query Parameter Stripping, it is designed to remove tracking parameters from web addresses to improve user […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Firefox 102: Query Parameter Stripping improves privacy appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux 5.19 Completes Multi-Platform Support For Intel PXA/XScale, HPE GXP SoC Added]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-More-Arm</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-More-Arm"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another set of Arm SoC and platform changes have been submitted for the in-development Linux 5.19 merge window...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 Insider Preview Build 25131 improves the performance of the Microsoft Store app and fixes a few bugs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178927</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/03/whats-new-in-windows-11-insider-preview-build-25131/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T03:59:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has released Windows 11 Insider Preview Build 25131 to the Dev Channel. There are no new features in this update, it focuses on fixing bugs. Fixes in Windows 11 Insider Preview […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Windows 11 Insider Preview Build 25131 improves the performance of the Microsoft Store app and fixes a few bugs appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch doesn't sense keyboard and mouse after boot from grub.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3qr0g/arch_doesnt_sense_keyboard_and_mouse_after_boot/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3qr0g/arch_doesnt_sense_keyboard_and_mouse_after_boot/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T03:55:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently installed vanilla arch, In the process I might've messed up the default grub file. I sorta fixed it(please send me a copy of your default grub file if you can) I also am installing the vanilla arch on a external hard drive and then booting it on my pc as my pc isn't detecting any pendrives in the bios for some reason(I tried every possible thing out).
 After I boot the pc the keyboard works in the bios and grub but when it asks me for my decryption key for my luks root the keyboard lights turn off and doesn't work... It simply doesn't sense me inputting the password...
 Someone suggested to check the build hooks again... I did and the problem still persists...
 Can someone please help? Thanks in advance.
    submitted by    /u/nicholas_tesla_rocks  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Orion browser for macOS is now available in public beta, it supports Firefox and Chrome extensions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178912</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/03/orion-browser-for-macos-firefox-and-chrome-extensions/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T03:52:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Orion is a new web browser for macOS that has entered public beta testing. The app from Kagi, uses Apple's Webkit engine and includes a lot of customization options. Since it is […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Orion browser for macOS is now available in public beta, it supports Firefox and Chrome extensions appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Atlassian Confluence zero-day actively used in attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/critical-atlassian-confluence-zero-day-actively-used-in-attacks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/critical-atlassian-confluence-zero-day-actively-used-in-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T01:41:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers are actively exploiting a new Atlassian Confluence zero-day vulnerability tracked as CVE-2022-26134 to install web shells, with no fix available at this time. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ip link says I have no IP address]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3n3g5/ip_link_says_i_have_no_ip_address/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3n3g5/ip_link_says_i_have_no_ip_address/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T00:31:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I connected to my wireless network using iwctl however, i do not have an ip adress. Is there a way to get an IP address in the live install?
    submitted by    /u/NotSheltr  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Legally Download a Windows Virtual Machine]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=490562</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15346647/legally-download-windows-virtual-machine"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to run a copy of Windows in a virtual machine on your computer, you need to pay for a Windows license, right? But did you know that you can actually legally get a pre-made Windows Virtual Machine directly from Microsoft? These are meant for software developers, but they aren’t locked behind any sort of paid program or login page. You can have your own copies within a few minutes of reading this.
   

Content

Why Use a Windows VM?
Where to Get Your Free Windows VM?
What's the Catch?
How to Use Your VM with VirtualBox
Can You Run These VMs on an Apple Silicon Computer?

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Share Files Between Host PC and Virtual Machines
    
Why Use a Windows VM?
    
These pre-made VMs aren’t a permanent solution, but they offer a reliable... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sydney Butler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch hard freezing on AMD hardware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3l1mu/arch_hard_freezing_on_amd_hardware/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3l1mu/arch_hard_freezing_on_amd_hardware/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T22:45:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi all! I've been trying to install Arch, but I'm having issues with it.
 During installation the Live OS will freeze. Using Arch itself, a GUI installer, and other Arch based distros. I did get an Arch based distro to install, but it freezes also minutes after booting. I would rather use vanilla Arch instead of a distro anyways. I've used Linux before, and even got my Linux+ certification in 2011. I haven't used Linux in a while and want to play around again.
 I want to use Arch since it's what SteamOS is based on, but I don't want to use SteamOS.
 My hardware is as follows Ryzen 5 3600x ASRock Fatal1ty B450 Gaming-ITX/ac 32GB crucial 3200 ram AMD Radeon 5700xt
 I've tried searching and using different commands but either I'm doing it wrong or it's not working for me.
 Thank you for your time!
    submitted by    /u/LooseGas  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 10 KB5014023 update fixes slow copying, app crashes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-10-kb5014023-update-fixes-slow-copying-app-crashes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-10-kb5014023-update-fixes-slow-copying-app-crashes/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T21:50:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has released optional cumulative update previews for Windows 10 versions 20H2, 21H1, and 21H2, with fixes for slow file copying and applications crashing due to Direct3D issues. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why are there only headers, and no actual source files, for various packages?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3jrt3/why_are_there_only_headers_and_no_actual_source/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3jrt3/why_are_there_only_headers_and_no_actual_source/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T21:45:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arch is supposed to bundle all development files in with the standard packages, yet it seems like half of the packages only include the headers, and no actual source files.
 Specifically, I'm trying to compile something using libsensors. /usr/include/sensors/sensors.h exists, but the linker is throwing a fit because the equivalent sensors.c file is nowhere to be found when searching in /usr.
 Am I missing something here? Why are these files not included in the packages?
    submitted by    /u/BassChaser710  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wake from sleep magically fixed. Thank You Arch Devs!!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3jha4/wake_from_sleep_magically_fixed_thank_you_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3jha4/wake_from_sleep_magically_fixed_thank_you_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T21:32:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm just throwing it out there for the people that have been having issues with wake from sleep since late 5.17 kernel. My issue magically resolved itself with my latest update. So if you have been having issues with waking from sleep maybe updating will get it working for you again.
 P.S. Any tips to troubleshoot this in the future would be cool, I never got it figured as powering off just worked.
    submitted by    /u/Im-Mostly-Confused  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Which drive should I install Arch on?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3jd7c/which_drive_should_i_install_arch_on/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3jd7c/which_drive_should_i_install_arch_on/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T21:27:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was wondering which drive should I install Arch on; nvme0n1 which is 223.6G or sda which is my hard drive which is 931.5G. (I'm a newbie so I don't know that much :D).
    submitted by    /u/frOSystem  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add Screenshots and Animation to GitHub Pull Requests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=336059</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15346476/add-screenshots-animation-github-pull-requests"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub programmers often add screenshots or animated GIFs to their repository pull requests. These techniques are definitely more eye-catching than making someone read several lines of plain text. Adding static screenshots is helpful if you want to insert visual changes or photographs inline. To demonstrate process flows and mouse-cursor motion, you can use MP4 videos and GIF animation. The following tutorial shows you how to add screenshots and MP4/GIF animation in GitHub pull requests. 
   

Content

1. Add a New Repository and Branch
2. Create Screenshots for GitHub
3. Create Videos and GIF Animation for GitHub
4. Add Screenshots or Animations to GitHub Pull Requests
5. Display Screenshots and GIF Images on a GitHub Page
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:The Beginner’s Guide to Git
    
1. Add a New Repository and Branch
    
Even if you have never used GitHub before, you can use the below steps... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sayak Boral</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 10 Android banking trojans target apps with 1 billion downloads]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/top-10-android-banking-trojans-target-apps-with-1-billion-downloads/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/top-10-android-banking-trojans-target-apps-with-1-billion-downloads/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T21:09:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ten most prolific Android mobile banking trojans target 639 financial applications that collectively have over one billion downloads on the Google Play Store. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make Your Taskbar Larger or Smaller on Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=759589</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/759589/how-to-make-your-taskbar-larger-or-smaller-on-windows-11/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As of October 2021, the taskbar size in Windows 11 can’t be adjusted with the Settings app. Luckily, we’ve discovered a registry hack that can make the taskbar larger or smaller. Here’s how to do it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evil Corp switches to LockBit ransomware to evade sanctions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/evil-corp-switches-to-lockbit-ransomware-to-evade-sanctions/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/evil-corp-switches-to-lockbit-ransomware-to-evade-sanctions/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T20:35:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Evil Corp cybercrime group has now switched to deploying LockBit ransomware on targets' networks to evade sanctions imposed by the U.S. Treasury Department's Office of Foreign Assets Control (OFAC). [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel Issues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3hwj7/kernel_issues/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3hwj7/kernel_issues/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T20:19:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Error! Bad return status for module build on kernel: 5.18.1-arch1-1 (x86_64) 
 what does this mean and what can be done about it?
    submitted by    /u/Sea-End9327  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cannot wrap my head around Filesystems and partitions, HELP REQUIRED]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3hhlb/cannot_wrap_my_head_around_filesystems_and/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3hhlb/cannot_wrap_my_head_around_filesystems_and/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T20:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So I want to install arch on my main BIOS machine and would like to avoid the archinstall.
 The only problem I got up until now is to find the BEST partition method for my system. I could go easy and simple and just repeat whatever guide or tutorial out there in Youtube like I've done so far but I really find myself in the need of step up.
 I know this depends on lots of factors and I would like some guidance.
 Some of my questions:
 should I go with btrfs or xfs? 
 why some partitions require one filesystem or another?
 should I allocate the swap at the beginning or at the end?
 ​
 Right now my tab looks like this:
 sda1 - ext4 - 8M
 sda2 - swap - 8G
 sda3 - xfs - 100G (root)
 sda4 - btrfs - 580G (home)
 ​
 Any help would be much appreciated
    submitted by    /u/cnovoa15  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Insert a Handwritten Signature in Google Docs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=755404</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/755404/how-to-insert-a-handwritten-signature-in-google-docs/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While digital signatures have become a popular way to sign documents, you may have a document of your own where you just want to handwrite your signature. Using Google’s drawing tool, you can create and insert your signature easily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save 21% on a Garmin Forerunner 245 Music Running Smartwatch]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=399290</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/14466607/garmin-forerunner-music-running-smartwatch"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you like to completely let go when you work out, you’ll like the Garmin Forerunner 245 Music Running Smartwatch. While getting advanced running dynamics during your training, you can listen to your favorite tunes.
    
Sync the smartwatch with your favorite playlists on Spotify or various other music streaming services for ad-free listening. You can store up to 500 songs on the device. Transfer music from your computer, add headphones via Bluetooth and listen while you train for your next marathon.
    

    
The Garmin Forerunner 245 Music Running Smartwatch will allow you to make smarter training decisions to help you prepare for your next race. Watch your VO2 max and erase your concerns about heat and altitude, as the watch will analyze the impacts on your performance. Your exercise history and performance indicators are evaluated to help you maintain productivity. Get feedback from your aerobic and anaerobic training.
    
Join the Garmin Connect online fitness community to create custom workouts with the available tools or download free workouts. Need a coach?... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Microsoft Store on Windows Is About to Get Much Better]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809010</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809010/the-microsoft-store-on-windows-is-about-to-get-better/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T19:19:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Microsoft Store is the main app store on Windows 10 and 11, and it received an overhaul last year in time for the first version of Windows 11. Now even more improvements are on the way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apps for recording audio on ArchLinux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3ghm8/apps_for_recording_audio_on_archlinux/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3ghm8/apps_for_recording_audio_on_archlinux/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T19:14:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What audio recording app do you use on ArchLinux?
 I've been using gnome-sound-recorder but I want to switch to something less bloat. I guess ffmpeg might help but I'm not sure if I could get a good audio quality using only ffmpeg.
 I use this command in my script to record my screen along with my voice but my voice is not usually recorded properly. For example, my last words [at the end of the recording] usually are cut off and I don't know why.
 ffmpeg -video_size ${SCREEN_WIDTH}x${SCREEN_HEIGHT} -framerate 16 -f x11grab -i :0.0 -f pulse -ac 2 -i default ~/Videos/$(date +%Y-%m-%d_%T).mp4
    submitted by    /u/i8ad8  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setting up WiFi on Arch.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3ghbc/setting_up_wifi_on_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3ghbc/setting_up_wifi_on_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T19:14:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, I'm a newbie to Arch and Linux in general so please excuse me if my knowledge is a little bit underwhelming. I was wondering how to properly set up WiFi on Arch. I already know how to use IWCTL and how to connect to WiFi but is there anything else needed for a working WiFi so it connects when I boot and is there anything to set up with NetworkManager. Unfortunately I don't have access to ethernet so using that and going the easy route is out of the picture. Thanks in advance!
    submitted by    /u/frOSystem  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Your Next Car Needs Adaptive Cruise Control]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119885/why-your-next-car-needs-adaptive-cruise-control/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119885/why-your-next-car-needs-adaptive-cruise-control/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T19:07:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s nothing better than turning on cruise control and relaxing to some music during a road trip. And while cruise control is useful, the latest premium feature you’ll want in your next vehicle is adaptive cruise control (ACC), and here’s why.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ransomware gang now hacks corporate websites to show ransom notes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ransomware-gang-now-hacks-corporate-websites-to-show-ransom-notes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ransomware-gang-now-hacks-corporate-websites-to-show-ransom-notes/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T19:01:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A ransomware gang is taking extortion to a new level by publicly hacking corporate websites to publicly display ransom notes. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Loop a Video on iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=806998</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/806998/how-to-loop-a-video-on-iphone/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T19:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using just the built-in features in iPhone’s Photos and YouTube app, you can make your videos play in a loop for as long as you want. This eliminates the need to manually re-play your videos, and we’ll show you how to do that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox Nightly Tries For VA-API Video Acceleration For Mesa Users]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Firefox-103-Nightly-VA-API</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Firefox-103-Nightly-VA-API"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T18:28:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Potentially for the Mozilla Firefox 103 release we could see VA-API video acceleration for Linux users finally enabled by default while as of today has been flipped back on again in Firefox Nightly builds...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[why is this package still installed?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3f247/why_is_this_package_still_installed/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3f247/why_is_this_package_still_installed/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I had installed wine earlier, and I uninstalled it. I uninstalled all dependencies along with it.
 pacman -Qdtq and pacman -Qdttq do not list lib32-attr, and lib32-libogg. (These commands list nothing)
 pacman -Qe does not list it either.
 When I try to uninstall them, they give no error or warning.
 They are not an explicitly installed package. Neither a normal or an optional dependency.
 Why are they still installed?
    submitted by    /u/abrattic  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trying to install on ThinkPad T61 on ethernet, can’t import PGP keys]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3ezzp/trying_to_install_on_thinkpad_t61_on_ethernet/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3ezzp/trying_to_install_on_thinkpad_t61_on_ethernet/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T18:07:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am trying to install Arch Linux (kernel 5.18.1) onto my T61, however, whenever I run pacman -Syyu or use the archinstall script, it asks me to manually import PGP keys, and then fails, telling me the required key is missing from the keyring. Any clue as to what is going on?
    submitted by    /u/1kelpy  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Disable the “These Files Might Be Harmful to Your Computer” Warning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=807905</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/807905/how-to-disable-the-these-files-might-be-harmful-to-your-computer-warning/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows can be pretty aggressive with security warnings, to the point that it warns you about your own files on your own home network. Here’s how to calm Windows down so you can use network shares and your NAS in peace.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Fitzpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BMW and Ford Just Announced More Electric Cars]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=808999</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/808999/bmw-and-ford-just-announced-more-electric-cars/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T17:45:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are now more options than ever for all-electric and hybrid vechicles, and now two more are on the way: an electric version of BMW’s X1 SUV, and a commercial vehicle from Ford.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[System76 & HP Formally Launch The HP Dev One AMD Ryzen Laptop With Pop!_OS Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=HP-Dev-One-Launches</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=HP-Dev-One-Launches"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T17:39:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last month System76 and HP began teasing an HP developer laptop with AMD Ryzen SoC and running Pop!_OS while today that HP Dev One laptop has formally launched...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft blocks Polonium hackers from using OneDrive in attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-blocks-polonium-hackers-from-using-onedrive-in-attacks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-blocks-polonium-hackers-from-using-onedrive-in-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T17:36:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft said it blocked a Lebanon-based hacking group it tracks as Polonium from using the OneDrive cloud storage platform for data exfiltration and command and control while targeting and compromising Israelian organizations. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smartproxy Review: The Reliable, High-Quality Proxy]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=489231</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15346221/smartproxy-review"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T17:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gathering data is critical for building businesses, but web scraping manually is tiresome and often leads to IP blocks and bans. Sadly, many proxy services only have limited options and aren’t always trustworthy, even after paying high fees to use them. I recently had the opportunity to test Smartproxy, which promises to not only be trustworthy but also offers high-quality services for a fair price. 
    
This is a sponsored article and was made possible by Smartproxy. The actual contents and opinions are the sole views of the author who maintains editorial independence even when a post is sponsored.
    
Overview of Smartproxy
    
Smartproxy doesn’t just specialize in one type of proxy service or tool. Between a a variety of proxies, tools, and user resources/tutorials, users get everything they need to scrape the web efficiently. In fact, Smartproxy actually won the 2021 Best Value Provider by Proxyway for their dedication to meeting customer needs. 
    
Some of the main features the service offers include:
    
Intuitive dashboard with a quick account setup
Free geo-targeting
Unlimited connections and threads
Advanced proxy rotation
Numerous informative resources that are... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Crystal Crowder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Select LEGO Sets Will See a Price Hike This August]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119886/select-lego-sets-will-see-a-price-hike-this-august/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119886/select-lego-sets-will-see-a-price-hike-this-august/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T17:09:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As if LEGO sets weren’t expensive enough, a new price hike is coming later this year. It seems that increased material and operating costs are finally getting the best of LEGO, as the company plans to increase prices on “around a quarter” of its catalog this August.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What to Look for in a Gaming Headset]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=797570</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/797570/what-to-look-for-in-a-gaming-headset/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T17:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to take your gaming up a notch? A gaming headset will help give you the competitive advantage you need to come out on top. Here are all the main factors to consider when shopping for a gaming headset.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Nguyen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Opens a PS5 and Xbox Waiting List for Real People, Not Bots]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119873/amazon-opens-a-ps5-and-xbox-waiting-list-for-real-people-not-bots/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119873/amazon-opens-a-ps5-and-xbox-waiting-list-for-real-people-not-bots/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T16:39:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a (at this point, noble) effort to evade bots and scalpers, Amazon is creating a by-request waiting list for purchasing the highly sought after PlayStation 5 and Xbox Series X gaming consoles after a recent restock. Users can request an invitation on the Amazon product page.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzanne Humphries</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese LuoYu hackers deploy cyber-espionage malware via app updates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/chinese-luoyu-hackers-deploy-cyber-espionage-malware-via-app-updates/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/chinese-luoyu-hackers-deploy-cyber-espionage-malware-via-app-updates/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T16:36:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Chinese-speaking hacking group known as LuoYu is infecting victims WinDealer information stealer malware deployed by switching legitimate app updates with malicious payloads in man-on-the-side attacks. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another Pixel 7 Prototype Ended Up In Someone's Pocket]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119876/another-pixel-7-prototype-ended-up-in-someones-pocket/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119876/another-pixel-7-prototype-ended-up-in-someones-pocket/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T16:29:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the end of May, we reported on Google’s unreleased Pixel 7 popping up on eBay. Now, it looks like another Pixel 7 prototype, the flagship Pixel 7 Pro, ended up on Facebook marketplace and in someone’s pocket.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BMW Reveals Its First Affordable EV]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119874/bmw-reveals-its-first-affordable-ev/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119874/bmw-reveals-its-first-affordable-ev/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T16:27:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The newly-revealed BMW X1 lineup is all about functionality, style, and affordability, with ICE cars starting at $35,000. But more notably, this lineup includes BMW’s first affordable electric car—the BMW iX1 xDrive30.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Experimenting With "NVK" Nouveau Open-Source Vulkan Driver]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Red-Hat-NVK-NVIDIA-Vulkan</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Red-Hat-NVK-NVIDIA-Vulkan"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T16:09:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following the recent news about Nouveau shifting code around so their shader compiler can be used outside of Nouveau Gallium3D, Red Hat's Karol Herbst who has been a longtime Nouveau developer has been posting patches for his new "NVK" Nouveau Vulkan driver effort...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Fastest Way to Type a Period on iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=808317</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/808317/the-fastest-way-to-type-a-period-on-iphone/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T16:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The iPhone keyboard is one of the most popular keyboards on the planet, but it’s not without its quirks. Strangely, the period key is buried in the secondary layout. There’s a much faster way to use it, though.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Social media’s ‘Doomscrolling Reminder Lady’ on her favorite corners of the internet]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.mozilla.org/?p=69042</id>
        <link href="https://blog.mozilla.org/en/internet-culture/interviews/karen-ho-twitter-doomscrolling-reminder-lady/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T15:55:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here at Mozilla, we are the first to admit the internet isn’t perfect, but we are also quick to point out that the internet is pretty darn magical. The internet opens up doors and opportunities, allows for people to connect with others, and lets everyone find where they belong — their corners of the internet. […]
The post Social media’s ‘Doomscrolling Reminder Lady’ on her favorite corners of the internet appeared first on The Mozilla Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kristina Bravo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[dropped into emergency shell, arch no longer boots]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3bxxp/dropped_into_emergency_shell_arch_no_longer_boots/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3bxxp/dropped_into_emergency_shell_arch_no_longer_boots/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T15:51:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I don't know what's going on. I've been experiencing a multitude of problems lately and have suspected something wrong with my system overall and then it finally stopped working on me.
 This is the screen I get now. https://ibb.co/s9Szc5r
 At first, it wasn't recognizing the kernel images that I had installed. I removed and reinstalled my kernels as well as my boot manager-refind-and that changed it to what you see now.
 The bootmanager pulls up fine. The normal options are all there. I can load into recovery media perfectly fine and see that everything is still there just the way it was before it stopped booting. It just won't boot into arch.
 It appears that, for some reason, the system cannot locate the file systems.
 Please help.
    submitted by    /u/reenmini  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unable to log-in on after installing nvidia drivers on laptop (fresh installs)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3bxhv/unable_to_login_on_after_installing_nvidia/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3bxhv/unable_to_login_on_after_installing_nvidia/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T15:50:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is what my screen looks like when i try to log in. This issue appears only after I install proprietary nvidia drivers via: sudo pacman -S nvidia-dkms nvidia-utils lib32-nvidia-utils nvidia-settings vulkan-icd-loader lib32-vulkan-icd-loader lib32-opencl-nvidia opencl-nvidia libxnvctrl
 Methods tried so far: • reinstalled arch few times • tried both kde and gnome • added nvidia related modules to /etc/mkinitcpio.conf • blacklisted iGPU modules (source: arch wiki)
    submitted by    /u/mmj0299  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is it worth encrypting my disk using LUKS if I'm the only person who has physical access to it ?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3bsst/is_it_worth_encrypting_my_disk_using_luks_if_im/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3bsst/is_it_worth_encrypting_my_disk_using_luks_if_im/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T15:44:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The title explains it all, i'm an Arch user, and I have it installed in my Desktop PC. I do trust my family members and I'm literally the only person who would ever have physical access to it. My question here is: Is it worth encrypting the disk in my case ? Cause I have to backup all my data + dotfiles before doing a clean install of Arch.
 Thanks in advance! I'm all ears to hear out ur opinions.
    submitted by    /u/1_7xr  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Pay e Google Pay sono sicuri per i pagamenti?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/06/apple-pay-e-google-pay-sono-sicuri-per.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/06/apple-pay-e-google-pay-sono-sicuri-per.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T15:40:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tra i metodi di pagamento digitale in rapida diffusione troviamo sicuramente Apple Pay e Google Pay, due app che si comportano in maniera del tutto simile a dei portafogli di nuova generazione. Con esse infatti è possibile inserire i dati della propria carta di credito (ma anche Bancomat o carte prepagate) e "virtualizzarla", così da poter pagare nei negozi abilitati semplicemente avvicinando il...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Newbie Question: Is there an arch installation guide within the arch iso?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3bjni/newbie_question_is_there_an_arch_installation/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3bjni/newbie_question_is_there_an_arch_installation/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T15:32:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I want to know if there is something like an installation guide within the arch iso that I can look up while I'm in the installation process without having to look for it on another device. 
 I hope I made myself clear. Thanks in advance.
    submitted by    /u/cnovoa15  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Safari Not Working on Your iPhone? Here’s How to Fix It]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=post-ideas&amp;p=243361</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/8302860/safari-not-working-iphone"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Although iPhones and iPads support other apps to reach the Web, Safari remains the most favored and frequently used browser for iOS users. Troubleshooting on Safari can be frustrating, especially if its issues prevent you from searching for a solution online. Here are a few common reasons why Safari may not be working on your iPhone and how to fix the problems.
   

Content

Turn on Mobile Data for the Safari App
Disable Experimental Features
Change Your Network Settings

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Make Mobile Safari Save Your Passwords on iOS
    
Test Your Internet Connection
    
To begin with, ensure that the problem is with Safari and not with your internet connection. For this, open, say, a non-Apple app like Facebook or Chrome, and see whether the website or the feed loads. If it does, then Safari is at fault.... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ojash Yadav</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Steam Deck Accessory Just Got Delayed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119869/the-best-steam-deck-accessory-just-got-delayed/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119869/the-best-steam-deck-accessory-just-got-delayed/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T15:24:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in April, I predicted that the Steam Deck Docking Station would launch in late June, “barring any last-minute delays.” And it seems that I jinxed everyone, because the Steam Deck Dock just got delayed indefinitely. We have no clue when it will launch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla releases local machine translation tools as part of Project Bergamot]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.mozilla.org/?p=69082</id>
        <link href="https://blog.mozilla.org/en/mozilla/local-translation-add-on-project-bergamot/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T15:23:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In January of 2019, Mozilla joined the University of Edinburgh, Charles University, University of Sheffield and University of Tartu as part of a project funded by the European Union called Project Bergamot. The ultimate goal of this consortium was to build a set of neural machine translation tools that would enable Mozilla to develop a […]
The post Mozilla releases local machine translation tools as part of Project Bergamot appeared first on The Mozilla Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rebecca Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Audio and video drivers?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3ay7d/audio_and_video_drivers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3ay7d/audio_and_video_drivers/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T15:05:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello,I'm trying to install video drivers for my system. I'm running arch off of a USB onto a Dell G15 laptop. It has a NVIDIA 3060 GPU and I think it has integrated Intel graphics. To log into my system I just use tty1 and then start X on login. I use i3.
 I've tried installing the NVIDIA package a couple times but it always leads to some sort of issue where my system completely stalls whenever I start X. Because of this, I'm pretty sure some sort of configuration is wrong, but it could be that I'm installing the wrong driver or even something else entirely.
 I'd be fine with only using the integrated Intel graphics, but for some reason, xrandr doesn't recognize my 2 external monitors that I connect via usbc dock.
 I've read through a a bunch of the wiki and done a decent amount of googling. Its entirely possible that I've missed something though. Any pointers in the right direction would be really really helpful. 
 Edit: I know the title says Audio and video, but I've decided to work on things one at a time haha.
    submitted by    /u/SyntaxAerror  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TCL Picks Up Where the LG Stylo Left Off]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119850/tcl-picks-up-where-the-lg-stylo-left-off/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119850/tcl-picks-up-where-the-lg-stylo-left-off/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T15:02:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After LG decided to stop selling smartphones, it left a huge gap in the “this phone is kinda weird” market. Most notably, the death of LG Stylo meant that only Motorola would sell affordable stylus-equipped smartphones. But the universe is correcting itself with the launch of TCL’s Stylus 5G.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Goal Seek in Microsoft Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=805858</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/805858/goal-seek-excel/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T15:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever had a financial goal you sought but weren’t exactly sure how to get there? Using Goal Seek in Microsoft Excel, you can determine what you need to accomplish your goal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Steam Deck’s Official Docking Station Is Now Delayed (Again)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=808977</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/808977/steam-decks-official-docking-station-is-now-delayed-again/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T14:40:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Valve originally promised a docking station would be available for the Steam Deck at the console’s release, but it has been delayed. Now Valve has confirmed it has been delayed, again.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iOttie Velox Wireless Charging Dash & Windshield Mount Review: Not Quite Wireless]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119089/iottie-velox-magnetic-wireless-charging-dash-and-windshield-mount-review/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119089/iottie-velox-magnetic-wireless-charging-dash-and-windshield-mount-review/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T14:24:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[iOttie’s Velox Magnetic Wireless Charging Dash & Windshield Mount does little to stand out among the ever-growing crowd of vehicle chargers and mounts. It solves just enough minor inconveniences to stand above the pack, but its bulky size means it’s only for cars with space to spare.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chazz Mair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video on websites are freezing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3a040/video_on_websites_are_freezing/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3a040/video_on_websites_are_freezing/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T14:22:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, today I discovered an issue on my Arch. I rarely watch videos on my laptop, so I am not sure since when this issue has been there.
 When I try to play a video, the video just freeze. I can seek the bar on the player, but it will only change the frame shown. The video will keep freezing.
 Not only on Reddit, but on youtube as well.
 You can see the issue in action here: https://i.imgur.com/XbSlmfv.mp4
 Hopefully someone can give me an idea to try. Thanks!
  
Os: Arch
 kernel: linux 5.18.1.arch1-1
 Browser: Occur on Firefox and Chrome
 GPU: Occur on both AMDGPU and Nvidia
  
   submitted by    /u/tom_yacht  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best VR Headsets of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=754839</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/754839/best-vr-headset/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Virtual reality prices are down, and the quality of games is up, so it’s a great time to jump in if you’ve been holding off on taking the plunge. While we aren’t quite in The Matrix yet, modern VR headsets are shockingly good. Here’s the best VR headset you can buy right now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sydney Butler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some users are reporting printing issues in Microsoft Edge 102]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178909</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/02/some-users-are-reporting-printing-issues-in-microsoft-edge-102/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T13:57:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft released a new stable version of the company's Edge web browser a few days ago. Microsoft Edge 102 fixed several security issues in the browser, including three that were specified to […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Some users are reporting printing issues in Microsoft Edge 102 appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>