<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-05-10T01:26:35.101Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel's ControlFlag 1.2 Released To Use AI To Provide Full Support For Spotting C++ Bugs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-ControlFlag-1.2</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-ControlFlag-1.2"/>
        <updated>2022-05-10T00:46:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year Intel open-sourced the ControlFlag project for using machine learning to uncover bugs within code. With today's ControlFlag 1.2 release, C++ is now a fully supported language for this AI-driven project for uncovering bugs within arbitrary code-bases...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Transfer Contacts From One Phone to Another]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=470662</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15284152/transfer-contacts-from-one-phone-another"/>
        <updated>2022-05-10T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re thinking about getting a new phone, you’re probably wondering about the best way to transfer your personal data such as photos, videos, messages, and contacts from one phone to another. We will explain in detail how to do that whether you’re making the jump from Android to Android, iPhone to iPhone, iPhone to Android, and vice versa.
   

Content

Transfer Contacts From Android to Android
Transfer Contacts From Android to iOS
Transfer Contacts From iPhone to Android
Transfer Contacts From iPhone to iPhone
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Hide Calls and Texts from Specific Contacts on Android
    
Transfer Contacts From Android to Android
    
There are two ways to transfer contacts from an Android to another Android phone.
    
1. Google Sync
    
Syncing contacts to your Google... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mehvish Mushtaq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox gnome theme aur package]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/um4jku/firefox_gnome_theme_aur_package/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/um4jku/firefox_gnome_theme_aur_package/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T23:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey guys I was wondering why there was no aur package for such a famous theme. Would be much easier to install.
 https://github.com/rafaelmardojai/firefox-gnome-theme
    submitted by    /u/freetoilet  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[video hardware acceleration in firefox]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/um2ycm/video_hardware_acceleration_in_firefox/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/um2ycm/video_hardware_acceleration_in_firefox/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T22:18:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, 
 I have a question about hardware acceleration in browsers (firefox especially). has anyone managed to make firefox / firefox developer edition to actually use hardware accelerated youtube playback on intel graphic cards ? I'm just getting tired of cpu usage and heavy fan speed... obviously i've tried everything what was on arch wiki in the topic, but no luck, i have I7-10810U with integrated graphics.
 in earlier versions of FF i had it working (but not every time, one in 5 firefox runs maybe, and it was really "unstable")
 I've tried literally everything - wandered searching on different forums without luck.
 obviously basics like va-api, vdpau works flawlessly, multiple video players in system uses them and it's working fine.
    submitted by    /u/noderblade  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lincoln College to close after 157 years due ransomware attack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/lincoln-college-to-close-after-157-years-due-ransomware-attack/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/lincoln-college-to-close-after-157-years-due-ransomware-attack/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T22:17:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lincoln College, a liberal-arts school from rural Illinois, says it will close its doors later this month, 157 years since it was founded and following a hard hit on its finances after the COVID-19 pandemic and a recent ransomware attack.  [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I am getting this error whenever I try to pacman -Syu, what should I do]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/um2oo3/i_am_getting_this_error_whenever_i_try_to_pacman/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/um2oo3/i_am_getting_this_error_whenever_i_try_to_pacman/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T22:06:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is the error
 error: failed retrieving file 'dav1d-1.0.0-1-x86_64.pkg.tar.zst' from archlinux.thaller.ws : OpenSSL SSL_read: Connection reset by peer, errno 104 error: failed retrieving file 'libunistring-1.0-1-x86_64.pkg.tar.zst.sig' from archlinux.thaller.ws : HTTP/2 stream 23 was not closed cleanly before end of the underlying stream error: failed retrieving file 'haskell-mono-traversable-1.0.15.3-44-x86_64.pkg.tar.zst.sig' from archlinux.thaller.ws : HTTP/2 stream 25 was not closed cleanly before end of the underlying stream warning: too many errors from archlinux.thaller.ws, skipping for the remainder of this transaction error: failed retrieving file 'python-setuptools-1:59.6.0-1-any.pkg.tar.zst' from archlinux.thaller.ws : HTTP/2 stream 27 was not closed cleanly before end of the underlying stream warning: failed to retrieve some files error: failed to commit transaction (unexpected error) Errors occurred, no packages were upgraded. 
    submitted by    /u/spcbfr  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arricchiamo di stile la nostra suite LibreOffice in ambiente Linux Mint]]></title>
        <id>3564|20220510000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/openoffice-libreoffice-136/arricchiamo-stile-suite-libreoffice-ambiente-linux-mint-3564"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LibreOffice è una conosciutissima suite di produttività "libera" e multipiattaforma (ossia disponibile per Windows, Linux e macOS), localizzata anche in lingua italiana, direttamente discendente, come fork, dal glorioso precursore OpenOffice.org. Oggi è ormai ampiamente impiegata per produrre testi, realizzare fogli di calcolo o gestire basi dati, tanto per fare qualche esempio, quale ottima ed efficace alternativa a blasonate soluzioni commerciali a pagamento, Office di Microsoft su tutte.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Updating from all pacnew files]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/um2hrc/updating_from_all_pacnew_files/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/um2hrc/updating_from_all_pacnew_files/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T21:58:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is there an easy way to update all config files with pacnew files?
 What I am looking for is something like - being able to automatically open all pacnew and their corresponding config file in a diff editor one after the other automatically (where saving a config file would open the next) and most importantly, not open config files where the config file modification date was later than the pacnew generation date (so that I do not overwrite old pacnew edits where I forgot to delete the pacnew file). What would be even better would be being able to delete all pacnew files where the config file modification date is later than the pacnew creation date.
    submitted by    /u/daredevildas  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I do think it's one of the best distro but]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/um23cu/i_do_think_its_one_of_the_best_distro_but/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/um23cu/i_do_think_its_one_of_the_best_distro_but/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T21:39:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[this amount of updates,jeez.
  
Total Installed Size: 6846.23 MiB
 Net Upgrade Size: 386.73 MiB
  
last update was on 27th April.
 It's going to kill my SSDs.
    submitted by    /u/AccurateVictory  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add Chrome Webpages and Bookmarks to the Home Screen on Android]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=247536</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/8230871/add-chrome-bookmarks-android-home-screen"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re a regular visitor to a specific website (maybe Make Tech Easier?), it can be useful to keep the websites you like on your Android home page. When you want to pay a visit to the site, simply head to the home page, tap the icon as if it were an app, and you’re there! While this post will cover Chrome specifically, the process to add your bookmarks to the home screen on Android usually works on most Chromium-based browsers.
   

Content

Adding a Specific Website
Adding Multiple Websites
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Set Custom Icons for Your Android Apps
    
Adding a Specific Website
    
If you have a specific website in mind that you’d like to add to the home screen, it can be done very easily. You can add individual webpages to your home page... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Crystal Crowder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add a Shared Google Drive to Windows File Explorer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=802048</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/802048/how-to-add-a-shared-google-drive-to-windows-file-explorer/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T21:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you and your team or coworkers use a shared Google Drive, you may want quick and easy access to it. In just a few minutes, you can add this shared drive to File Explorer on Windows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KDE Connect Arrives on iPhone and iPad For Linux Fans]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=804091</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/804091/kde-connect-arrives-on-iphone-and-ipad-for-linux-fans/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T20:38:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KDE Connect has been around for years as a companion Android app for connecting to Linux PCs, similar to Microsoft Link to Windows (formerly “Your Phone”). Now there’s finally a KDE Connect app for iPhone and iPad.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers display “blood is on your hands" on Russian TV, take down RuTube]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-display-blood-is-on-your-hands-on-russian-tv-take-down-rutube/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-display-blood-is-on-your-hands-on-russian-tv-take-down-rutube/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T20:19:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[​Hackers continue to target Russia with cyberattacks, defacing Russian TV to show pro-Ukrainian messages and taking down the RuTube video streaming site. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fix “This Site Can’t Be Reached” ERR_ADDRESS_UNREACHABLE in Chrome]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=799680</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/799680/how-to-fix-this-site-cant-be-reached-err_address_unreachable-in-chrome/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T20:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve all experienced the occasional error from Google Chrome, including “This site can’t be reached,” but what do you do if the error sticks around after restarting your browser? Here are some things you can try to fix the problem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Lewis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything to Expect From Google I/O 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117367/everything-to-expect-from-google-i-o-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117367/everything-to-expect-from-google-i-o-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T19:56:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After canceling in 2020 and having an intimate show for 2021, Google’s annual developer event, Google I/O 2022, is back and should be bigger than ever. And while these events are highly software-focused, we’re expecting some big hardware announcements later this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Are NFTs Coming to Instagram?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117380/why-are-nfts-coming-to-instagram/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117380/why-are-nfts-coming-to-instagram/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T19:49:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite their massive decline in popularity and value, NFTs are coming to Instagram. Select users will have the option to display and share NFTs on their profile beginning the week of May 16th. Instagram claims that NFT integration will help artists make money, but Instagram is a business, so it’s obviously searching for a way to profit off of NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What GUI would you recommend for NetworkManager?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ulzay9/what_gui_would_you_recommend_for_networkmanager/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ulzay9/what_gui_would_you_recommend_for_networkmanager/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T19:36:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have found a couple of them:
  
nm-connection-editor
 network-manager-applet
  
What GUI do you use for network management? I'm connecting my laptop to the wifi with a .sh file right now...
 ​
 I use arch with awesomewm btw.
    submitted by    /u/HansDCJ  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save 48% on HiFuture FlyBuds Pro Earbuds]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=487399</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15283765/hifuture-flybuds-pro-earbuds"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since 2016, HiFuture has been creating premium, quality consumer electronics and mobile audio accessories with a vision to offer them at affordable prices. The company now partners with Qualcomm, Realtek, BES, and more. On offer through June 30, 2022, is the HiFuture FlyBuds Pro Earbuds at nearly half off. They feature environmental noise canceling, anti-fragile graphite drivers, four mics, and long battery life.
    
The built-in environmental noise-canceling technology in these earbuds will filter out the sounds around you so that you can focus on your music, podcasts, audiobooks, or phone calls. The anti-fragile graphite-inspired drivers will deliver a rich, clear, accurate, perfect sound with a soft bass.
    

    
The four-mic calling system on the HiFuture FlyBuds Pro Earbuds features mics in the front upper and lower of each steam and provides real-time great talk quality with background noise being removed. You won’t have any worries about them dying on you, as they provide up to 20 hours of battery life to take calls, hear your favorite tunes and podcasts, etc. Charge them in minutes... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Aside Focus Time in Google Calendar]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=799852</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/799852/focus-time-google-calendar/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you ever just need to put your head down and work? You know how hard it can be to concentrate with distractions like meetings, phone calls, and the unexpected pop-in. Focus Time in Google Calendar can help.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pop!_OS 22.04 Benchmarks On The Threadripper-Powered System76 Thelio Major]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31108</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31108"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the end of April was the release of System76's Pop!_OS 22.04 based on Ubuntu 22.04 but with a variety of improvements from numerous graphical/desktop enhancements down to other changes like their scheduler work and more. For those currently on Pop!_OS 21.10 and wondering about the performance implications, here are some benchmarks showing the performance difference on the same hardware.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dell, Apple, Netflix face lawsuits for pulling services out of Russia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/dell-apple-netflix-face-lawsuits-for-pulling-services-out-of-russia/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/dell-apple-netflix-face-lawsuits-for-pulling-services-out-of-russia/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T18:59:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Moscow Arbitration Court has reportedly seized almost $11 million belonging to Dell LLC after the company failed to provide paid-for services to a local system integrator. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google I/O 2022: How to Watch and What to Expect]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=803991</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/803991/google-io-2022-how-to-watch-and-what-to-expect/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T18:02:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google I/O is the largest yearly event from Google, where the company usually reveals a mix of new products/services and new technologies for software developers. Read on to find out where to watch this year’s event and what we expect to see.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Mirror Your iPhone’s Screen to Amazon Fire TV Stick]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=798620</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/798620/how-to-mirror-iphone-to-firestick/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T18:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want the games, photos, and videos on your iPhone blown up on your big screen? Sometimes called “mirroring,” you can cast your iPhone’s screen to your Amazon Fire TV device using a free app. Here’s how to do it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Issues First Production Release Of Its CBL-Mariner 2.0 Linux Distribution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Microsoft-CBL-Mariner-2.0</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Microsoft-CBL-Mariner-2.0"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T17:53:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Made public last year by Microsoft was CBL-Mariner 1.0 as its internal Linux distribution used for selective purposes from Azure to WSL. This Microsoft "Common Base Linux" distribution has worked well for their internal needs while continuing to make roughly monthly public updates to its 1.0 branch. Today CBL-Mariner 2.0 marks its first production release...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[fuboTV Removes 4K Sports From Its Base Plan, but Only for New Subscribers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117345/fubotv-removes-4k-sports-from-its-base-plan-but-only-for-new-subscribers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117345/fubotv-removes-4k-sports-from-its-base-plan-but-only-for-new-subscribers/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T17:45:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sports fans are fuboTV’s bread and butter. Unfortunately, new subscribers who want to see events in 4K must now subscribe to fuboTV most expensive plan. The company’s “130+ events in 4K” are now exclusive to the “Elite” channel package.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft releases fixes for Azure flaw allowing RCE attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-releases-fixes-for-azure-flaw-allowing-rce-attacks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-releases-fixes-for-azure-flaw-allowing-rce-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T17:42:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has released security updates to address a security flaw affecting Azure Synapse and Azure Data Factory pipelines that could let attackers execute remote commands across Integration Runtime infrastructure. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boot without waiting for HDD]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ulwrhy/boot_without_waiting_for_hdd/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ulwrhy/boot_without_waiting_for_hdd/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T17:41:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Right now my system starts in about 10 seconds and according to systemd-analyze blame a lot of that is the time it takes to mount my drive. Is there a way to edit my fstab to make my drive mount after boot so it doesn't hang? Or is there any daemon for doing this after boot?
 I looked around online for some but didn't find anything that would do what I need.
    submitted by    /u/emptyskoll  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polybar has made it into the community repository]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ulwkbk/polybar_has_made_it_into_the_community_repository/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ulwkbk/polybar_has_made_it_into_the_community_repository/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T17:32:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/sierratango88  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ukraine warns of “chemical attack” phishing pushing stealer malware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ukraine-warns-of-chemical-attack-phishing-pushing-stealer-malware/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ukraine-warns-of-chemical-attack-phishing-pushing-stealer-malware/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T17:30:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ukraine's Computer Emergency Response Team (CERT-UA) is warning of the mass distribution of Jester Stealer malware via phishing emails using warnings of impending chemical attacks to scare recipients into opening attachments. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WELOCK Smart Door Knob with Keypad Review]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=product-review&amp;p=483167</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15283651/welock-smart-door-knob-with-keypad"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T17:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are looking to convert your house into a smart home, switching to a smart lock is one of the easiest way to get started. It is often a one-to-one replacement, which means you can easily remove your old lock and replace it with a smart lock. There is no need for major renovation or drilling of (additional) holes, and it is something you can do on your own. If you are looking for a smart lock, here we take a look at the WELOCK Smart Door Knob with Keypad to see how it performs.
    
This is a sponsored article and was made possible by WELOCK. The actual contents and opinions are the sole views of the author who maintains editorial independence, even when a post is sponsored.
    
Unboxing
    
The packaging of WELOCK Smart Lock is pretty basic. You get the door knob, the latch and spring bolt, a few screws, 3 RF cards, a set of keys and an instruction leaflet. The smart door knob requires 4 AAA batteries to operate, and they are not included in the package.
    
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Damien</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[App per creare emoji (Emoticon) personalizzate su chat e messenger]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2015/03/app-per-creare-emoji-emoticon.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2015/03/app-per-creare-emoji-emoticon.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T17:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Per i fan delle faccine da chat, emoticon o emoji possiamo utilizzare delle app dedicate per creare subito nuove faccine, da usare subito nelle chat di WhatsApp, nei gruppi di amici e sui social network. Queste emoji possono essere create su qualsiasi telefonino e, se rispettiamo alcuni parametri, possiamo visualizzarli su qualsiasi telefono, anche se il destinatario non ha la stessa app...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome cambierà le password non sicure: funzione utile o incubo?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Chrome-cambiera-le-password-non-sicure-funzione-utile-o-incubo_24489</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Chrome-cambiera-le-password-non-sicure-funzione-utile-o-incubo_24489"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T17:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google sta facendo di tutto per migliorare la gestione delle password e in generale delle credenziali di accesso in Chrome.In tanti nostri articoli abbiamo però visto quanto sia semplice risalire all'elenco delle credenziali memorizzate nel browser e perché, in generale, l'utilizzo dei password manager integrati nel software che si usa ogni giorno per 'navigare' sul Web non sia un'idea favolosa. Anzi. Trovare le password salvate con il browser è molto semplice: e non solo nel caso di Chrome ma anche di altri browser.Il password manager del browser, però, è uno strumento comodo da usare e sempre pronto: per questo la stragrande maggioranza degli utenti continua a servirsene; spesso attivando anche la sincronizzazione di Chrome e quindi lo scambio dei dati personali, credenziali comprese, tra più dispositivi.In occasione del World Password Day abbiamo visto come creare password sicure e qual è il ruolo ricoperto dall'autenticazione a due fattori.La novità è che Chrome non soltanto sarà presto in grado di rilevare le password 'compromesse' ovvero quelle già nelle mani dei criminali informatici (cosa possibile già oggi) ma provvederà a cambiare le password insicure in automatico.La notizia può suonare un po’ sinistra.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Clever Raspberry Pi Hack Adds Android Auto to Tesla Vehicles]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117348/this-clever-raspberry-pi-hack-adds-android-auto-to-tesla-vehicles/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117348/this-clever-raspberry-pi-hack-adds-android-auto-to-tesla-vehicles/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T17:06:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s easy to make an older car feel new by adding a few gadgets or accessories, but it’s not quite that simple when you drive a Tesla. That said, you can now get Apple’s CarPlay or Android Auto in Tesla vehicles with this neat Raspberry Pi hack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is OFDMA (Orthogonal Frequency-Division Multiple Access)?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=796110</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/796110/what-is-ofdma/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T17:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As more and more devices require a connection to the internet, our previous Wi-Fi standards can no longer handle the extra load. That’s where OFDMA, or Orthogonal Frequency-Division Multiple Access, comes in. So what does it do exactly, and do you need it?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Albert Bassili</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revo Uninstaller Pro 5.0.0 released with lots of improvements]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178473</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/05/09/revo-uninstaller-pro-5-0-0-released-with-lots-of-improvements/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T16:56:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Revo Uninstaller Pro 5.0.0 was released on May 9, 2022. The new version of the popular software removal tool introduces support for several new features, including an uninstall history log, batch uninstalls […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Revo Uninstaller Pro 5.0.0 released with lots of improvements appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[arch-chroot and chroot don't do anything at all]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ulv1qm/archchroot_and_chroot_dont_do_anything_at_all/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ulv1qm/archchroot_and_chroot_dont_do_anything_at_all/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T16:24:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[hello! i was looking to migrate arch linux to another drive in a very specific manner (keep the contents of /home on one drive, move the rest, edit fstab to mount the home drive at /home) and after doing that, my bios still wouldn't recognize the new drive. i mounted the old drive's efi partition at /boot/efi on the new drive and, when i was going to regenerate grub, the error described in the title happened.
 i wanted to chroot into a temporary mount folder for the new drive (/mnt), but no matter what command i typed in (i tried bin/bash, /usr/bin/bash, /bin/bash, usr/bin/bash, even normal commands like ls didn't work, i tried -i) it returned: chroot: failed to run command "<command here>": No such file or directory . this would always happen, chroot would not ever do anything else than this aside from showing help
    submitted by    /u/sic--semper_tyrannis  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11: le app in background consumano batteria. Come bloccarle]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-11-le-app-in-background-consumano-batteria-Come-bloccarle_24488</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-11-le-app-in-background-consumano-batteria-Come-bloccarle_24488"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T16:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Qualunque programma in esecuzione in Windows utilizza le risorse macchina e contribuisce ad aumentare il consumo energetico. Nel caso dei portatili tenere avviati tanti programmi porta a una progressiva riduzione dell'autonomia della batteria.Premendo CTRL+MAIUSC+ESC per accedere al Task Manager, cliccando su Più dettagli quindi sulla scheda Processi, è possibile capire quali applicazioni stanno consumando più risorse.Il consiglio è quello di cliccare sulle intestazioni delle colonne CPU, Memoria, Disco, Rete, GPU per capire come ciascun programma va ad impattare sulle risorse disponibile. Cliccando sull'intestazione delle colonne, i valori possono essere ordinati in ordine decrescente.I processi indicati con una foglia verde sono anch'essi in esecuzione ma risultano al momento sospesi da parte di Windows con il preciso intento di risparmiare batteria.Tante app Microsoft Store, per loro stessa natura, restano caricate in background e occupano le risorse disponibili.
Come bloccare le app Microsoft Store in esecuzione in background
 Se si vuole evitare che singole applicazioni restino sempre in esecuzione mentre si sta lavorando su altri programmi, è sufficiente digitare Batteria nella casella di ricerca di Windows 11, selezionare Attiva o disattiva il risparmio della batteria, scorrere la finestra fino a trovare Utilizzo della batteria e cliccare su tale voce.

Windows 11 mostra quali applicazioni 'pesano' di più sulle risorse della macchina e sono contraddistinte da maggiori consumi energetici.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FUSE Patch Allows Non-Extending, Parallel Direct Writes For Better Performance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=FUSE-Parallel-Direct-Writes</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=FUSE-Parallel-Direct-Writes"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T16:14:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For those making use of FUSE user-space file-system capabilities, developer Dharmendra Singh has posted a patch to allow for non-extending parallel direct writes. In turn for threaded write scenarios this can mean a huge boost to performance...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Reasons You Should Switch to Google Phone on Android]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=800390</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/800390/5-reasons-you-should-switch-to-google-phone-on-android/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Android phones are, well, phones at the core. You may not think much about the phone app that came pre-installed, but like many things in Android, it can be changed. You should try the Google Phone app.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save 42% on SanDisk's Extreme PRO Portable SSD]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117337/save-42-on-sandisks-extreme-pro-portable-ssd/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117337/save-42-on-sandisks-extreme-pro-portable-ssd/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T15:56:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you’re running out of storage or just need to back up your files, a portable SSD may be the answer to your problems. But in an amazing example of why you should never buy storage at full price, SanDisk is currently selling its Extreme PRO SSD for 42% off.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch VBox guest Arch host : graphics controller/acceleration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ulu9wm/arch_vbox_guest_arch_host_graphics/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ulu9wm/arch_vbox_guest_arch_host_graphics/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T15:50:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking through https://wiki.archlinux.org/title/VirtualBox/Install_Arch_Linux_as_a_guest#Hardware_acceleration
 I don't see advice on which graphics controller to use.
    submitted by    /u/buzzwallard  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 Things You Didn’t Know Telegram for PC Could Do]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=479773</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15283376/useful-features-telegram-for-pc"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram for PC is so much more than a messaging app. The service boasts tons of features, some of which you might not even be aware of. With that in mind, in this guide we’ll explore six things you can do with Telegram for PC that have the potential of making your life much easier.
   

Content

1. Store Your Files for Free
2. Take Notes
3. Set Reminders
4. Send and Receive Gmail Messages
5. Edit Photos
6. Convert Images to Text
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Create and Manage a Telegram Channel
    
1. Store Your Files for Free
    
Telegram allows you to store an unlimited number of files for free on its cloud servers. You can store audio, videos, documents, and photos, though you’re limited to 2GB per file. Here’s how to set up cloud storage on Telegram:
... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Kanyoro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s the New Microsoft Outlook App for Windows and Mac]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=803960</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/803960/heres-the-new-microsoft-outlook-app-for-windows-and-mac/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T15:24:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has reportedly been working on an updated mail client for desktop platforms, based on the company’s Outlook service. Now we have our first look at the app in action.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moto Razr 3 Leak Teases a More "Modern" Foldable]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117333/moto-razr-3-leak-teases-a-more-modern-foldable/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117333/moto-razr-3-leak-teases-a-more-modern-foldable/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T15:22:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the weekend, we received our first look at Motorola’s 3rd generation folding phone, the Moto Razr 3. Leaked images tease a phone with dual primary cameras and an upgraded modern design.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers exploiting critical F5 BIG-IP bug, public exploits released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-exploiting-critical-f5-big-ip-bug-public-exploits-released/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-exploiting-critical-f5-big-ip-bug-public-exploits-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T15:20:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors have started massively exploiting the critical vulnerability tracked as CVE-2022-1388, which affects multiple versions of all F5 BIG-IP modules, to drop malicious payloads. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Ilascu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11: come aprire le opzioni del menu di avvio avanzato]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-11-come-aprire-le-opzioni-del-menu-di-avvio-avanzato_24487</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-11-come-aprire-le-opzioni-del-menu-di-avvio-avanzato_24487"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T15:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quando si hanno problemi con l'avvio di Windows o con il funzionamento del sistema operativo Microsoft uno degli strumenti che si rivela più utile è il menu di avvio avanzato.Il menu di avvio avanzato, conosciuto anche con il nome di Windows Recovery Environment (WinRE), non è cambiato con il rilascio di Windows 11: generalmente risiede in una partizione separata rispetto a quella in cui è installato il sistema operativo (partizione di ripristino).Le opzioni del menu di avvio avanzato permettono di avviare il sistema da supporti esterni, come una chiavetta USB, di risolvere i problemi al boot, di eseguire strumenti diagnostici, di accedere al BIOS UEFI, di ripristinare Windows da un'immagine di sistema, di disinstallare gli ultimi aggiornamenti applicati, di scegliere il sistema predefinito per l'avvio del PC se sono installati più sistemi operativi.Attraverso di esso si può accedere al menu impostazioni di avvio che consente, tra le altre cose, di avviare Windows in modalità provvisoria.


Come accedere al menu avvio avanzato in Windows 11
 Per aprire le opzioni del menu di avvio avanzato in Windows 11 si possono utilizzare diverse metodologie.1) Cliccare sul pulsante Start di Windows 11 quindi sul pulsante Arresta in basso a destra.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon's Chromecast Listing Is Very Strange]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117316/amazon-changes-chromecast-listing-to-pre-order-and-hints-at-new-feature/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117316/amazon-changes-chromecast-listing-to-pre-order-and-hints-at-new-feature/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T15:11:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Generally speaking, Amazon doesn’t sell Google-branded smart home devices. But the companies often make small (and short-lived) concessions, and today, the Chromecast with Google TV is finally available for pre-order on Amazon. Wait, why pre-order?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Truncate Text in Microsoft Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=798898</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/798898/how-to-truncate-text-in-microsoft-excel/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T15:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If text is a big part of the data in your spreadsheet, you may need to adjust it to fit properly. The TRUNC function in Microsoft Excel works only with numbers. So if you want to truncate text, here’s how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come aggiungere eventi calendario su Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/05/come-aggiungere-eventi-calendario-su.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/05/come-aggiungere-eventi-calendario-su.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T15:00:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ogni volta che ci viene fornito un appuntamento di lavoro, per una visita medica o per qualsiasi altra cosa possiamo utilizzare il nostro fedele computer con Windows per segnarcela e ricevere al momento opportuno un promemoria, senza dover utilizzare la vecchia agenda cartacea. Quello di aggiungere gli eventi calendario direttamente sul PC è una pratica molto comune negli uffici di tutto il...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cancellare Cache e Dati delle app su Android]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2016/12/cancellare-cache-e-dati-delle-app-su.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2016/12/cancellare-cache-e-dati-delle-app-su.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Le applicazioni di uno smartphone Android, a partire dalla prima volta che vengono avviate, creano una cache sulla memoria ed una serie di dati interni. Analizzando la grandezza della cache generata dalle app possiamo constatare che quasi tutte le applicazioni presentano un quantitativo di cache salvata elevato rispetto quanto ci si aspettava e rispetto a quando queste sono state scaricate.

 Per...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Processori Intel Alder Lake HX: 16 core fisici e PCIe Gen5]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Processori-Intel-Alder-Lake-HX-16-core-fisici-e-PCIe-Gen5_24486</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Processori-Intel-Alder-Lake-HX-16-core-fisici-e-PCIe-Gen5_24486"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T14:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I nuovi processori Intel di fascia alta per i notebook avanzati, le workstation mobili e i portatili gaming sono ormai dietro l'angolo. Gli Alder Lake HX rappresentano la punta di diamante di un'architettura spiccatamente scalabile che fino ad oggi era stata svelata per quanto riguarda le serie H, P e U.Con Alder Lake HX la società di Santa Clara presenta CPU ancora più veloci: si tratta dei primi processori ibridi dell'azienda guidata a Pat Gelsinger con 16 core e 24 thread.Stando alle informazioni sin qui trapelate, questa serie di processori utilizzerà un package BGA delle stesse dimensioni del socket LGA utilizzato nella serie desktop (45 x 37 mm); lo spessore viene ridotto da 4,4 a 2 mm.Una novità importante consiste nell'aggiunta del supporto per l'interfaccia PCIe 5.0 con il numero di piste che sale a 48. Alder Lake HX abbraccia inoltre le memorie DDR5 con profili XMP 3.0 e una nuova funzione chiamata Dynamic Memory Boost.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EU will enforce the Digital Markets Act in Spring 2023 and it could allow iOS users to install apps from third-party sources]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178469</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/05/09/eu-says-digital-markets-act-is-coming-in-spring-2023/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T14:14:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The European Union will enforce the Digital Markets Act (DMA) in 2023, and this could have a huge impact on Big Tech companies such as Apple, Google, Microsoft, Amazon, and Meta (Facebook). […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post EU will enforce the Digital Markets Act in Spring 2023 and it could allow iOS users to install apps from third-party sources appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do This Instead of Reheating for Better Tasting Coffee]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lifesavvy.com/128193/do-this-instead-of-reheating-for-better-tasting-coffee/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lifesavvy.com/128193/do-this-instead-of-reheating-for-better-tasting-coffee/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T14:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re an all-day sipper, or you just always forget about your morning cuppa until it’s cold, reheating coffee can really alter its flavor, and not for the better. While there are some tricks to minimize this loss of tastiness, some brewing experts recommend something else entirely.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shea Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best iPhone 13 Pro Max Cases of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=762823</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/762823/best-iphone-13-pro-max-case/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ve chosen the big iPhone 13 Pro Max, which means the laws of physics will show no mercy if you drop your phone. Luckily we’ve got a list of sizable covers that will keep your colossal cellphone safe and shiny.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sydney Butler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improved Vulkan Profiling Support For Raspberry Pi's V3DV Driver]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=RPi-V3DV-Pipe-Exec-Properties</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=RPi-V3DV-Pipe-Exec-Properties"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Merged today into Mesa 22.2 for Raspberry Pi's "V3DV" Vulkan driver is VK_KHR_pipeline_executable_properties support with this extension being used by the likes of RenderDoc for providing more insightful information when profiling Vulkan games and applications...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reazioni WhatsApp: cosa sono e come si usano]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Reazioni-WhatsApp-cosa-sono-e-come-si-usano_24485</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Reazioni-WhatsApp-cosa-sono-e-come-si-usano_24485"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T13:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gli sviluppatori di WhatsApp hanno confermato, con la pubblicazione di una nota ufficiale, l'introduzione di una novità che sarà certamente ben accetta dagli utenti.Si tratta delle reazioni WhatsApp ovvero la rappresentazione del 'sentimento' di ciascun utente alla pubblicazione di un messaggio, di una foto, di un video o di un qualunque allegato.Pensate a ciò che accade oggi sui gruppi WhatsApp: la pubblicazione di un messaggio spesso ingenera la comparsa di decine di emoji che vengono inviate in rapida sequenza dai vari utenti. Una prassi che genera confusione e fa perdere di vista la comunicazione importante a partire dalla quale hanno avuto inizio le reazioni degli utenti.Con notevole ritardo rispetto ad applicazioni come Telegram, Facebook Messenger, Instagram, agli stessi messaggi RCS supportati da Google (l'evoluzione degli SMS) e così via anche WhatsApp si arricchisce finalmente delle reazioni: le varie emoji verranno d'ora in avanti raggruppate in modo ordinato sotto ciascun messaggio, un po’ come si vede nell'immagine pubblicata di seguito.

L'utilizzo delle reazioni su WhatsApp è possibile solo assicurandosi di aver aggiornato il client di messaggistica all'ultima versione disponibile.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here's Everything Coming to Netflix the Week of May 9, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lifesavvy.com/128059/heres-everything-coming-to-netflix-the-week-of-may-9-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lifesavvy.com/128059/heres-everything-coming-to-netflix-the-week-of-may-9-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ve gotten through all of last week’s drops, and now, you need new content to consume. As usual, Netflix is coming through for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shea Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How do I get a nice startup screen?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ulr74w/how_do_i_get_a_nice_startup_screen/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ulr74w/how_do_i_get_a_nice_startup_screen/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T13:25:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I really want a nice startup animation like the one in Linux Mint instead of the startup dialog of arch. Like when it says: "starting version.x.x-arch" I don't need personal help just some links to sources would be cool. Also grub is fine just after that I want an animation.
 Thanks!
    submitted by    /u/purplesycamore  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Govee Glide Hexa Light Panels Review: Put These On Your Wall]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/116872/govee-glide-hexa-light-panels-review-put-these-on-your-wall/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/116872/govee-glide-hexa-light-panels-review-put-these-on-your-wall/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T13:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are several options available when it comes to ambient or accent lighting. And while we’ve tested several of Govee’s ever-expanding smart lights product lineup, the new Govee Glide Hexa Light Panels are some of the brightest and best.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 5 Biggest Misconceptions About Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=799924</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/799924/the-5-biggest-misconceptions-about-crypto/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world of crypto is complex and sometimes overwhelming. You may encounter a variety of differing arguments and opinions which can make it challenging to sort out the signal from the noise. Let’s sort out the five biggest misunderstandings when it comes to cryptocurrency.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Colin Brightfield</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cambiare nome al computer con Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>711|20220509150000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/reti-1448/cambiare-nome-computer-windows-11-711"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In una rete di computer non possiamo avere due postazioni di lavoro con lo stesso nome, ma anche per un computer casalingo potremmo volergli dare un nome diverso da quello attuale, magari perché lo abbiamo ereditato da altre persone e ci siamo stancati di vederlo chiamato in un certo modo.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TexStudio painfully slow open file dialog. What to do?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ulqjng/texstudio_painfully_slow_open_file_dialog_what_to/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ulqjng/texstudio_painfully_slow_open_file_dialog_what_to/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T12:52:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been having hard time with texstudio and texmaker recently. Open file dialog is laggy and freezes the window entirely. Here is video. Im Kile/dolphin/kate and other programms that require file dialogs nothing similar is observed. 
 In what direction should I dig?
    submitted by    /u/MaximZotov  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Discord showing blank screen]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ulqj5z/discord_showing_blank_screen/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ulqj5z/discord_showing_blank_screen/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T12:51:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discord doesnt seem to work for me, when i launch it, it gets stuck on a black screen.
 Starting from terminal, shows this.
 Discord 0.0.17
 Quitting secondary instance. 
 (discord:124163): Gtk-WARNING **: 20:49:37.376: Theme parsing error: main-dark.css:2470:0: Expected a valid selector
    submitted by    /u/theguysk21  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can I Use an Apple Watch Without an iPhone?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=802150</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/802150/can-i-use-an-apple-watch-without-an-iphone/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T12:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple sells the world’s most popular smartwatch, but it’s not a standalone product. If you don’t have an iPhone, you might be wondering what you can do with an Apple Watch or if you can use one at all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers are now hiding malware in Windows Event Logs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-are-now-hiding-malware-in-windows-event-logs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-are-now-hiding-malware-in-windows-event-logs/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T12:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security researchers have noticed a malicious campaign that used Windows event logs to store malware, a technique that has not been previously documented publicly for attacks in the wild. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Ilascu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple M1 Mesa Code Begins To Run glmark2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Apple-M1-Gallium3D-glmark2</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Apple-M1-Gallium3D-glmark2"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T11:57:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the Apple M1 Linux support is off to a great start and using Asahi Linux is offering good CPU performance and most functionality working to at least some degree, the biggest blocker remaining is getting the Apple M1 3D graphics working. The latest progress on that front is the Mesa code working to begin correctly render glmark2, a basic OpenGL / GLES benchmark...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is 5G, and How Fast Is It?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=340002</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/340002/what-is-5g-and-how-fast-will-it-be/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to mobile carriers, it’s the latest, greatest thing: 5G, a fifth-generation wireless standard that is said to rival home internet speeds under ideal circumstances. Just how fast is it—and does it live up to the hype? We’ll take a look.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QEMU >= 7.0.0 changes split package setup]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ulodad/qemu_700_changes_split_package_setup/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ulodad/qemu_700_changes_split_package_setup/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T10:42:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/my_coll_cont_bot  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QEMU >= 7.0.0 changes split package setup]]></title>
        <id>tag:archlinux.org,2022-05-09:/news/qemu-700-changes-split-package-setup/</id>
        <link href="https://archlinux.org/news/qemu-700-changes-split-package-setup/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T10:35:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the update to qemu 7.0.0 the package has been turned into a more
fine grained split package utilizing meta packages.
The qemu package is now virtually provided by the meta packages
  qemu-base, qemu-desktop and qemu-full.
The functionality of qemu prior to 7.0.0 is replaced by
  qemu-desktop
The functionality of qemu-headless is replaced by
  qemu-base
The functionality of qemu-arch-extra and qemu-headless-arch-extra
  is replaced by qemu-emulators-full
The meta package qemu-full provides all QEMU related
  packages (excluding qemu-guest-agent)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Runge</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bug e ricompense: come funzionano le piattaforme di Bug Bounty]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Bug-e-ricompense-come-funzionano-le-piattaforme-di-Bug-Bounty_24484</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Bug-e-ricompense-come-funzionano-le-piattaforme-di-Bug-Bounty_24484"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T10:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Con il passare del tempo, sempre più società hanno spostato le proprie attività online. Così come sono nate nuove aziende che operano esclusivamente nel campo digitale. Tutto ciò ha portato alla creazione di innumerevoli nuove applicazioni, software, programmi, giochi, servizi, che oggi vengono usati da miliardi di persone in tutto il pianeta.Ovviamente la perfezione non esiste: tutti questi nuovi software e servizi vengono sviluppati da esseri umani. Motivo per il quale, spesso e volentieri, nascondono errori e bug di ogni genere. Al giorno d'oggi, i bug nella maggior parte dei casi creano problemi durante l'uso di un software complicando l'utilizzo da parte degli utenti.In altri casi invece, alcuni bug possono diventare delle vulnerabilità di sicurezza e venire sfruttati da gruppi di hacker malintenzionati. In entrambi i casi però, i bug si rivelano come un costo per l’azienda: un danno economico, ma anche di immagine.
L'importanza dell'attività di bug hunting
 Considerati tutti i problemi legati alla presenza dei bug nel software, diventa facile capire come mai le aziende investano molte risorse nel campo del bug hunting cioè sulla ricerca e risoluzione dei bug.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD Radeon ProRender Adds Support For Khronos' ANARI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Radeon-ProRender-ANARI</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Radeon-ProRender-ANARI"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T10:12:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Radeon ProRender as AMD's physically-based rendering engine has added support for The Khronos Group's ANARI analytical rendering interface for 3D data visualizations...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KDE Plasma 5.25's Exciting Improvements For KWin, Continued Wayland Optimizations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=KDE-Plasma-5.25-KWin</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=KDE-Plasma-5.25-KWin"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T09:59:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Plasma 5.25 now under a soft feature freeze ahead of its official release next month, KDE developers are focusing on bug fixing as well as talking more about all of the changes they managed to land this cycle...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD Zen 4 IBS Extensions Under Review For Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMD-Zen-4-IBS-Linux</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMD-Zen-4-IBS-Linux"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T09:40:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Upcoming AMD Zen 4 processors are bringing improvements to their Instruction-Based Sampling (IBS) capabilities that can be utilized by Linux's wonderful perf utility and subsystem...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recuperare Product Key Windows 10]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Recuperare-Product-Key-Windows-10_24483</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Recuperare-Product-Key-Windows-10_24483"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T09:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quando si installa Windows 10 o 11 spesso non è più neppure necessario digitare un codice Product Key.Ma cos'è il Product Key? Traducibile in italiano con il termine Chiave prodotto, il Product Key è un codice alfanumerico che identifica in modo univoco un software. Ricordiamo che possedere un Product Key non implica disporre di una licenza.Una licenza per usare Windows, Office o altri software si ottiene se il Product Key è acquisito mediante canali legittimi. Capita spesso di imbattersi online in venditori senza scrupoli che commercializzano Product Key rubati oppure provenienti da contratti a volume che le aziende hanno stipulato con Microsoft.Quei codici Product Key potrebbero funzionare ovvero permettere l'attivazione di Windows per brevi periodi o finestre temporali più lunghe ma in ogni caso espongono a rischi (anche sul piano legale) i soggetti che li utilizzano. Abbiamo visto dove trovare le migliori offerte software 2022 tra cui anche quelle sui sistemi operativi come Windows 10 e Windows 11.
Niente Product Key: Windows 10 è attivato con una licenza digitale
 In vista dell'aggiornamento a Windows 11 oppure per semplici finalità di backup spesso si ha l'esigenza di recuperare il Product Key di Windows 10.Innanzi tutto diciamo che il modo migliore per non avere problemi con le licenze di Windows è legare l'installazione del sistema operativo con il proprio account utente Microsoft.Se Windows 10 o Windows 11 sono attivati (e lo si può verificare digitando Impostazioni attivazione nella casella di ricerca del sistema operativo, il consiglio è quello di digitare Gestisci il tuo account, cliccare su Le tue info nella colonna di sinistra e assicurarsi di usare un account amministratore.Se sotto il nome dell'account amministratore compare un indirizzo email, significa che si sta già usando un account utente Microsoft per accedere a Windows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Costa Rica declares national emergency after Conti ransomware attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/costa-rica-declares-national-emergency-after-conti-ransomware-attacks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/costa-rica-declares-national-emergency-after-conti-ransomware-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T07:53:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Costa Rican President Rodrigo Chaves has declared a national emergency following cyber attacks from Conti ransomware group. BleepingComputer also observed Conti published most of the 672 GB dump that appears to contain data belonging to the Costa Rican government agencies. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ax Sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fresh booting arch, error- [Timed out waiting for device /dev/disk/by-uuid/"some uuid which does not match with any current partition"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ull4di/fresh_booting_arch_error_timed_out_waiting_for/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ull4di/fresh_booting_arch_error_timed_out_waiting_for/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T06:43:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whole error:
 [Timed out waiting for device /dev/disk/by-uuid/"some uuid which does not match with any current partition" [DEPEND] Dependency failed for File system Check on /dev/disk/by-uuid/"that same UUID"
 [DEPEND] Dependency failed for /boot/efi [DEPEND] Dependency failed for Local File System.
 Description: Just installed arch on main Hardware, after u mounting, i rebooted my system, and it shows this error after booting into arch
    submitted by    /u/Menace_g  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recover Options and Suggestions - What tools do you use?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ull43r/recover_options_and_suggestions_what_tools_do_you/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ull43r/recover_options_and_suggestions_what_tools_do_you/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T06:42:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kind of a noob question here.
 I've been toying around with a few different recovery scenarios, such as -
 What if an update breaks my install? What it's related to the BIOS/EFI?
 What would I do should I be stuck without a USB drive? (not terribly likely)
 What could I use for relatively stable options?
 **************************************************************
 My first inclination is to simply grab the Archinstaller USB and just repair what my be broken or mis-configured.
 Then I got to thinking about the scenarios above. I'm considering using a secondary boot partition with something like GRML installed, or a custom Arch installation with some sane defaults, such as an LTS kernel and limited to a few packages that I might want.
 Maybe this is overkill. I'd be happy setting up a few options, just to see whether I like any particular approach. Again, I veer toward using the Arch ISO/or usb disk, although I'd like to test other options, and concede that my system is using the latest packages and kernel.
 Do you have any suggestions for options to try, or suggestions for an Arch Recovery Partition? Or Custom Live USB/CD?
 Do any solutions appear particularly interesting and fun to try?
    submitted by    /u/RandomXUsr  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[i have accidentally deleted the the EFI system partition and i cant boot to my system.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ulkuho/i_have_accidentally_deleted_the_the_efi_system/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ulkuho/i_have_accidentally_deleted_the_the_efi_system/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T06:22:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[well my question is in the title so yea please help
 solved thanks for all of your replies
    submitted by    /u/killer7strike  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[gdm] Gnome Wayland has gone missing after update yesterday]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ulkqpa/gdm_gnome_wayland_has_gone_missing_after_update/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ulkqpa/gdm_gnome_wayland_has_gone_missing_after_update/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T06:14:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been using Gnome Wayland on my System76 Gazelle for a month or so and suddenly after the update yesterday gnome switched to xorg and gdm only has gnome and gnome classic options, both of which are using xorg.
 One weird thing is that in gdm is says Gnome as opposed to saying Gnome on Xorg.
 I have checked /usr/share/xsessions, it has four desktop files, one for gnome, one for gnome classic for both the xorg and wayland version.
 As for settings,
 /etc/gdm/custom.conf still has WaylandEnable=false commented out so I'm not sure what could be causing this.
    submitted by    /u/frustrated-nerd  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lose connection on public WiFi hotspot who require login page]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uljyoh/lose_connection_on_public_wifi_hotspot_who/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uljyoh/lose_connection_on_public_wifi_hotspot_who/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T05:19:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, 
 I am using a public hotspot that require me to sign in from a login page in order to access internet. I did it by using Firefox, however every 5 minutes I am disconnected and I have to login again from Firefox. Is there a way to maintain the connection ? I don't even know if the problem come from the way I am connecting or from the hotspot itself
    submitted by    /u/TeazYou  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Opinion: No One needs a screenshot tool in a web browser]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178461</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/05/09/opinion-no-one-needs-a-screenshot-tool-in-a-web-browser/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T04:59:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many modern web browsers support screenshot functionality to capture screenshots without leaving the browser, but are these tools really needed? Firefox users right-click on a page to select the "take screenshot" feature […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Opinion: No One needs a screenshot tool in a web browser appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to turn on laptop screen when lid is opened?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ulhr4h/how_to_turn_on_laptop_screen_when_lid_is_opened/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ulhr4h/how_to_turn_on_laptop_screen_when_lid_is_opened/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T03:01:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey all, I've been using a setup with dwm where when I close the slock runs to lock the screen. The only issue I've been having that's been bugging me is that when I open the lid, the screen is still off instead of turning on and showing the slock program. I need to touch the trackpoint or touchpad for the screen to light up. Anyone have any sort of advice for this?
    submitted by    /u/Distinct-Stranger931  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BTRFS Question]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ulh3hs/btrfs_question/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ulh3hs/btrfs_question/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T02:23:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In ArchWiki about BTRFS there is information about compression.. One of em talking about re compressing file system and this is the command
 btrfs filesystem defragment -r -v -czstd /
 However in the wiki there is no mention about compression level that ZSTD have and idk how pass the level.. if i want to use level 15 of compression i just need to add
 compress=zstd:15
 to the /etc/fstab 
 but seems like the same method doesnt work for re compressing the file system
 btrfs filesystem defragment -r -v -czstd:15 /
 btrfs filesystem defragment -r -v -czstd -level=15 / 
 or any other command i could think of it just doesnt work
 Searching on search engine doesnt give me some result either
 Thx for the help
    submitted by    /u/JnZann  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Steam won't start after updating nvidia drivers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ules5p/steam_wont_start_after_updating_nvidia_drivers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ules5p/steam_wont_start_after_updating_nvidia_drivers/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T00:11:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Asking for a friend I'm currently helping.
 https://i.imgur.com/GgUYe1u.png
 Steam gives this error when trying to run after updating nvidia drivers, after looking at other forum posts and checking the nvidia package versions they're all matching.
 They have a GT 1030 if that helps.
    submitted by    /u/ChickenPlenty  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cosa fare quando Chrome impedisce il download dei file eseguibili]]></title>
        <id>3560|20220509000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/browser-455/cosa-fare-quando-chrome-impedisce-download-file-eseguibili-3560"/>
        <updated>2022-05-08T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome ha un suo controllo sul download dei file eseguibili e, di solito, segnala e blocca quelli per lui strani e sospetti. In genere però l’utente ha la possibilità di scaricarli lo stesso, o conservarli, a seconda del messaggio o delle opzioni che compaiono. Questa volta però avevo un messaggio diverso nel mio computer con Windows 11, Operazione non riuscita. Blocca e non potevo fare altro se non aprire una pagina web con delle inutili Ulteriori informazioni.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux 5.18-rc6 Released - Linux 5.18 Is Looking "Quite Well-Behaved"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.18-rc6</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.18-rc6"/>
        <updated>2022-05-08T21:24:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linus Torvalds just released Linux 5.18-rc6 as the latest weekly release candidate ahead of the Linux 5.18 stable release expected later in May...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[efly: A Graphical Live Medium for Arch Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ulbi16/efly_a_graphical_live_medium_for_arch_linux/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ulbi16/efly_a_graphical_live_medium_for_arch_linux/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-08T21:19:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[i've been wanting to build a graphical live medium for arch linux for a long time. and i finally got around to creating one. it contains the exact same packages as the standard arch iso. and in addition it boots directly into a xfce desktop with a bunch of graphical tools at your disposal (web browser, text editor, etc.).
 use cases:
  
install arch linux according to official installation guide.
 a rescue system to fix a broken linux install (f.x. fix the bootloader after a defective kernel upgrade).
 a portable linux system for your bunch of keys. ready-to-use wherever you go.
  
there is a github repo with all the required data. you can build (and run) it yourself:
  sudo pacman -S archiso git clone https://github.com/flying-dude/efly sudo mkarchiso -v efly-live run_archiso -i out/efly-linux-2022.05.08-x86_64.iso 
 i'd highly appreciate some feedback, if the produced iso image works properly on your system.
 there is some stuff planned to be added to the live system. an important one is configuring it with proper fan control for the cpu. currently the fan just runs with high speed on my system regardless of cpu usage.
    submitted by    /u/flying-dude  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Charge Your Android Phone as Fast as Possible]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=724685</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/724685/how-to-charge-your-android-phone-as-fast-as-possible/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-08T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even the Android phones with the best battery life barely make it two days on a charge. When your phone is dead, you don’t want to wait forever to top it off. Here’s how to charge your phone in the quickest possible way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Check your gems: RubyGems fixes unauthorized package takeover bug]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/check-your-gems-rubygems-fixes-unauthorized-package-takeover-bug/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/check-your-gems-rubygems-fixes-unauthorized-package-takeover-bug/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-08T20:59:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The RubyGems package repository has fixed a critical vulnerability that would allow anyone to unpublish ("yank") certain Ruby packages from the repository and republish their tainted or malicious versions with the same file names and version numbers. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ax Sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Changing to Arch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ulazzf/changing_to_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ulazzf/changing_to_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-08T20:56:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[i have an minimal Debian (sid) install and i once installed arch on a virtual machine (then did nothing with it).
 I want to change to arch, should i be worried about hardware comp and other stuff?
 i know that i will need to basicly relearn the package manager but that will be no problem. 
 once i downloaded a arch based distro (don't remember wich) and said that i need special firmware for my in board ethernet card (Broadcom NetLink BCM57788) and didn't find it so i just went back to debian-kde at the time.
 also can i use my /home directory or is there something special about it on arch? also hold my xorg and other config files. 
 (i use dwm and startx)
 thanks and sorry for my english.
    submitted by    /u/Alexevier1  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Black screen on resume from hibernation after update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ulag5s/black_screen_on_resume_from_hibernation_after/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ulag5s/black_screen_on_resume_from_hibernation_after/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-08T20:29:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few months ago I updated my desktop system and hibernation stopped working. It had been working fine for a while. The computer hibernates but when attempting to resume, the screen is black and I'm fairly certain that the computer is not registering input or running any resumed programs.
 I've gone through this debugging guide and all the test modes work as expected. Suspending the system works as well. It only seems to be proper hibernation that doesn't work.
 I tried switching over to the LTS kernel but the issue persists. It used to work so this isn't a hardware issue.
 What other things can be done to troubleshoot this issue?
    submitted by    /u/Hipponomics  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Chrome Will Automatically Change Your Stolen Passwords]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117191/google-chrome-will-automatically-change-your-stolen-passwords/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117191/google-chrome-will-automatically-change-your-stolen-passwords/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-08T20:04:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You should really change your passwords after a data breach. But digging through a website’s settings to update your password is often harder than it should be. That’s why Chrome for Android’s latest feature automates the password replacement process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PCIe 6.0: What’s New, and When Can You Get It?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=786991</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/786991/pcie-6.0-whats-new-and-when-can-you-get-it/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-08T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes the technology industry moves too fast. We’ve only started kicking into gear with PCIe 4.0 in consumer products, PCIe 5.0 is just barely rolling out, and already PCIe 6.0 is on its way. Here’s what you can expect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Paul</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bluetooth off on boot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ul9pbp/bluetooth_off_on_boot/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ul9pbp/bluetooth_off_on_boot/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-08T19:54:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a recent update, my Bluetooth shows off in Gnome on boot, whereas previously it would be switched on at boot. If I check sysctl, it shows the Bluetooth service is running, but I need to activate it in Gnome before I can use any Bluetooth devices. 
 Would anyone be able to provide a suggestion to have this return to automatically switched on at boot?
    submitted by    /u/esceebee  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How can I see Xorg shutdown logs?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ul9eyt/how_can_i_see_xorg_shutdown_logs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ul9eyt/how_can_i_see_xorg_shutdown_logs/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-08T19:40:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whenever I turn off my computer, Xorg spits out a bunch of errors for a moment before the computer turns off. How can I save/see these logs? I have already tried /var/log/ as well as ~/.local/share/.
    submitted by    /u/Pay08  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Efficiently Share or Send Google Docs via Email]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=246190</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/8139054/send-google-docs-via-email"/>
        <updated>2022-05-08T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These days in the professional world, there are plenty of ways for people to communicate with one another, such as on LinkedIn or Slack. However, despite being one of the oldest means of communication on the Internet, the trusty email stays one of the top ways for professionals to discuss matters.
    
If you’re an avid Google Docs user, you may want to know how to send a Google Doc by email. In truth, there are multiple ways to email a Google document and share it with others. We discuss all of them below.
   

Content

As an Invitation
As a Link
As an Attachment
Within the Email Body

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Edit Google Docs: The Best Tips You Need to Know
    
As an Invitation
    
If you’d like to simply send... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Crystal Crowder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Since last few reboots... no apps seem to show at my default language. How can I fix this?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ul8xmh/since_last_few_reboots_no_apps_seem_to_show_at_my/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ul8xmh/since_last_few_reboots_no_apps_seem_to_show_at_my/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-08T19:16:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Operating System: Arch Linux KDE Plasma Version: 5.24.5 KDE Frameworks Version: 5.93.0 Qt Version: 5.15.3 Kernel Version: 5.17.5-zen1-1-zen (64-bit) Graphics Platform: Wayland Processors: 8 × AMD Ryzen 5 2500U with Radeon Vega Mobile Gfx Memory: 7.4 GiB of RAM Graphics Processor: AMD Radeon Vega 8 Graphics 
    submitted by    /u/anotheruser123123  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Find, Edit, and Delete Your Amazon Feedback]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=798993</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/798993/find-edit-delete-amazon-feedback/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-08T19:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone has a change of heart now and then. Luckily, Amazon has all your order reviews saved, so you can quickly find, edit, and delete them if you want. You can access it through Amazon’s website and the mobile app.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Long delay during boot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ul8ax3/long_delay_during_boot/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ul8ax3/long_delay_during_boot/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-08T18:46:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I noticed that there is a ~30s delay where not much seems to happen during bootup.
 systemd-analyze says
 Startup finished in 3.680s (kernel) + 33.896s (userspace) = 37.576s graphical.target reached after 33.895s in userspace 
 systemd-analyze blame says
 26.258s dev-nvme0n1p1.device 3.691s systemd-modules-load.service 3.353s systemd-random-seed.service 3.281s netctl@tenging.service 2.773s systemd-journal-flush.service 2.590s systemd-udevd.service 1.534s mnt-bigboi.mount 1.223s lvm2-monitor.service 123ms user@1000.service 113ms systemd-udev-trigger.service 112ms systemd-tmpfiles-setup-dev.service 78ms mnt-fruit.mount 65ms libvirtd.service 58ms systemd-journald.service 47ms swapfile.swap 47ms systemd-tmpfiles-setup.service 43ms mnt-windos.mount 34ms polkit.service 27ms systemd-logind.servic…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Problem with internal wifi card after connecting second one]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ul7diw/problem_with_internal_wifi_card_after_connecting/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ul7diw/problem_with_internal_wifi_card_after_connecting/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-08T18:02:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I connected second wifi card to my HP laptop to see it is any better than internal one, after unplugging usb card i can't connect to internet using internal card but usb card can connect to internet. Internal card can see wifi networks and connect to them and ping devices in local network.
    submitted by    /u/LepszaNazwax  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Turn Off Video Captions on Facebook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=798642</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/798642/turn-off-captions-on-facebook/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-08T18:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Facebook displays captions on its videos to help you follow the content, but if you don’t need them, they can be annoying. Here’s how you can disable the captions on Facebook videos on desktop, iPhone, and iPad.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Check Out This Working Fisher-Price Xbox Controller Mod]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117228/check-out-this-working-fisher-price-xbox-controller-mod/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117228/check-out-this-working-fisher-price-xbox-controller-mod/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-08T18:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fisher-Price baby toys are good for many things, but did you ever think one could be turned into a working Xbox controller? The popular modder and Twitch streamer Dylan “Rudeism” Beck did precisely that, then played Tony Hawk and Elden Ring with it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VAAPI Firefox 100]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ul74bz/vaapi_firefox_100/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ul74bz/vaapi_firefox_100/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-08T17:50:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, I installed Firefox 100 but VAAPI doesn't work. What are the necessary flags to change to get it works ?
    submitted by    /u/Spare_Prize1148  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia GBM Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ul73gn/nvidia_gbm_support/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ul73gn/nvidia_gbm_support/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-08T17:49:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is there package I need to install to enable GBM Support for KDE Nvidia Wayland? Both the archwiki and the KDE site mention that for Nvidia driver version 510, EGL is no longer required, but egl-wayland seems to be installed and a dependency for the nvidia-utils package. 
 Is that package needed, and if it's installed, am i still using the less compatible EGL?
    submitted by    /u/clockwork2011  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can't connect to internet via LAN to USB adapter in Arch Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ul6mky/cant_connect_to_internet_via_lan_to_usb_adapter/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ul6mky/cant_connect_to_internet_via_lan_to_usb_adapter/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-08T17:26:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I bought a LAN to USB adapter, because i got some issues with my LAN port. I can't connect to net via adapter. The IP link command shows the presence of the usb adapter
 I tried 
  ifconfig link net-interface-id up 
 And typed  dhcpcd 
 Also typed  dhcpcd with net-interface-id 
 Nothing works Details of the product can be found here.
 My network detects it, but can't connect to it
    submitted by    /u/Section_Disastrous  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Which iPhones Have Face ID?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=802077</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/802077/which-iphones-have-face-id/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-08T17:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[iPhones that use Face ID have a different physical design than iPhones with Touch ID, and it can determine how you use features on your phone. Here’s how to tell the difference—and a list of which iPhone models use Face ID.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Installing ARCH on 2018 macbook air]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ul5l5h/installing_arch_on_2018_macbook_air/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ul5l5h/installing_arch_on_2018_macbook_air/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-08T16:37:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey guys, I wanted to know if there is anyone here, who has any experience in installing arch on macs, especially macs with T2 chip inside, because I was thinking of installing Arch on my macbook air, and I am kinda afraid of drivers not working, performance hits etc. Also would love to know how difficult is to roll back to macOS. I was looking on the internet but could not find a single person who has done it.
    submitted by    /u/itisntmemario  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rockchip VOP2 DRM Driver Coming To Linux 5.19 For Display Support With Newer SoCs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Rockchip-VOP2-Linux-5.19</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Rockchip-VOP2-Linux-5.19"/>
        <updated>2022-05-08T16:36:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In addition to the ASpeed AST2600 DisplayPort support sent in as part of this week's drm-misc-next updates intended for Linux 5.19, another prominent addition worthy of its own article is the Rockchip VOP2 display driver being mainlined...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploits created for critical F5 BIG-IP flaw, install patch immediately]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/exploits-created-for-critical-f5-big-ip-flaw-install-patch-immediately/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/exploits-created-for-critical-f5-big-ip-flaw-install-patch-immediately/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-08T16:35:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security researchers are warning F5 BIG-IP admins to immediately install the latest security updates after creating exploits for a recently disclosed critical CVE-2022-1388 remote code execution vulnerability. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple's Latest Patent Looks Like a Microsoft Surface Book]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117221/apples-latest-patent-looks-like-a-microsoft-surface-book/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117221/apples-latest-patent-looks-like-a-microsoft-surface-book/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-08T16:34:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get ready, because Apple may “invent” the decade-old Microsoft Surface concept. The company’s latest patent describes a 2-in-1 laptop with a detachable screen. Notably, this device seems to use a macOS-like UI, at least when it’s docked.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is the status of the python-wxpython package]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ul5i6b/what_is_the_status_of_the_pythonwxpython_package/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ul5i6b/what_is_the_status_of_the_pythonwxpython_package/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-08T16:33:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am trying to use a python app that is not packaged for Arch, but it keeps crashing with some hard to trace errors. The app requires wxpython, which I have installed the python-wxpython. I think the crash is happening because the out of date python-wxpython package is not compatible with Python 3.10 (see this bug report). I thought about installing the python-wxpython-dev package from the AUR, but before I do that, I wanted to know:
 Is there a reason for the python-wxpython package being held back?
    submitted by    /u/AppointmentNearby161  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch Dualboot not Working]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ul5681/arch_dualboot_not_working/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ul5681/arch_dualboot_not_working/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-08T16:17:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[i'm trying to dualboot arch and Windows 11 on my MSI GF65 Thin Laptop , but when i finish the install GRUB doesn't appear, Windows does.
 (i never used or even sucessfully installed arch)
 I tried it all, disabled secure boot from BIOS, used the custom GUI install, followed allong multiple YT guides and no success!
    submitted by    /u/prtlw_  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use TikTok on a Chromebook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=802694</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/802694/how-to-use-tiktok-on-a-chromebook/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-08T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TikTok is very much designed to be experienced on a vertical smartphone display. However, you don’t have to just use your iPhone or Android phone. We’ll show you how to use TikTok on a Chromebook.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New install script]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ul4asn/new_install_script/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ul4asn/new_install_script/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-08T15:36:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So to use the new install script, do I have to use the new May ISO?
    submitted by    /u/PortalToTheWeekend  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Caramel credit card stealing service is growing in popularity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/caramel-credit-card-stealing-service-is-growing-in-popularity/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/caramel-credit-card-stealing-service-is-growing-in-popularity/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-08T15:06:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A credit card stealing service is growing in popularity, allowing any low-skilled threat actors an easy and automated way to get started in the world of financial fraud. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[15 Time Tracking Apps For Remote Workers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/?p=55041</id>
        <link href="https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/best-time-tracking-apps/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-08T15:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're working with remote teams, one of the tools that become almost inevitable is the time tracking app. The tool allows you to track the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hongkiat Lim</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Graph in Google Slides]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=796577</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/796577/create-a-graph-in-google-slides/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-08T15:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A chart or graph is a terrific way to show a snapshot of your data. So when you couple a chart with another visual tool like Google Slides, you can create the perfect presentation of data to your audience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Play now blocks paid app downloads, updates in Russia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/google/google-play-now-blocks-paid-app-downloads-updates-in-russia/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/google/google-play-now-blocks-paid-app-downloads-updates-in-russia/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-08T14:11:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google is now blocking Russian users and developers from downloading or updating paid applications from the Google Play Store due to sanctions, starting Thursday.  [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Streaming Services of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=748781</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/748781/best-streaming-services/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-08T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The recent proliferation of streaming services can feel overwhelming, with each touting its exclusive offerings and superior value. But different outlets serve different viewing habits. Our top picks will help you choose which service is worth the monthly subscription fee.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Bell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Plex has not read permissions to my home directory, so I added "plex" user to my user group. Then I gave my user group the read permissions to my home dir. Then I restarted plex server. Why doesn't it work? It works ONLY IF I also add "other user" read permission to my home dir. Why?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ul20pg/plex_has_not_read_permissions_to_my_home/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ul20pg/plex_has_not_read_permissions_to_my_home/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-08T13:43:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shouldn't be necessary to only give group permission to my home dir and then add plex user to my user group? Why doesn't it work?
    submitted by    /u/allexj  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>