<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-07-07T02:17:14.525Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Need help with getting Surround Sound to work on a USB headset.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vt5v74/need_help_with_getting_surround_sound_to_work_on/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vt5v74/need_help_with_getting_surround_sound_to_work_on/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-07T01:05:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Friend recently bought a 7.1 Surround Sound USB headset, however it does not want to play in anything more than 2 channels, if he tries to use 5.1 in the Volume Control for Pulseaudio, it makes a really loud buzzing noise, we've spent a while trying to figure out how to get 7.1 to work but have found no solutions, any potential solutions have not worked at all.
    submitted by    /u/Wandering_Phoenix  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[libvirt-qemu cannot access files in my home directory]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vt5inc/libvirtqemu_cannot_access_files_in_my_home/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vt5inc/libvirtqemu_cannot_access_files_in_my_home/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-07T00:49:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm trying to add a shared folder to one of my guests but libvirt cannot access any directory or file inside my home directory, it works if the directory is anywhere else. Changing permissions doesn't work, changing ownership of files doesn't work either. Anyone knows how I can alter this behavior?
    submitted by    /u/Secure_Eye5090  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Which package owns/installs /etc/systemd/system/display-manager.service symlink?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vt52gw/which_package_ownsinstalls/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vt52gw/which_package_ownsinstalls/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-07T00:27:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am using gdm now, hence it points to /usr/lib/systemd/system/gdm.service. But pacman -Qo display-manager.service returns nothing, with or without the full path. And I didn't find a package that contains an install script setting up that link. There is no pacman hooks/scripts in /usr/share/libalpm/ for this either. Does anybody know who did it?
    submitted by    /u/notnullnone  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Instagram Not Working? Here Are 14 Ways to Fix it]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=post-ideas&amp;p=317349</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/12893117/fix-instagram-not-working"/>
        <updated>2022-07-07T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Instagram is the dominant photo-sharing platform on the Internet and has become the sole social media site used by people who prefer to express themselves with pictures rather than words. But what do you do when Instagram goes down? Here we show you the main reasons for Instagram not working and how you can fix it.
   

Content

1. Restart Phone and Router
2. Is Instagram Down?
3. Update Instagram
4. Clear App Data and Cache (Android)
5. Offload Instagram App (iPhone)
6. Uninstall and Reinstall Instagram
7. Reinstall Older Version of Instagram (Android Only)
8. Enable Permissions for Instagram 
9. Turn Off VPN
10. Ensure Background Data Is Not Restricted (Android) 
11. Check Your Phone's Storage
12. Log Out of Your Account
13. Check Common Error Messages and Known Issues
14. Try a Different Device or Tool
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mehvish Mushtaq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Systemd Creator Lands At Microsoft]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Systemd-Creator-Microsoft</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Systemd-Creator-Microsoft"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday's surprise was that Lennart Poettering quietly had left Red Hat following a decade and a half there leading PulseAudio among other projects and ultimately going on to start systemd that has fundamentally reshaped modern Linux distributions. It turns out he had joined Microsoft and continuing his work on systemd...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 Subsystem for Android can now use VPN-assigned IPs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-subsystem-for-android-can-now-use-vpn-assigned-ips/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-subsystem-for-android-can-now-use-vpn-assigned-ips/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T22:40:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[​Microsoft has released an update for the Windows Subsystem for Android, allowing all Windows 11 Insiders to use their VPN's IP address with Android apps. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel Begins Open-Source Graphics Driver Preparations For Meteor Lake]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-Meteor-Lake-IGC</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-Meteor-Lake-IGC"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T22:11:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In addition to Intel's open-source Linux graphics driver developers being very busy rounding out their DG2/Alchemist enablement patches, beginning to mainline "Ponte Vecchio" work starting with Linux 5.20, and having already done the bit of enablement for Raptor Lake graphics that is predominantly based on existing Alder Lake, they have also started their Meteor Lake bring-up...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come creare con DiskGenius una copia del proprio sistema operativo da usare con VirtualBox o VMware]]></title>
        <id>3612|20220707000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/windows-10/come-creare-diskgenius-copia-sistema-operativo-usare-virtualbox-vmware-3612"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ci sono modifiche del sistema operativo, o programmi, che ci piacerebbe provare ma ci blocchiamo prima di farlo perché potremmo fare “danni”, la soluzione migliore per questo tipo di prova è una macchina virtuale, ancora meglio se è una copia del nostro sistema operativo reale. DiskGenius, disponibile anche in versione portable e freeware dalle funzioni ridotte, permette di creare una copia, “Hot” del vostro sistema operativo direttamente dal sistema attivo.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fix a Windows Infinite Reboot Loop Problem]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=495124</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15417167/fix-windows-infinite-reboot-loop-problem"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After starting your Windows device, you may occasionally run into an infinite reboot loop issue (also called “infinite boot loop”). The startup logo seems stuck on a black screen with a small circle going round and round. It’s a fairly common problem in Windows, old and new versions alike.
    
If you’re unable to get past the login screen, try one of the following solutions for Windows 10 and 11.
   

Content

What is the Infinite Reboot Loop Error?
1. Using Advanced Troubleshooting Options in Safe Mode
2. Fix Driver Validity Issues Using Sigverif
3. Remove Lock Screen Picture and Screensaver During Startup
4. Remove Unwanted Third-Party Apps from Startup Programs Sequence
5. Uninstall Bloat
6. Clean Install Windows 
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Boot to Safe Mode in Windows
    
What is the Infinite Reboot Loop Error?
   ... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sayak Boral</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Input not supported” after waking pc up from sleep]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vt0onr/input_not_supported_after_waking_pc_up_from_sleep/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vt0onr/input_not_supported_after_waking_pc_up_from_sleep/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T21:10:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m using KDE Plasma on a fresh Arch install and everytime the pc goes into a sleep state, I get an “input not supported” error on my monitor. I am using an nvidia card with the proprietary drivers installed, and I am using HDMI. Any way to fix this?
    submitted by    /u/Unknown_Rift  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can You Connect Bluetooth Headphones to the Xbox Series X|S?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=742895</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/742895/can-you-connect-bluetooth-headphones-to-the-xbox-series-x-s/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gaming headsets deliver immersive audio while allowing you to use your voice to communicate with other players. Wireless headsets offer a degree of freedom that wired ones can’t match, but most require a dedicated USB dongle to ditch the cable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why the iPhone’s Secure New Lockdown Mode Isn’t for You]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=816509</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/816509/why-the-iphones-secure-new-lockdown-mode-isnt-for-you/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T20:51:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Digital security is always difficult, but most people don’t have to worry about being targeted with the latest spyware. For the people who do worry about that, Apple is introducing a new Lockdown Mode on its devices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IT services giant SHI hit by "professional malware attack"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/it-services-giant-shi-hit-by-professional-malware-attack/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/it-services-giant-shi-hit-by-professional-malware-attack/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T20:46:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SHI International Corp, a New Jersey-based provider of Information Technology (IT) products and services, has confirmed that its network was hit by a malware attack over the weekend. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[steam games becoming completely unresponsive]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vt00lo/steam_games_becoming_completely_unresponsive/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vt00lo/steam_games_becoming_completely_unresponsive/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T20:42:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This has been something that's been a growing problem for me. 
 I have games that have run flawlessly which all of a sudden just won't even start anymore. I was playing a game literally just a few hours ago and after I did a system update it won't even boot up now.
 Doesn't matter if I am on runtime or native. I can load some games through wine, but almost nothing loads through steam any more-proton or not.
 I half suspect something with vulkan, as trying to run vulkaninfo just freezes up and does nothing.
 Other than that I don't know. I need help, if any one has help to give.
    submitted by    /u/reenmini  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for co-maintainers (AUR)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vszno7/looking_for_comaintainers_aur/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vszno7/looking_for_comaintainers_aur/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T20:26:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Archers,
 I would really appreciate help of Arch community with maintaining the list of packages I maintain in AUR. With almost 400 packages while I actively use approximately only about half of this number responding to "b0rked", "needs update" requests is less fun than one could imagine. Of course I could simply disown all I no longer use but I would like to take more responsible approach - see if I can get anybody else interested, add as a co-maintainer and then if it works well for some period of time step down. If you want to know if you use any of the PKGBUILDs I maintain you can run the following snippet in bash (aurutils, jq required):
 pacman -Qq | grep -xf <((aur search -r -m jose1711 | jq -r '.results|.[].Name')) 
 If you're interested in anything, please leave me a message at https://aur.archlinux.org/account/jose1711. Also I expect that you already have some experience with creating PKGBUILDs or are eager to learn.
 Thank you.
    submitted by    /u/Revolutionary_Gur583  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Unblock a Number on iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=742693</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/742693/how-to-unblock-a-number-on-iphone/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you want to start getting calls and text messages from someone who you once blocked on your iPhone? Unblock their phone number on your iPhone, and they’ll be able to contact you again. We’ll show you how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PCIe bus error while trying to boot Archiso]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vsydta/pcie_bus_error_while_trying_to_boot_archiso/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vsydta/pcie_bus_error_while_trying_to_boot_archiso/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T19:33:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey there, I have this issue after I replaced my GPU from a GTX 750 Ti to a Radeon RX 6600 XT and I want to totally rid of all Nvidia blobs and drivers and I don't think that
 sudo pacman -R nvidia 
 would work fully and I like installing Arch anyway.
 the error reads that there is an issue with the TLP headers and a non-fatal PCIe bus error with a timestamp on the left.
 I had a February Archiso but I downloaded a new one (July 2022) and it still has the same issues.
 Help?
 https://imgur.com/a/NTWpnzZ <- link to what it shows, this is also available on the Arch Fourms.
    submitted by    /u/CryptoR615  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security advisory accidentally exposes vulnerable systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/security-advisory-accidentally-exposes-vulnerable-systems/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/security-advisory-accidentally-exposes-vulnerable-systems/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T19:20:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A security advisory for a vulnerability (CVE) published by MITRE has accidentally been exposing links to remote admin consoles of over a dozen vulnerable IP devices since at least April 2022. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ax Sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fix Error Code 0x80004005 on Windows 10 and 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=810837</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/810837/how-to-fix-error-code-0x80004005-on-windows-10-and-11/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T19:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows loves to throw cryptic error codes with a million possible causes, and at least as many solutions. Error Code 0x80004005 is no exception, though it does have a few common causes. Here are some things you can try to fix it on either Windows 10 or Windows 11.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Lewis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUSE's Adaptable Linux Platform Considers Requiring AVX-Capable x86_64 CPUs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=SUSE-ALP-x86-64-Raising-Base</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=SUSE-ALP-x86-64-Raising-Base"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SUSE/openSUSE Adaptable Linux Platform (ALP) that is being viewed as the eventual successor to SUSE Linux Enterprise 15 is likely to require higher system requirements for x86_64 CPUs. Just how much newer the Intel/AMD support requirement will be has yet to be firmly decided but they are looking at a baseline of "x86-64-v3" that would effectively mean requiring Advanced Vector Extensions (AVX)...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get the Amazon Fire 7 Tablet for Just $30 Before Prime Day]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=816461</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/816461/get-the-amazon-fire-7-tablet-for-just-30-before-prime-day/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T18:45:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Fire tablets are popular for streaming media and basic games, mostly because they’re incredibly cheap. Prime Day is officially a week away, but the sale event is already live for some Amazon products.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple’s new Lockdown Mode defends against government spyware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/apple/apple-s-new-lockdown-mode-defends-against-government-spyware/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/apple/apple-s-new-lockdown-mode-defends-against-government-spyware/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T18:38:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple announced that a new security feature known as Lockdown Mode will roll out with iOS 16, iPadOS 16, and macOS Ventura to protect high-risk individuals like human rights defenders, journalists, and dissidents against targeted spyware attacks. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RADV Lands VK_EXT_shader_module_identifier, VKD3D-Proton Prepares Usage]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=VK_EXT_shader_module_ident</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=VK_EXT_shader_module_ident"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T18:07:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week's Vulkan 1.3.219 release introduced the VK_EXT_shader_module_identifier that was worked on in part by Valve. This ability for software to query an identifier associated with a Vulkan shader module is seeing quick driver adoption and is preparing for use within VKD3D-Proton as an efficiency improvement...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Restart a Roku]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=815147</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/815147/how-to-restart-a-roku/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T18:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes a device just isn’t working like it should, and the easiest solution is usually a good old restart. You can restart a Roku very easily and that will often solve any minor problems you’re experiencing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I created my first Archlinux package - tochd (a Python script)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vsvwf9/i_created_my_first_archlinux_package_tochd_a/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vsvwf9/i_created_my_first_archlinux_package_tochd_a/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T17:46:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone. Today I created my first Archlinux package using makepkg. I hope it went all right. Might someone want have a look at the PKGBUILD file? The program itself is not very complicated to install, just a single Python script to copy into a directory.
 Prior in generating the package, I have to update the checksum in PKGBUILD, upload the current state of the project to Github, create a release with a tag and change the version in the PKGBUILD file. Then I can use makepkg to build the package and upload it too in the release tab. Then one can download the "tochd-x.x-x-any.pkg.tar.zst" package from release page and install using pacman.
 Am I doing this right? The program itself is working correctly and I tested it by installing it myself (obviously). Just a note here about the program itself: It is more or less a commandline interface to automate extraction archives with 7z and convert certain types of files (such as .iso or .cue) with chdman. Intended use of generated files is for emulation of videogames.
    submitted by    /u/eXoRainbow  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ransomware, hacking groups move from Cobalt Strike to Brute Ratel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ransomware-hacking-groups-move-from-cobalt-strike-to-brute-ratel/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ransomware-hacking-groups-move-from-cobalt-strike-to-brute-ratel/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T17:32:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hacking groups and ransomware operations are moving away from Cobalt Strike to the newer Brute Ratel post-exploitation toolkit to evade detection by EDR and antivirus solutions. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The rust package in official Arch repositories does not update llvm libraries]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vsv59g/the_rust_package_in_official_arch_repositories/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vsv59g/the_rust_package_in_official_arch_repositories/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T17:14:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learned this the hard way today. You should be good to go if you update the llvm-libs using pacman, or otherwise you'll be stuck with a dysfunctional rustc.
    submitted by    /u/AlpinDale  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How do I delete Eclipse IDE (pacman -Rns doesn't work)?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vsut8k/how_do_i_delete_eclipse_ide_pacman_rns_doesnt_work/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vsut8k/how_do_i_delete_eclipse_ide_pacman_rns_doesnt_work/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T17:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I installed Eclipse IDE from the website (using a tarball) but now I want to remove it. I tried to do `sudo pacman -Rns eclipse` but it said the target wasn't found. How do I delete Eclipse without using Pacman or manually deleting files?
    submitted by    /u/brapbrapbrapsutututu  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fix an iPad Stuck on the Apple Logo: 5 Solutions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=812199</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/812199/how-to-fix-an-ipad-stuck-on-the-apple-logo-5-solutions/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T17:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t panic if your iPad is stuck on the Apple logo, update progress bar, or in a boot loop. There are a few things you can try to get things working again before getting Apple or a third-party repair service involved.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTG Deals: Get a Great Samsung SSD for $84.99 and More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=816298</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/816298/htg-deals-get-a-great-samsung-ssd-for-84.99-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T17:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prime Day is coming next week, but that doesn’t mean you can’t save on some great tech now! From a great deal on an internal gaming SSD to discounts on one of our favorite Bluetooth speakers, read on for some of the best deals this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Henges</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Canceling Amazon Prime Just Got Easier, but Not in the US]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/122405/canceling-amazon-prime-just-got-easier-but-not-in-the-us/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/122405/canceling-amazon-prime-just-got-easier-but-not-in-the-us/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T16:59:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks to the European Commission, Amazon customers in the EU can now cancel a Prime membership with just two clicks. Additionally, the cancellation process is now free of “distracting information” and small, hidden buttons. But Amazon doesn’t seem interested in bringing these changes to the United States.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Outlook Lite Is Coming to Your Android Phone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=816407</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/816407/microsoft-outlook-lite-is-coming-to-your-android-phone/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T16:57:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Outlook has been available on Android phones and tablets for a while now, but an optimize version that will work better on lower-end devices is in development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come Forzare l'aggiornamento di Windows e installare l'ultima versione]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2016/09/se-windows-10-non-ha-ancora-lupdate.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2016/09/se-windows-10-non-ha-ancora-lupdate.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T16:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 e Windows 10 sono progettati per aggiornarsi automaticamente. Questa forzatura, che per molti può essere un'invasione all'autonomia di gestione del computer, è stata però una scelta obbligata per fare in modo che tutti gli utenti, anche i più sbadati e quelli che non curano la manutenzione del loro PC, possano sempre avere installate le ultime patch di sicurezza e le ultime funzioni...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Marriott hit by new data breach and a failed extortion attempt]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/marriott-hit-by-new-data-breach-and-a-failed-extortion-attempt/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/marriott-hit-by-new-data-breach-and-a-failed-extortion-attempt/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T16:52:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hotel giant Marriott International confirmed this week that it was hit by another data breach after an unknown threat actor managed to breach one of its properties and steal 20 GB worth of files. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Noticed that I was downloading something in the background despite not having any programs opened.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vsuclv/noticed_that_i_was_downloading_something_in_the/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vsuclv/noticed_that_i_was_downloading_something_in_the/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T16:40:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is my journalctl log showing the activity possibly corresponding to the internet usage until I manually turned off the internet on my computer. The last few lines should reflect that:
  
Jul 06 06:15:09 arch gnome-software[1793]: ignoring percentage 99% -> 71% as going down on app system/flatpak/flathub/org.freedesktop.Platform.GL.nvidia-515-57/1.4 
 Jul 06 06:15:10 arch gnome-software[1793]: ignoring percentage 99% -> 72% as going down on app system/flatpak/flathub/org.freedesktop.Platform.GL.nvidia-515-57/1.4 
 Jul 06 06:15:11 arch gnome-software[1793]: ignoring percentage 99% -> 73% as going down on app system/flatpak/flathub/org.freedesktop.Platform.GL.nvidia-515-57/1.4 
 Jul 06 06:15:12 arch gnome-software[1793]: ignoring percentage 99% -> 73% as going down on app system/flatpak/…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Samsung Wireless PowerShare, and How Do You Use It?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=812660</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/812660/what-is-samsung-wireless-powershare-and-how-do-you-use-it/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T16:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many flagship phones have wireless charging but few have the ability to reverse charge other devices. But Samsung phones have had the technology for some years, albeit branded Wireless PowerShare. This article will cover everything you should know about it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Haroun Adamu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your Chromebook Could Get a Longer Battery Life with Upcoming Update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/122394/your-chromebook-could-get-a-longer-battery-life-with-upcoming-update/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/122394/your-chromebook-could-get-a-longer-battery-life-with-upcoming-update/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T15:44:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chromebooks offer a much longer battery life than the average Windows machine, but there’s still room for improvement. The upcoming Chrome OS 105 update introduces new browser optimizations will the intent of saving extra battery life.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The iPhone 14 Could Use Last Year's Processor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/122390/the-iphone-14-could-use-last-years-processor/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/122390/the-iphone-14-could-use-last-years-processor/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T15:35:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier this year, we heard reports and rumors that Apple could split the iPhone 14 lineup with two different processors. The company might reserve the latest and greatest for its Pro-model phones to help it stand out and improve sales.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Microsoft Lists and How to Get Started with It?]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=494827</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15416606/get-started-microsoft-lists"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T15:25:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Managing any team can be a challenging task, especially if you’re working remotely. The last thing you’d want is your employees not knowing what tasks has been assigned to them, when they are due, etc.  
    
Microsoft Lists is a platform built to help you become a better team leader. It offers an intuitive environment for managing resources, people, or data and comes with a long list of features that let you customize it according to your unique needs. In this article, we will take a look at some of Microsoft Lists’ essential features and use cases and demonstrate how you can get started with it.
   

Content

What is Microsoft Lists?
What is Microsoft Lists Used For?
1. Create a List
2. Add Team Members
3. Create Tasks and Assign Them
4. Track Your Workflow
5. Leave Comments
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ojash Yadav</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your Amazon Prime Now Includes Free Grubhub Food Delivery]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=816321</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/816321/your-amazon-prime-now-includes-free-grubhub-food-delivery/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T15:22:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Prime already includes a lot of services, from free shipping on orders to the Prime Video streaming services, which also serves as justification for the ever-increasing price. Now another reward is available to Prime subscribers: free food deliveries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple's MacBook Air M2 Goes on Sale Starting July 8th]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/122381/apples-macbook-air-m2-goes-on-sale-starting-july-8th/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/122381/apples-macbook-air-m2-goes-on-sale-starting-july-8th/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T15:08:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last month, Apple announced several new products, including an all-new redesigned MacBook Air with the M2 chip. After a short wait, it’ll finally go on sale starting Friday, with pre-orders shipping on July 15th.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Govee and Razer Will Light Up Your PC Life]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/122321/govee-and-razer-will-light-up-your-pc-life/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/122321/govee-and-razer-will-light-up-your-pc-life/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T15:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A collaboration between Govee and Razer just makes sense. That’s why select Govee smart lighting products, including the popular Neon Rope lights, now feature Razer Chroma RGB compatibility. You just need a Chroma-compatible game, the Razer Synapse 3 software, and the Govee Desktop App.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fix Common Formula Errors in Microsoft Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=813794</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/813794/how-to-fix-common-formula-errors-in-microsoft-excel/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T15:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Formulas can be powerful ways to manipulate, evaluate, find, and analyze data. But with formulas can come problems. Here are several common formula errors in Microsoft Excel, how to correct them, and tools for further help.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is this menu called and how to hide, or get rid, of it?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vsrvf2/what_is_this_menu_called_and_how_to_hide_or_get/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vsrvf2/what_is_this_menu_called_and_how_to_hide_or_get/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T14:53:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/Galactic_CakeYT  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US govt warns of Maui ransomware attacks against healthcare orgs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-govt-warns-of-maui-ransomware-attacks-against-healthcare-orgs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-govt-warns-of-maui-ransomware-attacks-against-healthcare-orgs/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T14:47:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The FBI, CISA, and the U.S. Treasury Department issued today a joint advisory warning of North-Korean-backed threat actors using Maui ransomware in attacks against Healthcare and Public Health (HPH) organizations. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come evitare la truffa SMS delle Poste]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/07/come-evitare-la-truffa-sms-delle-poste.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/07/come-evitare-la-truffa-sms-delle-poste.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T14:46:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gli SMS sono caduti in disuso per lo scambio di messaggi ma vengono ancora utilizzati per ricevere i codici monouso delle Poste Italiane o per ricevere i codici OTP delle banche. Questa importante funzione di sicurezza viene sfruttata dai malintenzionati per far scattare delle trappole molto pericolose per gli utenti, con messaggi di phishing del tutto simili a quelli ricevuti via email (in...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Prime Members Get Free Grubhub+ for a Year]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/122379/amazon-prime-members-get-free-grubhub-for-a-year/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/122379/amazon-prime-members-get-free-grubhub-for-a-year/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T14:41:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Prime members can now redeem a year of Grubhub+ for free. This service, which usually costs $10 a month, waives delivery fees on Grubhub orders of $12 or more (at participating restaurants). It’s a killer benefit, and if you order a ton of food, it could save you hundreds of dollars.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Hide the Google Meet and Chat Sidebar in Gmail]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=816307</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/816307/how-to-hide-the-google-meet-and-chat-sidebar-in-gmail/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T14:21:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In early 2022, Google introduced a new Material You-inspired look for Gmail on the web. That redesign started rolling out to everyone in June 2022. It features a new sidebar that takes up more space. You can hide it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ACPI BIOS Error after rebooting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vsr1i2/acpi_bios_error_after_rebooting/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vsr1i2/acpi_bios_error_after_rebooting/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T14:15:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello Arch Linux friends 
 After rebooting I got stuck with a blank screen I ran journalctl in the tty
 Here's the output
 ACPI BIOS Error (bug) : Could not resolve symbol [\_PR.CPU0._CPC] , AE_NOT_FOUND (20211217/psarg-330)
 ACPI Error : Aborting method \_PR.CPU1._CPC due to previous error (AE_NOT_FOUND) (20211217/psparse-529)
 ACPI BIOS Error (bug) : Could not resolve symbol [\_PR.CPU0._CPC] , AE_NOT_FOUND (20211217/psargs-330)
 ACPI Error : Aborting method \_PR.CPU2._CPC due to previous error (AE_NOT_FOUND) (20211217/psparse-529)
 ACPI BIOS Error (bug) : Could not resolve symbol [\_PR.CPU0.CPC] , AE_NOT_FOUND (20211217/psarg-330
 ACPI Error : Aborting method \_PR.CPU3._CPC due to previous error (AE_NOT_FOUND) (20211217/psparse-529)
 uname -r 5.18.9-arch1-1
 I have no idea how to fix it maybe a driver issue I am still new to linux so feel free to ask me anything.
    submitted by    /u/2spdy  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple MacBook Air With M2 Goes on Sale Starting July 8]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=816290</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/816290/apple-macbook-air-with-m2-goes-on-sale-starting-july-8/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T14:11:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple revealed a few new products a month ago, including a redesigned MacBook Air with the new M2 chipset. You’ll be able to order one in just two days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft is testing an image editor in Edge]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179571</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/07/06/microsoft-is-testing-an-image-editor-in-edge/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T14:03:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft is testing a new feature in its Edge web browser currently that allows users to edit images before they are saved to the local system. Spotted by Reddit user Leopeva64-2, the […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Microsoft is testing an image editor in Edge appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Ethernet Cables of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=807220</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/807220/best-ethernet-cable/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T14:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Buying the right Ethernet cable is important. Getting the wrong cable will slow down your network performance and speed—and it might apart quickly to boot. The right Ethernet cable will be fast and durable. Here are the best ones to buy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Max Buondonno</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xiaomi Mi Band 7 Pro: il confine tra smart band e smartwatch si fa più sfumato]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Xiaomi-Mi-Band-7-Pro-il-confine-tra-smart-band-e-smartwatch-si-fa-piu-sfumato_24746</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Xiaomi-Mi-Band-7-Pro-il-confine-tra-smart-band-e-smartwatch-si-fa-piu-sfumato_24746"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T13:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dopo la recente presentazione dello Xiaomi Mi Band 7, l'azienda ha appena annunciato l'arrivo della nuova smart band Mi Band 7 Pro, un modello che si mette in evidenza per le migliori specifiche e le maggiori dimensioni rispetto ai predecessori.Pur avvicinandosi alla dotazione di uno smartwatch, Xiaomi Mi Band 7 Pro mantiene un prezzo particolarmente aggressivo.Al momento non conosciamo il prezzo che sarà praticato in Europa ma stando alle informazioni che arrivano dalla Cina dovrebbe essere molto interessante.

Con uno schermo AMOLED da 1,64 pollici 280 x 456 pixel (326 ppi), il nuovo Mi Band 7 Pro ha un display significativamente più ampio della maggior parte dei tracker per il fitness.Xiaomi ha cercato di evidenziare questa qualità prevedendo alcune funzionalità aggiuntive: lo schermo p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Most Arch-compatible laptops 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vsprpj/most_archcompatible_laptops_2022/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vsprpj/most_archcompatible_laptops_2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T13:14:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I know this question is often asked, but when I did a quick search I didn't see any answers from this year. Apologies if I've missed something. 
 I'm currently using a Dell XPS15 9560, which I originally purchased because I figured that Dell's hardware would be very Linux friendly given their "comes with Linux preinstalled" options. 
 While the Linux compatibility hasn't been terrible, it also hasn't been painless. I wound up replacing the wifi card because the one it shipped with was incredibly finicky. I also had to spend some time getting it to play nicely with an external monitor (and the 4k display has given me a fair bit of grief in general). Most troubling, rebooting/resuming often results in a frozen machine that must be killed by holding the power button and then restarted, and despite repeated attempts to fix this I've never succeeded. 
 I'm looking for a workhorse to do web development on, so I don't really care about GPU, in fact having to deal with nVidia is probably a con. I'm more concerned with memory, CPU, and playing nicely with an external monitor. 
 I've seen lots of love for thinkpads in the older threads. Are they still a good pick in 2022?
    submitted by    /u/mrfiddles  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[System Crashes/Kernel Panics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vspnfm/system_crasheskernel_panics/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vspnfm/system_crasheskernel_panics/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T13:08:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Been fighting an issue on my headless arch server for about the last month. The problem seemingly came out of nowhere, as I hadn't done an update in a couple weeks, and I haven't been able to figure out what might be going on. The issue seems random, and I'll generally get a crash once every day or two, as long as I'm home and using my equipment like normal. Copy of this morning's errors is here.
 Things I've tried:
 -Rolling back all recently installed updates to previous versions from cache
 -Completely disabling C6 states on the processor (Ryzen 5 3400G)
 -Running Memtest to check for errors (none found in 4 passes)
 -Checking disks for critical errors (simple nvme tests for the M.2 drive, and smarttest for the normal disk drives).
 -Moving to linux-zen kernel from linux-lts (this actually led to more frequent issues, so I've since moved back)
 -Added "blacklist sp5100-tco" to kernel parameters (I read some threads that indicated a compatibility issue with Ryzen on this)
 -Update all packages to most recent versions (this was my last-ditch effort after everything else had failed me)
 I'm still hitting problems, and outside of it being a hardware issue I'm not properly identifying (I've considered switching the PSU for another good one I have here), I'm at a loss. I've had this headless installation up and running for years. Only once before did I ever encounter a struggle like this, but it was fixed by moving off the arch linux kernel and installing linux-lts. Any help/guidance you might have is appreciated. For what it's worth, I was out of town for the 4th from Friday until Monday, and the server ran the whole time with no problems. Crashed this morning for the first time since we got back, so it appears to almost certainly be tied to usage in some way.
 Edit: Current kernel is 5.15.50-1-lts, running on the AM4 platform with a Ryzen 5 3400G. Headless system, so I just use the integrated video. BIOS is also on the most recent version.
    submitted by    /u/GreatTragedy  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[YouTube Briefly Banned a Lifesaving Video]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/122315/youtube-briefly-banned-a-lifesaving-video/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/122315/youtube-briefly-banned-a-lifesaving-video/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T13:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve been around the woodworking YouTube scene for long, you may have seen “fractile wood burning.” It’s beautiful and exquisite. The one hitch? It’s incredibly deadly. And YouTube banned a video warning of that danger before it pulled the dangerous videos describing how to do it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Hendrickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t Go Overboard With Your First Whole Home Audio Purchase]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=807960</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/807960/first-whole-home-audio-purchase/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T13:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Making your first whole home audio purchase can be daunting. After all, you’re talking about audio for your entire home. That’s exactly why you don’t want to jump into the world of multi-room audio head first.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kris Wouk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Digital Services Act e Digital Markets Act: cambia il ruolo di aziende come Google, Apple e Facebook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Digital-Services-Act-e-Digital-Markets-Act-cambia-il-ruolo-di-aziende-come-Google-Apple-e-Facebook_24745</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Digital-Services-Act-e-Digital-Markets-Act-cambia-il-ruolo-di-aziende-come-Google-Apple-e-Facebook_24745"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T12:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Da tempo il legislatore europeo stava lavorando per modificare quella che viene considerata come una situazione di squilibrio a favore delle aziende più importanti come Google, Apple e Facebook-Meta. Sono due i pilastri sui quali si sta basando l'azione in campo europeo: Digital Services Act (DSA) e Digital Markets Act (DMA). Entrambi prevedono una serie di restrizioni che mirano a frenare comportamenti anticoncorrenziali e un utilizzo troppo ampio dei dati personali degli utenti.I due nuovi pacchetti di normative sono stati appena approvati dal Parlamento europeo aprendo così la strada al 'via libera' definitivo da parte del Consiglio dell'Unione.Abbiamo già visto cos'è e cosa cambia con la Legge sui Servizi Digitali (DSA) e come DMA possa avere effetto sul funzionamento delle app di messaggistica istantanea.Nel complesso, però, le nuove disposizioni introducono la figura del gatekeeper: esso corrisponde ai soggetti che gestiscono le piattaforme che tutti conosciamo e usiamo ogni giorno.Gestori di store online come Google Play Store ed Apple Store devono accettare e consentire l'installazione di app da altre sorgenti, permettere agli sviluppatori di servirsi di strumenti di pagamento di terze parti nelle rispettive app, consentire il download e l'installazione di file binari da Internet, l'integrazione di applicazioni e servizi digitali con quelli del gatekeeper.Servizi di messaggistica istantanea, quelli per le chiamate vocali e le videochiamate devono quindi, a norma di legge, essere integrabili reciprocamente.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[cpufreq wrong max limit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vsol5r/cpufreq_wrong_max_limit/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vsol5r/cpufreq_wrong_max_limit/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T12:13:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have an ASUS VivoBook Flip14 TM420IA
 All hardware info: https://linux-hardware.org/?probe=b80097333e 
 /sys/devices/system/cpu/cpu0/cpufreq/cpuinfo\_max\_freq as well as lscpu https://linux-hardware.org/?probe=b80097333e&log=lscpu report 2 GHz
 But when I run a stress test like 
 stress-ng --cpu 8
 grep "^[c]pu MHz" /proc/cpuinfo returns 3.9 GHz which is in line with the CPU spec of "up to 4.1 GHz".
  
The problem is, that when I use autocpu-freq, I am only allowed to set a scaling_max_freq in /etc/auto-cpufreq.conf of 2 GHz, because it is reading the values above and doing a check when running a stress test, it only reaches 2 GHz, even though turbo is enabled. 
 But I want my laptop to run full power when it is charging and as slow as possible when discharging.
 I could of course make a hacky patch, but I would rather understand why the values in /sys/devices/system/cpu/... are the way they are.
 Any help is welcome.
    submitted by    /u/Deckweiss  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No audio after updating system]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vsogwu/no_audio_after_updating_system/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vsogwu/no_audio_after_updating_system/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T12:06:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I updated my system yesterday, when I did it asked to remove some conflicting package to which I responded "yes" immediately without thinking about it.... It broke my audio and I have no idea how to debug this.
 ---
 Update:
 I checked the logs and the package removed was pipewire-media-session, it was replaced by wireplumber. I enabled and started the services, but they are reporting these errors: https://imgur.com/a/TLhZ6Nz
 ---
 Solved, I really dont know exactly how but after enabling wireplumber and pipewire-alsa services I did a couple of resets and it started working.
    submitted by    /u/joalcava  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripristinare Windows dopo un malware con il Remediation Tool]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Ripristinare-Windows-dopo-un-malware-con-il-Remediation-Tool_24744</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Ripristinare-Windows-dopo-un-malware-con-il-Remediation-Tool_24744"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T12:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Un'infezione malware può avere effetti dirompenti sulla configurazione del sistema operativo tanto che in generale è sconsigliabile continuare a usare la macchina così com'è, anche dopo l'effettiva rimozione di una minaccia.In tanti preferiscono eseguire un'installazione da zero di Windows oppure procedere con un aggiornamento in-place del sistema operativo.Uno strumento gratuito e open source come Windows Malware Effects Remediation Tool consente di correggere le configurazioni di Windows che sono state modificate dal malware ripristinandole ai valori predefiniti.Alcune minacce disattivano ad esempio l'accesso al registro di sistema, l'utilizzo del Task Manager, del Prompt dei comandi, della finestra Esegui (Windows+R), del tasto Windows e così via.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Undervolting a GPU or CPU, and When Should You Do It?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=805771</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/805771/what-is-undervolting-gpu-or-cpu/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T12:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ve probably heard of overclocking in the context of computers, where systems are pushed beyond their factory-approved settings. Yet not all modifications are about making your system go faster; undervolting is the art of restricting the flow of power.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sydney Butler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tecnologia più conveniente dopo 40 anni: cosa è cambiato dal 1982]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Tecnologia-piu-conveniente-dopo-40-anni-cosa-e-cambiato-dal-1982_24665</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Tecnologia-piu-conveniente-dopo-40-anni-cosa-e-cambiato-dal-1982_24665"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Negli anni '80 e '90 noi e le nostre famiglie abbiamo speso non pochi soldini sulle innovazioni informatiche introdotte all'epoca. Nel 1981 nasceva il primo storico PC IBM 5150: i modelli presentati da Big Blue in precedenza non potevano essere considerati personal computer e fu allora che nacque il fenomeno dell'home computing.Quarant'anni fa un IBM 5150 con 10 MB di disco fisso e una copia di Word sarebbe costato qualcosa come l'equivalente odierno di circa 14.000 euro. Un importo folle tanto che la maggior parte degli appassionati sceglieva ad esempio un sistema come il Commodore 64 dal costo di circa 1.500 euro calcolando l'andamento dell'inflazione.Fu proprio nel 1982 che Intel lanciò sul mercato il suo processore 80286 che introdusse il concetto di memoria protetta e favorì la diffusione dei sistemi Unix-like anche sui PC IBM grazie al supporto multi-threading.I prezzi di computer e stampanti sono crollati nel corso degli anni '80 e '90 e lo storage per PC sempre più economico e prestazionale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Collegare lo smartphone Android alla TV (via cavo o wireless)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2018/04/collegare-lo-smartphone-android-alla-tv.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2018/04/collegare-lo-smartphone-android-alla-tv.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T11:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ogni smartphone Android può essere collegato a una qualsiasi TV in modo da vedere tutti i video in streaming, le applicazioni, i giochi e le foto sul grande schermo.

 Nella guida che segue vi mostreremo tutti i metodi per collegare lo smartphone Android alla TV, effettuando collegamenti via cavo o utilizzando direttamente la connessione senza fili, grazie all'uso di tecnologie già integrate...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Great! I broke arch again.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vsnirk/great_i_broke_arch_again/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vsnirk/great_i_broke_arch_again/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T11:14:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I had a 40GB root partition that filled up pretty quick so I wanted to add 100GB to it. I used rsync to do a full system back on my HDD. I think the mistake was that I accidentally combined the partitions before having unmounted them. When I boot I am promopted with the grub rescue mode, but when I find the ext2 partition, set it as boot, set theprefix and run insmod normal, I get an error. What can I do now to restore my backup on the new 140GB partition? Do I need to reinstall arch using a live usb first, then backing up after the full install is done? Is it possible to use the live usb to setup the partitions, then just copy the backup over to it? Thanks!
 I am dual booting with Windows 10.
    submitted by    /u/whimsical_tittynope  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does Hibernating My PC Save More Energy Than Sleep?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=814538</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/814538/does-hibernating-my-pc-save-more-energy-than-sleep/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows has two main options for shutting down your PC without really shutting it down—“Sleep” and “Hibernate.” There are some key differences between these two modes, but which one actually uses the least electricity? Let’s find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AlmaLinux 9, openSUSE Leap 15.4, Ubuntu 22.04, Debian 11.3 & Clear Linux Benchmarks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31269</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31269"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Given the recent releases of openSUSE Leap 15.4 and AlmaLinux 9.0, here are some fresh Linux server/workstation-oriented benchmarks on a dual Intel Xeon Platinum 8380 "Ice Lake" platform and running the fresh releases of various enterprise Linux choices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visual Studio Code download e configurazione della versione portabile]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Visual-Studio-Code-download-e-configurazione-della-versione-portabile_24654</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Visual-Studio-Code-download-e-configurazione-della-versione-portabile_24654"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T10:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Che siate sviluppatori di lungo corso o programmatori in erba, Visual Studio Code è un eccellente compagno di lavoro. Si tratta di un editor di codice sviluppato da Microsoft e distribuito gratuitamente nelle versioni per Windows, Linux e macOS.Nell'articolo in cui spieghiamo cos'è Visual Studio Code abbiamo visto che diversamente rispetto ad altri programmi alternativi offre l'evidenziazione della sintassi riconoscendo automaticamente quella dei vari linguaggi di programmazione e integra IntelliSense, un meccanismo che suggerisce le funzioni, i metodi e le istruzioni da digitare con una sorta di autocompletamento.Oltre a integrare il supporto per il debugging, per Git, per gli snippet e il refactoring del codice, Visual Studio Code è un editor ampiamente personalizzabile che si adatta al modo di lavorare dello sviluppatore.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Picsart Gold Review: A True Treasure for Quick Photo and Video Editing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=814043</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/814043/picsart-gold-review/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T10:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In days past, to edit a photo, you needed to hop onto your desktop, open photo editing software, and get to work. Now, plenty of tools exist to help you add special effects to your photos, create simple logos, and so much more in just a few clicks (or taps). Picsart is perhaps one of the best.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brenna Miles</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows Malware Effects Remediation Tool]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179561</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/07/06/windows-malware-effects-remediation-tool/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T09:57:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Successful malware attacks may make modifications to the systems, usually to decrease the chance of detection or removal of malicious processes. Even after a successful cleaning, effects of the malware attack may […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Windows Malware Effects Remediation Tool appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fedora May Finally Provide Official Support For The Raspberry Pi 4]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Fedora-37-Raspberry-Pi-4</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Fedora-37-Raspberry-Pi-4"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T09:54:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For as popular as the Raspberry Pi 4 has been since its 2019 launch, Fedora hasn't officially supported this Arm single board computer with its Linux distribution. But now thanks to the upstream, open-source graphics acceleration finally coming together for the Raspberry Pi 4, with Fedora 37 they may end up finally providing "official" support for this popular, low-cost developer board...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD Hiring For Another Open-Source GPU Driver Developer With Multimedia Expertise]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMD-2022-Multimedia-Hiring</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMD-2022-Multimedia-Hiring"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T09:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's great seeing AMD continuing to hire for more Linux/open-source driver developers. Beyond their many roles they are still working to fill on the CPU side of the house, they have a new job posting in hiring for their open-source GPU driver stack with a focus on multimedia efforts...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Asahi Linux Nears Release "Real Soon" For Apple M2 Hardware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Apple-M2-On-Linux-Asahi-Soon</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Apple-M2-On-Linux-Asahi-Soon"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T09:30:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While Apple just recently introduced their first M2-powered Apple Silicon devices, thanks to the dedication of Hector Martin with Asahi Linux and not too many breaking changes over the M1, Asahi Linux is looking at "soon" having a Linux release to support the new platform...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft releases two new builds to the Windows 11 Insider Preview Beta channel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179558</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/07/06/windows-11-insider-preview-beta-build-22621-and-build-22622/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T09:23:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has released not 1, but  two new builds to the Windows 11 Insider Preview Beta channel. Some users will get Build 22621, while others may get Build 22622. Why has Microsoft […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Microsoft releases two new builds to the Windows 11 Insider Preview Beta channel appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oracle Linux 9 Reaches GA With Unbreakable Enterprise Kernel R7]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Oracle-Linux-9-GA</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Oracle-Linux-9-GA"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T08:58:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oracle Linux 9 as Oracle's offshoot of Red Hat Enterprise Linux 9 is now available in general availability (GA) form. Besides being based on RHEL9, Oracle Linux 9 offers up their latest "Unbreakable Enterprise Kernel" for extra kernel features while also continuing to produce a Red Hat Compatible Kernel flavor as well...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel Evo: cos'è e come funziona la certificazione]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Intel-Evo-cos-e-e-come-funziona-la-certificazione_24662</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Intel-Evo-cos-e-e-come-funziona-la-certificazione_24662"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T08:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[È molto probabile che nell'ultimo periodo abbiate sentito parlare sempre più spesso di Intel Evo: si tratta di una certificazione per PC ultraportatili, compatti e performanti che l'azienda di Santa Clara aveva presentato a novembre 2020.Inizialmente noto come Project Athena, il marchio Intel Evo è utilizzato sui notebook basati su processore Core di undicesima e dodicesima generazione con grafica Iris Xe integrata. Si tratta dei sistemi che rispondono a certi requisiti in termini di prestazioni, reattività, durata della batteria, ricarica rapida e supporto dei più recenti standard in termini di connettività.L''etichetta' Intel Evo esplicita agli acquirenti che si trovano dinanzi a un prodotto di classe Premium.L'idea alla base di Intel Evo è quella di fornire portatili per un utilizzo 'senza compromessi'. Di solito, infatti, quando si sceglie un notebook compatto e ultrasottile, è necessario sacrificare un po’ di prestazioni.I prodotti che si fregiano della certificazione Intel Evo, invece, soddisfano alcuni requisiti minimi:- Assicurano prestazioni di primo livello pur essendo sottili e leggeri- Si risvegliano dallo stato di stand by in meno di un secondo- Supportano la tecnologia WiFi 6 basata su chip Intel per collegarsi alla rete wireless ad alta velocità- Con la ricarica rapida della batteria si hanno almeno 4 ore di autonomia a fronte di 30 minuti di connessione alla rete elettrica- Garanzia di un'autonomia della batteria pari ad almeno 9 ore sui sistemi dotati di pannello Full HD- Facile connessione con un unico cavo USB-C e supporto per la tecnologia Thunderbolt 4.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wifi device drivers detected but can't detect wifi device (Newbie)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vsl69u/wifi_device_drivers_detected_but_cant_detect_wifi/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vsl69u/wifi_device_drivers_detected_but_cant_detect_wifi/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T08:40:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone,
 So today I installed arch on Dual boot with Windows 11 via wifi on my HP laptop, everything went smoothly with the install, but after I booted into the installation I couldn't connect to the wifi. I have both network manager and dhcpcd both installed and enabled and running. I ran lspci and sure enough it detected the Network Controller Network controller: Realtek Semiconductor Co., Ltd. RTL8852AE 802.11ax PCIe Wireless Network Adapter. But when I use device list under iwctl I get nothing, whereas I got wlan0 during the installation phase.
 I have installed both linux and linux-lts kernels btw.
 It's also worth to mention that I faced the same issue, but in Ubuntu, where my wifi device couldn't be detected, but it also couldn't be detected by windows 11 on dual boot either, only to be fixed by uninstalling Ubuntu.
 Excuse my stupidity, still new to linux.
    submitted by    /u/Cartoon_JR  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch Linux on an XPS 15, gdm breaks the system]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vsl5qz/arch_linux_on_an_xps_15_gdm_breaks_the_system/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vsl5qz/arch_linux_on_an_xps_15_gdm_breaks_the_system/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T08:39:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Installed arch on my xps 15, rebooted into the system fine. Then when I install gnome and nvidia drivers, and enable gdm.service I get stuck on a black screen with a white underscore in the top left like a tty, and no shortcuts work so I can't access a terminal. While booting an error flashes on the screen among all the other boot text saying "failed to start load kernel modules". Using the iso to chroot into the system allows me to disable gdm.service, which fixes it - but then we're back at square one. 
 Nvidia drivers are definitely installed so I doubt that's causing it, however the laptop also has an integrated gpu from the intel chip, so I have no way of knowing which one it's even using.
 Any help would be greatly appreciated, kinda losing hope. Might just reinstall fedora on it even though I had a few issues / bugs on it that were really annoying - which is what prompted me to try arch on it.
 Thanks.
    submitted by    /u/MangoWizard_  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VPN, quando e perché usarne una a casa]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=VPN-quando-e-perche-usarne-una-a-casa_24629</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=VPN-quando-e-perche-usarne-una-a-casa_24629"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T07:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Una connessione VPN (Virtual Private Network) protegge i dati che vengono scambiati sulla rete Internet, sia quelli inviati che quelli ricevuti. Il server VPN stabilisce un tunnel crittografato con ciascun client collegato: all'interno di esso vengono fatti transitare i pacchetti dati in entrambe le direzioni.In un altro articolo abbiamo visto cos'è una VPN e come funziona.
Quando e perché usare una VPN a casa
 Per anni le reti VPN sono state considerate strumenti prevalentemente destinati a professionisti e imprese. Oggi le VPN vengono invece sempre più frequentemente utilizzate anche da parte di utenti privati. Perché?Iniziamo col fare un'importante distinzione: ci sono i servizi VPN offerti da provider specializzati e i server VPN attivabili all'interno della propria rete.
Differenza tr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fingerprinting: utenti riconoscibili dalle estensioni installate in Chrome e Chromium]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Fingerprinting-utenti-riconoscibili-dalle-estensioni-installate-in-Chrome-e-Chromium_24664</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Fingerprinting-utenti-riconoscibili-dalle-estensioni-installate-in-Chrome-e-Chromium_24664"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T07:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tutelare la propria privacy durante la navigazione sul Web diventa sempre più complicato. Il legislatore europeo si è concentrato sui cookie ma esistono molteplici modalità per tracciare uno stesso utente o quanto meno il medesimo dispositivo da questi adoperato. In un altro articolo abbiamo visto come funzionano le protezioni di Mozilla e Google attivabili da browser Web.Si chiama fingerprinting l'attività che permette di tracciare uno stesso utente durante i suoi spostamenti tra le pagine Web senza neppure ricorrere ai cookie. L'utente viene riconosciuto anche in tempi successivi (sessioni di lavoro sul Web differenti) o addirittura quando usa la modalità di navigazione in incognito.Come? Il browser fornisce alle applicazioni Web via via caricate l'accesso a un insieme di dati che danno indicazione circa la configurazione del sistema in uso.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox 102.0.1 release information]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179552</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/07/06/firefox-102-0-1-release-information/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T05:17:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla plans to release Firefox 102.0.1 later today. The first point release update for Firefox 102 fixes a number of bugs and stability issues. The release date is July 6, and if […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Firefox 102.0.1 release information appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Focus Assist Companion Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=493661</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15415007/focus-assist-companion-apps"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No matter which industry you work in, whether it’s in an office or at home, or what your job title is, you can benefit from spending more time in a state of concentration instead of constant distraction. Let’s face it: our computers are powerful tools that allow us to do incredible things, but they can also hijack our attention and prevent us from getting work done. Focus Assist is an integrated Windows option that can help, but there are plenty of other apps that work with the native app to ensure that you’re not distracted by third-party apps or the Internet.
   

Content

What Is Focus Assist?
Robust Focus Assist Companion Apps
Simplistic Focus Assist Companion Apps
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Use Windows 10 Focus Assist to Control Notifications
    
What Is Focus Assist?
    
In short,... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Yoder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Problem with the fonts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vscgx4/problem_with_the_fonts/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vscgx4/problem_with_the_fonts/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T00:19:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I got this problem where the fonts look fuzzy and thin, unlike windows 10 good looking out of the box fonts.
 I tried various things, read various articles, but just cant find the solution.
 Also my gpu is an nvidia card.
 Any ideas of how i could make it look good? Like in windows 10?
 I would also need to reset all the fonts, and xorg conf, since i touched many things there, and dont know how to do that also :/
 Any help would be appreciated :)
    submitted by    /u/Ramaax  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD Makes More RDNA3 GPU Driver Preparations For Linux 5.20]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMDGPU-More-RDNA3-For-5.20</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMDGPU-More-RDNA3-For-5.20"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T23:24:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AMD today sent out "new stuff" concerning their AMDGPU and AMDKFD kernel graphics and compute drivers to DRM-Next in preparation for the Linux 5.20 cycle kicking off in a few weeks...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[`pacman -Fx keyword` doesn't work with `| grep -v anotherword`]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vsah39/pacman_fx_keyword_doesnt_work_with_grep_v/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vsah39/pacman_fx_keyword_doesnt_work_with_grep_v/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T22:45:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So I want to know which package (the file or package may not be installed) owns a file such pacman -Fx /etc/pacman.conf will list  etc/pacman.conf is owned by core/pacman 6.0.1-5 
 but since I got several third party repos in my /etc/pacman.conf such as chaotic-aur, there will be over 50 lines like the following in the result  error: chaotic-aur database is inconsistent: version mismatch on package libshumate-git error: chaotic-aur database is inconsistent: version mismatch on package linux-next-git error: chaotic-aur database is inconsistent: version mismatch on package linux-next-git-headers error: chaotic-aur database is inconsistent: version mismatch on package linux-tt error: chaotic-aur database is inconsistent: version mismatch on package php80 error: chaotic-aur database is inconsistent: version mismatch on package php80-apache error: chaotic-aur database is inconsistent: version mismatch on package php80-bcmath error: chaotic-aur database is inconsistent: version mismatch on package php80-bz2 error: chaotic-aur database is inconsistent: version mismatch on package php80-calendar 
 I don't want to see the long list of ...database is inconsistent... lines from the result of pacman -F keyword, so I use command like pacman -F /etc/pacman.conf | grep -v "database is inconsistent: ", but it seems grep -v command doesn't work in this case.
 The database is inconsistent: issue from some repo in my /etc/pacman.conf occurs to me occasionally, most of the time I cannot get this fixed, and I can't be bothered fixing it any more, what I need is just hide the long lines oferror: from the result of pacman -Fx keyword command, so what can I do?
    submitted by    /u/CodyChan  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[System76 Announces New Alder Lake Laptop With Coreboot Firmware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=System76-ADL-Lemur-Pro</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=System76-ADL-Lemur-Pro"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T22:32:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[System76 has announced a new Lemur Pro laptop model that is now offering 12th Gen "Alder Lake" Intel processors while continuing to feature Coreboot firmware...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Issues installing MATLAB]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vsa5o2/issues_installing_matlab/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vsa5o2/issues_installing_matlab/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T22:30:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi there, 
 I've taken a look online at similar issues and followed all their suggestions, but I haven't had any success.
 The problem: MATLAB install says that there is an undefined symbol in the libcairo.so.2 library.
 Tried solutions: Reinstalling cairo, cairomm, freetype, and lib32-freetype
 ``` ./bin/glnxa64/MATLABWindow: symbol lookup error: /usr/lib/libcairo.so.2: undefined symbol: FT_Get_Color_Glyph_Layer ```
 ​
 Any advice would be appreciated
    submitted by    /u/bingbing_  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New RedAlert Ransomware targets Windows, Linux VMware ESXi servers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-redalert-ransomware-targets-windows-linux-vmware-esxi-servers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-redalert-ransomware-targets-windows-linux-vmware-esxi-servers/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T22:20:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new ransomware operation called RedAlert, or N13V, encrypts both Windows and Linux VMWare ESXi servers in attacks on corporate networks. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What do you use to take snip screenshot?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vs9tab/what_do_you_use_to_take_snip_screenshot/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vs9tab/what_do_you_use_to_take_snip_screenshot/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T22:15:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I hate using third party apps for basic operations such as screenshots. What light weight and simple screenshot tool do you use?
    submitted by    /u/sugmaJIFF  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crea una pendrive avviabile, per installare sistemi operativi e fare diagnostica, con Rufus]]></title>
        <id>667|20220706000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/windows-10/crea-pendrive-avviabile-installare-sistemi-operativi-fare-diagnostica-rufus-667"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sempre più spesso ci troviamo nella necessità di installare dei sistemi operativi in computer privi di lettore CD-Rom, per fortuna ci sono ormai molti programmi che ci permettono di trasferire l’immagine ISO, di un sistema operativo o di un supporto di utility di vario genere, in una pendrive avviabile. In questo articolo volevo parlarvi di Rufus piccolissimo applicativo, disponibile anche in versione portable, che permette di trasferire l’immagine ISO di moltissimi sistemi operativi, Windows e Linux, oltre a numerosi supporti che contengono utility di vario genere. Trovate una lista, non esaustiva, delle ISO supportate in fondo a questa pagina.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Convert HEIC to JPG in Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=279393</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/10771189/convert-heic-jpg-windows10"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most annoying things in computing is having files that cannot be used by applications on your computer. If this happens to you, then you know how frustrating it can be.
    
This is apparently the case with the new HEIF file format. Newer iPhones and iPads currently take pictures in HEIF (High-Efficiency Image Format) and save images with an HEIC extension. This format, with all its advantages, isn’t native to Windows, but you can quite easily convert HEIC files to JPG using Windows’ standard tools, like Photos and Paint (as well as myriad third-party apps).
    
With its ability to occupy very little storage space, it seems like an extension for the long run. If you hit a brick wall viewing HEIC files on Windows, try some of these ways to convert HEIC to JPG.
   

Content

Opening HEIC In Windows
1. Photos App
2. Paint
3. HEICtoJPEG Web App
4. HEIC Converter Free
5. iMazing HEIC Converter
6. iOS "Automatic" Transfer Mode
7. CopyTrans HEIC for Windows
8. iMobie HEIC Converter
9. GIMP
10. CloudConvert
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Megan Glosson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to jump to Microsoft Edge from Internet Explorer]]></title>
        <id>031d416f-bd48-4283-ae87-8eb52f29ea60</id>
        <link href="https://www.zdnet.com/article/how-to-jump-to-microsoft-edge-from-internet-explorer/#ftag=RSSbaffb68"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T21:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Internet Explorer no longer supported by Microsoft, here's how to jump ship to Microsoft Edge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest topics for ZDNet in Windows</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is a Smart Plug?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=730221</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/730221/what-is-a-smart-plug/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smart plugs make any appliance or device smarter by allowing you to control them remotely. You can track energy consumption, schedule when a device turns on and off, and control it with your voice.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Nguyen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Install Minecraft on Ubuntu or Any Other Linux Distribution]]></title>
        <id>http://www.howtogeek.com/?p=198476</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/198476/how-to-install-minecraft-on-ubuntu-or-any-other-linux-distribution/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Minecraft runs just fine on Linux, but it’s probably not available for easy installation in your Linux distribution’s package manager. Here’s how to get your Linux system ready for Minecraft.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Azure now has confidential VMs with ephemeral storage]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-azure-now-has-confidential-vms-with-ephemeral-storage/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-azure-now-has-confidential-vms-with-ephemeral-storage/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T19:40:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has expanded its confidential computing offering and is now allowing Azure cloud computing service customers to create hardware isolated virtual machines (aka confidential VMs) with Ephemeral OS disks. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Pixel's Next Update Is Timely Yet Late]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/122317/google-pixels-next-update-is-timely-yet-late/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/122317/google-pixels-next-update-is-timely-yet-late/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T19:39:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The slow trickle of new At a Glance features are always keeping Pixel owners on the edge of their seat. But an upcoming “Cross Device Timer” could take the smart widget a whole new level—soon, At a Glance will show you a countdown for timers made on Nest Hubs and other Google Assistant devices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Timeshift terminated by signal SIGSEGV (Address boundary error)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vs66p2/timeshift_terminated_by_signal_sigsegv_address/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vs66p2/timeshift_terminated_by_signal_sigsegv_address/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T19:37:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, I just built Timeshift from the AUR and I get this error when trying to execute it:
 [Warning] Deleted invalid lock ** (timeshift-gtk:9177): CRITICAL **: 16:31:14.785: string_strip: assertion 'self != NULL' failed (timeshift-gtk:9177): GLib-CRITICAL **: 16:31:14.785: g_str_has_prefix: assertion 'str != NULL' failed fish: Job 1, 'sudo timeshift-gtk' terminated by signal SIGSEGV (Address boundary error) 
 I've searched the web and found nothing that could help me. Tried rebuilding it and nothing.
 This is a semi-fresh Arch installation cause my previous one broke after an update and I wanna make a backup before I update again.
    submitted by    /u/LongSnakes  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pacman pause on "Reloading system manager configuration..."]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vs635v/pacman_pause_on_reloading_system_manager/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vs635v/pacman_pause_on_reloading_system_manager/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T19:32:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi
 I was wondering if anyone can shed some light as to why pacman pauses (roughly 1-2 minutes) on the step "Reloading system manager configuration..." during an upgrade process? I can't seem to find any clues as to what it's blocking/waiting for.
 Thanks
    submitted by    /u/Zatie12  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get an Amazon Echo Show 5 Kids for Under $39]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=502448</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15414691/amazon-echo-show-5-kids"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are your kids already bored this summer? They don’t have to be. You can get them an Echo Show 5 Kids for just $39.99. And at that price, you can get one for each of your children. They can watch videos, have access to Alexa, make video calls, get homework help, and more.
    
Forget your worries about your children having this type of device, as easy-to-use parental controls are included, allowing you to set bedtimes and time limits, filter for certain content, and review your kids’ activity. Amazon will not sell your personal information to others, and the device has multiple layers of privacy controls. You can even shut off the mic and camera.
   
 
   
Your kids will certainly be entertained on the Echo Show 5 Kids. It includes one year of Amazon Kids+ that gives them thousands of videos, audiobooks, games, music stations, etc. After the first year, your subscription will automatically renew for $4.99 a month plus tax. But you can cancel at any time if you decide it’s too much.
... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Open JAR Files on Windows 10 and 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=812583</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/812583/how-to-open-jar-files-windows/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T19:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Windows 10 and Windows 11, JAR files don’t open by default as there are no built-in apps to handle this file format. But, you can install the free Java utility and access this file format on your PC. We’ll show you the process to do that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Share Notes on iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=811950</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/811950/how-to-share-notes-on-iphone/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T18:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you want to share a copy of your note with someone, or you want to invite someone to collaborate on your notes with you, your iPhone’s Notes app allows you to do both. We’ll show you how to use those Notes’ features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NPM supply-chain attack impacts hundreds of websites and apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/npm-supply-chain-attack-impacts-hundreds-of-websites-and-apps/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/npm-supply-chain-attack-impacts-hundreds-of-websites-and-apps/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T17:55:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An NPM supply-chain attack dating back to December 2021 used dozens of malicious NPM modules containing obfuscated Javascript code to compromise hundreds of downstream desktop apps and websites. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lennart Poettering - systemd + PulseAudio Creator - Departed Red Hat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Lennart-Poettering-Out-Red-Hat</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Lennart-Poettering-Out-Red-Hat"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T17:30:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To much surprise, the lead developer of systemd Lennart Poettering who also led the creation of PulseAudio, Avahi, and has been a prolific free software contributor has reportedly left Red Hat...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Chrome Keyboard Shortcuts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=cheatsheet&amp;p=152827</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15414568/google-chrome-keyboard-shortcuts"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T17:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Chrome is one of the most widely used browser on both PC and mobile. If you’re a Chrome user, you must be familiar with at least the basic keyboard shortcuts like opening a new tab, checking history, and so on. In this cheatsheet, we will cover almost all the available keyboard shortcuts for Google Chrome on Windows and macOS.
    
We have divided the shortcuts into various sections like tabs, display, bookmarks, windows, etc., to make the shortcuts easier to find and remember.
       

WindowsmacOSFunction

Window Shortcuts
Ctrl + NCommand + NOpen a new window.
Ctrl + Shift + NCommand + Shift + NOpen a new window in Incognito mode.
Ctrl + Shift + W or Alt + F4Command + Shift + WClose the current window.
Alt + Space then NCommand + MMinimize the current window.
Alt + Space then XMaximize the current window.
Alt + F then XCommand + QQuit Google Chrome.
Command + HHide Google Chrome.
Tabs
Ctrl + TCommand + TOpen a new tab.
Ctrl + Shift + TCommand + Shift + TReopen previously closed tabs one by one.
Ctrl + Tab or Ctrl + PgDnCommand + Option + Right arrowJump to the next open tab.
Ctrl + Shift... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mehvish Mushtaq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quick Tip: restore system desktop icons on Windows 10 and 11 PCs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179549</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/07/05/quick-tip-restore-system-desktop-icons-on-windows-10-and-11-pcs/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T17:18:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vanilla Windows 10 and 11 PCs display desktop icons by default on the first run after installation. Manufacturers may place custom icons on the desktop, but if you install one of the […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Quick Tip: restore system desktop icons on Windows 10 and 11 PCs appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Freevee's Latest Free Channels Features Cooking, Music, and Nostalgia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/122303/freevees-latest-free-channels-features-cooking-music-and-nostalgia/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/122303/freevees-latest-free-channels-features-cooking-music-and-nostalgia/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T17:12:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Freevee, Amazon’s free streaming service formally known as IMDB TV, has always offered free content to watch with ads. But “free” doesn’t mean much without something actually good watch. Now the service is getting ready to add even more, and there’s a little something for everyone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Hendrickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Check Out This Drag Racing VW Beetle EV]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/122302/check-out-this-drag-racing-vw-beetle-ev/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/122302/check-out-this-drag-racing-vw-beetle-ev/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T17:02:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While it may sound a bit odd, people really like to convert old VW Beetles into electric drag-racers. The practice goes back twenty years, and back in 2011, two brothers shocked the world with their Black Current III electric Beetle. Now they’re back with an even more ridiculous car, the “V8-killing” Black Current IV.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Change the RDP Port on Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=814556</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/814556/how-to-change-the-rdp-port-on-windows-11/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T17:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’d like to access your Windows 11 PC remotely, it’s easy to do thanks to Remote Desktop Protocol (RDP), which comes with Pro and Enterprise versions of Microsoft’s OS. Although the default RDP port is 3389, there are times when you might want to change it. Here’s how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video sorveglianza con WebCam PC e telecamere IP: migliori programmi]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2008/09/video-sorveglianza-con-la-webcam-i.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2008/09/video-sorveglianza-con-la-webcam-i.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T16:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Con le telecamere IP o con le webcam del PC è possibile creare un vero e proprio sistema di sorveglianza low cost, gestito dal computer di casa. I programmi di questa lista, tutti gratuiti, permettono di gestire più telecamere o webcam contemporaneamente e sono in grado anche di registrare video o scattare foto quando vengono rilevati movimenti.

 Diventa quindi possibile creare un sistema di...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft quietly fixes ShadowCoerce Windows NTLM Relay bug]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-quietly-fixes-shadowcoerce-windows-ntlm-relay-bug/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-quietly-fixes-shadowcoerce-windows-ntlm-relay-bug/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T16:17:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has confirmed it fixed a previously disclosed 'ShadowCoerce' vulnerability as part of the June 2022 updates that enabled attackers to target Windows servers in NTLM relay attacks. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ASUS' New Wireless Earbuds Can Convert to Wired Listening]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/122293/asus-new-wireless-earbuds-can-convert-to-wired-listening/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/122293/asus-new-wireless-earbuds-can-convert-to-wired-listening/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T16:06:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wireless headphones are convenient, but they’re rarely the best option for gamers. Even the best Bluetooth audio codecs come with a bit of latency, and if you want to game without laggy audio, you have to deal with a drop in sound quality. The solution, at least in ASUS’ eyes, may be simpler than you expect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Started With firewalld on Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=807545</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/807545/how-to-get-started-with-firewalld-on-linux/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T16:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re looking for a modern, powerful firewall for Linux that is easy to configure on the command line or with its GUI interface, then firewalld is probably what you’re looking for.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKay</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Filesystem type exfat not configured in kernel." error suddenly when trying to mount external drive with udisks2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vs0j4k/filesystem_type_exfat_not_configured_in_kernel/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vs0j4k/filesystem_type_exfat_not_configured_in_kernel/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T15:29:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[it just suddenly gave me this error:
 failed to mount /org/freedesktop/UDisks2/block_devices/sdb1: GDBus.Error:org.freedesktop.UDisks2.Error.Failed: Error mounting /dev/sdb1 at /run/media/user/drive: Filesystem type exfat not configured in kernel. 
 it was working before I updated using sudo pacman -Syu, I'm guessing something changed with the kernel?
    submitted by    /u/ImALoooserOk  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[9 Charging Stands for Your Apple Watch]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=post-ideas&amp;p=481594</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15414326/apple-watch-charging-stands"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you in the market for a docking station or charging stand for your Apple Watch? We came up with a list of options, at various price points, for you to choose from. We’ll tell you what each docking station can do for your Apple Watch and the rest of your (compatible) Apple devices.
   

Content

What Is a Docking Station and When Do You Need One?
1. Lamicall Apple Watch Charging Stand
2. Conido Charging Stand
3. JackCube Design Wooden Charging Stand
4. OLEBR 3-in-1 Charging Station
5. WAITIEE 3-in-1 Wireless Charging Station
6. Belkin Boost Charge Pro Portable Fast Charger
7. Apple Watch Magnetic Charging Dock
8. MagSafe Duo Charger
9. Belkin Boost Charge Pro 3-in-1 Wireless Charger with MagSafe
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:What Is a GaN Charger? 5 of the Best GaN... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Natalie dela Vega</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Error installing Arch into Docker]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vs0cct/error_installing_arch_into_docker/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vs0cct/error_installing_arch_into_docker/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T15:21:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following steps at https://wiki.archlinux.org/title/Install_Arch_Linux_via_Docker I am trying to install Arch into a Docker container. Here's what I've done:
 mkdir /arch_docker docker run \ --env PS1="ADC(\#)[\d \T:\w]\\$ " \ --interactive \ --privileged \ --rm \ --tty \ --volume "/arch_docker:/target" \ "index.docker.io/library/archlinux:latest" /bin/sh # inside ADC: pacman -Sy reflector reflector > /etc/pacman.d/mirrorlist pacman -S arch-install-scripts pacstrap /target base 
 What I am getting from pacstrap command:
 ==> Creating install root at /target mount: /target/dev: permission denied. dmesg(1) may have more information after failed mount system call. ==> ERROR: failed to setup chroot /target 
 Did I miss something or the wiki instructions are incomplete? dmesg did not reveal any additional information.
    submitted by    /u/Revolutionary_Gur583  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ghacks Deals: The Game Design & Development Bundle]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179545</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/07/05/ghacks-deals-the-game-design-development-bundle/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T15:08:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Game Design & Development Bundle includes seven eLearning courses that take you from game design and development beginner to creating your own computer games. Here is the list of the seven […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Ghacks Deals: The Game Design & Development Bundle appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How do I expand my EFI file system to fill the partition?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vs01y9/how_do_i_expand_my_efi_file_system_to_fill_the/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vs01y9/how_do_i_expand_my_efi_file_system_to_fill_the/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T15:08:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm using the Windows EFI partition but I wanted to expand it a bit, so I downloaded the Gparted Live ISO and went ahead and did that. Now the partition is expanded, but the EFI file system hasn't changed size and still only shows as the Windows default of 100MB free. How can I change that?
 Edit: Fixed! Evidently, there's a "bug" with Gparted making it so that small partitions can't be resized properly - https://bugzilla.gnome.org/show_bug.cgi?id=649324.
 I roughly followed the steps in comment 4 of the bug to get the EFI file system expanded.
 My steps:
  
Back up contents of /boot - I did # dd if=/dev/nvme0n1p1 of=/backup/nvme0n1p1.img then # cp -r /boot ~/boot-backup.
 Re-format the EFI partition to EXT4 - # mkfs.ext4 /dev/nvme0n1p1.
 Re-size the newly-created EXT4 partition to the correct size - for my scenario, I opened Gparted and ran the "check" function on the new EXT4 partition. (I'm not sure if this step was necessary but whatever).
 Reformat the partition back to FAT32 - # mkfs.fat -F 32 /dev/nvme0n1p1.
 Restore the EFI partition files from the backup - # cp -r ~/boot-backup/* /boot
  
Possibly required steps in no particular order
  
Modify /etc/fstab for the new PARTUUID of the EFI partition
 Modify bootloader to check the correct partition - I use rEFInd so I had to edit the volumefield in my Arch configuration stanza to the new PARTUUID. 
  
After that, everything seems to be working but I still have the original backup created with dd for now in case I messed something up that I haven't noticed yet.
 If you need to restore the original partition - # dd if=/backup/nvme0n1p1.img of=/dev/nvme0n1p1 which (I think) should restore the entire original partition to how it was.
 I'd probably keep a flash drive with ARCHISO on-hand if you need to do this, but YMMV.
 EDIT2: Evidently, the Arch fatresize package may be able to do the same thing without copying the partition around... so maybe try that first.
    submitted by    /u/NormGreen  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Things You Didn’t Know You Could Do in PowerPoint]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=808441</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/808441/things-you-didnt-know-you-could-do-in-powerpoint/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T15:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some features in Microsoft PowerPoint stand out like creating animations, adding slide transitions, and inserting charts, shapes, and 3D models. But then there are those features that are a bit hidden.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monitorare gli spostamenti dei bambini anche in vacanza con lo smartwatch Xplora X5 Play]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Monitorare-gli-spostamenti-dei-bambini-anche-in-vacanza-con-lo-smartwatch-Xplora-X5-Play_24743</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Monitorare-gli-spostamenti-dei-bambini-anche-in-vacanza-con-lo-smartwatch-Xplora-X5-Play_24743"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T14:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Difficile non preoccuparsi quando non si sa dove sono i propri figli, soprattutto i più piccoli: bastano pochi secondi di distrazione in spiaggia, mentre si fa una gita, durante un'escursione in montagna, mentre giocano al parco o si è in viaggio ed eccoli sparire. Tanti particolari possono incuriosirli, attirare la loro attenzione e spingerli ad allontanarsi. Per monitorare gli spostamenti dei bambini ed essere un po’ più tranquilli, soprattutto durante un periodo di vacanza, è possibile dotarsi di uno smartwatch come Xplora X5 Play, un dispositivo ideato per i bambini che offre solo le funzioni di comunicazione necessarie. È dotato di un chip GPS integrato che consente ai genitori, grazie all'app collegata, di sapere sempre dove sono i propri figli. 

Con al polso lo smartwatch Xplora X5 Play i bambini hanno la possibilità di essere più indipendenti e autonomi senza preoccupare la famiglia: è possibile anche creare delle zone di sicurezza per ricevere una notifica ogni volta che il minore entra o esce dalle aree preimpostate. Xplora X5 Play è uno smartwatch leggerissimo con funzioni di cellulare e connettività dati 4G, in grado di ricevere e inviare messaggi vocali, messaggi di testo pre-salvati, fotografie ed emoji.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Slashes Trade-In Value Ahead of iPhone 14 Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/122290/apple-slashes-trade-in-value-ahead-of-iphone-14-launch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/122290/apple-slashes-trade-in-value-ahead-of-iphone-14-launch/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T14:49:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you were hoping to get a good trade-in value for your old iPhone—tough luck. Apple quietly adjusted the maximum trade-in rates for all of its devices, including the iPhone, iPad, Mac, and Apple Watch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JBL Live Pro 2 TWS Review: All About That Bass]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/122017/jbl-live-pro-2-tws-review/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/122017/jbl-live-pro-2-tws-review/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T14:24:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Incredible bass? Check. Hefty battery life? Check. Noise canceling? Check. When clear, uninterrupted sound matters most, the JBL Live Pro 2 TWS earbuds deliver. These earbuds feature JBL’s Signature Sound, adaptive noise canceling, and wireless charging capabilities among many other features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brenna Miles</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>