<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-06-15T02:03:57.401Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to find Chrome rendered font?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcjh2w/how_to_find_chrome_rendered_font/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcjh2w/how_to_find_chrome_rendered_font/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T02:01:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Firefox, there is Inspector->Fonts tab.
 In Chrome, there is no Fonts tab. This post says chrome has Element->Computed -> Rendered Fonts, but on my box (version 102.x). Did chrome remove this functionality, or move it somewhere else?
    submitted by    /u/notnullnone  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Panda Wireless PAU09 & Arch Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcis4s/panda_wireless_pau09_arch_linux/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcis4s/panda_wireless_pau09_arch_linux/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T01:25:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have had many many problems getting the PAU09 to work on arch, sometimes it works for hours, other times not at all, and some times for a few minutes, after that dmesg is either spammed with rt2x00usb_vendor_request: Error - Vendor request 0x07 failed for offset 0x101c with error -110 or rt2800usb_fill_rxdone: Error - Bad frame size (varying number), forcing to 0, rt2x00lib_rxdone: Error - Wrong frame size 0 max 3840
 Please help, as I can not stay online for long without getting disconnected
    submitted by    /u/Official_Nugget  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SSD vs. SSHD: Are Hybrid Drives Worth It in 2022?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=post-ideas&amp;p=350605</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/13762015/ssd-vs-sshd-are-hybrid-drives-worth-it"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In only a few years, the solid state disks (SSD) have nearly replaced magnetic hard disks (HDD) as the default storage option in laptops and PCs. However, there is also now an option of a solid state hybrid drive (SSHD), offering the best of SSD and HDD. So which one is better? The only way to find out is through a head-to-head comparison as shown here. 
   

Content

Differences Between SSD and SSHD
1. Raw Speed Comparison
2. Benchmark Speed Comparison
3. Load Time Comparison 
4. Price vs. Capacity Comparison
5. Life Expectancy: SSD vs. SSHD
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:SSD vs. HDD vs. USB Flash Drive: Everything You Need to Know
    
Differences Between SSD and SSHD
    
SSD is flash storage similar to a USB drive but is much... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sayak Boral</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ransomware gang creates site for employees to search for their stolen data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ransomware-gang-creates-site-for-employees-to-search-for-their-stolen-data/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ransomware-gang-creates-site-for-employees-to-search-for-their-stolen-data/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T23:03:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ALPHV ransomware gang, aka BlackCat, has brought extortion to a new level by creating a dedicated website that allows the customers and employees of their victim to check if their data was stolen in an attack [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zoom windows are magic cloaks? (screen sharing issues)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcfutj/zoom_windows_are_magic_cloaks_screen_sharing/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcfutj/zoom_windows_are_magic_cloaks_screen_sharing/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T22:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sharing my whole screen in Zoom is somewhat broken for me, as Zoom's own windows obscure the stream in weird ways. I noticed this running it with dwm, but easily reproduced it with KDE Plasma.
 For background on how the program works, there are three windows involved: - The screen sharing overlay, on all desktops. Present when screen sharing. - The meeting overlay, on all desktops. Present when screen sharing. - The Zoom home menu. Functions as a normal window with normal window decorations.
 Issues with sharing the whole screen in KDE Plasma: - The panel rendering is inconsistent. On occasion it will disappear or go black in the stream. See this host view (pink censoring added in editing). - On any desktop other than the first, parts of the stream are obscured by the Zoom overlays. Within…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Proton 7.0-3 With More Games Running Well On Linux, Experimental Preps More Changes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Proton-7.0-3-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Proton-7.0-3-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T22:31:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Valve today promoted Proton 7.0-3 to stable as the newest version of this software based on Wine and leveraging DXVK / VKD3D-Proton and other components for running Windows games with great success on Linux. Proton 7.0-3 is now available for Steam Play when firing up the Steam client while Valve also today issued a new Proton Experimental update...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[arch is stuck too much !!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcf302/arch_is_stuck_too_much/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcf302/arch_is_stuck_too_much/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T22:16:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, my arch stucks too much and I can do nothing. When it happens I see that the clock seconds is frozen (not changing) I can't even use my system like that ! anyone got that problem ??
 I use gnome 42.2 BTW. If you need any command to troubleshoot tell me!
    submitted by    /u/Spare_Prize1148  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GIMP 2.10.32 Released With JPEG-XL Backported & Other Work While Waiting On GIMP 3.0]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=GIMP-2.10.32-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=GIMP-2.10.32-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T22:12:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have been writing about GIMP 3.0 for nearly a decade and with that stable release still out of sight, GIMP 2.10.32 is out as a six-month update to the aging GIMP 2.10 stable series...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adobe Photoshop Might Soon Be Available for Free]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=811617</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/811617/adobe-photoshop-might-soon-be-available-for-free/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T21:37:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adobe Photoshop has been a paid product for its entire lifetime (unless you sail on the high seas), but now the company is testing a free version accessible through the web.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Broadcom]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vce2b6/broadcom/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vce2b6/broadcom/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T21:27:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So I have a MacBook Pro 7,1 and it has a bcm4322 Wi-Fi card I’ve tried broadcom-wl and broadcom-wl-dkms and b43-firmware but I can’t get Wi-Fi to work after a reboot I’ve tried everything such as blacklisting modules and I’m just kind of stuck…
    submitted by    /u/Expensive_Pudding846  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows Security Not Opening in Windows? Here are 6 Fixes]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=488171</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15368624/fix-windows-security-not-opening"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows Security, which also includes an antivirus program known as Windows Defender, is designed to protect your PC from viruses and malware. But just like other Windows apps, it can run into problems.
    
One of the issues is Windows Security failing to start. Fortunately, we have some quick fixes for you.
   

Content

1. Reset or Repair Windows Security
2. Use SFC and DISM
3. Disable Background Apps
4. Disable and Uninstall Third-Party Security Tools
5. Install the Latest Windows Updates
6. Restart Windows Security Center Service
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:The Best Windows 10 and 11 Easter Eggs to Seek Out
    
1. Reset or Repair Windows Security
    
Windows 11 comes with a native repair tool that can identify minor issues in apps and resolve them automatically. Windows Security is no exception.... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Kanyoro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are the mirrors throttling me?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcdmsc/are_the_mirrors_throttling_me/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcdmsc/are_the_mirrors_throttling_me/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T21:06:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey folks! So I have lately installed arch about a dozen times and the same thing keeps happening to me, no matter if I change my PC, network, am in a VM or on real hardware. To my knowledge the arch iso updates the mirrors once. Everytime my download rate starts at 50mb/s which gets the job done really quickly, but over the course of 10-30s it goes down to just 100kb/s and stays at that rate. Which surprisingly only happens with Arch. Am I being throttled in some way or another and is there a way to fix this issue, as it makes the download take an hour or two instead of the 3 minutes it would usually take. Thanks :)
    submitted by    /u/OakArtz  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Change Windows 10’s Wallpaper Without Activation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=717894</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/717894/how-to-change-windows-10s-wallpaper-without-activation/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you use an unactivated copy of Windows 10, you know that you can’t change your desktop wallpaper using the Settings app. But there’s a workaround to change the desktop background on an unactivated copy of Windows 10.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Is NVIDIA Shield TV so Expensive?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120880/why-is-nvidia-shield-tv-so-expensive/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120880/why-is-nvidia-shield-tv-so-expensive/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T20:56:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most streaming sticks from Roku, Google, and Amazon cost less than $50 and support 4K video. But the NVIDIA Shield TV starts at $150, a price that’s only matched by Apple TV boxes. It’s an outrageous amount of money to pay for a streaming stick, but still, the NVIDIA Shield TV is worth every penny.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Requesting thoughts + answers about double GPU]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vccb3o/requesting_thoughts_answers_about_double_gpu/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vccb3o/requesting_thoughts_answers_about_double_gpu/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T20:08:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So ever since I built my 1st system I've wanted to do xfire. I hear negative things about it and until now my GPU was 3x what I paid for it thanks to coin miners. Now prices are starting to settle down and I can get an identical graphics card for a realistic price. So I have questions/would like thoughts about the pros and cons of this setup.
 I mostly use my computer to work but also for gaming. I have 2 monitors + 2 tvs that I use for screens. I recently switched over to Arch as my base system and load various OSes via VMs which I really, really enjoy. 
 The problem is I don't know how much a 2nd GPU would help me or if it would do more harm than good. I understand it would use much more energy, have little payoff in terms of framerate, but am considering it both for xfire, passthru, and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Relative newbie to Arch, but computer-literate1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcc7zk/relative_newbie_to_arch_but_computerliterate1/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcc7zk/relative_newbie_to_arch_but_computerliterate1/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T20:04:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi,
 I've been dicking with computers for around 45 years, so no not a newbie in that sense.
 Then I migrated from Mandriva, through Magiea, and then into Ubuntu.
 Now trying for the first time to install raw Arch. Tried six times on my old BIOS-boot netbook and once in a UEFI-boot virtual machine on my current whoop-de-whoop laptop.
 On all of these, everything goes swimmingly, until the point when I exit the chroot environment and then reboot. All I ever then get is a 'grub' prompt rather than a usable OS!
 I'm guessing I've either missed a step, or something else is messed up. Assistance would be welcome.
    submitted by    /u/Bytebrother  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Copy Files to a USB Flash Drive on a Mac]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=720039</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/720039/how-to-copy-files-to-a-usb-flash-drive-on-a-mac/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’d like to copy files to a USB flash drive on a Mac so you can transfer them to another machine or back them up, it’s easy to do using Finder in macOS. Here’s how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Single Beaver Caused Internet Outages in Canada]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=811604</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/811604/a-single-beaver-caused-internet-outages-in-canada/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T19:58:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Internet outages are common, especially in rural areas where it can take a while for internet service providers to find the source of a problem. That just happened earlier this month in Canada, where a beaver was responsible for a long-lasting internet outage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Hertzbleed side-channel attack affects Intel, AMD CPUs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-hertzbleed-side-channel-attack-affects-intel-amd-cpus/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-hertzbleed-side-channel-attack-affects-intel-amd-cpus/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T19:55:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new side-channel attack known as Hertzbleed allows remote attackers to steal full cryptographic keys by observing variations in CPU frequency enabled by dynamic voltage and frequency scaling (DVFS). [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My NUC server, plugged into a monitor, doesn't display anything until the Arch login prompt, skipping boot screens and the screen where I can choose what disk to boot into. How can I fix this?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcbutr/my_nuc_server_plugged_into_a_monitor_doesnt/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcbutr/my_nuc_server_plugged_into_a_monitor_doesnt/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T19:47:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Problem: My NUC server, plugged into a monitor, doesn't display anything until the login prompt, skipping boot screens and the screen where I can choose what disk to boot into.
 Background: I installed Arch on a NUC and plugged in a keyboard (USB) and a monitor (Mini Display Port on the NUC to HDMI on the monitor). Nothing appears on the monitor until I get to the login prompt, so it skips right over the NUC splash screen and the screen that lets me select what disk to boot into. Very rarely if I turn on the monitor and the NUC at exactly the right times with respect to each other, I can see the disk selection screen for a brief moment. And if I press any keys to prevent the system from getting to the arch login prompt (e.g. F2/ F10/ <Down + enter> to enter the firmware options screen), then nothing at all appears on my screen at any point. It's not even a black screen - the monitor is telling me there is no input whatsoever (except, like I said, when the the login screen appears.)
 Occasionally I also see some of the logs for a moment before the login (the ones starting with [ok]
 ).
 My question: I want to be able to select a different disk to boot from (e.g. a. USB with arch.iso so I can reinstall arch) but I can't access the screen to do that. Any ideas?
 What I've tried: Holding shift on startup; using a different Mini-DP to HDMI cable; plugging into my television's HDMI instead of the monitor
    submitted by    /u/_cs  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Laptop energy saving TLP package. Any experienced here?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcbo0y/laptop_energy_saving_tlp_package_any_experienced/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcbo0y/laptop_energy_saving_tlp_package_any_experienced/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T19:39:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello!
 It is my intention to install in my laptop with Arch in order to save battery the package TLP (https://wiki.archlinux.org/title/TLP) and I wanted to know your experiences with this software.
 The package is presented as a install-and-forget. That is pretty anti-arch philosophy, so I wanted to read some opinion/experience with it.
 Alternatives are welcome, my main way to save energy right now is to low the brightness. It ain't much but it's honest work.
 Thank you all!
    submitted by    /u/HansDCJ  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Android malware on the Google Play Store gets 2 million downloads]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/android-malware-on-the-google-play-store-gets-2-million-downloads/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/android-malware-on-the-google-play-store-gets-2-million-downloads/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T19:36:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered adware and information-stealing malware on the Google Play Store last month, with at least five still available and having amassed over two million downloads. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save $60 on an Amazon Fire HD 10 Kids Tablet]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=426537</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/14739303/amazon-fire-hd-10-kids-pro-tablet"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is your child already bored and looking for stuff to do this summer? Consider an Amazon Fire HD 10 Kids Tablet to keep their minds sharp during the summer months. They can have their own tablet – yet one that will be safe as well, eliminating your parental concerns.
    
Bear in mind that this is in no way a child’s toy. It’s a full-featured tablet for ages 6 through 12. It has an octa-core processor, 3GB RAM, and a 10.1″ Full HD display with strengthened aluminosilicate, dual cameras, and USB-C port. The storage is expandable up to 1 TB. You’ll have no concerns about the tablet breaking, as it carries a two-year worry-free guarantee.
   
 
   
A one-year Amazon Kids+ subscription is included with the Fire 10 Kids Tablet. It unlocks more than 20,000 apps, games, books, videos, songs, and audiobooks. The purchase includes educational content from PBS Kids, Nickelodeon, Disney, and more. The subscription will automatically renew after one year, when you will be charged $4.99 plus tax monthly. Easily cancel at... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bluetooth earphones connected but make no sound]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcavsh/bluetooth_earphones_connected_but_make_no_sound/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcavsh/bluetooth_earphones_connected_but_make_no_sound/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T19:03:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi there, I am one of the arch newbies and I am in the phase of switching from Windows to a Linux distro.
 I decided to install arch today.
 However, when I try to connect my bluetooth earphones, they are connected but make no sound.
 Can someone help me?
 Thanks.
    submitted by    /u/AsuxAX  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Delete Videos on Facebook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=810067</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/810067/how-to-delete-videos-on-facebook/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T19:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Regret uploading that video to Facebook that you thought was funny? No worries, you can always delete the videos you’ve uploaded to your Facebook account. You can do this from both your desktop and your mobile, and we’ll show you how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 KB5014697 update adds Spotlight for Desktop, fixes 33 bugs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-kb5014697-update-adds-spotlight-for-desktop-fixes-33-bugs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-kb5014697-update-adds-spotlight-for-desktop-fixes-33-bugs/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T18:18:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has released the Windows 11 KB5014697 cumulative update with security updates, improvements, and the new Spotlight for Desktop feature that automatically changes your desktop background. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Windows Security Updates June 2022 overview]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179174</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/14/microsoft-windows-security-updates-june-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T18:04:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft released security updates and non-security updates for all client and server versions of Windows on the June 2022 Patch Day. Other Microsoft products, including Visual Studio, SQL Server, Windows Autopilot, Microsoft […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Microsoft Windows Security Updates June 2022 overview appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 10 KB5014699 and KB5014692 updates released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-10-kb5014699-and-kb5014692-updates-released/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-10-kb5014699-and-kb5014692-updates-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T18:02:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has released the Windows 10 KB5014699 and KB5014692 cumulative updates for versions 21H2, version 21H1, version 20H2, and 1809 to fix security vulnerabilities and resolve bugs. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mayank Parmar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Unblock a Number on Android]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=810057</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/810057/how-to-unblock-a-number-on-android/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T18:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’d like to start receiving calls and text messages from a blocked number, you’ll have to unblock that number on your Android phone. It’s quick and easy to do this on most phones and we’ll show you how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft patches actively exploited Follina Windows zero-day]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-patches-actively-exploited-follina-windows-zero-day/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-patches-actively-exploited-follina-windows-zero-day/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T18:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has released security updates with the June 2022 cumulative Windows Updates to address a critical Windows zero-day vulnerability known as Follina and actively exploited in ongoing attacks. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft June 2022 Patch Tuesday fixes 1 zero-day, 55 flaws]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-june-2022-patch-tuesday-fixes-1-zero-day-55-flaws/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-june-2022-patch-tuesday-fixes-1-zero-day-55-flaws/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T17:45:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today is Microsoft's June 2022 Patch Tuesday, and with it comes fixes for 55 vulnerabilities, including fixes for the Windows MSDT 'Follina' zero-day vulnerability and new Intel MMIO flaws. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux Patched For New Intel "MMIO Stale Data" Vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=MMIO-Stale-Data-Vulnerabilities</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=MMIO-Stale-Data-Vulnerabilities"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T17:39:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In addition to the Hertzbleed frequency scaling side-channel attack being made public today as part of "Patch Tuesday" and affecting both Intel and AMD CPUs, Intel is additionally disclosing a set of "MMIO Stale Data" vulnerabilities. The Linux kernel has already been patched for these new vulnerabilities affecting multiple generations of Intel CPUs from Rocket Lake back to Haswell X and Skylake...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Browser-Based Photoshop Will Be Free for Everyone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120873/browser-based-photoshop-will-be-free-for-everyone/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120873/browser-based-photoshop-will-be-free-for-everyone/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T17:29:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adobe Photoshop will soon be free for everyone, thanks to a basic web-based version of the app. The company is currently testing the free trial in Canada, where those interested can access the suite of Photoshop editing tools from a web browser.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft PowerPoint Keyboard Shortcuts]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=485212</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15368403/powerpoint-keyboard-shortcuts"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T17:25:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft PowerPoint has remained the “go to” presentation app since Microsoft first released it in 1990. Despite its wild success, Microsoft PowerPoint can be a bit of a pain to navigate at times, both when creating and presenting your work. However, knowing some of the commonly used keyboard shortcuts for the program can help you save time and energy while you prepare and present your next PowerPoint at work or on the go.
   
   
  
Download this Cheatsheet
 Enter your email below to receive this PDF cheatsheet in your Inbox.
     
  
  
   
                   #cheatsheet-box{border:1px solid #ddd;background-color:#d9edf7;}              ... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Megan Glosson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Siti per comprare componenti PC al miglior prezzo]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2018/07/siti-per-comprare-componenti-pc.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2018/07/siti-per-comprare-componenti-pc.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T17:24:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon è un punto di riferimento per tutti gli utenti che vogliono assemblare un PC partendo da zero e acquistando tutte le componenti necessarie per l'assemblaggio, ma i prezzi non sempre sono i più economici disponibili, in particolare con le schede video e le schede madri.

 Per poter realizzare il nostro futuro PC fisso (magari dedicato al gaming) con tutte le componenti necessarie spendendo...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keychron's Q5 QMK Keyboard Offers Full-Sized Functionality In a Small Package]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120869/keychrons-q5-qmk-keyboard-offers-full-sized-functionality-in-a-small-package/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120869/keychrons-q5-qmk-keyboard-offers-full-sized-functionality-in-a-small-package/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T17:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Keychron just added an impressive new keyboard to its mechanical arsenal. The Q5 QMK comes in the rare 1800 (96%) layout, offering full-sized features like a function row and numpad in a compact package. Of course, it’s also fully customizable, has a backlight, and comes with Gateron G Pro switches.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hertzbleed Disclosed As New Family Of Side-Channel Attacks Affecting Intel + AMD]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Hertzbleed</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Hertzbleed"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T17:12:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hertzbleed has been made public today as a new family of side-channel attacks making use of frequency side channels. Both Intel and AMD have issued security advisories as a result...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gaming vs. Regular Mouse Pads: What’s the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=803040</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/803040/gaming-vs-regular-mouse-pads/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T17:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mouse pads are very cheap compared to other computer accessories. You can find gaming and regular pads around the same size for as low as $5-10. The price increases in size, so if you’re looking at a large pad, it’ll be about $20-30 with extra-large options around $40.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Nguyen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Verizon Will Boost 5G Service With More Mid-Band Frequencies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=811441</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/811441/verizon-will-boost-5g-service-with-more-mid-band-frequencies/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T16:50:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rollout of 5G networks in the United States has been slow-moving, especially for Verizon and AT&T. However, Verizon is now testing a new network feature that should improve coverage in some areas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram founder criticizes Apple for web app limitations on iOS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179169</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/14/telegram-founder-criticizes-apple-safari-on-ios/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T16:35:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram founder Pavel Durov has criticized Apple for limiting web developers on iOS and iPadOS. He isn't the first to lash out at Safari on iOS. Apple's mobile browser has been slammed […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Telegram founder criticizes Apple for web app limitations on iOS appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ford Halts All Mustang Mach-E Sales Over Dangerous Battery Malfunction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120861/ford-halts-all-mustang-mach-e-sales-over-dangerous-battery-malfunction/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120861/ford-halts-all-mustang-mach-e-sales-over-dangerous-battery-malfunction/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T16:35:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ford has issued a stop-sale order and instructed all dealers to temporarily stop selling or demoing the popular new Mustang Mach-E over safety concerns that it could lose power while in motion, among other things.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ghacks Deals: Surfshark VPN 2-4 year subscriptions 80% off]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179172</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/14/ghacks-deals-surfshark-vpn-2-4-year-subscriptions-80-off/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T16:32:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mike reviewed Surfshark's VPN service back in October 2021 and concluded that it offered good options and performance. Now is your chance to grab a 2-year, 3-year or 4-year Surfshark subscription for […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Ghacks Deals: Surfshark VPN 2-4 year subscriptions 80% off appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox Now Protects Its Users From Third Party Cookies by Default]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120859/firefox-now-protects-its-users-from-third-party-cookies-by-default/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120859/firefox-now-protects-its-users-from-third-party-cookies-by-default/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T16:16:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Firefox desktop browser now enables Total Cookie Protection by default. This feature, which initially launched in 2021 to enhance the security of Private Browsing mode, limits the third-party cookies’ ability to track you throughout the web.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to set Firefox as your default browser on Windows]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.mozilla.org/foxtail/2020/01/20/how-to-set-firefox-as-your-default-browser-on-windows/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.mozilla.org/en/products/firefox/how-to-set-firefox-as-your-default-browser-on-windows/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T16:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During a software update, your settings can sometimes change or revert back to their original state. For example, if your computer has multiple browsers installed, you may end up with a different default browser than Firefox. That’s easy to fix so that Firefox is there for you when you expect it, like when you click […]
The post How to set Firefox as your default browser on Windows appeared first on The Mozilla Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>M.J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mic with JACK super distorted?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vc6v9y/mic_with_jack_super_distorted/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vc6v9y/mic_with_jack_super_distorted/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T16:04:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So I had this problem with PulseAudio but I fixed it by using the fix in the arch wiki (Here), and now I'm having the same problem but with JACK. is there any fix? All the fixes I found online have all been for PulseAudio. 
 ​
 Thanks!
    submitted by    /u/DiamondDanMan12  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Fastest Ways to Search the Web in Chrome]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=810270</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/810270/the-fastest-ways-to-search-the-web-in-chrome/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Searching the web is one of the most common things people do in web browsers. Whether you use Google, Bing, or DuckDuckGo, there are things you want to find. We’ll show you the fastest ways to do it in Chrome.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Owner of ‘DownThem’ DDoS service gets 2 years in prison]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/owner-of-downthem-ddos-service-gets-2-years-in-prison/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/owner-of-downthem-ddos-service-gets-2-years-in-prison/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T15:40:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matthew Gatrel, 33, a citizen of Illinois, has been sentenced to two years in prison for operating platforms offering DDoS (distributed denial of service) services to subscribers. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come trasferire i messaggi WhatsApp da Android a iOS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Come-trasferire-i-messaggi-WhatsApp-da-Android-a-iOS_24639</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Come-trasferire-i-messaggi-WhatsApp-da-Android-a-iOS_24639"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dopo la novità di WhatsApp Cloud API, uno strumento particolarmente utile per gli sviluppatori che hanno la necessità di integrare le applicazioni aziendali con il network di messaggistica di proprietà di Facebook, è Mark Zuckerberg ad annunciare l'arrivo di un'altra novità.Lo scorso anno è stata aggiunta una funzione per trasferire i messaggi WhatsApp da iOS ad Android, chat e allegati corrispondenti. In un primo momento il trasferimento delle chat WhatsApp era limitato ad alcuni smartphone Samsung; successivamente Google ha esteso il supporto ai suoi Pixel.In un altro articolo abbiamo visto come non perdere le chat WhatsApp cambiando telefono.Adesso il numero uno di Facebook rivela in anteprima che WhatsApp può spostare i messaggi da Android a iOS preservando la crittografia end-to-end.Al momento il meccanismo di migrazione WhatsApp da Android a iOS supporta la versione 15.5 del sistema operativo Apple (iOS 16 non è ancora ufficialmente compatibile).Il passaggio dei dati da un telefono all'altro avviene se entrambi i dispositivi, Android e iOS, sono connessi alla medesima rete WiFi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung Offers $50 Galaxy Phone Screen Repairs for a Limited Time]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120847/samsung-offers-50-galaxy-phone-screen-repairs-for-a-limited-time/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120847/samsung-offers-50-galaxy-phone-screen-repairs-for-a-limited-time/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T15:27:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For a limited time this month, Samsung is generously replacing cracked and damaged smartphone screens at the low price of only $50. If you’ve ever broken a screen on your fancy new flagship phone, you know the cost can be crazy expensive without insurance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is a Mini PC and Should You Buy One?]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=491193</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15368179/what-is-mini-pc"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re in the market for a new computer, you might find yourself a bit overwhelmed when contemplating all the options available on the market. But before you rush out and purchase another laptop, stop and consider if a mini PC would be better suited to your needs. In a work-from-home environment, these miniature versions of powerful PCs could be the answer for a lot of folks.
   

Content

What Are Mini PCs
Use Cases for Mini PCs
Choosing a Mini PC
Ready-to-Go Mini PCs
Barebones Mini PCs
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Turn Your Raspberry Pi into a Video Conferencing Station
    
What Are Mini PCs
    
Mini PCs are exactly that: scaled-down versions of desktop computers. They come in a variety of sizes and offer unique advantages, as well as some drawbacks.
  ... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Yoder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lightroom Gets Video Editing Support with Color Grading]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120838/lightroom-gets-video-editing-support-with-color-grading/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120838/lightroom-gets-video-editing-support-with-color-grading/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T15:24:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of Lightroom’s most requested features is finally here. The latest Lightroom update (v 5.4) lets you edit videos with basic trimming and color grading tools. You can even apply your custom photography presets to videos.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Back in Arch!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vc5s5t/back_in_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vc5s5t/back_in_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T15:16:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well, I'm back using Arch again (coming from NixOS for about a week). After a few attempts setting EFI, I was finally able to get Legacy installed and booting up properly (See this post).
 Everything is running great. I've spent most of the morning reinstalling my programs I use on a daily basis. But everything is working fine under Legacy. I did it all manually (no archinstall script) because archinstall doesn't really cover everything for my system. I have a second HDD I use for my /home directory. It's a 4TB drive and I just never seemed to get that second drive to work the way I want it with archinstall. That would have to be something the archinstall developers need to work on. 
 But, we're all good here now. I'm gonna kinda miss NixOS though. It has so much potential. But Arch is more than welcome to live on my system now.
    submitted by    /u/Phydoux  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox now blocks cross-site tracking by default for all users]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/firefox-now-blocks-cross-site-tracking-by-default-for-all-users/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/firefox-now-blocks-cross-site-tracking-by-default-for-all-users/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T15:04:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla says that starting today, all Firefox users will now be protected by default against cross-site tracking while browsing the Internet. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Evaluate Formulas Step-by-Step in Microsoft Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=807481</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/807481/how-to-evaluate-formulas-step-by-step-in-microsoft-excel/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T15:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re collaborating on a spreadsheet, you may want to break down a formula someone entered. While many times this easy, there are others where the formula is more complicated. Excel provides a tool to evaluate formulas step-by-step.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Internet Explorer ritirato il 15 giugno 2022: cosa implica per gli utenti]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Internet-Explorer-ritirato-il-15-giugno-2022-cosa-implica-per-gli-utenti_24462</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Internet-Explorer-ritirato-il-15-giugno-2022-cosa-implica-per-gli-utenti_24462"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T14:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Era il 16 agosto 1995 quando Microsoft presentò la prima versione di Internet Explorer, browser che mirava a combattere lo strapotere assoluto dello storico Netscape Navigator.Agli albori Internet Explorer veniva distribuito come parte integrante del pacchetto Plus! per Windows 95, che forse alcuni dei nostri lettori ricorderanno, ed era basato sul motore di rendering Spyglass Mosaic il cui utilizzo era stato ottenuto in licenza da Microsoft.La società di Redmond non ha dovuto lavorare troppo per rendere popolare il suo browser: non importava se Internet Explorer fosse migliore o peggiore della concorrenza. Semplicemente includendolo come parte integrante dei suoi sistemi operativi, Microsoft riuscì a scalzare Netscape e consolidare un monopolio durato anni.Nel 2002 il browser Phoenix, poi diventato Firefox, lanciò la vera sfida a Internet Explorer cominciando a guadagnare importanti quote di mercato a danno del browser Microsoft con Opera che nel frattempo denunciò la società per abuso di posizione dominante.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare mitigates record-breaking HTTPS DDoS attack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cloudflare-mitigates-record-breaking-https-ddos-attack/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cloudflare-mitigates-record-breaking-https-ddos-attack/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T14:31:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Internet infrastructure firm Cloudflare said today that it mitigated a 26 million request per second distributed denial-of-service (DDoS) attack, the largest HTTPS DDoS attack detected to date. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox Now Blocks Cross-Site Cookie Tracking Everywhere]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=811311</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/811311/firefox-now-blocks-cross-site-cookie-tracking-everywhere/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T14:24:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox is one of two major browsers left with a non-Chromium engine (the other being Apple’s Safari), which means it can experiment with lower-level changes that Google isn’t interested in. Now one of those changes is rolling out to everyone: Total Cookie Protection.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Withings ScanWatch Review: Timeless Style Meets Modern Tech]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120080/withings-scanwatch-review/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120080/withings-scanwatch-review/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T14:24:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re considering a smartwatch to monitor your health stats, but aren’t too impressed with sporty styles or digital watch faces, the Withings ScanWatch’s gorgeous analog design and premium health-tracking features are the perfect companions for your wrist.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arnold Carreiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to setup a default dns server for all networks?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vc4887/how_to_setup_a_default_dns_server_for_all_networks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vc4887/how_to_setup_a_default_dns_server_for_all_networks/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T14:04:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have setup adguard-home on arch and everytime I change my network I have to change the dns used by that netwrok to localhost. Is there anyway to make all these networks default to local host??
    submitted by    /u/Sad-Excitement9311  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Gaming TVs of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=749603</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/749603/best-gaming-tvs/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The best TVs for gaming don’t just show picture-perfect visuals; they also provide features like high refresh rates to ensure your gaming experience is top-notch. Our recommendations include the right mix of features to make big-screen gaming perfect whether you’re playing on a console or PC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gaurav Shukla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telefono si riavvia di continuo: come risolvere]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/06/telefono-si-riavvia-di-continuo-come.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/06/telefono-si-riavvia-di-continuo-come.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T13:39:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Un telefono che si riavvia sempre senza motivo è fonte d'apprensione per qualsiasi utente visto che, oltre ad essere inutilizzabile durante i continui riavvii, avvicina sempre di più la spesa necessaria per ripararlo o per sostituirlo con un telefono nuovo che non si blocca. Prima di spendere dei soldi però possiamo provare a risolvere il problema con alcuni semplici trucchi da applicare in casa,...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Pixar Movies to Stream on Disney+ in 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=810776</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/810776/best-pixar-movies/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T13:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since 1995, Pixar Animation Studios has set the standard for computer-animated films. The studio’s movies have won numerous Oscars and made billions of dollars at the box office. Here are the best Pixar movies to stream on Disney+.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Bell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 7 Best Lenovo Laptops]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119332/the-best-lenovo-laptops/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119332/the-best-lenovo-laptops/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T13:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lenovo is a reputable brand in the world of laptops, desktops, tablets, and more. That means, however, that you have a lot of options to choose from when picking out your next laptop, which can understandably be overwhelming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Chaney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox rolls out Total Cookie Protection by default to all users worldwide]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.mozilla.org/?p=69120</id>
        <link href="https://blog.mozilla.org/en/products/firefox/firefox-rolls-out-total-cookie-protection-by-default-to-all-users-worldwide/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Take back your privacy Starting today, Firefox is rolling out Total Cookie Protection by default to all Firefox users worldwide, making Firefox the most private and secure major browser available across Windows, Mac and Linux. Total Cookie Protection is Firefox’s strongest privacy protection to date, confining cookies to the site where they were created, thus […]
The post Firefox rolls out Total Cookie Protection by default to all users worldwide appeared first on The Mozilla Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mozilla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD HIP vs. NVIDIA CUDA vs. NVIDIA OptiX On Blender 3.2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31208</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31208"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week with the release of Blender 3.2 bringing AMD HIP support for Linux to provide for Radeon GPU acceleration, I posted some initial benchmarks of AMD Radeon RX 6000 series with HIP against NVIDIA RTX with OptiX. There was interest by some Phoronix readers in also seeing NVIDIA CUDA results even though OptiX is in good shape with RTX GPUs, so with that here are results of NVIDIA CUDA vs. NVIDIA OptiX vs. AMD HIP with Blender 3.2 on Ubuntu Linux.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Installare Windows 11 su un PC non compatibile]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Installare-Windows-11-su-un-PC-non-compatibile_23600</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Installare-Windows-11-su-un-PC-non-compatibile_23600"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T12:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Si è parlato per mesi delle limitazioni imposte da Microsoft circa l'installazione di Windows 11.In un altro articolo abbiamo visto come preparare il PC per Windows 11 e verificare se la configurazione hardware e software è supportata.I portavoce di Microsoft hanno dichiarato che in alcuni casi Windows 11 risulta installabile anche sui PC non compatibili ma che la ricezione degli aggiornamenti attraverso Windows Update potrebbe in futuro non essere più possibile.Dall'azienda di Redmond si è utilizzato il condizionale anche perché, ed è probabilmente questa la ratio, da un lato c'è la volontà di portare quanti più utenti possibile su Windows 11 ma dall'altro si vuole sostenere la domanda di nuovi PC.D'altra parte i vecchi sistemi che oggi eseguono Windows 10 potranno utilizzare il sistema operativo fino al 14 ottobre 2025 e fino a tale data Microsoft si impegna a rilasciare gli aggiornamenti di sicurezza per tutte le edizioni.Per questo Windows 10 è destinato a diventare quasi immortale, seguendo un po’ le orme di Windows 7 e - ai tempi - di Windows XP.Posto che le procedure illustrate di seguito vanno eventualmente utilizzate soltanto per scopi di test, è possibile verificare come si comporta Windows 11 su PC incompatibili, almeno così considerati in via ufficiale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KDE Plasma 5.25 Released With Wayland Improvements, Improved Gestures]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=KDE-Plasma-5.25-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=KDE-Plasma-5.25-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T12:30:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KDE Plasma 5.25 is now shipping as the latest half-year major update to the KDE desktop...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Identificare gli oggetti nelle immagini (Android e iPhone)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2017/03/identificare-gli-oggetti-nelle-immagini.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2017/03/identificare-gli-oggetti-nelle-immagini.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T12:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Il riconoscimento di oggetti in foto è una tecnologia di intelligenza artificiale molto potente, che viene sperimentata da anni con successo variabile. Quelli che si sono più avvicinati a fornire uno strumento adeguato e migliore degli altri è Google, che da diverso tempo permette di fare la ricerca su Internet tramite immagine.

 Nella guida che segue vi mostreremo le migliori app che è...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Edge 102.0.1245.41 fixes security and PDF printing issues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179166</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/14/microsoft-edge-102-0-1245-41-fixes-security-and-pdf-printing-issues/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T12:23:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft released a security update on Friday and another today. The Friday update addressed an Edge-specific security issue, while today's update security issues that affect all Chromium-based browsers. The new version of […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Microsoft Edge 102.0.1245.41 fixes security and PDF printing issues appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VPN Alternatives: What Can You Use Besides a VPN?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=802198</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/802198/vpn-alternatives-what-can-you-use-besides-a-vpn/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VPN providers would have you believe that VPNs are a one-stop cybersecurity shop that will solve all your worries about being tracked or hacked while browsing. That’s not entirely true, though. VPNs aren’t your only option when trying to cover your digital tracks, either.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fergus O'Sullivan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitLab Now The Main Development Platform For Wine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Wine-GitLab-Main-Workflow</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Wine-GitLab-Main-Workflow"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T11:30:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier this year Wine began experimenting with GitLab to improve their development workflow for this open-source project that allows Windows games and applications to run on Linux. It's now been decided that the GitLab workflow is useful and will now be their path forward...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Hidden iOS 16 Features You Might Have Missed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809989</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809989/hidden-ios-16-features/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T11:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[iOS 16 arrives as a free update in fall 2022 alongside the next iteration of the iPhone, with a ton of new features. With so much news it can be easy to overlook some of the subtle yet meaningful changes the new update will bring, so here are some highlights.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can I transfer my Windows upgrade license from an old PC to a new one? [Ask ZDNet]]]></title>
        <id>89235835-8ec8-492a-a9db-21f40c3a60af</id>
        <link href="https://www.zdnet.com/article/can-i-transfer-my-windows-upgrade-license-from-an-old-pc-to-a-new-one-ask-zdnet/#ftag=RSSbaffb68"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T10:30:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Got a tech question? Ed Bott and ZDNet's squad of editors and experts probably have the answer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest topics for ZDNet in Windows</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Engineer on Leave for Concern About Sentient Chatbot]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=497035</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15367747/google-engineer-sentient-chatbot"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T10:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are many questions left to be answered after Google placed an engineer on paid leave for speaking up about a chatbot that he believes is sentient. He’s worried about religious discrimination and went as far as to take his concerns to a U.S. senator.
   
Also read:Google Experimenting with Museletter to Publish Newsletters
    
Google Engineer’s Concerns
    
Senior software engineer in Responsible A.I. at Google, Blake Lemoine, spoke up to say the tech giant placed him on paid leave. He turned over documents to a senator, with claims that the Google chatbot in development is sentient.
    
In addition, Lemoine published a post on Medium that complained he “may be fired soon for doing A.I. ethics work.”
   
 Image source: Unsplash
   
On Saturday, the engineer published his interview with the chatbot Google has named “LaMDA (Language Model... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HyperX Debuts Its First True Wireless Earbud, the Cloud MIX Buds]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120791/hyperx-debuts-its-first-true-wireless-earbud-the-cloud-mix-buds/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120791/hyperx-debuts-its-first-true-wireless-earbud-the-cloud-mix-buds/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T10:15:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The gaming peripherals company HyperX has been on a roll lately with high-end headsets. Now, it just debuted its first set of insanely low-latency true wireless earbuds perfect for gamers on any platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gnome does not start anymore]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vc05ow/gnome_does_not_start_anymore/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vc05ow/gnome_does_not_start_anymore/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T10:10:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello archis, I have a major problem here for weeks that I now have to address.
 After an Arch update gnome does not start anymore. I only get this very extensive hint that I should contact the system administrator.
 As a workaround I am using Plasma now, but I really want to use gnome again. It works neither with gdm, lightdm, nor with kdm.
 Graphics card is a nvidia:
 26:00.0 VGA compatible controller: NVIDIA Corporation GP107 [GeForce GTX 1050 Ti] (rev a1)
 With the following driver:
 Name : nvidia
 Version : 515.48.07-9
 Same problem with current nouveau driver.
 Here is the Xorg.0.log:
 https://hastebin.com/gohicasuvo
    submitted by    /u/rototommer  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Calling for Antitrust Reform]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.mozilla.org/?p=69126</id>
        <link href="https://blog.mozilla.org/en/mozilla/calling-for-antitrust-reform/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla supports the American Innovation and Choice Online Act (AICOA). The time for change is now. It’s time for governments to address the reality that five tech companies—not everyday consumers—control our online experiences today. Updated competition laws are essential for the internet to be private, secure, interoperable, open, accessible, transparent, and a balance between commercial […]
The post Calling for Antitrust Reform appeared first on The Mozilla Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Urmika Devi Shah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Performance-Boosting MGLRU Patches Updated Against Current Linux 5.19 State]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=MGLRU-v12-For-Linux-5.19-rc</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=MGLRU-v12-For-Linux-5.19-rc"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While there are many exciting new features coming with Linux 5.19, one of the features that wasn't submitted this cycle unfortunately was the Multi-Gen "MGLRU" code led by Google. As covered in several prior Phoronix articles, the MGLRU support has exciting performance implications for making the Linux kernel's page reclaim code far more efficient...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fedora 37 Looks To Boost Its Cloud Posture As An Official Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Fedora-Cloud-Base-37-Plan</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Fedora-Cloud-Base-37-Plan"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T09:38:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Approved by the Fedora Engineering and Steering Committee this week is returning Fedora Cloud base to be listed as an official Fedora edition...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RHEL9-Derived Oracle Linux 9 Developer Preview Released With 5.15-Based UEK Kernel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Oracle-Linux-9-Developer-Pre</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Oracle-Linux-9-Developer-Pre"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T09:16:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oracle on Monday released the Oracle Linux 9 Developer Preview as their take on Red Hat Enterprise Linux 9 that reached general availability last month...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FreeCAD 0.20 Released For Open-Source CAD Software]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=FreeCAD-0.20-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=FreeCAD-0.20-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T09:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For those interested in open-source CAD solutions, FreeCAD 0.20 is out today as the newest version of this general purpose 3D computer-aided design modeler that has been in development now for nearly twenty years...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Failed to start Load Kernel Modules how to fix]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vbz4ir/failed_to_start_load_kernel_modules_how_to_fix/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vbz4ir/failed_to_start_load_kernel_modules_how_to_fix/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T08:55:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/yuzenamu  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Provenienza di una foto o di un contenuto: Adobe rilascia un toolkit per le certificazioni digitali]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Provenienza-di-una-foto-o-di-un-contenuto-Adobe-rilascia-un-toolkit-per-le-certificazioni-digitali_24638</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Provenienza-di-una-foto-o-di-un-contenuto-Adobe-rilascia-un-toolkit-per-le-certificazioni-digitali_24638"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T08:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nella moderna società digitale accertare la provenienza di un contenuto può non essere cosa propriamente semplice. Nell'articolo in cui parliamo di fake news abbiamo presentato alcuni strumenti che aiutano a risalire all'autore di un'immagine, di un video, di una foto e in generale di un qualunque contenuto. Accade molto spesso, infatti, che immagini altrui vengano utilizzate senza autorizzazione o che siano spacciate per raffigurare eventi recenti quando invece i contenuti si riferiscono a fatti completamente diversi verificatisi nel passato.Il progetto promosso da Adobe (Content Authenticity Initiative, CAI) mira a offrire alla comunità degli sviluppatori e dei creatori di contenuti strumenti utili a certificare la provenienza di immagini, foto e altri oggetti su Web, desktop e dispositivi mobili indipendentemente dalle competenze tecniche.Conosciamo già EXIF, l'insieme di metadati che vengono aggiunti alle foto e che descrivono il luogo di scatto di un'immagine e i parametri tecnici utilizzati per l'acquisizione (ad esempio apertura focale, velocità dell'otturatore e così via…).La visione di Adobe consiste nell'inserimento di ulteriori metadati (content credentials) che 'viaggiano' insieme con il contenuto e ne certificano l'autore.L'azienda ha infatti annunciato il rilascio di un toolkit open source che si articola in tre componenti e che mira a portare rapidamente la tecnologia nelle mani degli utenti.I nuovi strumenti open source di Adobe includono un SDK JavaScript per visualizzare le credenziali all'interno di un browser, un'utilità a riga di comando e un SDK Rust per creare app desktop, app mobili e altre esperienze al fine di controllare la provenienza di qualunque contenuto.Lo standard sottostante si chiama C2PA (Coalition for Content Provenance and Authenticity) ed è frutto della collaborazione tra Adobe-CAI e partner come Microsoft, Sony, Intel, Twitter, Nikon e altri nomi di primo piano.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TIM 3G: comincia lo switch off. Restano le reti 5G, 4G e 2G]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=TIM-3G-comincia-lo-switch-off-Restano-le-reti-5G-4G-e-2G_24637</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=TIM-3G-comincia-lo-switch-off-Restano-le-reti-5G-4G-e-2G_24637"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T08:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Già da mesi si parla della progressiva dismissione della rete 3G: le frequenze che saranno liberate permetteranno di potenziare l'offerta 4G e 5G migliorando copertura e prestazioni sull'intero territorio nazionale.L'abbandono della rete mobile di terza generazione è sostenuto anche da motivazioni economiche: come abbiamo visto nell'articolo sullo spegnimento della rete 3G, gli operatori di telecomunicazioni trovano sconveniente mantenere contemporaneamente in piedi l'utilizzo di più standard differenti.Nel caso della rete TIM 3G lo switch off è iniziato, dopo alcuni rinvii, il 13 giugno per concludersi il 15 ottobre 2022. L'operatore ha pubblicato il piano di spegnimento della rete 3G: per ogni comune vengono indicate le date di inizio e di fine dell'intervento programmato.L'operazione interessa quindi non soltanto gli utenti in possesso di una SIM TIM ma anche tutti coloro che dispongono di un'utenza mobile fornita dagli operatori virtuali di rete mobile (MVNO) attestati sulla rete TIM: Kena Mobile, Fastweb, CoopVoce, Tiscali e Vianova.
Cosa comporta lo switch off della rete TIM 3G
 L'addio alla rete TIM 3G è un passo importante che porta con sé alcune conseguenze di rilievo: in primis tutti i dispositivi che non supportano il 4G non potranno più collegarsi alla rete dati utilizzando una connessione a banda larga.In questi casi il dispositivo 'ripiegherà' sull'utilizzo degli standard 2G che, com'è noto, consentono di scambiare dati con una larghezza di banda assolutamente inadeguata per le moderne comunicazioni.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[intel_pstate] CPU frequency stuck at lowest setting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vbxujy/intel_pstate_cpu_frequency_stuck_at_lowest_setting/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vbxujy/intel_pstate_cpu_frequency_stuck_at_lowest_setting/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T07:20:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello,
 since a recent update, my system got really sluggish, and I ended up tracing it back to the CPU scaling being stuck at the lowest setting (400MHz) (sudo cpupower frequency-info). The tool also reported that it was unable to get the frequency from the hardware and had to fall back to the kernel.
 I tried both the performance and the powersave governor, but no difference. This happens both on the "normal" and the LTS kernel. My CPU is a i7-8650U.
 My current workaround is to disable the intel_pstate driver.
 Has anyone else also observed this behaviour? I would appreciate any kind of insight a lot.
 Many thanks in advance!
    submitted by    /u/no-such-user  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Receiving "can't change power state from D3cold to D0 (config space inaccessible)" on boot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vbxl11/receiving_cant_change_power_state_from_d3cold_to/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vbxl11/receiving_cant_change_power_state_from_d3cold_to/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T07:02:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi all,
 On a new HP Laptop (HP ZBook Fury 15.6 inch G8 Mobile Workstation PC), I receive "can't change power state from D3cold to D0 (config space inaccessible)" during boot for what appears to be devices on the PCI port. This is preventing the use of the Nvidia GPU. Switching the BIOS to use only Discrete Graphics will work, however this rapidly drains the battery life when set to Hybrid Graphics.
 Dmesg outout _ https://pastebin.com/nqD3B3x8
 ​
 ... [ 5.469559] snd_hda_intel 0000:00:1f.3: Digital mics found on Skylake+ platform, using SOF driver [ 5.469602] snd_hda_intel 0000:01:00.1: can't change power state from D3cold to D0 (config space inaccessible) [ 5.469644] snd_hda_intel 0000:01:00.1: can't change power state from D3cold to D0 (config space inaccessible) [ 5.470087] snd_hda_int…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Banda larga servizio universale in Italia: cosa significa]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Banda-larga-servizio-universale-in-Italia-cosa-significa_24636</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Banda-larga-servizio-universale-in-Italia-cosa-significa_24636"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T06:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Un servizio universale è un servizio che viene messo a disposizione di tutti gli utenti sul territorio nazionale a prescindere dalla loro ubicazione geografica. Il prezzo deve essere accessibile e il fornitore deve garantire l'erogazione di un insieme minimo di funzionalità.Nel campo delle telecomunicazioni, quando praticamente tutti dispongono di una o più utenze mobili, il servizio di accesso alla rete telefonica da postazione fissa (telefono fisso) rimane considerato servizio universale.Incredibilmente, invece, come in passato era stato chiesto a gran voce dai cittadini e dalle imprese in aree digital divise, la banda larga non è considerata un servizio universale: in altre parole, nessun operatore è obbligato a fornire l'accesso a Internet in tutte le unità immobiliari d'Italia.Fino a qualche anno fa, prima dell'avvento della fibra misto rame, fa il benchmark era la disponibilità di una connessione ADSL a 20 Mbps (commerciali).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[File Explorer Tabs in Windows 11 version 22H2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179162</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/14/file-explorer-tabs-windows-11/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T05:05:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft released a new update for Windows 11 Insider devices today that brings the version of the operating system to 22621.160. The update is a smaller bug fix one, which is expected, […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post File Explorer Tabs in Windows 11 version 22H2 appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here are the new features in macOS Ventura's Mail app]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179153</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/14/new-features-in-macos-venturas-mail-app/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T04:23:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spotlight is not the only app that Apple has improved in macOS Ventura. The Mail app has received similar treatment, let's take a look at the new features in it. Undo Send […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Here are the new features in macOS Ventura's Mail app appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All arch mirror downloads are safe?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vbtawg/all_arch_mirror_downloads_are_safe/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vbtawg/all_arch_mirror_downloads_are_safe/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T02:44:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi im new on arch linux and i download it from a mirror from colombia and i have a question, all downloads from mirror are safe and malware free? i dont open it yet on virtual box
    submitted by    /u/ThisRenny  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NVIDIA 515 Driver with realtime kernel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vbs80g/nvidia_515_driver_with_realtime_kernel/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vbs80g/nvidia_515_driver_with_realtime_kernel/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T01:48:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anyone doing this on arch and could give me some pointers. I can't find a patch or a relevant package. The nouveau driver keeps crashing and I'm about to throw the card out the window!
    submitted by    /u/sjf83  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why is this happening? Only thing I'm doing differently is I'm using EFI instead of MBR.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vbqqdq/why_is_this_happening_only_thing_im_doing/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vbqqdq/why_is_this_happening_only_thing_im_doing/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T00:28:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My screens are pink when I try to boot into the system. Os this an EFI issue with a 10 year old PC?
 I've never had this issue using standard grub...
    submitted by    /u/Phydoux  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Change the Default Search Engine in Various Browsers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=post-ideas&amp;p=312093</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/12782907/change-default-search-engine-browsers"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Changing the default search engine only takes a few clicks, regardless of the browser you’re using. Even if you were to change your mind later, you always have the option of using another search engine or switching to the default option. While Google is the most popular search engine, there are other choices as well. Let’s examine how to change the default search engine in popular browsers.
   

Content

Change the Default Search Engine in Chrome
Change the Default Search Engine in Firefox
Change the Default Search Engine in Microsoft Edge
Change the Default Search Engine on Opera
Change the Default Search Engine in Brave
Change the Default Search Engine in Safari
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:Google vs. Bing vs. DuckDuckGo: Which Is Best?
    
Change the Default Search Engine in Chrome
    
The popular Chrome browser works on all major platforms. While... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mehvish Mushtaq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD Linux CPU Temperature Driver Sees Latest Patches For Zen 4 & Likely Mendocino]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMD-k10temp-Zen-4-v5</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMD-k10temp-Zen-4-v5"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T23:13:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of my personal gripes with AMD's Zen CPU support on Linux has been the lack of timely support for CPU temperature monitoring with their "k10temp" driver. Even though usually just new IDs are often needed and sometimes needing to adjust offsets or other minor changes, it has traditionally been done post-launch and sometimes left up to patches from the open-source community. Thankfully that has been changing and with Zen 4 it looks like that support will be ready for launch-day with the mainline Linux kernel...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kaiser Permanente data breach exposes health data of 69K people]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/kaiser-permanente-data-breach-exposes-health-data-of-69k-people/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/kaiser-permanente-data-breach-exposes-health-data-of-69k-people/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T22:54:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kaiser Permanente, one of America's leading not-for-profit health plans and health care providers, has recently disclosed a data breach that exposed the health information of more than 69,000 individuals. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[kde plasma on arch linux not showing wifi connections]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vborwi/kde_plasma_on_arch_linux_not_showing_wifi/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vborwi/kde_plasma_on_arch_linux_not_showing_wifi/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T22:50:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I installed kde network manager using yay -S plasma-nm and all I see is blank when I go to connections under settings. https://imgur.com/a/PGtLDEO
    submitted by    /u/Righteous_Warrior  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gallium hackers backdoor finance, govt orgs using new PingPull malware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/gallium-hackers-backdoor-finance-govt-orgs-using-new-pingpull-malware/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/gallium-hackers-backdoor-finance-govt-orgs-using-new-pingpull-malware/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T21:56:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Gallium state-sponsored hacking group has been spotted using a new 'PingPull' remote access trojan against financial institutions and government entities in Europe, Southeast Asia, and Africa. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Map a WebDAV Drive in Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=post-ideas&amp;p=300221</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/11335444/map-webdav-drive-windows10"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web Distributed Authoring and Versioning (WebDAV) is an HTTP extension that provides a collaborative way of editing and managing your files on a remote web server. Here we will show you how to map a WebDAV drive in Windows so you can access your remote files directly in File Explorer.
    
In order to connect to the WebDAV directory in Windows, you’ll need the WebDAV site URL, your WebDAV account login details, and a name for the shortcut or connection. All three allow you to map WebDAV by mounting its folder as a mapped drive so you can view, edit, or delete files from the remote web server using your computer.
   

Content

How to Map a WebDAV Drive in Windows
What to Do When You Cannot Connect to WebDAV Directory
What to Do If You Can't Access Your WebDAV Folder?
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Crystal Crowder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Internet Explorer (almost) breathes its final byte on Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/internet-explorer-almost-breathes-its-final-byte-on-wednesday/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/internet-explorer-almost-breathes-its-final-byte-on-wednesday/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T21:12:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft will finally end support for Internet Explorer on multiple Windows versions on Wednesday, June 15, almost 27 years after its launch on August 24, 1995. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Macbook Pro 2011 keyboard not recognized in cli, but works in wayland/swaywm]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vbmkmt/macbook_pro_2011_keyboard_not_recognized_in_cli/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vbmkmt/macbook_pro_2011_keyboard_not_recognized_in_cli/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T21:11:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arch installed and runs great when I use an external keyboard to login at CLI.
 Without the external keyboard nothing I type on the internal macbook keyboard is recognized (or recognized correctly.
 Once I login at CLI with external keyboard and start Sway, the internal keyboard works perfectly.
 Is this typical of Arch on Macbook Pro and is there anything that can be done to help?
    submitted by    /u/TakeDownYourLights  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Reasons to Own a NAS Device]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120778/the-best-reasons-to-own-a-nas-device/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120778/the-best-reasons-to-own-a-nas-device/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T21:03:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A dedicated NAS device is sort of like a cloud server for your home—it lets you back up and access data through the internet. But NAS devices are more than just glorified hard drives. With minimal effort, they unlock a world of functionality for computer nerds, movie snobs, music fans, or even small businesses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Disable the Lock Screen on Windows 10 or Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>http://www.howtogeek.com/?p=134620</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/134620/how-to-disable-the-lock-screen-on-windows-8-without-using-group-policy/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 10’s lock screen is at home on a tablet, but it just adds an additional keypress to the login process on a desktop or laptop.  You can disable the lock screen with a quick registry hack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Should You Use a Flash in Your Photography?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=719804</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/719804/when-should-you-use-a-flash-in-your-photography/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Flash has a bad reputation among photographers. Many articles for beginners—and I’ve written a few—recommend avoiding using it whenever possible. But, while you will generally get better photos when you don’t use flash, there are some situations where it’s essential. Let’s dig in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Harry Guinness</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Will Soon Remove Internet Explorer From Windows 10]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=811246</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/811246/microsoft-will-soon-remove-internet-explorer-from-windows-10/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T19:58:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft dropped Internet Explorer from Windows 11, instead only making it accessible through ‘IE Mode’ on the new Edge browser. Now the company is preparing to remove it from some builds of Windows 10, too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GM’s Next Electric Car Is the Chevrolet Blazer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=811216</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/811216/gms-next-electric-car-is-the-chevrolet-blazer/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T19:47:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are more choices than ever for electric cars, especially as older companies like General Motors and Ford are starting to create electric versions of their gas and hybrid cars. GM has now (partially) revealed another upcoming model: the Chevrolet Blazer EV.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers clone Coinbase, MetaMask mobile wallets to steal your crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-clone-coinbase-metamask-mobile-wallets-to-steal-your-crypto/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-clone-coinbase-metamask-mobile-wallets-to-steal-your-crypto/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T19:32:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security researchers have uncovered a large-scale malicious operation that uses trojanized mobile cryptocurrency wallet applications for Coinbase, MetaMask, TokenPocket, and imToken services. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make a Calendar in Google Sheets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=804259</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/804259/how-to-make-a-calendar-in-google-sheets/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you want an online calendar to share with others, or you just want a physical calendar you can print and use in the office, you have three options for creating a calendar in Google Sheets. Let’s get started.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Metasploit 6.2.0 improves credential theft, SMB support features, more]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/metasploit-620-improves-credential-theft-smb-support-features-more/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/metasploit-620-improves-credential-theft-smb-support-features-more/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T18:15:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[​Metasploit 6.2.0 has been released with 138 new modules, 148 new improvements/features, and 156 bug fixes since version 6.1.0 was released in August 2021. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Choose the Perfect Mouse Pad]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=803236</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/803236/how-to-choose-a-mouse-pad/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T18:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tired of replacing cheap mouse pads that wear out quickly? Or maybe you want to upgrade to something bigger or better? Here’s what you need to know when choosing the perfect mouse pad.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Nguyen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Proposed SIG Could Help Fedora Linux Become A Leader For Heterogeneous Computing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Fedora-HC-Compute-SIG</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Fedora-HC-Compute-SIG"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To organize efforts around improving Fedora Linux for heterogeneous computing, a new special interest group "SIG" is looking to be established to help ensure the success of Fedora in the world of XPUs, the growing and very diverse software ecosystem around accelerators, etc...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Prime's Air Drone Delivery Takes Flight Later This Year]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120779/amazon-primes-air-drone-delivery-takes-flight-later-this-year/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120779/amazon-primes-air-drone-delivery-takes-flight-later-this-year/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T17:43:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After years of work and several delays, on Monday, Amazon said it’s ready to let a fleet of Amazon Prime Air delivery drones take flight. Once it receives the final approval from the Federal Aviation Administration (FAA), deliveries will begin in California.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CEO and Founder of HER Robyn Exton Shares Celebrates Pride from Her Corner of the Internet]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.mozilla.org/?p=69108</id>
        <link href="https://blog.mozilla.org/en/internet-culture/ceo-and-founder-of-her-robyn-exton-shares-celebrates-pride-from-her-corner-of-the-internet/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T17:42:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here at Mozilla, we are the first to admit the internet isn’t perfect, but we are also quick to point out that the internet is pretty darn magical. The internet opens up doors and opportunities, allows for people to connect with others, and lets everyone find where they belong — their corners of the internet. […]
The post CEO and Founder of HER Robyn Exton Shares Celebrates Pride from Her Corner of the Internet appeared first on The Mozilla Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Damiano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LUMI Inaugurated As Europe's Most Powerful Supercomputer - Powered By AMD CPUs/GPUs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=LUMI-Supercomputer-Inaugurated</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=LUMI-Supercomputer-Inaugurated"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T17:22:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While not record-shattering like the 1.1 Exaflops Frontier supercomputer at ORNL that took the Top500 spot this year from Fugaku, LUMI was inaugurated today with the claim of Europe's most powerful supercomputer...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chip ad architettura universale: Tachyum Prodigy ha 128 core a 64 bit, 5,7 GHz di clock e 950W di TDP]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Chip-ad-architettura-universale-Tachyum-Prodigy-ha-128-core-a-64-bit-57-GHz-di-clock-e-950W-di-TDP_24635</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Chip-ad-architettura-universale-Tachyum-Prodigy-ha-128-core-a-64-bit-57-GHz-di-clock-e-950W-di-TDP_24635"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T17:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Di solito una CPU per sistemi server ad alte prestazioni è contraddistinta da un TDP inferiore a 300W.Il TDP (Thermal Design Power) non esprime il consumo energetico bensì restituisce un'importante informazione circa il calore che il sistema di dissipazione deve correttamente smaltire per mantenere la temperatura del processore entro una soglia limite. Il consumo energetico è ovviamente funzione del TDP ma i due termini non sono sovrapponibili.Tachyum è un'azienda con sede a Santa Clara, negli Stati Uniti, che progetta, sviluppa e commercializza CPU prestazionali per data center, high performance computing, private cloud, telecomunicazioni, intelligenza artificiale.

La società ha appena tolto il velo dalla sua gamma Tachyum Prodigy che integra CPU, GPU e TPU (Tensor Processing Unit per le…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AT&T’s New Unlimited Plan Drops HBO Max]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=811123</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/811123/atts-new-unlimited-plan-drops-hbo-max/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T17:17:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AT&T used to own Warner Media, which in turn owns HBO and its associated streaming services, but AT&T completed its sale of Warner to Discovery earlier this year. Now we’re seeing the first real-world effects of the deal: no more free Game of Thrones for AT&T unlimited subscribers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft: Exchange servers hacked to deploy BlackCat ransomware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-exchange-servers-hacked-to-deploy-blackcat-ransomware/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-exchange-servers-hacked-to-deploy-blackcat-ransomware/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T17:14:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft says BlackCat ransomware affiliates are now attacking Microsoft Exchange servers using exploits targeting unpatched vulnerabilities. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Rename a Directory on Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=807990</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/807990/rename-directory-linux/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T17:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Renaming a directory in Linux is easy, and there are plenty of ways to go about it. From renaming a single directory to finding and renaming many, here’s how to do it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKay</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD Adds Radeon Memory Visualizer Support For Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Radeon-Memory-Visualizer-Linux</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Radeon-Memory-Visualizer-Linux"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T16:30:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AMD's Radeon Memory Visualizer "RMV" tool from their GPUOpen initiative has allowed better understanding video memory usage with Windows across multiple APIs. In citing the "rising popularity of gaming on the Linux OS", AMD has now enabled Linux support for this tool...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla's Thunderbird Email Client Is Coming to Android]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120767/mozillas-thunderbird-email-client-is-coming-to-android/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120767/mozillas-thunderbird-email-client-is-coming-to-android/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T16:26:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like many people, I used Thunderbird to manage my email accounts throughout the 2000s and early 2010s. But Mozilla practically gave up on the client sometime between 2012 and 2015, forcing me to find something new. Now, as part of Thunderbird’s revival, Mozilla is finally bringing the email client to Android devices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come calibrare la batteria del PC portatile]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2011/09/calibrare-la-batteria-del-pc-portatile.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2011/09/calibrare-la-batteria-del-pc-portatile.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T16:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[La batteria dei portatili è una delle componenti che si rovina più velocemente: già dopo un anno inizia a perdere la carica e, sui computer più vecchi, la durata è talmente breve che a malapena si riesce ad aprire un sito web prima che si spenga.

 Per fortuna possiamo applicare subito qualche semplice trucco per calibrare la batteria del PC portatile, così da ripristinare la lettura della carica...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Backup Microsoft 365: perché è importante]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Backup-Microsoft-365-perche-e-importante_24622</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Backup-Microsoft-365-perche-e-importante_24622"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T16:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stando ai dati diffusi dall'azienda di Redmond sono circa 320 milioni gli utenti paganti di Microsoft 365 (dato aggiornato ad aprile 2022). Tanti se si pensa che Microsoft 365 è una piattaforma cloud (Software-as-a-Service) principalmente destinata a professionisti e imprese.Microsoft 365 ambisce a semplificare la complessità del software sollevando le aziende dalla necessità di configurare in locale account di posta, servizi per lo storage dei dati, siti SharePoint, condivisioni dei dati e strumenti per la produttività e la collaborazione in team.Tutto si sposta sul cloud permettendo agli amministratori IT di avere una visione completa su ciò che avviene all'interno dell'infrastruttura aziendale.Il fatto che Microsoft 365 sia una soluzione cloud viene comunemente visto come un indiscusso punto a favore: se i dati sono memorizzati sui server Microsoft penserà l'azienda a crearne delle copie di sicurezza.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Leaked Chrome OS Feature Is Perfect for Big Screens]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120766/this-leaked-chrome-os-feature-is-perfect-for-big-screens/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120766/this-leaked-chrome-os-feature-is-perfect-for-big-screens/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T16:10:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s Chrome OS has improved by leaps and bounds since it first debuted in 2011, but the company hasn’t slowed down when it comes to adding new features. If the latest leaks are accurate, Chrome OS could soon get an improved “split view” mode for bigger screens or multi-display users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[External monitor not working]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vbfm4a/external_monitor_not_working/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vbfm4a/external_monitor_not_working/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T16:05:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sorry if this turns out to be an easy question
 so i have laptop with HDMI port and old monitor using VGA so i bought HDMI to VGA converter so it can be connected to the laptop and after checking it with xrandr -q it did shown as connected this is the output 
 Screen 0: minimum 8 x 8, current 1600 x 900, maximum 16384 x 16384 eDP-1-1 connected 1600x900+0+0 (normal left inverted right x axis y axis) 309mm x 173mm 1366x768 59.97 + 1280x720 60.00 59.99 59.86 59.74 1024x768 60.04 60.00 960x720 60.00 928x696 60.05 896x672 60.01 1024x576 59.95 59.96 59.90 59.82 960x600 59.93 60.00 960x540 59.96 59.99 59.63 59.82 800x600 60.00 60.32 56.25 840x525 60.01 59.88 864x486 59.92 59.57 700x525 59.98 800x450 59.95 59.82 640x512 60.02 700x450 59.96 59.88 640x480 60.00 59.94 720x405 59.51 58.99 684x384 59.88 59.85 640x400 59.88 59.98 640x360 59.86 59.83 59.84 59.32 512x384 60.00 512x288 60.00 59.92 480x270 59.63 59.82 400x300 60.32 56.34 432x243 59.92 59.57 320x240 60.05 360x202 59.51 59.13 320x180 59.84 59.32 1600x900_60.00 59.95* HDMI-1-1 connected 1024x768+0+0 (normal left inverted right x axis y axis) 256mm x 192mm 1024x768 60.00*+ 1920x1080 60.00 59.94 1280x1024 85.02 60.02 1440x900 74.98 59.90 1280x960 60.00 1360x768 60.02 1280x800 59.91 1280x720 60.00 59.94 720x480 60.00 59.94 1600x900_60.00 (0x24f) 118.250MHz -HSync +VSync h: width 1600 start 1696 end 1856 total 2112 skew 0 clock 55.99KHz v: height 900 start 903 end 908 total 934 clock 59.95Hz 
 after that im suppose to do this according to wiki and thats it
 xrandr --output eDP-1-1 --auto --output HDMI-1-1 --auto --right-of eDP-1-1 
 but my second monitor still gave me a black screen no i cant see my cursor either in there is just a black screen
 And also im using I3 and i have hybrid graphics (Intel and Nvidia) and yes i already using Nvidia according to optimus-manager --status oh and for Xorg config i dont have it for some reason already search it at /etc/x11
    submitted by    /u/Skyinthenight  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11: come cambia la ricerca integrata]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-11-come-cambia-la-ricerca-integrata_24634</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-11-come-cambia-la-ricerca-integrata_24634"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T16:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[La funzionalità di ricerca di Windows è stata rimaneggiata più volte nel corso del tempo e con Windows 10 cercare file nel PC è diventato oggettivamente più semplice ed efficace.Anche se in molti preferiscono utilizzare soluzioni di terze parti come l'ottimo Everything, la ricerca di Windows consente di ottenere rapidamente ciò che è di proprio interesse. A patto di configurarla correttamente e avere un po’ di pazienza durante la fase iniziale di costruzione dell'indice che può richiedere tempo, soprattutto se si hanno tanti file memorizzati sulla macchina.Il vantaggio della ricerca di Windows è che essa non solo restituisce documenti e file basati sul nome degli stessi ma permette di ottenere risultati anche sulla base del loro contenuto. Inoltre permette di individuare comandi e funziona…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Stop Accidental Cellular Data Usage on iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=808728</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/808728/how-to-stop-accidental-cellular-data-usage-on-iphone/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you don’t have unlimited cellular data on your iPhone plan, it can waste money if you accidentally use cell data when your Wi-Fi signal gets bad—or if a data-hungry app goes awry. Here’s how to prevent that from happening.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fiat Testing Roads That Wirelessly Charge EVs While You Drive]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120760/fiat-testing-roads-that-wirelessly-charge-evs-while-you-drive/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120760/fiat-testing-roads-that-wirelessly-charge-evs-while-you-drive/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T15:27:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A common concern when it comes to electric vehicles is charging. That includes the electric grid handling the growing demand or having enough charging stations where we drive. Thankfully, in the future, we could have roads with wireless charging built-in, and our cars can charge as we drive.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Check Sudo History in Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=357483</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/13760636/check-sudo-history-linux"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When sharing your computer with others, and you’ve granted them sudo access, it’s prudent to monitor how they’re using it. Thankfully, it’s easy to check out sudo history. Let’s see how.
   

Content

The Authentication Log
Making Sense of Chaos
Normal Bash
Journalctl
GUI-specific Programs
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:What Is Doas and How to Install It
    
The Authentication Log
    
Plenty of Linux services keep logs to help in troubleshooting problems. Thankfully, among other things, it also keeps a detailed list of precisely the information we seek in this article. In this list, you can check out who and when issued which command using sudo. To find this information, if you’re using a distribution based on Debian or Ubuntu, enter the following into your favorite terminal:
    

sudo Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramces Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My stupid question of the day NetworkManager vs systemd-networkd]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vbemef/my_stupid_question_of_the_day_networkmanager_vs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vbemef/my_stupid_question_of_the_day_networkmanager_vs/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T15:21:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever since I made the switch to Arch few years ago...I just followed the wiki and never really looked at systemd-networkd. Is there any reason why i should use it over the other etc? or just personal preference?
    submitted by    /u/ErnestT_bass  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TP-Link's Energy-Monitoring Smart Plug Comes to HomeKit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120755/tp-links-energy-monitoring-smart-plug-comes-to-homekit/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120755/tp-links-energy-monitoring-smart-plug-comes-to-homekit/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T15:20:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TP-Link just unveiled a HomeKit-compatible version of its energy-monitoring smart plug. And man, it’s a serious bargain. While similar HomeKit plugs cost about $40 each, a four-pack of the Kasa Smart Plug Mini costs just $49 (that’s about $12.50 per plug).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Syslogk Linux rootkit uses magic packets to trigger backdoor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-syslogk-linux-rootkit-uses-magic-packets-to-trigger-backdoor/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-syslogk-linux-rootkit-uses-magic-packets-to-trigger-backdoor/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T15:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new rootkit malware named 'Syslogk' has been spotted in the wild, and it features advanced process and file hiding techniques that make detection highly unlikely. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Perfectly Align Objects and Images in Microsoft Word]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809759</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809759/perfectly-align-objects-images-in-word/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T15:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you create a document that contains shapes, images, or other objects, lining them up can make all the difference in your document’s appearance. Luckily, Microsoft Word provides you with features to help you align your objects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Citrix ICAClient - Can I manipulate the super key behavior?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vbdwoq/citrix_icaclient_can_i_manipulate_the_super_key/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vbdwoq/citrix_icaclient_can_i_manipulate_the_super_key/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T14:49:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey guys,
 I just migrated from W10 to my first linux installation and I'm using KDE as the launcher for my Arch. I use the Citrix application to connect to my work environment and when I hit the super key it activates both startup menus, the one from my KDE desktop and the one from de citrix VDI (When the VDI screen is on). When I'm using any other software, it doesn't activate the key inside the VDI.
 So my question is: Can I change that behavior to isolate the super key when I'm using my VDI? 
 For example, if I'm typing inside the VDI and I hit the super key, it just opens the startup menu from the VDI and not both the VDI and the desktop.
    submitted by    /u/fabioreisritter  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thunderbird per Android sarà basato sulla nota app K-9 Mail]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Thunderbird-per-Android-sara-basato-sulla-nota-app-K-9-Mail_24633</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Thunderbird-per-Android-sara-basato-sulla-nota-app-K-9-Mail_24633"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T14:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nelle scorse settimane vi avevamo dato per certo l'arrivo di Thunderbird su Android sotto forma di app dedicata.Thunderbird è infatti uno dei client di posta elettronica più apprezzati per i sistemi Windows, macOS e Linux. Mozilla non ha però mai rilasciato un client email per i dispositivi mobili.La notizia è che Thunderbird per Android sarà costruito partendo dalle solide fondamenta della nota app K-9 Mail.È dal 2018, infatti, che Ryan Lee Sipes, Product Manager di Thunderbird, e Christian Ketterer, responsabile dello sviluppo di K-9 Mail si confrontavano sulla possibilità di 'unire le forze' e realizzare un client di posta per i dispositivi Android senza ripartire da zero.Così oggi arriva la conferma: K-9 Mail si trasformerà in Thunderbird per Android. L'attuale applicazione K-9 Mail cambierà nome e utilizzerà il nome e il marchio Thunderbird.'Prima che ciò accada dobbiamo raggiungere alcuni traguardi di sviluppo che porteranno K-9 Mail ad allinearsi con l'insieme di funzionalità e l'aspetto visivo di Thunderbird' per i sistemi desktop, si legge in una nota ufficiale.Tante funzionalità saranno quindi a breve aggiunte in K-9 Mail: la configurazione dell'account utilizzando il rilevamento e l'impostazione automatica di Thunderbird; la gestione delle cartelle migliorata; il supporto per i filtri dei messaggi; la sincronizzazione tra client desktop e mobile Thunderbird.Già oggi K-9 Mail supporta una casella di posta unificata, la gestione di identità multiple, il supporto per i messaggi crittografati con GPG e PGP/MIME, l'assegnazione di etichette e 'marcatori' alle varie email, le notifiche per singolo account e molto altro ancora.A questo punto è lecito aspettarsi che K-9 Mail supporti a sua volta, come fa Thunderbird desktop, anche l'autenticazione via OAuth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chromebook Multitasking Is About to Get a Lot Better]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=811086</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/811086/chromebook-multitasking-is-about-to-get-a-lot-better/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T14:31:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chromebooks are already capable computers for many people, but they still lack some of the advanced features found on Windows PCs and Macs. Now it looks like another helpful addition is on the way: partial split window snapping.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russian hackers start targeting Ukraine with Follina exploits]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/russian-hackers-start-targeting-ukraine-with-follina-exploits/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/russian-hackers-start-targeting-ukraine-with-follina-exploits/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T14:28:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ukraine's Computer Emergency Response Team (CERT) is warning that the Russian hacking group Sandworm may be exploiting Follina, a remote code execution vulnerability in Microsoft Windows Support Diagnostic Tool (MSDT) currently tracked as CVE-2022-30190. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come riutilizzare un vecchio modem o router]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/06/come-riutilizzare-un-vecchio-modem-o.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/06/come-riutilizzare-un-vecchio-modem-o.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T14:19:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quando piazziamo un nuovo modem in casa molti si limitano a deporre il vecchio modem in soffitta a fare polvere, da usare solo in caso di emergenza, da regalare o da buttare nella spazzatura il prima possibile. Il vecchio modem sarà pure obsoleto ma può essere ancora utile come ripetitore Wi-Fi, come router di protezione della privacy (configurando un accesso VPN dedicato) oppure come...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FreeDesktop.org GitLab Service Restored]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=FreeDesktop-GitLab-Back-Online</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=FreeDesktop-GitLab-Back-Online"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T14:15:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After battling Ceph storage issues and related problems for the past day after two solid-state drives failed, the FreeDesktop.org GitLab that is used for the centralized, coordination of the open-source Linux graphics driver development and other open-source software is back online...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google ha creato un'intelligenza artificiale senziente: non è così per l'azienda. Cosa significa]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Google-ha-creato-un-intelligenza-artificiale-senziente-non-e-cosi-per-l-azienda-Cosa-significa_24632</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Google-ha-creato-un-intelligenza-artificiale-senziente-non-e-cosi-per-l-azienda-Cosa-significa_24632"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nei giorni scorsi l'ingegnere Google Blake Lemonine ha raccontato su Medium di essere stato posto dall'azienda di Mountain View in 'congedo amministrativo retribuito', l'anticamera del licenziamento.Stando a quanto riferito pubblicamente da Lemonine all'ingegnere sarebbe stata contestata la violazione del segreto professionale che lo lega all'azienda e la rivelazione di informazioni riservate a soggetti terzi, esterni rispetto a Google.Di proposito Lemonine non è voluto scendere nei particolari con un post pubblico limitandosi però a sottolineare di aver più volte segnalato problemi etici collegati con lo sviluppo e i continui progressi della soluzione per l'intelligenza artificiale ideata nei laboratori della multinazionale statunitense.Come si legge in una lunga intervista rilasciata alla testata The Washington Post, Lemonine ha lavorato insieme con un altro dipendente Google per dimostare che l'intelligenza artificiale realizzata dalla società fosse senziente.Un essere senziente è un essere dotato della capacità di sensazione: l'espressione è usata in tanti campi; nella filosofia, nel diritto, nella bioetica.Forse influenzati anche dall'ampia letteratura e cinematografia fantascientifica, a più livelli ci si è spesso chiesti se l'intelligenza artificiale possa in qualche modo condurre allo sviluppo di macchine senzienti.In occasione del suo evento I/O 2021 Google ha presentato LaMDA, una 'tecnologia di conversazione rivoluzionaria' in grado di impegnarsi in modo fluido su un numero potenzialmente infinito di argomenti.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>