<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-06-10T01:58:03.118Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Help! I Am Locked Out of My Google Account]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=363036</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/13857143/recover-locked-out-google-account"/>
        <updated>2022-06-10T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s unthinkable today to not be able to access Gmail or other Google services. But it can happen for so many reasons. You may forget the password, find your account hacked, or simply lose access to your recovery email or phone number. Occasionally you’ll be unable to access Google if the main smartphone device where you were signed in is damaged or stolen.
    
The following is a comprehensive guide on the steps that should be followed if you find yourself locked out of your Google account. We will also cover the best ways to avoid such a situation.
   

Content

Set Up Google Account Recovery
Scenario 1: Forgot Password + Your Phone Isn't Nearby
Scenario 2: Forgot Password + Your Phone Is Lost/Stolen 
Scenario 3: No Longer Have Access to Your Recovery Email 
Scenario 4: Forgot Username
Scenario 5: The Best Option to Recover Google Account in Any Situation
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sayak Boral</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to bypass zenbook login on asus computer running arch linux?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v8tjrr/how_to_bypass_zenbook_login_on_asus_computer/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v8tjrr/how_to_bypass_zenbook_login_on_asus_computer/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T23:08:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey guys, some context:
 I live on the property of a retirement since I’m a minor and live with a parent who works on the property. Sometimes we’ll be given random stuff that’s left behind by residents who have passed and didn’t have anyone to claim their items. 
 This time it was an asus computer running arch Linux and I’m very curious as to what could be on this device, but there’s a zenbook login and password needed. Is there anyway I can bypass this?
 The screen is all black and the only test is up in the upper left corner;
 Arch Linux 4.9.11-1-ARCH (tty1) zenbook login:
 Thanks!
    submitted by    /u/idonttrustatoms  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USB Webcam/Mic not being used as either.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v8t9vs/usb_webcammic_not_being_used_as_either/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v8t9vs/usb_webcammic_not_being_used_as_either/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T22:55:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi there, sorry for a probably pointless issue. I've got a few logitech camera/microphone combination devices, and they are not at all detected or used as either mic or camera. This used to work before, and just in general makes no sense. lsusb detects them, just nothing else, really. Kind of at the end of the rope with this as don't really have any other mics or cameras.
    submitted by    /u/CrazyIronMyth  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD Talks Up Zen 4 AVX-512, Genoa, Siena & More At Financial Analyst Day]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMD-Financial-Day-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMD-Financial-Day-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T22:06:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AMD today hosted their 2022 Financial Analyst Day where they made some new disclosures and firmed up past product road-map plans...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rclone: il coltellino svizzero per la gestione degli spazi cloud! [Linux][MacOS][Windows][Android][iOS]]]></title>
        <id>3596|20220610000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/backup-18/rclone-coltellino-svizzero-gestione-spazi-cloud-linuxmacoswindowsandroidios-3596"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avevo sentito parlare di Rclone ma non avevo mai avuto occasione di provarlo perché non utilizzo nessun cloud. Poi crazy.cat mi ha chiesto di dargli un occhiata e dato che ho una macchina virtuale con Windows 11 Pro configurata con un utente "online" (e quindi con 5GB di spazio OneDrive disponibile), ho deciso di testarlo approfonditamente e... sono rimasto affascinato da questo potentissimo strumento, open source e disponibile per tantissime piattaforme, tanto da dirvi che, se utilizzate un qualunque cloud, non dovreste assolutamente farne a meno!!
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft starts rolling out Windows 11 File Explorer tabs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-starts-rolling-out-windows-11-file-explorer-tabs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-starts-rolling-out-windows-11-file-explorer-tabs/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T21:43:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft is finally rolling out the new File Explorer tabbed interface with the release of Windows 11 Insider Preview Build 25136 to the Dev Channel. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[is this safe to do? downgrading package (package manager questions)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v8rf1n/is_this_safe_to_do_downgrading_package_package/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v8rf1n/is_this_safe_to_do_downgrading_package_package/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T21:28:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[hope you all are doing good, so recently a libvirt update came and it broke my kvm, but i tried fixing it by downgrading it one version and it worked but wanted to know if it is getting verified same as downloading new package from the repo with command line also i am downloading the package from archive.archlinux.org(package download link) 
 i don't have old packages in cache cause reinstalled arch so just wanted to know if i download package from that site and then run "pacman -U filename.tar.zst" will it perform same checks as installing from the official repo, when i installed it ran these checks (1/1) checking keys in keyring, (1/1) checking package integrity. 
 also, what are the chances of getting a malicious package and how to avoid getting one? and what if you get one?
 thanks, have a nice day
    submitted by    /u/surele  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Windows Hello and Should You Use It?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=post-ideas&amp;p=181057</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/5852695/setup-use-windows-hello"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows Hello is a sophisticated facial scanning technology. It lets you quickly log in to your Windows PC without a passcode. You need a special webcam to make Windows Hello work, but with the right hardware, it’s fast and convenient. Does that mean you should use it? What are the pros and cons?
   

Content

What Makes Windows Hello Special
Windows Hello Requirements
When Not to Use Windows Hello
Who Should Use Windows Hello
Improving Windows Hello Recognition
How To Disable Windows Hello
Saying Goodbye to Hello?

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Know if Someone Else Is Logging in to Your Windows PC
    
What Makes Windows Hello Special
    
While many different facial unlocking systems exist, Windows Hello is one of the most sophisticated solutions.
    
Facial recognition security always... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sydney Butler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Enable Dark Mode for Google Chrome]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=360650</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/360650/how-to-enable-dark-mode-for-google-chrome/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Chrome has had a built-in dark theme like Mozilla Firefox and Microsoft Edge since Chrome 74. You can even apply a dark theme to every web page you visit using third-party themes or an extension. Here’s how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Control Roku with Your Voice]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120598/how-to-control-roku-with-your-voice/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120598/how-to-control-roku-with-your-voice/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T20:42:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Typing your Netflix email with a Roku remote is a nightmare, and digging through every streaming service just to find Wedding Crashers isn’t worth the time or effort. Thankfully, Roku streaming sticks and smart TVs offer voice control functionality, allowing you to perform simple and complicated tasks with just a few spoken words.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notepad on Windows 11 Will Soon Be Faster (Was It Slow?)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=810547</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/810547/notepad-on-windows-11-will-soon-be-faster-was-it-slow/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T20:11:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft revamped the Notepad application in Windows 11 last year, giving it a fresh new look and a few new features. More improvements are on the way, according to a new blog post.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Enable Dark Mode in Microsoft Edge]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=360357</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/360357/how-to-enable-dark-mode-in-microsoft-edge/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Edge has a dark theme that will be activated if you enable Windows 10’s dark theme. If you’re using the light theme on Windows 10, but want Edge to run in dark mode, you’ll need to manually enable a theme in Edge’s application settings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bizarre ransomware sells decryptor on Roblox Game Pass store]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/bizarre-ransomware-sells-decryptor-on-roblox-game-pass-store/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/bizarre-ransomware-sells-decryptor-on-roblox-game-pass-store/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T19:29:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new ransomware is taking the unusual approach of selling its decryptor on the Roblox gaming platform using the service's in-game Robux currency. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is there any command to see if modprob.d loaded confs correctly?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v8opmn/is_there_any_command_to_see_if_modprobd_loaded/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v8opmn/is_there_any_command_to_see_if_modprobd_loaded/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T19:27:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I followed this guide to load "NVreg_TemporaryFilePath=/tmp-nvidia" . Ive created the .conf file and put the modules and parameters there. 
 $modinfo nvidia: Shows the list and parameters. 
 One of them is: parm: NVreg_TemporaryFilePath:charp 
 The fact that showed in modinfo so its on?
 https://wiki.archlinux.org/title/NVIDIA/Tips_and_tricks#Preserve_video_memory_after_suspend
 Thanks for the attention.
    submitted by    /u/kingsvell  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save 43% on a Sceptre Curved 24″ LED Monitor]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=496303</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15360151/sceptre-curved-24-led-monitor"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you like to be completely immersed in your game, or even a movie or your work, a curved monitor will work out well. It makes you feel like you’re right there in the middle of it. If you’ve been considering getting one, this may be the deal you’ve been waiting for. For 43% off, you can get a Sceptre Curved 24″ LED Monitor with 98% sRGB, HDMI, VGA, and built-in speakers.
    
The anti-flicker in the monitor will allow you to see a sharper picture, as it won’t allow the backlight that you would otherwise occasionally get from flickering. The 75Hz Refresh Rate is more than the industry standard and helps gamers with visibility. There are no blurry images, as frames transition instantly.
   
 
   
The curved display in the Sceptre Curved 24″ LED Monitor has a 1500R screen curvature to envelop you in your favorite streamed movies and TV shows. Tilt the screen 15 degrees backward and 5 degrees forward to get the optimum angle for you, leading to more comfortability.
   ... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ubuntu Deciding How To Tame Their systemd-oomd Killing Experience]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Ubuntu-systemd-oomd-Headaches</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Ubuntu-systemd-oomd-Headaches"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T19:15:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the many changes with the recent Ubuntu 22.04 LTS release was enabling systemd-oomd by default as the out-of-memory daemon that can kill processes when under memory pressure. Unfortunately, for some users this has led to a poor desktop experience with finding their applications being unexpectedly killed. Ubuntu developers are now discussing how to improve this OOMD handling...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Replacing the mainline kernel with zen kernel?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v8o3te/replacing_the_mainline_kernel_with_zen_kernel/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v8o3te/replacing_the_mainline_kernel_with_zen_kernel/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T19:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do I do this properly, without bricking my installation? I do not wish to keep both the kernels installed (unless absolutely necessary/recommended). What would be the correct order of commands/procedure to be followed? 
 I've never had to do this (switching/replacing) and the reason I insist on wanting to use zen is because I've used it on my arch + KDE setup from the get go, so I have a general sense of the performance I would get on that setup. Tried looking things up but the two situations (choosing/replacing) are described separately everywhere, which has left me a little unsure about what to do and how to do it safely.
 Help is appreciated!
    submitted by    /u/beyond9thousand  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gaming Headsets vs. Regular Headsets: What’s the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=802361</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/802361/gaming-headsets-vs.-regular-headsets-whats-the-difference/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T19:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gaming headsets are not always more expensive than regular ones. In fact, non-gaming headphones might be better for you! Let’s discuss what the main differences are between the two so you can decide for yourself.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Nguyen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Switching from X11 to Wayland]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v8ntqo/switching_from_x11_to_wayland/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v8ntqo/switching_from_x11_to_wayland/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T18:48:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have an Arch desktop PC with X11+KDE Plasma and I'd like to switch it to Wayland, mostly for security reasons. I installed what is suggested on the wiki. On my laptop I never installed X11 and sddm nicely offers a Wayland+KDE session, so on my desktop I had expected sddm to let me select either X11 or Wayland, now that both are installed. Still X11 is all that is offered.
 sddm log just says running /usr/bin/X but doesn't tell me why.
 Does anyone know what I am missing here?
    submitted by    /u/TheCakeWasNoLie  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How well does unity run on arch?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v8neij/how_well_does_unity_run_on_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v8neij/how_well_does_unity_run_on_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T18:28:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, I’ve been running an install of arch with xmonad on my spare SSD for a while now and I’m looking to make the full switch. Literally the only thing holding me back is how well the unity game engine runs on arch Linux (I prefer engineless programming but I’m working on a partnered project in which the scope demands that I use it). I know that Ubuntu and Debian are (apparently) fully supported, but I would prefer to use something arch based. Can anyone vouch for its stability and performance on arch?
    submitted by    /u/TaleHappy  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Notepad, Media Player updates out for Windows 11 Insiders]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/new-notepad-media-player-updates-out-for-windows-11-insiders/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/new-notepad-media-player-updates-out-for-windows-11-insiders/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T18:09:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has announced that the Windows 11 Notepad and Media Player applications are getting some new updates for Windows Insiders. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is a Wrapped Bitcoin (WBTC)?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=808855</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/808855/what-is-a-wrapped-bitcoin-wbtc/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T18:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A wrapped Bitcoin (WBTC) is a way to represent Bitcoin on the Ethereum blockchain. Bitcoin and Ethereum are the top two cryptocurrencies in the world, but they can’t normally interact with each other—hence the need for wrapping.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>RJ Fulton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Maps Can Now Tell You Where to Find Clean Air]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=810449</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/810449/google-maps-can-now-tell-you-where-to-find-clean-air/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T17:50:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google added air quality alerts to the Nest Hub smart displays last year, and now the company is bringing the same air quality data to Google Maps on iPhone and Android.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cync Finishes Launching Its New Line of Smart Home Products]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120582/cync-launches-its-new-line-of-smart-home-products/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120582/cync-launches-its-new-line-of-smart-home-products/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T17:49:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We were very excited when Cync (formerly C by GE) unveiled a line of affordable smart home products during CES 2022, including a smart thermostat and outdoor camera. And now that Cync has launched its new smart bulbs, you can finally buy the entire lineup.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox crashes when click on the font selection button in Settings on Wayland]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v8mggs/firefox_crashes_when_click_on_the_font_selection/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v8mggs/firefox_crashes_when_click_on_the_font_selection/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T17:47:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi,
 I was trying to change the font in Firefox on a newly set up system using Wayland. When I click on the font selection button in the Setting page, Firefox crashes immediately.
 The error msg is shown in the terminal as follow:
 ExceptionHandler::GenerateDump cloned child 3190 ExceptionHandler::WaitForContinueSignal waiting for continue signal... ExceptionHandler::SendContinueSignalToChild sent continue signal to child Exiting due to channel error. Exiting due to channel error. Exiting due to channel error. Exiting due to channel error. Exiting due to channel error. Exiting due to channel error. Exiting due to channel error. Exiting due to channel error. user1% Missing chrome or resource URL: resource://gre/modules/UpdateListener.jsm 
 Also I am getting
 Missing chrome or resource URL: resource://gre/modules/UpdateListener.jsm
 every time Firefox starts.
 I was wondering if anyone have any idea on this. Would this be a bug or do I miss something?
 Thank you!
    submitted by    /u/6324part2  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PipeWire 0.3.52 Released To Continue Enhancing Linux Audio/Video Streams]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=PipeWire-0.3.52-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=PipeWire-0.3.52-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T17:46:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PipeWire 0.3.52 was released today as the newest version of this open-source server for handling audio/video streams on the Linux desktop and increasingly being used now as a replacement for PulseAudio...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oops! Microsoft Just Gave Unsupported PCs Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120584/oops-microsoft-just-gave-unsupported-pcs-windows-11/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120584/oops-microsoft-just-gave-unsupported-pcs-windows-11/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T17:38:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As many of you probably know, Microsoft’s Windows 11 update has strict and controversial hardware requirements. But this week, when the company started rolling out the final test version of its highly anticipated Windows 11 (22H2) update, it accidentally gave unsupported PCs the new software.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EKSA Star Engine E5000 Pro Gaming Headset Review]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=495035</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15359993/eksa-star-engine-e5000-pro-gaming-headset"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T17:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comfort and quality sound are must-haves when it comes to a great gaming headset. The EKSA Star Engine E5000 Pro Gaming Headset seeks to give you a more immersive experience that’s comfortable enough to wear for marathon gaming sessions. But how well does it actually perform? I spent a week testing out this stylish headset to see if they work as well as promised.
    
This is a sponsored article and was made possible by EKSA. The actual contents and opinions are the sole views of the author who maintains editorial independence even when a post is sponsored.
    
Overview of Features
    
The EKSA Star Engine E5000 Pro Gaming Headset features a sci-fi design with RGB backlights on each earphone. The memory foam ear cushions not only provide optimal comfort, but help improve sound isolation. The adjustable headband is even cushioned to ensure players get even more comfort. The 3.94 in. x 3.53 in. with 1.1 in. earphones have ear cushions that fit most gamers very well.
   
 
... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Crystal Crowder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[mutter-performance vs mutter-dynamic-buffering?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v8lsmp/mutterperformance_vs_mutterdynamicbuffering/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v8lsmp/mutterperformance_vs_mutterdynamicbuffering/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T17:17:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greetings Arch Community,
 I've been running Gnome for a couple releases now (since ~3.30), and while performance improves with each new release, which I'm always very grateful for, it always feels like there is still room for some improvement. There can be the occasional lag/stutter with animations, like going in/out of Overview mode or going in/out of the App Drawer for example. This is noticeable not just on Arch, but on other distros I've tested like Fedora, PopOS, Solus, etc, so it's not unique to just Arch, but more so to the Gnome DE and quite possibly my hardware too. 
 I have an Acer Aspire E5-576G laptop, which has an Nvidia MX150/Intel hybrid setup, currently setup with EnvyControl, using the latest nvidia-dkms driver, to use the Nvidia GPU as the primary since I'm always connected to a power source. Since it's Nvidia, I still need to use Xorg for a majority of my workflow. I do like to test out Wayland every so often, but my default still needs to be Xorg for now.
 I'm currently using mutter v42.2-1 as my window manager, but I've noticed there are two other options available in the AUR: mutter-performance and mutter-dynamic-buffering
 I'm curious if these packages could offer any significantly noticeable improvement(s) under Xorg or if the gains are negligible under Xorg. 
 I'm wondering for any other Nvidia and/or Xorg users out there that have tried either of these two AUR packages, how your experience has been and if you recommend one package over the other for any reason(s)? Would appreciate any feedback so I have an idea what to expect before I can test them out. My understanding is it looks like the patches work better under Wayland than Xorg, so I appreciate any comments from others that have already tried either of these patches, thank you.
    submitted by    /u/dswhite85  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Does “Current Period” Mean in Cellular Data Settings on iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=808051</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/808051/what-does-current-period-mean-in-cellular-data-settings-on-iphone/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T17:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re looking at your cellular data usage in the Settings app on your iPhone, you might notice data usage statistics from a “Current Period.” But what exactly is the current period, and when did it start? Here’s how to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft's New Xbox TV App Is the Beginning of the End for Console Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120566/microsofts-new-xbox-tv-app-is-the-beginning-of-the-end-for-console-gaming/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120566/microsofts-new-xbox-tv-app-is-the-beginning-of-the-end-for-console-gaming/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T16:52:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s finally happening; Xbox Cloud Gaming is coming to smart TVs. Staring in late June, anyone with a Game Pass membership and a compatible TV can stream AAA games without additional hardware. This is Microsoft’s most significant step toward the future of gaming, and for better or worse, it’s the beginning of the end for the console era.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Tesla Key Card Vulnerability Lets Hackers Silently Steal Your Ride]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120570/new-tesla-key-card-vulnerability-lets-hackers-silently-steal-your-ride/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120570/new-tesla-key-card-vulnerability-lets-hackers-silently-steal-your-ride/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T16:47:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s no secret that Tesla has endured its share of potential problems regarding hackers accessing vehicles. However, a new report out of Austria shows a big vulnerability with Tesla’s NFC key cards that could let a hacker add a new card, then steal your car.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modificare testo e immagini nei PDF]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2014/05/modificare-testo-e-immagini-nei-pdf.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2014/05/modificare-testo-e-immagini-nei-pdf.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T16:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ci sono diversi motivi per cui il formato di file PDF è così popolare per lo scambio di documenti: i file PDF sono più compatti (di dimensioni più piccole) rispetto al documento originale; è possibile aprire un file PDF su qualsiasi computer o dispositivo mobile con un software gratuito come Adobe Acrobat Reader o altri programmi simili; i file PDF non possono essere modificati con facilità, specie con i software che funzionano solo da reader.
 Se utilizziamo il PDF vogliamo impedire a chi lo riceve di modificarlo come si potrebbe fare con un documento Word, limitando le modifiche solo ai campi di testo necessari (firma, data etc.). La maggior parte degli strumenti di modifica PDF però sono programmi commerciali a pagamento; in questa guida vi mostreremo i migliori programmi e servizi onli…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Defender now isolates hacked, unmanaged Windows devices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-defender-now-isolates-hacked-unmanaged-windows-devices/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-defender-now-isolates-hacked-unmanaged-windows-devices/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T16:35:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has announced a new feature for Microsoft Defender for Endpoint (MDE) to help organizations prevent attackers and malware from using compromised unmanaged devices to move laterally through the network. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ghacks Deals: Offcloud Lifetime Subscription]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179073</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/09/ghacks-deals-offcloud-lifetime-subscription/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T16:31:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Offcloud is a cloud-based download management service that acts as a middleman for downloads. Basically, what it allows you to do is use it to download files from any location and device, […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Ghacks Deals: Offcloud Lifetime Subscription appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Resources for learning and understanding pacman hooks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v8kp3g/resources_for_learning_and_understanding_pacman/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v8kp3g/resources_for_learning_and_understanding_pacman/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T16:28:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I want to learn and understand about pacman hooks and its usage. 
 I tried to search but most of the websites are so confusing to me. 
 Could someone give me some resources or something I can start with? (Or I'd better learn something else first)
 Thanks a lot.
    submitted by    /u/HynDuf  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Chrome for Android Will Get a Toolbar That Adapts to You]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120564/google-chrome-for-android-will-get-a-toolbar-that-adapts-to-you/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120564/google-chrome-for-android-will-get-a-toolbar-that-adapts-to-you/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T16:03:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Chrome continues to get better with each update, and in the next version of Chrome for Android, the toolbar will adapt to our needs automatically and much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 of the Most Expensive Mobile Apps You Can Buy Today]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=805774</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/805774/6-of-the-most-expensive-mobile-apps-you-can-buy-today/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T16:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like our list of “Most Expensive Phones of All Time,” we need to set some parameters for what we mean by “expensive.” When it comes to apps, there are two types of “expensive.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[efly: A Graphical Live Medium with Persistent Storage]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v8jtep/efly_a_graphical_live_medium_with_persistent/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v8jtep/efly_a_graphical_live_medium_with_persistent/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T15:49:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello Friends.
 I have tweaked the efly live system to facilitate persistent storage, so that changes are kept after rebooting.
 You can change keymap, timezone, language etc. and don't have to retype everything, when you decide to reboot. Everything stays.
 Installing packages and creating files is also possible without problems. The system will auto-expand at boot to the size of your stick. Usage as a hybrid rescue system / portable storage is possible.
 Creating the disk image yourself is very easy, if you are running an Arch Linux system. How to do that is explained on github.
 This is how you can place it on a stick:
  wget https://github.com/flying-dude/efly/releases/download/latest/efly-live.img sudo cp efly-live.img /dev/sdX # replace sdX with the device node of your stick 
 If you want to run it inside a VM, you need to truncate first:
  wget https://github.com/flying-dude/efly/releases/download/latest/efly-live.img truncate --size=10G efly-live.img git clone https://github.com/flying-dude/efly efly/scripts/efly-qemu --uefi efly-live.img 
 This is brand-new but so far it works really well. Let me know, if you are encountering issues.
    submitted by    /u/flying-dude  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vice Society ransomware claims attack on Italian city of Palermo]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/vice-society-ransomware-claims-attack-on-italian-city-of-palermo/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/vice-society-ransomware-claims-attack-on-italian-city-of-palermo/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T15:43:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Vice Society ransomware group has claimed responsibility for the recent cyber attack on the city of Palermo in Italy, which has caused a large-scale service outage. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft: basta hard disk per installare Windows. Dal 2023 solo SSD]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Microsoft-basta-hard-disk-per-installare-Windows-Dal-2023-solo-SSD_24621</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Microsoft-basta-hard-disk-per-installare-Windows-Dal-2023-solo-SSD_24621"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T15:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gli hard disk sono tutt'altro che superati: tecnologie sempre più moderne consentono la realizzazione e la commercializzazione di unità capienti e performanti, con un costo a gigabyte ridotto.Secondo Seagate gli SSD non uccideranno gli hard disk e continueranno a convivere con le unità a stato solido per lungo tempo.Microsoft starebbe lavorando perché tutti i partner che si occupano di progettazione, sviluppo e commercializzazione di dispositivi basati su Windows usino esclusivamente unità SSD per l'installazione del sistema operativo. Questo a partire dal 2023.Al momento i requisiti per l'installazione di Windows 11 non obbligano a usare un SSD ma anche gli utenti potrebbero essere presto esortati ad accantonare gli hard disk.Allo stato attuale Microsoft si limita a rimarcare che funziona…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Dell XPS 13 Series Has 12th-Gen Intel, No Headphone Jack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=810367</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/810367/new-dell-xps-13-series-has-12th-gen-intel-no-headphone-jack/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T15:31:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Dell XPS 13 has been around for years as one of the best laptops with Windows, and now Dell has updated it with two distinct models for 2022 — right on the heels of Apple’s new MacBook Air.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[M2 vs. M1 MacBook Pro: What’s the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809657</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809657/m2-vs-m1-macbook-pro/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T15:30:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The M2 MacBook Pro might just be the odd one out in Apple’s notebook line-up, but that doesn’t mean you should write it off completely. If you’re fond of the 13-inch form factor or Apple’s previous design choices, the M2 upgrade might just be worth your time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Samsung’s Quick Share Feature and How to Use It]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=476688</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15359804/use-samsung-quick-share"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sharing photos, videos, and other documents between different devices without loss of quality has always been rather tricky. Sure, many third-party apps exist that do the job, but wouldn’t it be nice if there was a native feature to quickly and easily share files? Say hello to Samsung’s Quick Share solution. Find out what is Quick Share and how to use it to send files to Samsung and non-Samsung devices.
   

Content

What Is Quick Share in Samsung Galaxy Phones
Types of Quick Share
How to Share Files With Nearby Galaxy Devices
How to Send Files as a Link
How to View Link Sharing History
How to Stop Sharing a File
How to Send Files as Link in the Samsung Messages App
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Use S Pen Like a Pro on Samsung Galaxy Phones
  ... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mehvish Mushtaq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 6 Best Free Email Services]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119720/the-best-free-email-services/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119720/the-best-free-email-services/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T15:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most people use at least one free email account for regular correspondence. In addition to being free, these services are also convenient and easy to use. If you’re setting up an email account for the first time or want to try a new service, read on to see which one suits your needs best.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Chadwick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reti mobili 6G in fase di test: provato il primo collegamento a 1 petabit per secondo]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Reti-mobili-6G-in-fase-di-test-provato-il-primo-collegamento-a-1-petabit-per-secondo_24620</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Reti-mobili-6G-in-fase-di-test-provato-il-primo-collegamento-a-1-petabit-per-secondo_24620"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T15:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Italia la  è in fase di dispiegamento. Le prestazioni migliori, con concreti vantaggi anche in termini di riduzione della latenza, dei consumi energetici e miglioramento della sicurezza, sono garantite dalle reti 5G Standalone (5G SA) capaci di autosostenersi senza dipendere da nessun'altra tecnologia sottostante.Le aziende impegnate nella progettazione e produzione dei dispositivi per le telecomunicazioni stanno nel frattempo già guardando avanti tanto che sono iniziati i primi test per creare network 6G: essi permetteranno di sviluppare reti mobili di sesta generazione con una velocità di trasmissione dati fino a 100.000 volte superiore al massimo teorico del 5G.NTT DOCOMO, il principale operatore di telecomunicazioni mobili del Giappone, la sua società madre NTT, NEC, Fujitsu e Nokia sono stati incaricati dei primi test relativi alla prossima generazione di reti mobili.Ma sarà del tutto inutile disporre di tecnologie 6G a livello di singole celle se l'infrastruttura sottostante non sarà in grado di offrire una larghezza di banda sufficiente.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[bash history not working?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v8is4g/bash_history_not_working/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v8is4g/bash_history_not_working/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T15:01:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I press up in a terminal the wrong command is popping up. But the .bash_history shows the right latest commands. 
 What do I need to do to fix it?
    submitted by    /u/Pure_Pasifist  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Easiest Way to Create a Mail Merge in Microsoft Word]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=806904</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/806904/the-easiest-way-to-do-a-mail-merge-in-word/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T15:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you need to print letters or send emails to many customers, clients, or employees, you can do so quickly using a mail merge. With the mail merge wizard in Microsoft Word, you can set this up in just minutes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dell's Latest XPS Takes On the Surface Tablet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120551/dells-latest-xps-takes-on-the-surface-tablet/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120551/dells-latest-xps-takes-on-the-surface-tablet/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T14:59:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dell is giving its reversible laptop a Surface-inspired redesign. The new XPS 13 2-in-1 is a fully-functional tablet with a detachable magnetic keyboard, a touchscreen, and a stylus. It runs on the impressive hardware for the form-factor, and oddly enough, it packs a 4K rear camera.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Mass Effect’, ‘It Takes Two’, and More Come to GeForce NOW Today]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=810243</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/810243/mass-effect-it-takes-two-and-more-come-to-geforce-now-today/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T14:58:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every Thursday, NVIDIA’s GeForce NOW gets a fresh batch of games you can purchase from your favorite PC game stores and play on your existing devices through the cloud. This week, EA is adding two critically acclaimed titles, plus you’ll find eight more games ready to stream today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zach Laidlaw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come verificare se la VPN funziona e protegge la privacy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/06/come-verificare-se-la-vpn-funziona-e.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/06/come-verificare-se-la-vpn-funziona-e.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T14:55:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quando utilizziamo una VPN vogliamo ottenere il massimo rispetto della privacy per i nostri dispositivi ed evitare che il nostro indirizzo IP pubblico e il nostro traffico di rete sia spiato dai siti web e dal provider della connessione Internet. Purtroppo sono ancora numerosi gli scenari in cui, anche utilizzando una VPN, è possibile ricavare alcune informazioni sull'utente nascosto, sfruttando alcune debolezze presenti sul sistema operativo o sul browser web che stiamo utilizzando in quel preciso momento.
 Per ottenere il massimo rispetto della privacy e per navigare davvero anonimi vi consigliamo di eseguire alcuni semplici test per verificare se la tua VPN funziona, proteggendo ogni dato che passa dal dispositivo al sito scelto.
 Se riscontriamo qualche vulnerabilità sulla nostra conne…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[is it safe to dual boot windows and pure arch linux on the same hard drive?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v8ihha/is_it_safe_to_dual_boot_windows_and_pure_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v8ihha/is_it_safe_to_dual_boot_windows_and_pure_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T14:48:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I only have one hard drive for my tower computer. I don't really want to buy another hard drive since I don't really use windows at all when I dual boot. I would like to have pure arch linux on the same drive but I've heard its not a good idea, which is strange because by that logic all laptop users shouldnt dual boot windows and linux. I guess it's safer if you never really use windows since windows has a lot of updates here and there? I never really use windows anyways. Right now I am dual booting windows and pop os on my tower and everything works fine. Just want to know if I can expect the same result with arch (assuming I do the long installation process correctly). Any tips on making installing arch linux an easier experience would be appreciated as well.
    submitted by    /u/Righteous_Warrior  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung T7 Shield Review: Safe Data Wherever You Go]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/116638/samsung-t7-shield-ssd-review/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/116638/samsung-t7-shield-ssd-review/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T14:24:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Would you trust your portable SSD in the rain, sleet, or dust and debris? The Samsung T7 Shield’s IP65 rating makes it a resilient companion for storage wherever data takes you. It’s not just a pretty face with rugged protection, though; this 1TB NVMe drive also puts up serious read/write speeds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcus Mears III</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Wireless Earbuds of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=772140</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/772140/best-wireless-earbuds/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The best truly wireless earbuds offer a nice refuge from untangling pesky wired headphones without compromising sound quality. Drown out the sounds of the world around you with some of our favorite wireless earbuds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Prince</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[how to make ur own aur helper in py]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v8hg1z/how_to_make_ur_own_aur_helper_in_py/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v8hg1z/how_to_make_ur_own_aur_helper_in_py/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T13:58:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm a complete noob i want to make something to help the community or else just learn something different so can y'all guide toward the right direction
    submitted by    /u/thelastgodkami  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fixing a corrupt exfat device?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v8hdzi/fixing_a_corrupt_exfat_device/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v8hdzi/fixing_a_corrupt_exfat_device/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T13:55:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm trying to repair a corrupt SD card on my arch laptop that was formatted on Android with exFAT.
 There appear to be two versions of fsck.exfat in the repos, one in exfatprogs and one in exfat-utils. Neither version will agree to repair the errors. The one in exfat-utils finds 33 errors on the device, but no matter what flags I give it it won't attempt to repair them.
 The version in exfatprogs only finds two errors, but it automatically answers all the repair questions as "no", even if I pass the -p -r, or -y flags.
 In both cases, I tried running as root and as a regular user.
 The man page says nothing helpful here, anyone know what might be up?
    submitted by    /u/lykwydchykyn  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vivaldi browser integra un client email: come funziona]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Vivaldi-browser-integra-un-client-email-come-funziona_24619</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Vivaldi-browser-integra-un-client-email-come-funziona_24619"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T13:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nell'elenco dei browser web alternativi c'è Vivaldi. Il suo nome deriva dal compositore italiano e seppur basato su Chromium, come molti altri prodotti concorrenti tra cui Microsoft Edge, Vivaldi ha recuperato molte delle caratteristiche che caratterizzavano il motore di rendering Presto utilizzato dal browser Opera.Perché Opera? Perché il cofondatore del progetto Vivaldi, l'islandese Jon Stephenson von Tetzchner, presentò il nuovo browser nel 2015-2016 dopo aver abbandonato il ruolo di CEO in Opera Software. A suo tempo parlammo di Vivaldi come il nuovo browser del padre di Opera.Vivaldi non è completamente open source: essendo un browser derivato da Chromium, tutte le modifiche applicate vengono sempre rese di pubblico dominio.Il browser utilizza però componenti di terze parti e un'esclusiva interfaccia utente che gli sviluppatori non vogliono vedere in prodotti derivati.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Where to Stream the ‘Jurassic Park’ Franchise in 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=807194</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/807194/where-to-stream-jurassic-park/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting with one blockbuster movie about genetically engineered dinosaurs in the modern world, Jurassic Park has become one of the most lucrative pop-culture properties of the last three decades. Here’s how to stream the Jurassic Park franchise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Bell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.11 Is Much Faster, But Pyston & PyPy Still Show Advantages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31198</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31198"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T13:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There was much interest in the recent Python 3.11 beta benchmarks showing much performance uplift from this in-development version of Python compared to prior 3.x releases. While Python 3.11 performance is looking great and huge advantages compared to prior versions, there are also alternative Python implementations like PyPy and Pyston. Stemming from Phoronix reader requests, here are benchmarks showing how Python 3.11 beta performance compares to those alternative Python implementations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Download Instagram Reels (5 Ways)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/?p=60035</id>
        <link href="https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/download-instagram-reels/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T13:01:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Instagram is an incredibly popular photo-sharing app where users can upload and share their pictures with friends and family members. However, in recent]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hongkiat.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will My Internet Connection Support Smart Security Cameras?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=804637</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/804637/will-my-internet-connection-support-smart-security-cameras/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T13:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When shopping for smart security cameras there’s a good chance you’ve focused on the flashier aspects like the camera resolution, app features, and cloud capabilities. Here’s why you should consider your internet connection, too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Fitzpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will iOS 16 and iPadOS 16 Run on My iPhone or iPad?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809665</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809665/will-ios-ipados-16-run-on-my-iphone-ipad/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T12:30:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every year Apple releases a new major update for iPhone and iPad devices, but some devices won’t receive the update, usually around seven years after they first debuted. Here’s which devices are compatible with iOS 16 and iPadOS 16.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dark web sites selling alleged Western weapons sent to Ukraine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/dark-web-sites-selling-alleged-western-weapons-sent-to-ukraine/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/dark-web-sites-selling-alleged-western-weapons-sent-to-ukraine/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several weapon marketplaces on the dark web have listed military-grade firearms allegedly coming from Western countries that sent them to support the Ukrainian army in its fight against the Russian invaders. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Opera 88 launches with Shopping Corner feature]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179066</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/09/opera-88-launches-with-shopping-corner-feature/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T12:21:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Opera Software released Opera 88 Stable this week. The new version of the web browser introduces support for horizontal tab scrolling and a new feature that Opera Software calls Shopping Corner. Shopping […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Opera 88 launches with Shopping Corner feature appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulkan 1.3.217 Adds Extension To Interact With Apple Metal Objects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Vulkan-1.3.217</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Vulkan-1.3.217"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T12:02:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vulkan 1.3.217 is out this morning as the newest version of the Khronos' high performance graphics/compute API specification. With Vulkan 1.3.217 comes two new extensions...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Smaller SSDs Are Slower Than Larger SSDs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=797011</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/797011/why-smaller-ssds-are-slower-than-larger-ssds/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T12:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SSDs with larger capacities reliably post better performance numbers than smaller capacity drives of the same make and model. If you don’t know anything about how SSDs work, this seems like a mystery, but the reason behind the slowdown makes perfect sense.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sydney Butler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Symbiote malware infects all running processes on Linux systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-symbiote-malware-infects-all-running-processes-on-linux-systems/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-symbiote-malware-infects-all-running-processes-on-linux-systems/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T12:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat analysts have discovered a new malware targeting Linux systems that operates as a symbiote in the host, blending perfectly with running processes and network traffic to steal account credentials and give its operators backdoor access. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[login issue]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v8f8ej/login_issue/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v8f8ej/login_issue/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T11:59:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I updated my system this morning and i did a restart. Not too long after logging in (my drive is encrypted, just extra info), i just got stuck. Like after logging in, it was stuck stransitioning from the greeter to my usual config. I did not do anything weird. It just kinda broke itself.
    submitted by    /u/Waffreo  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quale scegliere tra Intel Core i3, i5, i7 e i9]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2017/02/quale-scegliere-tra-intel-core-i3-i5-e.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2017/02/quale-scegliere-tra-intel-core-i3-i5-e.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T11:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quando si va a comprare un portatile o un PC desktop si potrebbe notare che nella maggior parte dei casi il processore è Intel, appartenente alla famiglia Intel i3, Intel i5, Intel i7 o Intel i9. Mentre i PC con processore i3 sono più economici, gli i5 sono un ottimo compromesso tra potenza e costo mentre i processori i7 e i9 sono tra i processori più potenti ed anche più costosi.
 A seconda delle esigenze si potrebbe pensare di scegliere un PC con processore i3 per risparmiare oppure andare su un i5 o comprare un i7 per avere una CPU più veloce e più capace. Questo tipo di criterio di scelta non è, però, da usare in modo così preciso e chiaro, perché ci sono differenze anche tra modelli della stessa famiglia: possiamo trovare un i7 vecchio che gira peggio di un i5 nuovissimo.
 Con questo …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Awesome Google Chrome Features You Should Be Using]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=808973</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/808973/10-awesome-google-chrome-features-you-should-be-using/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T11:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Chrome has become the go-to browser for many people. It’s chock full of powerful features that make it popular, but you may not have found all the best ones yet. We’ll make sure you do.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese hacking group Aoqin Dragon quietly spied orgs for a decade]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/chinese-hacking-group-aoqin-dragon-quietly-spied-orgs-for-a-decade/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/chinese-hacking-group-aoqin-dragon-quietly-spied-orgs-for-a-decade/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A previously unknown Chinese-speaking threat actor has been uncovered by threat analysts SentinelLabs who were able to link it to malicious activity going as far back as 2013. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux 5.20 With AMD Zen Will Prefer MWAIT Over HALT As An HPC Optimization]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.20-AMD-MWAIT</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.20-AMD-MWAIT"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T10:45:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier this year was an AMD Linux patch to prefer using MWAIT rather than HALT for cases where the CPU idle driver isn't being used. Using MWAIT can lead to significant improvements for the exit latency and now for the Linux 5.20 cycle later this year that change is expected to land...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come copiare testo da foto su smartphone e tablet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Come-copiare-testo-da-foto-su-smartphone-e-tablet_24618</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Come-copiare-testo-da-foto-su-smartphone-e-tablet_24618"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T10:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avete scattato una foto a una pagina cartacea, a un documento o comunque a qualcosa che contiene del testo (ad esempio un'insegna, un menu, un cartello,...) e volete copiarlo altrove?Per copiare testo da foto su Android e iOS è possibile utilizzare diverse strategie: la prima è probabilmente più semplice ed efficace si basa sull'utilizzo di Google Foto.Dopo aver scattato una foto è possibile selezionarla nella galleria di Google Foto e aprirla. Nella parte inferiore dello schermo si deve toccare l'icona Lens quindi toccare Testo.

Utilizzando l'intelligenza artificiale di Google Lens l'app mostra il messaggio 'Trovato testo nell'immagine'.

Toccando il pulsante Seleziona tutto, il testo sarà evidenziato nella sua interezza.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EU USB-C Requirement Could Put iPhone Plans on Hyperdrive]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=496210</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15359403/eu-usb-c-requirement-iphone"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T10:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You know that drawer you have in your home that holds all your old chargers and cords, with some most likely far outlasting the actual devices? I can’t be the only one. The European Union wants to help us with that. An agreement was reached that will require smartphones and other devices to charge via USB-C, limiting that mess. Does this mean Apple will finally have to ditch the Lightning port on the iPhone and replace it with USB-C?
   
Also read:What Is a GaN Charger? 5 of the Best GaN Chargers You Can Buy
    
EU USB-C Proposal
    
In September 2021, the European Commission proposed a mandate that would require USB-C charging for many devices.
   
 Image source: Unsplash
   
Apple was voicing its concerns... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub's Atom text editor will be retired in December]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179057</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/09/githubs-atom-text-editor-will-be-retired-in-december/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T10:10:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub has announced that it is sunsetting its text editor, Atom. The application, which debuted in 2011, will be retired on December 15, 2022. Atom emerged as a promising tool for code […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post GitHub's Atom text editor will be retired in December appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Freelance Writers’ Guide to Better Time Management]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/?p=20314</id>
        <link href="https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/freelancers-time-management-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T10:01:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time. There just isn't enough of it. Ask any freelance content writer what their biggest concern happens to be at any given moment, and unless they are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Kuttner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More Intel Raptor Lake & Meteor Lake Driver Additions Coming For Linux 5.20]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=More-Raptor-Meteor-Linux-5.20</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=More-Raptor-Meteor-Linux-5.20"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T09:57:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intel's open-source Linux driver engineers are busy not only preparing support for next-generation 13th Gen Core "Raptor Lake" processors but also the follow-on 14th Gen "Meteor Lake" on Linux...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RADV Adds EXT_primitives_generated_query To Help Zink OpenGL-On-Vulkan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=RADV-Primitives-Generated</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=RADV-Primitives-Generated"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T09:25:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The newest contribution to the open-source Radeon Vulkan "RADV" driver in Mesa by Valve's Linux graphics driver developers is for supporting VK_EXT_primitives_generated_query...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BeOS-Inspired Haiku Makes Progress On Driver Porting, Plans For Usable RISC-V Images]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Haiku-May-2022-Report</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Haiku-May-2022-Report"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T09:09:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Haiku open-source operating system project building off the success of BeOS continues steadily improving its hardware support and making other improvements...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[eSIM: Apple permette di copiare i dati da un dispositivo all'altro]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=eSIM-Apple-permette-di-copiare-i-dati-da-un-dispositivo-all-altro_24617</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=eSIM-Apple-permette-di-copiare-i-dati-da-un-dispositivo-all-altro_24617"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T08:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Le eSIM rappresentano la versione virtuale della SIM tradizionale. Anziché avere a che fare con un chip su supporto plastico da inserire in uno slot, con una eSIM è possibile abilitare lo smartphone a comunicare sulla rete dati di uno specifico operatore e con piano tariffario 'ad hoc' semplicemente scansionando un codice QR. I dati della eSIM vengono infatti memorizzati all'interno del dispositivo, in un chip saldato sul circuito integrato.In passato abbiamo visto nel dettaglio cos'è una eSIM e come funziona: con il lancio di iOS 16 Apple offre la possibilità di trasferire le eSIM da un iPhone all'altro via Bluetooth.Per attivare il trasferimento delle eSIM è necessario che l'iPhone 'di destinazione' abbia il modulo Bluetooth attivo, sia sbloccato e che, ovviamente, sia fisicamente nelle immediate vicinanze.Perché la procedura vada a buon fine è necessario che l'operatore di telefonia mobile supporti il trasferimento delle sue eSIM da un telefono all'altro.Al momento ciò è tutt'altro che scontato dal momento che iOS 16 è stato appena presentato in veste definitiva e la funzione per spostare le eSIM da un iPhone all'altro è ancora in 'beta'.Gli iPhone XS e successivi supportano una singola eSIM mentre tutti i modelli di iPhone 13 assicurano l'utilizzo di una configurazione dual eSIM.Anche Google sta spingendo l'acceleratore sul supporto eSIM: Android 13 permette di effettuare connessioni multiple anche con un solo chip eSIM.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 10 RAID - Readable from Arch/Linux?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v8bruz/windows_10_raid_readable_from_archlinux/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v8bruz/windows_10_raid_readable_from_archlinux/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T08:02:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Helping out a friend. Trying to boot from a USB to look at his Windows 10 hard drive (actually NVME), but not finding it recognized. This is an image of what I see in UEFI for this Dell Inspiron 15 5501. How can I get access to this drive? (As far as I know there's only one NVME in there, despite the UEFI making it appear differently.)
    submitted by    /u/DiagonalArg  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Calcolo pi greco: Google Cloud batte un nuovo record e arriva a 100.000 miliardi di cifre]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Calcolo-pi-greco-Google-Cloud-batte-un-nuovo-record-e-arriva-a-100000-miliardi-di-cifre_24616</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Calcolo-pi-greco-Google-Cloud-batte-un-nuovo-record-e-arriva-a-100000-miliardi-di-cifre_24616"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T07:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Il pi greco esprime il rapporto tra la circonferenza di un cerchio e il suo diametro ed equivale a circa 3,14. 'Circa' perché le cifre decimali che formano la 'costante pi greco' sono infinite e da anni i matematici fanno a gara per scoprirne di nuove.Il pi greco è un numero irrazionale che non può essere scritto come quoziente di due valori interi ed è anche numero trascendente che cioè non può essere espresso usando un numero finito di valori interi, di frazioni e di loro radici. Ecco perché il problema della quadratura del cerchio non è risolvibile: non è possibile costruire un quadrato di area esattamente corrispondente a quella di un cerchio. Al massimo ci si può avvicinare per approssimazioni successive.Al di là dei problemi matematico-geometrici, il calcolo del valore del pi greco c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox 101.0.1 fixes issues in Mac, Windows and Linux versions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179061</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/09/firefox-101-0-1-fixes-issues-in-mac-windows-and-linux-versions/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T07:04:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla Firefox 101.0.1 will be released later today (if you are reading this on June 9, 2022). The new point release of Firefox Stable fixes three main issues and several smaller issues, […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Firefox 101.0.1 fixes issues in Mac, Windows and Linux versions appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vivaldi Mail 1.0: email client with calendar and feed reader launches]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179056</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/09/vivaldi-mail-1-0-email-client-with-calendar-and-feed-reader-launches/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T07:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vivaldi Technologies launched Vivaldi Mail 1.0 with calendar and feed reader today in the company's web browser. Released in late 2020 as a preview, Vivaldi Mail was launched in Vivaldi 4.0 officially. […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Vivaldi Mail 1.0: email client with calendar and feed reader launches appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vivaldi Browser’s Mail Client Is Now Ready for Everyone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=810128</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/810128/vivaldi-browsers-mail-client-is-now-ready-for-everyone/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T07:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Vivaldi web browser isn’t just a browser: it added an email client last year as a beta feature. Now the email client is officially exiting beta with today’s 1.0 release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can I run only a specific program (Lattice Diamond) with a certain color profile?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v8atck/can_i_run_only_a_specific_program_lattice_diamond/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v8atck/can_i_run_only_a_specific_program_lattice_diamond/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T06:53:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At work I use Lattice Diamond, which does not play well with dark color schemes. Is there a way that I can have *only* that program launch with a light color scheme?
    submitted by    /u/fir_with_feedback  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making new installation better on my laptop]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v89x01/making_new_installation_better_on_my_laptop/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v89x01/making_new_installation_better_on_my_laptop/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T05:53:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello.
 I installed Arch a couple of days ago on my laptop.
 It works great - super snappy and lightweight which is exactly what I wanted.
 I'm unable to find a tool that allows me to map the function modifiers (brightness, volume, enable WLAN, etc) to do those functions.
 Is there some software on the AUR that lets me do this?
 For ref: It's an HP laptop, and I'm using Arch without a DE, only i3.
    submitted by    /u/Decent-Squirrel-6316  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I noticed a bug in 5.18 kernel version:touchpad is not recognized after a first resume after suspend; but if I suspend it and resume it again, it works. I put this bug in an non-new bugzilla related report...but should I report it again somewhere else? Since now it happens at EVERY resume after 5.18]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v891x3/i_noticed_a_bug_in_518_kernel_versiontouchpad_is/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v891x3/i_noticed_a_bug_in_518_kernel_versiontouchpad_is/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T04:58:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I reported it here: https://bugzilla.kernel.org/show_bug.cgi?id=214749 which is a general freezing that happens in random times after resume. But now after 5.18 kernel version, it happens ALWAYS after wake up after suspend.
 How can I make kernel devs know that this is a new kernel version bug? Should I report it again somewhere else?
    submitted by    /u/allexj  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is there a way to exclude a BTRFS subvolume from snapshots with snapper ?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v85o4i/is_there_a_way_to_exclude_a_btrfs_subvolume_from/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v85o4i/is_there_a_way_to_exclude_a_btrfs_subvolume_from/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T01:48:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm looking to reinstall Arch with BTRFS filesystem + encryption on my hard drive. I will create '@','@home','@cache' for /var/cache,'@boot'. and what I want to do is to exclude the '@cache' and '@home' when creating snapshots as i don't wanna take a snapshot of cache files and my own files (I have them backed up elsewhere).
 Is this possible ? and if yes, How to do it ?
    submitted by    /u/1_7xr  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[btw i use arch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v84qcy/btw_i_use_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v84qcy/btw_i_use_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T00:58:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meant in a good way. Gentoo is for ppl who like overworking themselves!
    submitted by    /u/LuigiHacker  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Check How Much Google Storage You Have Left]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=491998</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15358306/check-how-much-google-storage-left"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you sign up with a Google account, you automatically receive 15GB of cloud storage for free. Here you can store your photos, documents, messages and more. While this may seem like a lot, you can actually run out of space pretty fast. In this article, we show you how to check how much Google storage you have left so that you’re never caught off guard. We also share some tips that show how to free up some space and avoid exceeding the limit.
   

Content

What Counts Toward Your Google Storage Limit?
What Happens When You Run Out Of Space?
How to Check How Much Google Storage You Have Left
How to Free Up Google Storage
Buy More Storage
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Free Up Storage Space on Android
    
What Counts Toward Your Google Storage Limit?
    
To keep... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexandra Arici</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[systemd TPM2 decryption keeps asking for LUKS passphrase]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v83q1i/systemd_tpm2_decryption_keeps_asking_for_luks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v83q1i/systemd_tpm2_decryption_keeps_asking_for_luks/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T00:05:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been using secure boot with systemd to auto-decrypt my LUKS system partition on boot for about a year on all my bare metal arch systems, but my headless server has been having issues since 251.1-1 was installed. My desktop and laptop auto-decrypt just fine. BIOS version hasn't changed between systemd updates. It's using AMD fTPM.
 251.2-1 hit my server but the issue continues. When systemd-boot reaches the disk decryption for root, it takes 5 seconds to run two cryptsetup jobs (without error) to decrypt as if it's working, but then prompts for a passphrase. If I wipe the TPM2 slot, it skips that 2-job step and instantly prompts for passphrase. Entering the passphrase will allow the boot to continue successfully.
 I'm using PCRs 0 and 7, and they have the exact same values after each boot according to tpm2_pcrread.
 I tried enrolling with option --tpm2-with-pin=no, clearing TPM from BIOS, enabling all sha1 and sha256 banks, wiping tpm2 cryptenroll slots and turning TPM off + power cycling and setting it all up again but still no progress. It's always the same 5 sec cryptsetup jobs that results in a LUKS passphrase prompt. My systemd-boot entry hasn't changed since I first set it up, and the rd.luks options are all the exact same from when it worked before.
 Tried to re-cryptenroll the root by sdX and by-uuid. A secondary storage disk decrypts using crypttab just fine (using keyfile, not TPM).
 Output of bootctl status seems good:
 System: Firmware: UEFI 2.70 (American Megatrends 5.17) Secure Boot: enabled (user) TPM2 Support: yes Boot into FW: supported Current Boot Loader: Product: systemd-boot 251.2-1-arch 
 I can't find any related errors in journalctl, where else could I troubleshoot this issue?
    submitted by    /u/Terry-51C  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conky & Dash to Dock]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v83n4r/conky_dash_to_dock/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v83n4r/conky_dash_to_dock/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T00:01:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I run conky, it sets off the auto-hide feature of dash to dock. Even on a black workspace the dash to dock minimizes... I have to drag my mouse down to the bottom of the screen for it to show up. Dash to dock should ignore Conky, but I don't know how to do this... I tried editing conky.conf and changed own_window = true to false, but that didn't create change...
 Anyone know what setting I'm missing?
    submitted by    /u/PaulLee420  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mesa 22.2 RADV Driver Adds Vulkan Ray-Tracing Maintenance Extension]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Mesa-22.2-RT-Maintenance1</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Mesa-22.2-RT-Maintenance1"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T22:36:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As added reason for Radeon Linux users to celebrate today beyond Blender 3.2 releasing with AMD HIP Linux render support is that Mesa's Radeon Vulkan driver "RADV" continues maturing with its ray-tracing support...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come togliere l’icona “Informazioni su questa immagine” dal desktop di Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>3593|20220609000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/windows-10/come-togliere-licona-informazioni-questa-immagine-desktop-windows-11-3593"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[L’arrivo della patch KB5014019 ha comportato l’aggiunta di una nuova funzione alla personalizzazione dello sfondo di Windows 11, i Contenuti in evidenza di Windows o Windows Spotlight, praticamente lo stesso tipo di immagini che vedete all’avvio del computer o nella schermata di logon dell’account. Se utilizzate questo tipo di personalizzazione dello sfondo troverete anche una nuova icona sul desktop, Informazioni su questa immagine, che non si può cancellare o nascondere, e una volta cliccata apre Microsoft Edge e mostra una serie di link riguardanti l’immagine visualizzata.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How do Doas function? Considering opendoas]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v80s10/how_do_doas_function_considering_opendoas/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v80s10/how_do_doas_function_considering_opendoas/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T21:42:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm currently using sudo for system maintenance tasks and it seems to work well.
 I noticed that opendoas is available in the community repo.
 What are the benefit of Doas?
 Is it more secure? Less resource intensive?
    submitted by    /u/RandomXUsr  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The New LEGO Roller Coaster Is Pretty Loopy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120529/the-new-lego-roller-coaster-is-pretty-loopy/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120529/the-new-lego-roller-coaster-is-pretty-loopy/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T21:38:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LEGO just unveiled the next set in its Fairground Collection, the massive Loop Coaster. While not as large as the previous Creator Expert Roller Coaster, the Loop Coaster is 36 inches tall, features two loops, and has an elevator that you can motorize for an endless ride (with an add-on Technic Large Motor and Battery).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kali Linux team to stream free penetration testing course on Twitch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/kali-linux-team-to-stream-free-penetration-testing-course-on-twitch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/kali-linux-team-to-stream-free-penetration-testing-course-on-twitch/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T21:26:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Offensive Security, the creators of Kali Linux, announced today that they would be offering free access to their live-streamed 'Penetration Testing with Kali Linux (PEN-200/PWK)' training course later this month. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Identify Songs from Movies and TV Shows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=341924</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/13489000/identify-songs-from-movies-tv-shows"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With many shows boasting high production values, everything including the soundtrack is impressive. While many people are watching their favorite show, their ears perk up, thanks to the soundtrack. Great music-identifier apps like TuneFind and Shazam do the job better than ever, but there are many ways to identify your favorite songs! If you’ve always wanted help identifying the earworms you’ve heard on TV and in movies, don’t fret, as your phone is here to help.
   

Content

IMDb
Google Assistant/Siri
TuneFind
WhatSong
Shazam
SnapChat
SoundHound
Soundtrack.net
AdTunes
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Easily Download Streaming Video on Any Platform
    
IMDb
    
Most likely you have heard of IMDb. The Internet Movie Database is home to information about virtually every movie and TV show ever produced. IMDb is truly a treasure trove for pop culture junkies. It includes... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Lynch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are Smart Homes Worth the Hassle?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120490/are-smart-homes-worth-the-hassle/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120490/are-smart-homes-worth-the-hassle/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T21:13:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smart homes promise to make our lives easier. And while that promise may be genuine, it’s always flanked by a great irony. Building and maintaining a smart home takes time, money, and research—it’s a hassle, and for some people, that hassle can run the potential benefits of a smart home straight into the ground.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LOOKING FOR HELP!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v7zyhe/looking_for_help/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v7zyhe/looking_for_help/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T21:02:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WE ARE LOOKING FOR HELP FINDING A BUG WITH THE YUZU EMULATOR AND MESA
 The emulator seems to present weird graphical glitches when using mesa and arch linux.
 These isuess are not present on fedora 35.
 ​
 So please.
 ANYBODY WITH A FUNCTIONING YUZU EMULATOR, PLEASE GET A COPY OF MARIO ODYSSEY, BOOT THE GAME UP, AND LOOK FOR THESE GLITCHES!
 ​
 The glitches look like the game being put through a "meme deep-frier".
 Examples:
 Image 1
 ​
 Close up of Image 1
 You can see a lot of pixelation/black lines around objects.
 ​
 If you spot this, please let me know, or even better, go comment on the github issue.
 issue
    submitted by    /u/RelevantMacaron  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to See Song Lyrics on Spotify]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=750825</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/750825/how-to-see-song-lyrics-on-spotify/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spotify makes it easy to sing along to a song by displaying the song lyrics on the app. We’ll show you how to reveal these lyrics in Spotify on the web, desktop, and mobile phones.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Discord got an update. Guess it's waiting time now. :)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v7z9bb/discord_got_an_update_guess_its_waiting_time_now/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v7z9bb/discord_got_an_update_guess_its_waiting_time_now/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T20:31:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's tell us something interesting in the comment section in the meantime.
    submitted by    /u/TheFlean  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to copy colors with the Color Picker tool in PowerToys]]></title>
        <id>bb16b6d5-fdb9-46bb-a01e-23a543bff75c</id>
        <link href="https://www.zdnet.com/article/how-to-copy-colors-with-the-color-picker-tool-in-powertoys/#ftag=RSSbaffb68"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T20:14:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Color Picker tool helps you duplicate any color you see on the screen to use for design or development purposes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest topics for ZDNet in Windows</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Copy and Paste Text from a Photo with Your Phone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=756329</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/756329/how-to-copy-and-paste-text-from-a-photo-with-your-phone/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With so much of our lives spent online, we’re often bringing things from the real world into the digital space. Google Photos makes it easy to copy and paste text from a photo and it works for iPhone and Android.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How should I prepare my Arch system for not getting used over the summer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v7ygqa/how_should_i_prepare_my_arch_system_for_not/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v7ygqa/how_should_i_prepare_my_arch_system_for_not/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T19:57:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am going out of country for the summer and i wont be using my pc what should i do to minimize the chance of a sudo pacman -Syyu not working when i get back
    submitted by    /u/whypickthisname  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save 32% on a NexiGo N60 Plug-and-Play Webcam]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=496014</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15357991/nexigo-n60-plug-and-play-webcam"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even though many people have gone back to work after the pandemic, there is still an increase in videoconferencing. Why go through the unnecessary travel if you can get it done during a video conference? If you agree but just need the right tools to do the job, think about getting a NexiGo N60 Plug-and-Play Webcam. It’s plug and play through USB and has 110º FOV.
    
The 1080p FHD two-MP CMOS in the webcam provides sharp, clear video with resolutions up to 1920 x 1080 and 30fps. After it’s clipped on, the ideal fixed distances between 19.6 inches and 13 feet and the 3.6mm glass lens provide images that can’t be beat. The fixed focal length lens shoots in high definition at a 110º wide angle for your presentations.
   
 
   
The NexiGo N60 Plug-and-Play Webcam has a noise-canceling mic built in that lessens the ambient noise while increasing the sound of your recording. When you’re not using the webcam, you can use the privacy protection cover for security and peace of mind... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gaming Mice vs. Regular Mice: What’s the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=802350</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/802350/gaming-mouse-vs-regular-mouse/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T19:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Heard a lot of good things about gaming mice but don’t know how it compares to a regular mouse? Let’s discuss the difference between these two types to see which might be better for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Nguyen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Massive Facebook Messenger phishing operation generates millions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/massive-facebook-messenger-phishing-operation-generates-millions/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/massive-facebook-messenger-phishing-operation-generates-millions/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T18:54:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers have uncovered a large-scale phishing operation that abused Facebook and Messenger to lure millions of users to phishing pages, tricking them into entering their account credentials and seeing advertisements. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What to do?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v7wz0k/what_to_do/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v7wz0k/what_to_do/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T18:53:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I installed arch on my new laptop, and i'm currently on the latest release with kernel 5.18. I need to use some virtual machines, but after trying virtual box, it appears I'm running into an issue because the kernel is 5.18 and isn't supported yet by virtual box. I then tried Qemu/KVM and I ran into an issue where I can't bridge my wireless interface, as that isn't supported by KVM. I also don't have previous versions of arch installed as it's fresh so I'm struggling to find a way to downgrade the kernel (and tbh, I don't really wanna do that anyway, I'd rather not have the headaches). Like, what to do?
    submitted by    /u/sg4rb0sss  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux botnets now exploit critical Atlassian Confluence bug]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/linux-botnets-now-exploit-critical-atlassian-confluence-bug/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/linux-botnets-now-exploit-critical-atlassian-confluence-bug/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T18:22:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several botnets are now using exploits targeting a critical remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability to infect Linux servers running unpatched Atlassian Confluence Server and Data Center installs. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Atom Text Editor Will Officially Die Later This Year]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=810186</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/810186/atom-text-editor-will-officially-die-later-this-year/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T18:14:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Atom is a text editor that has been around since 2011, and for a while, it was one of the most popular editors for programmers and anyone else who needed powerful plain text editing. Sadly, it will officially be discontinued later this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Boot Multiple Linux Distributions With Ventoy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=802328</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/802328/how-to-boot-multiple-linux-distributions-with-ventoy/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T18:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trying out multiple Linux distributions? Writing and rewriting to a single USB drive will test your patience, and managing a gaggle of drives quickly gets out of hand. Let’s learn to install Ventoy, a tool that can help you store and boot multiple distros with one USB stick.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mohammed Abubakar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome custom theme becomes the default after every reboot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v7vle8/chrome_custom_theme_becomes_the_default_after/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v7vle8/chrome_custom_theme_becomes_the_default_after/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T17:52:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As title says, I’m going mad. Anyone know what’s wrong?
    submitted by    /u/QictR  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LastPass Gains an Essential Feature on iPhone and iPad]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120484/lastpass-gains-an-essential-feature-on-iphone-and-ipad/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120484/lastpass-gains-an-essential-feature-on-iphone-and-ipad/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T17:40:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After what seems like a lifetime, LastPass now automatically saves new passwords made in iOS and iPadOS. The update saves you from jumping back and forth between apps when generating new logins with LastPass. Additionally, LastPass can now autofill credit card information and save online forms to the vault on iPhone and iPad.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blink Video Doorbell: cos'è e come funziona il videocitofono smart di Amazon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Blink-Video-Doorbell-cos-e-e-come-funziona-il-videocitofono-smart-di-Amazon_24615</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Blink-Video-Doorbell-cos-e-e-come-funziona-il-videocitofono-smart-di-Amazon_24615"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T17:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[È arrivato in Italia il nuovo Amazon Blink Video Doorbell, il primo campanello e videocitofono smart della società di Jeff Bezos.Può essere installato sia nella modalità con cavo o senza fili e consente di dialogare a distanza, grazie alla telecamera e al microfono incorporati (audio bidirezionale), con chi si trova fisicamente davanti al dispositivo.

Blink Video Doorbell è alimentato da due batterie al litio AA che garantiscono una durata fino a due anni senza necessità di alcuna supervisione o manutenzione.Il campanello può essere collegato con lo smartphone in modo da ricevere eventuali notifiche e accedere al flusso video 1080p in streaming, anche di notte grazie al sensore a infrarossi.Le sequenze video raccolte a fronte di qualunque interazione con il dispositivo possono essere registrate, salvate e condivise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Android 13 Is One Step Closer With New Beta 3 Release]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=810182</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/810182/android-13-is-one-step-closer-with-new-beta-3-release/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T17:19:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has already released several previews of the next major version of Android, known as Android 13, and now the third beta is now available to download.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Perchè iPhone si scarica subito e come calibrare la batteria]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2017/02/percentuale-sballata-batteria-iphone.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2017/02/percentuale-sballata-batteria-iphone.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T17:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sugli iPhone c'è un misterioso problema che coinvolge la batteria. Il problema riguarda la percentuale dell'indicatore di carica della batteria dell'iPhone, che può essere completamente sballato, passare dal 45% al 12% in un secondo o, viceversa, passare da 18% al 43% un secondo dopo averlo messo in carica. In pratica l'iPhone si scarica subito, anche se teoricamente avrebbe dovuto durare di più, come se la batteria fosse fallata.
 In altri casi, può capitare che dopo aver tenuto in carica tutta la notte il telefono, lo si prenda la mattina e lo si ritrovi scarico o quasi. Se anche noi siamo vittime di un iPhone che si scarica subito o che mostra una durata della carica completamente sballata, vediamo insieme come fare per calibrare la batteria e farla durare di più.
 LEGGI ANCHE -> Come v…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTG Deals: Pixel 6 Pro Hits All-Time-Low Price, Plus More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=810134</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/810134/htg-deals-pixel-6-pro-hits-all-time-low-price-plus-more/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T17:01:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another week, another batch of deals served up piping hot for your buying pleasure. In this edition of How-To Geek Deals, the Google Pixel 6 Pro drops to its lowest price since it launched in 2021, Otterbox is running a 20% off site-wide sale, plus we found more discounts on a USB-C hub, RFID-blocking wallet, and more. Let’s get into it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zach Laidlaw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the nohup Command in Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=804823</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/804823/nohup-command-linux/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T17:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Linux nohup command lets important processes carry on running even when the terminal window that launched them is closed. We show you how to use this venerable command on today’s Linux.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKay</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[YouTube TV Adds 5.1 Surround Sound to at Least One Device You Care About]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120459/youtube-tv-adds-5-1-surround-sound-to-at-least-one-device-you-care-about/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120459/youtube-tv-adds-5-1-surround-sound-to-at-least-one-device-you-care-about/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T16:58:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s an overdue update, but YouTube TV now supports 5.1 surround sound on Roku, Google TV, and Android TV devices. This feature previously rolled out for a handful of other smart TVs and streaming sticks, meaning that most YouTube TV customers can now enjoy theatrical 5.1 Dolby Audio with a compatible speaker system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenVPN + Browser = external sites timeout]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v7u3wd/openvpn_browser_external_sites_timeout/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v7u3wd/openvpn_browser_external_sites_timeout/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T16:48:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been working remote using SSH for the last couple years but now my employer is being forced to put us all on VPN. I was able to connect to the Watchguard VPN using NetworkManger & openVPN, and once connected I can browse internal web apps just fine.
 However, firefox cannot access any external content at all when connected to the VPN. Sites just timeout.
 Chromium can bring up google and even do google searches, but it's a 50/50 shot whether a site will load. 
 If I try to do a pacman -Sy on the VPN, it seems to load (slowly), but then fails out saying all the downloads timed out.
 Network admin says that it shows my HTTP requests going out just fine, but somehow they don't make it back to my laptop.
 Those using Windows don't have this issue, so I'm stuck having to fix this myself.
 Anyone have any ideas?
    submitted by    /u/lykwydchykyn  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[font]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v7u07a/font/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v7u07a/font/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T16:43:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[hi guys, persian fonts look very annyoing and weird on my linux and i need some help with that, the aur fonts are not exactly what i need, i installed some of em, some others do not just install since the dependencies cannot be resolved.
    submitted by    /u/Vegetable-Ad-8224  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New in iPadOS 16]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809659</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809659/whats-new-in-ipados-16/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T16:34:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[iPadOS 16 was announced at WWDC 2022, and it shares much in common with its iPhone counterpart iOS 16. Arriving in September 2022, many of the same improvements are coming to all Apple devices, including the Mac, but there are a few iPad-specific changes to look forward to.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Should You Replace Your Samsung Galaxy S10?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120452/when-should-you-replace-your-samsung-galaxy-s10/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120452/when-should-you-replace-your-samsung-galaxy-s10/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T16:22:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung is slowly ending support for the Galaxy S10 lineup. These devices received their last major OS update (Android 12) back in May, and they just got demoted to quarterly security updates. So, while you don’t need to replace your Galaxy S10 today, you should keep your eyes peeled for an upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emotet malware now steals credit cards from Google Chrome users]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/emotet-malware-now-steals-credit-cards-from-google-chrome-users/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/emotet-malware-now-steals-credit-cards-from-google-chrome-users/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T16:20:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Emotet botnet is now attempting to infect potential victims with a credit card stealer module designed to harvest credit card information stored in Google Chrome user profiles. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Got arch linux installed and having trouble booting...]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v7t0tn/got_arch_linux_installed_and_having_trouble/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v7t0tn/got_arch_linux_installed_and_having_trouble/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T16:01:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I finally got it installed on my pc after like an hour. I then booted it up, and the only result was "Failed to mount /efi" and it entered emergency mode. I am pretty sure it is supposed to be /boot/efi. What did I do wrong. It could also only mount my windows partition in read only mode...
    submitted by    /u/LuigiHacker  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Schedule Dark Mode on Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809031</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809031/how-to-schedule-dark-mode-on-windows-11/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T16:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 has a nice Dark Mode, but just like Windows 10, it can’t be scheduled to turn on automatically at night. Thankfully, there is a way to fix this without downloading any extra software.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Edge: il browser ha fatto risparmiare 274 Petabyte di memoria RAM. Cosa significa]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Edge-il-browser-ha-fatto-risparmiare-274-Petabyte-di-memoria-RAM-Cosa-significa_24614</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Edge-il-browser-ha-fatto-risparmiare-274-Petabyte-di-memoria-RAM-Cosa-significa_24614"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T15:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I principali browser web integrano una funzione che si occupa di rimuovere dalla memoria RAM il contenuto delle schede aperte che non si usano da un po’ di tempo. Chrome, ad esempio, usa la sua 'ricetta' per liberare memoria scaricando le schede che non si utilizzano. Scrivendo chrome://discards nella barra degli indirizzi si ottengono informazioni sullo stato di ciascuna scheda visualizzata nel browser.Allo stesso modo, scrivendo edge://discards nella barra degli indirizzi di Edge si ottengono informazioni molto simili anche se il criterio usato è differente.Parlando dei migliori browser per la gestione della memoria e delle schede aperte abbiamo visto che la funzione che si occupa di eliminare dalla RAM il contenuto delle schede inutilizzate si chiama Schede in sospensione.Accedendo alle impostazioni di Edge e cliccando su Sistema e prestazioni, si può notare come il browser ponga in sospensione le schede aperte dopo circa 5 minuti di inutilizzo.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Insteon Smart Homes Mysteriously Come Back From The Dead]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120432/insteon-smart-homes-mysteriously-come-back-from-the-dead/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120432/insteon-smart-homes-mysteriously-come-back-from-the-dead/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T15:35:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s been two months since Insteon randomly shuttered its servers and closed its offices. But Insteon’s servers are back from the dead without any explanation. Excited users say that their Insteon hubs, apps, and Alexa integrations are working again.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Finally Fixed the Pixel 6 DAC Problem]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120441/google-finally-fixed-the-pixel-6-dac-problem/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120441/google-finally-fixed-the-pixel-6-dac-problem/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T15:34:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Right on time, Google is rolling out the June Pixel update for several devices, and it’s full of software fixes and resolves several security vulnerabilities. In the update, Google has finally fixed the DAC problem on the Pixel 6, something many audiophiles will be glad to see.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Which Email Marketing Platform Is Best For You?]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=444059</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/14988486/best-email-marking-platform"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Email marketing has become one of the most important parts of any business, especially as so many of our shopping transactions move online. But how do you know which email marketing platform is best for your individual business? Well, hopefully this will help you decide.
   

Content

1. Mailchimp
2. Constant Contact
3. Hubspot
4. ConvertKit
5. Emma
6. MailerLite
7. SendGrid
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:8 Tools for Designing Amazing Social Media Graphics
    
1. Mailchimp
    
With around 12 million active customers, Mailchimp is easily one of the most popular email marketing systems out there. Mailchimp offers numerous pricing plans and can handle campaigns for nearly any size of business. The company boasts their “award-winning support” and hefty list of features helps them stand out from the crowd.
   
 Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Megan Glosson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dark Sky Is Now WeatherKit, Android Apps Could Come Soon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=810146</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/810146/dark-sky-is-now-weatherkit-android-apps-could-come-soon/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T15:14:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dark Sky is a popular weather application with hyper-local forecasts, but the Android version was discontinued in 2020 after the service was acquired by Apple. Dark Sky has now been reworked into a service that other apps can use, opening up the door for new third-party apps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come stampare da un Chromebook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/06/come-stampare-da-un-chromebook.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/06/come-stampare-da-un-chromebook.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T15:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I Chromebook sono dei portatili molto veloci realizzati da Google e dotati di sistema operativo Chrome OS. Questo sistema operativo sfrutta le potenzialità di Google Chrome come interfaccia di sistema ed è ottimizzato per utilizzare in prevalenza app web, applicazioni realizzate per girare su Google Chrome ed estensioni del browser (che in questo caso diventano estensioni di sistema).
 Chi necessita di stampare un documento importante non deve temere nulla, visto che il "core" Linux su cui si basa Chrome OS offre un ottimo supporto per la maggior parte delle stampanti presenti sul mercato, con la possibilità di sfruttare anche le ottimizzazioni che Google aveva reso disponibili sul suo (defunto) Google Cloud Print.
 Nella guida che segue vi mostreremo come stampare da un Chromebook, mostra…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding a cron job]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v7rvej/adding_a_cron_job/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v7rvej/adding_a_cron_job/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T15:10:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi,
 I am trying to run a simple cron job, which checks my battery status every 5 minutes, and if the battery level is below a certain percentage or above a certain percentage, it sends a notification using dunstify. I have installed cronie and postfix, and also exported my DISPLAY variable and PATH. But, it doesn't seem to work. The following is the log,
 ​
 Unable to send notification: Error spawning command line “dbus-launch --autolaunch=0a0346fd261a47c585e85476f8e10480 --binary-syntax --close-stderr”: Child process exited with code 1 Unable to send notification: Error spawning command line “dbus-launch --autolaunch=0a0346fd261a47c585e85476f8e10480 --binary-syntax --close-stderr”: Child process exited with code 1 Unable to send notification: Error spawning command line “dbus-launch --autolaunch=0a0346fd261a47c585e85476f8e10480 --binary-syntax --close-stderr”: Child process exited with code 1 Unable to send notification: Error spawning command line “dbus-launch --autolaunch=0a0346fd261a47c585e85476f8e10480 --binary-syntax --close-stderr”: Child process exited with code 1 
 ​
 The link to my script: https://pastebin.com/DGcSfRuC
 ​
 And, this is my crontab entry,
 */5 * * * * env DISPLAY=:0 && /home/ruturajn/.local/bin/bat_val >> /tmp/cron_bat_val_log.txt 2>&1
 I have made the script executable, and it works perfectly, when I run it normally, in the terminal. So could someone help me out with this?
 ​
 Thanks
 ​
 Edit:
 I figured it out, I had to add these two lines at the beginning of my script,
 ​
 export DISPLAY=:0 export DBUS_SESSION_BUS_ADDRESS=unix:path=/run/user/1000/bus 
 ​
 It works now, Thanks for all your suggestions.
    submitted by    /u/Clock_Suspicious  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Better Handle Writing Deadlines]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/?p=19117</id>
        <link href="https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/better-handle-writing-deadlines/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T15:01:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The writing process is a creative process, for the most part, and when it comes to having too much freedom to work with, sometimes time is not of the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Kuttner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Extract a Substring in Microsoft Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=806027</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/806027/excel-substring/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T15:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to extract a substring from the left, right, or middle of your text, you can use Microsoft Excel’s LEFT, RIGHT, MID, LEN, and FIND functions to do that. We’ll show you how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cuba ransomware returns to extorting victims with updated encryptor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cuba-ransomware-returns-to-extorting-victims-with-updated-encryptor/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cuba-ransomware-returns-to-extorting-victims-with-updated-encryptor/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T14:55:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Cuba ransomware operation has returned to regular operations with a new version of its malware found used in recent attacks. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenVPN w/ SAML authentication (AWS VPN Client)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v7r3v6/openvpn_w_saml_authentication_aws_vpn_client/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v7r3v6/openvpn_w_saml_authentication_aws_vpn_client/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T14:36:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I would like to avoid an extra "AWS VPN Client" (which uses SAML authentication) and use the openvpn NetworkManager module.
 Is there anyone who knows whether this can be done and how?
 TIA.
    submitted by    /u/0BAD-C0DE  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New in macOS 13 Ventura]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809661</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809661/whats-new-in-macos-13-ventura/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T14:24:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Expected in fall 2022, Apple’s macOS 13 for Macs and MacBooks comes with the release name Ventura and looks visually very similar to the previous version. A few new features and improvements are coming, some of which tie in with iOS 16.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Phishing: use of reverse tunnel services to avoid detection and shutdown increases]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179050</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/08/phishing-use-of-reverse-tunnel-services-to-avoid-shutdowns-increases/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T14:12:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security researchers at CloudSEK have noticed an increase in the use of reverse tunnel service and URL shorteners in phishing campaigns. Cyber criminals use services such as bit.ly, Ngrok or LocalhostRun to […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Phishing: use of reverse tunnel services to avoid detection and shutdown increases appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DisplayPort over USB alt mode without laptop battery?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v7qepo/displayport_over_usb_alt_mode_without_laptop/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v7qepo/displayport_over_usb_alt_mode_without_laptop/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T14:03:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After removing a laptop's swollen battery, DisplayPort over USB C alt mode no longer works. Is this dependant on the battery/charging controller?
 The same adapter works on another laptop and worked before removing the battery. Also tried a different adapter over HDMI to no avail.
 Running GNOME Wayland (also tested Xorg). Nothing relevant in kernel, xrandr, logs.
    submitted by    /u/harlondorm  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Wi-Fi 6E Routers of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=797523</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/797523/best-wi-fi-6e-router/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T14:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wi-Fi 6E routers provide the best wireless speeds combined with low latency, less network interference, and the increased stability of the 6GHz band. Our picks for the best Wi-Fi 6E routers will help you build a better home network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Russ Ware</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>