<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-06-30T02:06:58.271Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Audio on Lenovo Yoga C380 Glass not being found]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vnw8tv/audio_on_lenovo_yoga_c380_glass_not_being_found/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vnw8tv/audio_on_lenovo_yoga_c380_glass_not_being_found/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-30T01:41:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's a Realtek chip, not sure which one, can probably find out, but Arch can't seem to find it, nothing in journalctl even remotely pointing to audio is showing up. Any thoughts on what might be going on? Selected Pipewire during install. Zen kernel.
    submitted by    /u/npaladin2000  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do You Really Need Kubernetes (K8s)?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?post_type=devops&amp;p=800714</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/devops/do-you-really-need-kubernetes-k8s/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-30T00:48:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes has a reputation for being complicated. While it’s a fantastic piece of software, sometimes the benefits may not outweigh the added complexity, especially for small businesses managing simple deployments. Is plain old Docker good enough?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Heddings</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cannot docker pull or git clone because server is unreachable?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vnuvr8/cannot_docker_pull_or_git_clone_because_server_is/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vnuvr8/cannot_docker_pull_or_git_clone_because_server_is/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-30T00:34:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just installed via archinstall and am having no trouble running 
 curl google.com 
 And i can install via pacman just fine
 But when i run a git clone command i get 
 fatal: unable to access 'https://github.com/Bash-it/bash-it.git/': Couldn't connect to server 
 When running a docker pull command i get:
 Error response from daemon: Get "https://registry-1.docker.io/v2/": dual tcp 52.21.28.242:443: connect: network is unreachable 
 Oddly enough i can clone yay from aur but when i run the makepkg command i get this error
 curl: (7) Couldn't connect to server 
 I have no idea what is going on the internet is working at home but for some train i can't clone from github or pull from docker hub
 Please help
    submitted by    /u/Pickinanameainteasy  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Drivers for integrated iGPU?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vnuqrr/drivers_for_integrated_igpu/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vnuqrr/drivers_for_integrated_igpu/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-30T00:27:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've got a laptop with AMD iGPU and NVIDIA GPU. i know the linux kernel has the drivers for the cpu but i am unsure if it contains the drivers for the iGPU , and if it doesn't what do i need to install for the iGPU?
 EDIT:And should i install mesa , vulkan drivers if i don't intent to game on the iGPU ?
    submitted by    /u/SPQR_Never_Fergetti  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use vDos to Run Old DOS Programs on Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=post-ideas&amp;p=317346</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/12903811/use-vdos-run-dos-programs-windows"/>
        <updated>2022-06-30T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re feeling nostalgic for 8-bit games or need to run some old software, 32-bit Windows 10 doesn’t accommodate. Old DOS programs need a little extra to run on the 64-bit version of Windows 10 as well as Windows 11.
    
You can use vDos to help you run old DOS software if you need to, although it isn’t a suitable option for gaming. Here’s how to use it.
   

Content

What Is vDos?
How to Install vDos on Windows 10
How to Use vDos
Running DOS Programs on Windows 10
Running vDos on Windows 11
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:Latest Windows 10 Update Problems and How to Fix Them
    
What Is vDos?
    
To allow older DOS programs to run on newer Windows platforms, the Virtual DOS Machine (NTVDM) is used. Windows 10 32-bit includes... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sayak Boral</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[problem getting sound from jack "SEVERE: Exception in dependency handler"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vnum5v/problem_getting_sound_from_jack_severe_exception/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vnum5v/problem_getting_sound_from_jack_severe_exception/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-30T00:20:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No sound is being generated when I run the sound-producing line at bottom. nor do I know what's causing those dependency exception errors.
 Possibly of note, for some reason at startup I've been needing to sign in and enter 'startxfce4' at terminal, whereas previously I've had a gui that pops up and handles the sign-in.
 Below is the log from terminal; assuming the 
 'SEVERE: Exception in dependency handler: :overtone.sc.machinery.server.connection/connect-jack-ports' 
 line is stating my main problem, can anyone point me in the right direction?
 jlord@revengencer testing-overtone]$ lein repl nREPL server started on port 35623 on host 127.0.0.1 - nrepl://127.0.0.1:35623 REPL-y 0.5.1, nREPL 0.8.3 Clojure 1.11.1 OpenJDK 64-Bit Server VM 1.8.0_332-b09 Docs: (doc function-name-here) (find-doc …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to display laptop screen to tv through hdmi?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vntcpu/how_to_display_laptop_screen_to_tv_through_hdmi/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vntcpu/how_to_display_laptop_screen_to_tv_through_hdmi/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T23:20:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What programs do I need to be able to do this? I’m looking online and can’t figure it out. Brand new to Arch linux btw.
    submitted by    /u/StringNo8495  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How unsafe is it to use unofficially supported custom kernels?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vns1rt/how_unsafe_is_it_to_use_unofficially_supported/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vns1rt/how_unsafe_is_it_to_use_unofficially_supported/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T22:23:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was using linux-zen, but I decided to switch to linux-tkg-pds because it improves gaming performance. However, on the Arch Linux wiki, this warning is shown:
 Warning: Using custom kernels may cause all kinds of stability and reliability issues, including data loss. Having backups is strongly advised. Arch Linux only has official support for #Officially supported kernels. When using a different kernel, please mention so in support requests. 
 This warning seems serious, however I've seen many people use custom kernels but I rarely stumbled upon someone having issues. What's the matter here with that warning?
    submitted by    /u/ily_ayoub  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[come Cancellare le code di stampa bloccate]]></title>
        <id>125|20220630000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/stampanti-70/come-cancellare-code-stampa-bloccate-125"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Qualche file mandato in stampa si è bloccato e non riesci più a eliminarlo? Vediamo come bisogna fare per risolvere il problema e riprendere a stampare. Per quanto Windows ci offra la possibilità di cancellare le code di stampa (da Stampante, Elimina tutti i documenti) che si sono bloccate per qualche motivo, ogni tanto questa rimozione non funziona e ci troviamo nell’impossibilità di riprendere a stampare.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Stage Manager on Mac and iPad]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=499465</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15401026/stage-manager-mac-ipad"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stage Manager is an innovative new way to multitask with dynamically organizable windows on Mac computers running macOS Ventura and iPad models equipped with the M1 chip running iPadOS 16. Learn how to get the most out of Stage Manager on your iPad and Mac in this tutorial.
   

Content

What Is Stage Manager?
 Using Stage Manager on an iPad
Using Stage Manager on a Mac
How to Get Stage Manager 
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:Everything About Apple Silicon and the M1 Chip That You Need To Know
    
What Is Stage Manager?
    
Stage Manager is a new multitasking interface for the iPad and the Mac that automatically groups together your recently used apps into stacks of windows that become pinned to the left side of the display.... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brahm Shank</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Walmart denies being hit by Yanluowang ransomware attack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/walmart-denies-being-hit-by-yanluowang-ransomware-attack/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/walmart-denies-being-hit-by-yanluowang-ransomware-attack/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T21:23:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[American retailer Walmart has denied being hit with a ransomware attack by the Yanluowang gang after the hackers claimed to encrypt thousands of computers. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Enter the BIOS on Your Windows 11 PC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=765108</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/765108/how-to-enter-the-bios-on-your-windows-11-pc/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accessing the BIOS on your Windows 11 PC can help you solve a variety of problems or allow you to adjust low-level settings. There are multiple ways you can enter BIOS, and we’ll show you how to use all of them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iFixit Now Sells Google Pixel Genuine Replacement Parts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=814946</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/814946/ifixit-now-sells-google-pixel-genuine-replacement-parts/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T20:52:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google and iFixit teamed up earlier this year to offer genuine replacement parts and repair guides for Google Pixel phones, with the goal of making self-repairs as easy as possible. Now the promised parts are available to purchase.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is it possible to include external /boot partition in encrypted BTRFS root ?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vnorq1/is_it_possible_to_include_external_boot_partition/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vnorq1/is_it_possible_to_include_external_boot_partition/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T20:02:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have an encrypted "/" partition using Btrfs file system, during installation I made an separate (in same disk) "/boot" partition which is not encrypted. So, in order to make my Arch install more secure, I'm thinking of doing a full disk encryption without doing a reinstallation. I'm thinking of doing it this way :
  
Unmount the /boot partition.
 Mount it under another name, create a boot directory in root partition.
 Copy all the content of older boot partition to the new directory
 Removing Fstab entry which was responsible for mounting old boot
 Modifying Grub config file to allow booting from an encrypted partition and surely regenerate grub config.
  
Is this correct ? Did I miss any part ? Please tell me in the comments, thanks in advance!
    submitted by    /u/1_7xr  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How do I make yay use doas instead of sudo?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vnoqg6/how_do_i_make_yay_use_doas_instead_of_sudo/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vnoqg6/how_do_i_make_yay_use_doas_instead_of_sudo/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T20:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sudo has a timeout, and isn't very minimal for what it does. How do I configure yay to use doas?
 Solved with the following command:
 yay --sudo doas --save
 ​
    submitted by    /u/Klutzy-Ad-6528  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Indent Paragraphs in Google Docs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=347309</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/347309/how-to-indent-the-start-of-paragraphs-in-google-docs/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Indenting paragraphs in Google Docs requires access to the ruler, which you’ll only find in the full web version. The ruler is not present in the mobile apps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Crider</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Finally Afford to Buy a GPU Again]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/122006/you-can-finally-afford-to-buy-a-gpu-again/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/122006/you-can-finally-afford-to-buy-a-gpu-again/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T19:53:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The day you’ve waited for is finally here; GPUs are now reasonably priced, in stock, and on sale. Buying a graphics card today guarantees you the best price of the last three years—yeah, you can finally afford to buy a GPU again.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get an Amazon Halo View Fitness Tracker for Under $45]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=443749</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/14910705/amazon-halo-view-fitness-tracker"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The summer’s ticking away fast, isn’t it? It’s not too late, though, to start doing all those activities you dreamed of over the long winter. You can start them now with an Amazon Halo View Fitness Tracker. It’s an early Amazon Prime Day deal, saving you $35.
    
When fitness trackers first became the rage, it was enough just to have a device that counted your steps. But with the advancements in trackers and smartwatches, we demand more from our fitness trackers. Halo health metrics allow you to access your heart rate, activity points, sleep score, oxygen levels, and more.
    
Along with the Amazon Halo View Fitness Tracker, you’ll get 12 months of full access to the Halo membership that provides features, workouts, and programs. After one year, it auto-renews for $3.99/monthly plus tax. The Halo app will give you a movement assessment and personalized exercise program to improve your health. It will measure the quantity and quality of your sleep and allow you to experience daily meditations and recipes from WW and Whole Foods Market.
   
 Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Turn Off Dark Mode in Microsoft Word]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=807568</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/807568/how-to-turn-off-dark-mode-on-word/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T19:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Word’s dark mode applies a dark theme to your entire user interface. If you’d like to keep your page’s color white while still using dark mode, or if you’d like to bring Word back to light mode, there are ways to do that. We’ll show you how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This EV Battery Could Go 620 Miles on a Single Charge]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/122016/this-ev-battery-could-go-620-miles-on-a-single-charge/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/122016/this-ev-battery-could-go-620-miles-on-a-single-charge/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T18:46:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Range anxiety and slow charging could soon be a thing of the past, thanks to new EV battery technology coming in 2023. The Chinese battery maker and one of the largest EV battery suppliers in the world, CATL, recently unveiled its new battery cells capable of 620 miles per charge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fedora 37 Proposing To Allow Unrestricted Access To Flathub]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Fedora-37-Unfiltered-Flathubs</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Fedora-37-Unfiltered-Flathubs"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T18:45:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To this point Fedora out-of-the-box has been restricted to a filtered subset of Flathub packages when enabled via GNOME Software or GNOME Initial Setup. However, legal has now cleared Fedora for allowing unfiltered/unrestricted access to Flathub, allowing a far greater selection of Flatpaks to become available on Fedora Linux with the plan for this to begin with Fedora 37...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avaya sysadmin indicted for illegally generating, selling VoIP licenses]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/avaya-sysadmin-indicted-for-illegally-generating-selling-voip-licenses/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/avaya-sysadmin-indicted-for-illegally-generating-selling-voip-licenses/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T18:44:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Three defendants who allegedly sold over $88 million worth of software licenses belonging to Avaya Holdings Corporation have been charged in Oklahoma, U.S., facing 14 counts of wire fraud and money laundering. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How do I purge LightDM and all its subparts from my system for all of eternity never to plague me with its bugs again?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vnmsnn/how_do_i_purge_lightdm_and_all_its_subparts_from/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vnmsnn/how_do_i_purge_lightdm_and_all_its_subparts_from/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T18:35:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Severe Bug One LightDM exposes my screen for ~10-15 seconds everytime the laptop lid is re-opened (and allows clicking and typing). Absolutely ENORMOUS security issue.
 Severe Bug Two If my machine goes to suspend after five minutes, LightDM will (do the above and then) show an unlock screen. After unlocking, it shows another unlock screen. Then it shows an unlock screen again before going to the desktop.
 Networking gets killed (complete service crash where the icon doesn't even work). Bluetooth gets killed (complete crash). The power manager gets killed (complete crash, wildly inaccurate battery readings).
 The machine will refuse to restart, shut down, or "sudo poweroff --force" because "Another shutdown or something something service something is already in progress" error.
 The notification area (literally the only thing other than volume that works) shows "GDBus.Error:org.freedesktop.login1.Operati...
  
I'm sick of this. I want it all gone.
 How do I mass purge LightDM, "dm-tool --lock", and anything else vaguely related to LightDM from my system?
 If it sat above or below LightDM in the Task Manager, I want it gone.
 If it sat next to LightDM in the Applications list, I want it gone.
 Anything that shared a folder next to LightDM I want utterly destroyed via the Death Star.
  
Once it's gone, what's something actually reliable and secure I can replace it with? (GTK only please)
 Thanks.
    submitted by    /u/Remarkable-River-300  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Lock Formulas in Microsoft Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=810715</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/810715/lock-formulas-excel/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T18:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To avoid getting your formulas messed up, you can lock the cells that contain formulas while keeping all other cells unlocked in your Microsoft Excel spreadsheets. We’ll show you how to do just that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Will Help You Switch From iPhone to a Samsung Galaxy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=814579</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/814579/google-will-help-you-switch-from-iphone-to-a-samsung-galaxy/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T18:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google released an official ‘Switch to Android’ app for iPhone and iPad earlier this year, making it easier to move all your stuff to a new Android phone. Starting today, the app works with even more Android phones.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New YTStealer malware steals accounts from YouTube Creators]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-ytstealer-malware-steals-accounts-from-youtube-creators/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-ytstealer-malware-steals-accounts-from-youtube-creators/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T17:53:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new information-stealing malware named YTStealer is targeting YouTube content creators and attempting to steal their authentication tokens and hijack their channels. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ubuntu Touch OTA-23 Released - Still Based On Ubuntu 16.04, Adds Support For FM Radios]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Ubuntu-Touch-OTA-23</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Ubuntu-Touch-OTA-23"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T17:53:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ubuntu Touch OTA-23 is out today as the newest Ubuntu mobile operating system update for smartphones from the folks at UBports that continues maintaining the code-base left by Canonical and now pushing ahead in their own direction...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gmail Redesign Is Now Rolling Out: Here’s What to Expect]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=814852</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/814852/gmail-redesign-is-now-rolling-out-here%e2%80%99s-what-to-expect/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T17:51:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google started rolling out an updated design for Gmail on the web earlier this year, with Material You-inspired tweaks and a new sidebar. Now Google is ready to bring the fresh look to everyone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt LUKS partition on login]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vnkxgj/decrypt_luks_partition_on_login/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vnkxgj/decrypt_luks_partition_on_login/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T17:14:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everybody!
 I want to install Arch on my laptop and use LUKS encryption like it's described here https://wiki.archlinux.org/title/dm-crypt/Encrypting_an_entire_system#LUKS_on_a_partition
 But as far as I understood, my passphrase will be asked before the system is loaded. And only after that I will see display manager and will be asked to enter user password.
 What I'm looking for is something like FileVault experience on Mac. There I have user login menu after some basic system is loaded and I need to enter my user password. The key is encrypted with my user password, so I need to enter the password only once.
 Is there any way to do something like that with LUKS and linux?
    submitted by    /u/dimitrimus  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Atari 50th Anniversary Collection Revealed With 90 Classic and New Titles]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/122007/atari-50th-anniversary-collection-revealed-with-90-classic-and-new-titles/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/122007/atari-50th-anniversary-collection-revealed-with-90-classic-and-new-titles/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T17:14:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Atari is enjoying its 50th anniversary this year since it changed the world with gaming. And while the company already debuted some limited-edition working Atari 2600 cartridges, Atari just announced its 50th Anniversary Celebration game pack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Check Your iPhone’s IMEI Number]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=813540</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/813540/how-to-check-your-iphones-imei-number/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T17:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An iPhone’s IMEI number is a 15-17 digit identifier that distinguishes it from all other iPhones, and it can sometimes be helpful to find out what it is. Here’s why—and how to do it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTG Deals: Get This RTX 3080 GPU for $230 Off, Plus More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=814798</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/814798/htg-deals-get-this-rtx-3080-gpu-for-230-off-plus-more/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T17:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s a lot for gamers to love in this edition of How-To Geek deals. To finish out the month of June, we’re sharing big discounts on RTX 3080 GPUs, Xbox Series X|S controllers, game streamer webcams, and more. Jump down for all the details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zach Laidlaw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox: remove known tracking parameters from URLs in all modes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179447</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/29/firefox-remove-known-tracking-parameters-from-urls-in-all-modes/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T16:53:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla launched Firefox 102 this week, and with it came support for the new query parameter stripping functionality to boost user privacy. Many sites and services add parameters to the web address […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Firefox: remove known tracking parameters from URLs in all modes appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA warns of hackers exploiting PwnKit Linux vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisa-warns-of-hackers-exploiting-pwnkit-linux-vulnerability/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisa-warns-of-hackers-exploiting-pwnkit-linux-vulnerability/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has added a high-severity Linux vulnerability known as PwnKit to its list of bugs exploited in the wild. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Videochat gratis con sconosciuti per vedersi e parlare (migliori app)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2018/11/videochat-gratis-con-sconosciuti-per.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2018/11/videochat-gratis-con-sconosciuti-per.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T16:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Le videochat sono sempre esistite fin da Windows 95, che includeva un programma chiamato Microsoft NetMeeting, anche se le connessioni non permettevano una qualità elevata. Qualche anno più tardi arrivò ChatRoulette, un modo per conoscere o chattare in video con sconosciuti senza bisogno di registrare un account, che ebbe uno straordinario successo e che fu subito imitato da tanti altri siti...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I can’t connect to a specific wifi network.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vnjr2b/i_cant_connect_to_a_specific_wifi_network/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vnjr2b/i_cant_connect_to_a_specific_wifi_network/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T16:24:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Im on vacation and I can’t connect to the wifi access point of the place I’m staying at. My phone and all other devices I own can connect to it but my laptop can’t. I’m using networkmanager. The laptop can connect to other networks. I think it may have something todo with the fact that they use repeaters for each section and room of the building and they connect every single guest to the same Wi-Fi but I don’t know. I have never had any issues previously. I appreciate the help and I hope that this is the right place to ask this question.
    submitted by    /u/InjectedCode  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thunderbird 102 released with highly anticipated features, bug fixes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/software/thunderbird-102-released-with-highly-anticipated-features-bug-fixes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/software/thunderbird-102-released-with-highly-anticipated-features-bug-fixes/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T16:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla has announced the release of Thunderbird 102, one of the world's most popular open-source email clients with an estimated userbase of over 25 million. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does Your Android Phone Have a “High-Performance Mode”?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=813488</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/813488/does-your-android-phone-have-a-high-performance-mode/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T16:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many mid-range Android phones are more powerful than top-of-the-line Android phones from a few years ago. That doesn’t mean we should stop pushing the limits, though. Your phone may even have a “High-Performance Mode.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla Thunderbird 102 Arrives with a Taste of What's to Come]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/121989/mozilla-thunderbird-102-arrives-with-a-taste-of-whats-to-come/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/121989/mozilla-thunderbird-102-arrives-with-a-taste-of-whats-to-come/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T15:59:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla Thunderbird just got its biggest update in nearly a decade. The email client’s Version 102 update includes a ton of useful changes, like an improved account import process, a revamped address book, and an all-new Spaces Toolbar.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Tool Now Helps You Install Windows 11 on Unsupported PCs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=814793</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/814793/this-tool-now-helps-you-install-windows-11-on-unsupported-pcs/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T15:55:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rufus is a popular USB formatting utility that can also be used to create installation media for Windows, Linux distributions, and other operating systems. Now it can help you install Windows 11 on unsupported PCs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hyundai's IONIQ 6 EV Revealed with Futuristic Good Looks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/121988/hyundais-ioniq-6-ev-revealed-with-futuristic-good-looks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/121988/hyundais-ioniq-6-ev-revealed-with-futuristic-good-looks/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T15:49:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hyundai just gave the world an early look at its upcoming electric sedan, the IONIQ 6, which will make its full debut later in July. The unique and futuristic good looks were inspired by the Hyundai Prophecy concept EV from 2020 that had aerodynamics in mind.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ukraine arrests cybercrime gang operating over 400 phishing sites]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ukraine-arrests-cybercrime-gang-operating-over-400-phishing-sites/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ukraine-arrests-cybercrime-gang-operating-over-400-phishing-sites/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T15:27:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ukrainian cyberpolice force arrested nine members of a criminal group that operated over 400 phishing websites crafted to appear like legitimate EU portals offering financial assistance to Ukrainians. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 of the Best Offline Shooting Games for Android and iOS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=post-ideas&amp;p=315978</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/12869632/best-offline-shooting-games-android"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mobile phones are an under-appreciated platform when it comes to single-player offline shooting games. Yes, the big online shooters like PUBG and Call of Duty have made their mark on phones, but if you’re looking to pit yourself against AI soldiers, aliens, and other automated baddies, there’s plenty of choice.
    
From cerebral sniping games to Wild West adventures, we’ve rounded up the best offline shooting games you can play on mobile.
   

Content

1. Six-Guns: Gang Showdown
2. Cover Fire
3. Hitman Sniper
4. Overkill 3
5. Dead Effect 2
6. N.O.V.A. Legacy
7. Lonewolf

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:17 Fun Offline Games to Play on Your Phone
    
1. Six-Guns: Gang Showdown
    
There have been many great cowboy-themed games on consoles over the years, and Six-Guns: Gang Showdown (Android | iOS) channels the core of what makes... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sydney Butler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Se la ricerca di Windows non funziona, come risolvere]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/06/ricerca-di-windows-non-funziona-come.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/06/ricerca-di-windows-non-funziona-come.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T15:03:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[La funzionalità di ricerca su Windows permette di aprire velocemente le app e i programmi installati sul computer, oltre a cercare velocemente i file custoditi sul disco del PC o su qualsiasi altro supporto collegato ad esso. Purtroppo anche questa utilissima funzionalità può venir meno, in particolare dopo un aggiornamento difettoso di Windows o un riavvio non previsto. 
Nella guida che segue vi...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bluetooth dongle not turning off]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vnhusa/bluetooth_dongle_not_turning_off/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vnhusa/bluetooth_dongle_not_turning_off/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T15:02:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bluetooth dongle keeps "flashing" even after I turn off bluetooth in the gnome menu. I'm using blueman and PipeWire.
 It usually just works out of the box, any help would be appreciated.
    submitted by    /u/SmileCraby_Gamer  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NZXT Signal 4K30 Capture Card Review: Lossless High-Quality Footage]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=813481</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/813481/nzxt-signal-4k30-capture-card-review/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T15:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Streamers and video content creators should look to a capture card for lossless recording across multiple consoles or PCs, especially if the footage is 4K. NZXT’s Signal 4K30, released June 29, 2022, is a simple solution to high-quality screen recording without suffering a blow to performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcus Mears III</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NZXT Launches Its First Lag-Free 4K Capture Card]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/121982/nzxt-launches-its-first-lag-free-4k-capture-card/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/121982/nzxt-launches-its-first-lag-free-4k-capture-card/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T15:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you thought NZXT was just a custom PC assembler, you’re dead wrong. NZXT has slowly expanded its catalog with new and exciting products, including a keyboard, mouse, and microphone. And the company’s newest product, the Signal capture card, may be its most impressive.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[9 Bash Script Examples to Get You Started on Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=808593</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/808593/bash-script-examples/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T15:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re starting out with Bash scripting on Linux, getting a solid grasp of the basics will stand you in good stead. They’re the foundation of deeper knowledge and higher scripting skills.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKay</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get Free YouTube Premium With Google’s New Referral Program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=814742</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/814742/get-free-youtube-premium-with-googles-new-referral-program/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T14:56:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[YouTube Premium is a premium subscription for YouTube that removes advertisements and grants access to more YouTube Music features. Premium subscribers can now get up to 12 months for free, if they recruit others to sign up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blinking cursor upon login screen]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vnhmac/blinking_cursor_upon_login_screen/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vnhmac/blinking_cursor_upon_login_screen/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T14:51:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello! So originally I was originally having this exact issue. I solved it by simply booting from a live usb, installing an arch dbus package, extracting it and then running rsync -avh. It worked, however now I get a blinking cursor with a blank screen. Neither of the solutions I found online worked! I would be really grateful if you could help me in any way! Thanks in advance!
    submitted by    /u/SneatRebellion  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Use Docker with a UFW Firewall]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?post_type=devops&amp;p=800715</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/devops/how-to-use-docker-with-a-ufw-firewall/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T14:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Surprisingly, Docker does not work out of the box with Linux’s “Universal Firewall,” or UFW. They both modify the same iptables configuration, and this can lead to misconfigurations exposing containers that weren’t supposed to be public. Here’s how to fix it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Heddings</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Use Docker with a UFW Firewall]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?post_type=devops&amp;p=800715</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/devops/how-to-use-docker-with-a-ufw-firewall/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T14:08:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Surprisingly, Docker does not work out of the box with Linux’s “Universal Firewall,” or UFW. They both modify the same iptables configuration, and this can lead to misconfigurations exposing containers that weren’t supposed to be public. Here’s how to fix it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Heddings</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Ring Alternatives of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=810929</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/810929/best-ring-alternative/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T14:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re not sold on the Amazon Ring lineup of products, there’s no shortage of great options in today’s market. From video doorbells and outdoor security cameras to floodlights and alarm systems, here are the best Ring alternatives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Bitner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Backup Windows 11 con lo strumento di sistema wbAdmin]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Backup-Windows-11-con-lo-strumento-di-sistema-wbAdmin_24721</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Backup-Windows-11-con-lo-strumento-di-sistema-wbAdmin_24721"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T13:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Non ci stancheremo mai di ripetere che disporre di un backup aggiornato è il miglior modo per superare qualunque incidente in ambito informatico, a tutti i livelli.Un buon piano di disaster recovery passa attraverso una corretta gestione delle politiche di backup.In passato abbiamo parlato delle migliori strategie di backup per proteggere i dati differenziando anche queste attività sulla base della tipologia di backup che viene eseguito. È possibile concentrarsi ad esempio sui documenti e sui file personali oppure (o in aggiunta) creare backup dell'intero sistema o, ancora, impostare backup bare metal che effettuano una copia del sistema operativo sistema operativo e di tutti i dati tranne i dati utente nei volumi critici.Come il predecessore, anche Windows 11 integra uno strumento per eseguire il backup del sistema: si chiama wbAdmin ed è parte integrante della dotazione offerta da Microsoft.
Backup Windows 11 con wbAdmin
 Esistono molteplici soluzioni di disk imaging che permettono di creare una copia di backup dell'intero contenuto del sistema o di singole partizioni.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How do use my 2nd GPU for arch only?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vnfhoy/how_do_use_my_2nd_gpu_for_arch_only/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vnfhoy/how_do_use_my_2nd_gpu_for_arch_only/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T13:11:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have 2 GPUs, rtx 2070 and rx 6500 xt, both of them are connected however the monitor that is connected with rx 6500 xt is a black screen. I'm wondering if I could somehow use my other gpu for arch because I need the rtx for a virtual machine.
    submitted by    /u/Palemdi  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA warns orgs to switch to Exchange Online Modern Auth until October]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisa-warns-orgs-to-switch-to-exchange-online-modern-auth-until-october/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisa-warns-orgs-to-switch-to-exchange-online-modern-auth-until-october/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T13:06:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CISA has urged government agencies and private sector organizations using Microsoft's Exchange cloud email platform to expedite the switch from Basic Authentication legacy authentication methods without multifactor authentication (MFA) support to Modern Authentication alternatives. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wyze Video Doorbell Pro Review: You Get What You Pay For]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/121076/wyze-video-doorbell-pro-review-you-get-what-you-pay-for/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/121076/wyze-video-doorbell-pro-review-you-get-what-you-pay-for/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T13:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even if you’re interested in home security, dropping hundreds of dollars on a smart doorbell probably isn’t a priority right now. But what if you could buy a competent video doorbell for just $100? Well, the Wyze Video Doorbell Pro certainly fits the bill. Just don’t put your expectations too high.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 10 Best Movies on Amazon Prime Video in 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=730543</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/730543/best-free-movies-on-amazon-prime-video/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Prime subscriptions include access to thousands of movies for free. If you’re looking for something to watch, here are the best movies to watch for free with Amazon Prime Video.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Bell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Benchmarking The Linux Kernel With An "-O3" Optimized Build]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31250</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31250"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stemming from last weeks Linux kernel patches suggesting an -O3 experimental option for all CPU architectures and Linus Torvalds rather quickly shooting it down, here are some fresh benchmarks looking at the Linux kernel performance when the kernel image is rebuilt with the -O3 optimization level rather than -O2.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Foxit PDF Reader 12.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179443</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/29/foxit-pdf-reader-12-0-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T12:57:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Foxit Software released Foxit PDF Reader 12.0 and Foxit PDF Editor 12.0, new major versions of two of the company's PDF flagship products. Foxit PDF Reader 12.0 is a free program to […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Foxit PDF Reader 12.0 released appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Workspace now alerts of critical changes to admin accounts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/google-workspace-now-alerts-of-critical-changes-to-admin-accounts/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/google-workspace-now-alerts-of-critical-changes-to-admin-accounts/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Workspace (formerly G Suite) has been updated to notify admins of highly sensitive changes to configurations, including those made to single sign-on (SSO) profiles and admin accounts. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is a Secured-Core PC for Windows 11?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=812013</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/812013/what-is-a-secured-core-pc/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T12:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Home PCs can face very different threats from business machines, which is why Microsoft and its manufacturing partners developed the Secured-Core PC for enterprises. However, some of their security features are included on all versions of Windows 11. Let’s take a look at how a Secured-Core PC compares to your laptop at home.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Paul</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monopattino elettrico in offerta: a 100 euro c'è quello per bambini]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Monopattino-elettrico-in-offerta-a-100-euro-c-e-quello-per-bambini_24720</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Monopattino-elettrico-in-offerta-a-100-euro-c-e-quello-per-bambini_24720"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T11:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Il grande interesse per la mobilità elettrica è esploso ormai da tempo tanto che sono sempre di più le persone che scelgono mezzi 'smart' per spostarsi da un luogo all'altro senza emissioni di CO2.Per un periodo di tempo limitato il monopattino elettrico pieghevole GOGOBEST V1 è in offerta a soli 99,99 euro.Non c'è alcun codice coupon da digitare: il prezzo scontato è per tutti ma verrà praticato solo fino al prossimo 31 luglio, salvo esaurimento delle scorte di magazzino.GOGOBEST V1 è un monopattino elettrico per bambini che può infatti sostenere un peso massimo pari a 50 chilogrammi. Integra una batteria da 2 Ah (21,6V) ricaricabile completamente in circa 2 ore e un motore da 150W.Si tratta di un dispositivo che viene venduto con spedizione dall'Europa (assicurarsi di scegliere Germany Warehouse al momento dell'ordine) in maniera tale che l'acquirente non debba sostenere alcuna spesa aggiuntiva in sede di consegna.

Capace di raggiungere una velocità massima di 6 km/h, GOGOBEST V1 tollera una pendenza non superiore a 5 gradi e può essere utilizzato da bambini di altezza compresa tra 100 e 160 centimetri.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Buying a Mac? A Base M1 or M2 Chip Is Probably All You Need]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=812201</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/812201/a-mac-base-m1-or-m2-chip-is-probably-all-you-need/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T11:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s a great time to buy a Mac. Apple’s new ARM-based processors are fast and efficient, plus old favorites like MagSafe and built-in card readers are making an appearance once again. Best of all, thanks to Apple Silicon, you don’t need to spend big bucks to get serious performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon fixes high-severity vulnerability in Android Photos app]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/amazon-fixes-high-severity-vulnerability-in-android-photos-app/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/amazon-fixes-high-severity-vulnerability-in-android-photos-app/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon has confirmed and fixed a vulnerability in its Photos app for Android, which has been downloaded over 50 million times on the Google Play Store. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Azure FabricScape bug let hackers hijack Linux clusters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-azure-fabricscape-bug-let-hackers-hijack-linux-clusters/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-azure-fabricscape-bug-let-hackers-hijack-linux-clusters/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T10:48:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has fixed a container escape bug dubbed FabricScape in the Service Fabric (SF) application hosting platform that let threat actors escalate privileges to root, gain control of the host node, and compromise the entire SF Linux cluster. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modifica foto online con app web gratuite senza registrazione]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2018/03/programmi-di-modifica-foto-online.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2018/03/programmi-di-modifica-foto-online.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T10:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Il più famoso editor di foto è sicuramente Adobe Photoshop, potente software di fotoritocco fornito dietro pagamento di una licenza molto costosa per l'uso casalingo.

 Per venire incontro agli utenti occasionali ed a quelli che modificano foto per hobby e per passione, sono nate in questi anni molte applicazioni web di modifica foto online che funzionano senza scaricare e installare nulla sul PC...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google begins rolling out the new Gmail design to users as the default option]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179430</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/29/new-gmail-design-rolls-out-to-users-as-the-default-option/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T10:13:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier this year, Google revealed a new Gmail design. The email service is now rolling out the new interface for users as the default option. New Gmail design The new Gmail design […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Google begins rolling out the new Gmail design to users as the default option appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 10: nuove funzionalità per gestire la stampante]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-10-nuove-funzionalita-per-gestire-la-stampante_24719</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-10-nuove-funzionalita-per-gestire-la-stampante_24719"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T10:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft ha modificato a più riprese il funzionamento dello spooler della stampante in Windows: all'interno di quel componente sono state infatti scoperte varie vulnerabilità che potevano essere sfruttate per disporre l'esecuzione di codice arbitrario ed acquisire privilegi utente più elevati.La falla chiamata PrintNightmare è stata ed è ancora oggi utilizzata per sferrare attacchi informatici, diffondere ransomware e muoversi lateralmente all'interno delle reti oggetto di aggressione.Le patch rilasciate da Microsoft per sistemare le vulnerabilità PrintNightmare hanno tuttavia causato non pochi problemi in alcuni contesti portando al malfunzionamento delle stampanti di rete.Dopo tanti aggiornamenti correttivi finalmente un po’ di novità: Microsoft ha infatti annunciato che Windows 10 vede…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD ROCm 5.2 Released With New rocWMMA Library]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMD-ROCm-5.2-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMD-ROCm-5.2-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T09:44:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AMD has released ROCm 5.2 as the newest version of its open-source GPU compute stack...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[installing nvidia-utils-beta (515.57-1) breaks dependency 'nvidia-utils-beta=515.48.07' required by nvidia-beta-dkms]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vnbq9o/installing_nvidiautilsbeta_515571_breaks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vnbq9o/installing_nvidiautilsbeta_515571_breaks/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T09:33:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey all, I had this issue a month ago in the last nvidia-beta update, which I solved by manually installing both at the same time, however it's happened again. I'm not sure why this has been happening in the first place. 
 Whenever my nvidia drivers need updating, nvidia-beta-dkms doesn't seem to be able to see that the other packages are also being installed when using yay. This also happens if I try to install any permutation of nvidia-beta-dkms, nvidia-settings-beta, nvidia-utils-beta. Anyone have any idea why this might be happening?
 When installing I'm prompted with
 :: 5 Packages to upgrade. 5 aur/lib32-nvidia-utils-beta 515.48.07-1 -> 515.57-1 4 aur/nvidia-beta-dkms 515.48.07-1 -> 515.57-1 3 aur/nvidia-settings-beta 515.48.07-1 -> 515.57-1 2 aur/nvidia-utils-beta 515.48.07-1 -> 515.57-1 1 aur/opencl-nvidia-beta 515.48.07-1 -> 515.57-1 
 but then at some point down the line I get 
 ==> Sources are ready. -> nvidia-utils-beta-515.57-1 already made -- skipping build -> nvidia-utils-beta=515.57 not satisfied, flushing install queue loading packages... resolving dependencies... looking for conflicting packages... error: failed to prepare transaction (could not satisfy dependencies) :: installing nvidia-utils-beta (515.57-1) breaks dependency 'nvidia-utils-beta=515.48.07' required by nvidia-beta-dkms -> exit status 1 
    submitted by    /u/big_Gorb  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Radeon Software For Linux 22.20 Driver Prepared With Ubuntu 22.04 LTS, RHEL 9.0 Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Radeon-Software-22.20-Coming</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Radeon-Software-22.20-Coming"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T09:28:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For consumer Radeon GPUs the "Radeon Software for Linux" packaged driver version has been on the 22.10 series since the end of March. For AMD Radeon PRO professional/workstation graphics the advertised "Radeon Pro Software for Enterprise on Linux" driver is still the 21.Q4 driver from last December. AMD appears to be finally prepping to release the "22.20" packaged driver as the next feature release to this packaged AMD Linux driver stack for those not relying just on the upstream kernel and Mesa...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft's "Dzn" Vulkan-On-D3D12 Adds Working Pipeline Cache]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Mesa-Dozen-Pipeline-Cache</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Mesa-Dozen-Pipeline-Cache"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T09:11:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Microsoft Dozen "Dzn" code within Mesa that allows for the Vulkan API to be implemented atop Direct3D 12 for benefit on Windows now has a working pipeline cache implementation...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LLVM 15.0 Planning For Early September Release - Important For RDNA3 Graphics Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=LLVM-15.0-Release-Plan</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=LLVM-15.0-Release-Plan"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LLVM release manager Tom Stellard of Red Hat has laid out the planned LLVM/Clang 15.0 release schedule for this next major version of this open-source compiler stack...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Niente più Hangouts: le soluzioni per gli utenti business si chiamano Google Meet e Chat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Niente-piu-Hangouts-le-soluzioni-per-gli-utenti-business-si-chiamano-Google-Meet-e-Chat_21033</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Niente-piu-Hangouts-le-soluzioni-per-gli-utenti-business-si-chiamano-Google-Meet-e-Chat_21033"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T08:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Le soluzioni per effettuare videoconferenze, organizzare riunioni online e collaborare a distanza sono diventate estremamente popolari nel corso degli anni di emergenza pandemica. I meeting online si sono rivelati mezzi preziosi per lavorare in team e rimanere il più possibile produttivi.Ad aprile 2020 Google ha deciso di abbandonare la denominazione Hangouts per rinominare la sua piattaforma di videoconferenza per professionisti e imprese in Google Meet.Google Chat era invece diventato il nome dello strumento per la collaborazione che la società di Page e Brin presenta come concorrente di Slack e prodotti similari.Come abbiamo visto nell'articolo in cui parliamo di come organizzare videoconferenze con i servizi Google, la piattaforma Hangouts non è stata particolarmente fortunata lato con…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NVIDIA GeForce RTX 3070 on Arch Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vnaxrq/nvidia_geforce_rtx_3070_on_arch_linux/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vnaxrq/nvidia_geforce_rtx_3070_on_arch_linux/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T08:38:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm planning to buy a new laptop with the aforementioned GPU, and I'd love to know how well does it work on [Arch]linux?
 I'm fine with using proprietary blob drivers, and I am planning to use Sway, but if X is better with it, I'll use that.
 I'd love to know of possible pitfalls beforehand
 Any help is appreciated <3
 Edit: Thanks for all your comments! My anxiety has definitely increased. I've decided to bite the bullet, and return if it's terrible as some have said. I've ordered a Lenovo Legion 5 15IAH7H with a 3070 Ti, which I'll test, if it doesn't work, I'll return it and try a pure AMD laptop, most likely MSI Delta 15 A5EFK.
    submitted by    /u/Potato-of-All-Trades  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4TB drive]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vnaeue/4tb_drive/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vnaeue/4tb_drive/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T08:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have 4TB HDD, it's now formatted to NTFS after I've been using windows but now I want to use it under Linux to store games and virtual drive for windows kvm. What you guys would go for? BTRFS or EXT4?
    submitted by    /u/PiotrLobo6780  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding GRUB parameters for GPU passthrough]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vnab3j/adding_grub_parameters_for_gpu_passthrough/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vnab3j/adding_grub_parameters_for_gpu_passthrough/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T07:55:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, I'm trying to add some parameters to grub for gpu passthrough on a vm, but my arch installation apparently doesn't have a /boot/grub folder, what can I do? I just want to add intel_iommu=on, should I just reinstall grub? Or is something else the problem?
    submitted by    /u/sebramirez4  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Hangouts will shut down in November 2022, users are being redirected to Google Chat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179412</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/29/google-hangouts-is-shutting-down/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T07:49:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Hangouts will shut down in November 2022. The instant messaging service, which debuted in 2013, will be replaced by Google Chat. This isn't unexpected, we reported about it in 2019. Last […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Google Hangouts will shut down in November 2022, users are being redirected to Google Chat appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thunderbird 102 released: lots of new features and improvements]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179418</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/29/thunderbird-102-released-lots-of-new-features-and-improvements/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T04:17:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thunderbird 102 is out now. The new version of the popular desktop email client is a major new release that introduces several new features and improves others. You may want to check […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Thunderbird 102 released: lots of new features and improvements appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are they doing over at protonvpn?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vn2h6v/what_are_they_doing_over_at_protonvpn/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vn2h6v/what_are_they_doing_over_at_protonvpn/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T00:41:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's like someone is actively trying to make conflicts here. Whenever I try to upgrade my system: python-protonvpn-nm-lib and protonvpn-cli are in conflict. Trying to remove either before the other doesn't work because removing protonvpn-cli breaks dependency 'protonvpn-cli' required by protonvpn and removing python-protonvpn-nm-lib breaks dependency 'python-protonvpn-nm-lib' required by protonvpn-cli.
 I'm not really looking for a solution, will probably just uninstall everything and possibly lose config. Just wanted to point out we have some sadists on the AUR.
    submitted by    /u/algebra4life  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[libldap_r-2.4.so.2 and liblber-2.4.so.2 missinh]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vn28lf/libldap_r24so2_and_liblber24so2_missinh/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vn28lf/libldap_r24so2_and_liblber24so2_missinh/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T00:29:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I overwritten some libraries and now a lot of my systems doesn't work! I already fixed the other libraries that where missing but i'm not able to find this two... I know that they are both part of openldap but reinstalling the pkg doesn't seem to help. N.B. I need to fix the system true chroot because main system pacman doesn't work without those libraries. Any help is really really welcome
    submitted by    /u/Error916  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emacs Keyboard Shortcuts]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=485185</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15399061/emacs-keyboard-shortcuts"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Emacs is a fully-featured text editor that is both powerful and extensible out of the box, without needing to install any additional packages to make it work. With Emacs, you can easily manipulate text and files by executing Lisp commands. These commands, in turn, are then bound to a series of simple keybindings which allows you to focus on what you need to do.
   
   
  
Download this Cheatsheet
 Enter your email below to receive this PDF cheatsheet in your Inbox.
     
  
  
   
                   #cheatsheet-box{border:1px solid #ddd;background-color:#d9edf7;}                 @media(min-width:576px){#cheatsheet-box{grid-template-columns:200px 1fr;}}    ... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramces Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Compiling software inside arch-nspawn chroot (without PKGBUILD)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vn21rf/compiling_software_inside_archnspawn_chroot/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vn21rf/compiling_software_inside_archnspawn_chroot/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T00:19:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm trying to compile this application for rendering Lego models and instructions, and encountering difficulties because the maintainer's build script was written for cloud-based CI services. Consequently, the PKGBUILD that is included in the repository will not work properly. I'm in the process of figuring out exactly what the scripts do so I can make a PKGBUILD that does work, but in the meantime I'd like to be able to be able to build it in a semi-isolated environment. 
 The Arch developer tools do include scripts that allow packages to be compiled within a clean chroot, but how can I spawn a chroot for building software that doesn't conform to the usual packaging standards?
    submitted by    /u/zoqaeski  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple M2 Enablement For Linux Begins With Good Progress]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Apple-M2-Linux-Starts</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Apple-M2-Linux-Starts"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T23:45:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hector Martin who has been leading the Asahi Linux effort for bringing up Linux on Apple Silicon recently received his new 2022 MacBook Pro 13-inch to begin porting Linux to Apple's new M2 SoC. While only started this week, he's already making significant progress. Fortunately, much of the existing M1-written Linux code can work for the M2 but some new drivers will need to be written before the new M2 Macs are fully usable on Linux...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thunderbird 102 Released With Big Improvements To This Leading Open-Source Mail Client]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Thunderbird-102-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Thunderbird-102-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T23:38:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After what has felt like years of neglect and little progress in advancing this open-source mail/communications client, Thunderbird 102 is out today with some shiny new features and a lot of UI refinements...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 10 KB5014666 update brings new printing features, bug fixes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-10-kb5014666-update-brings-new-printing-features-bug-fixes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-10-kb5014666-update-brings-new-printing-features-bug-fixes/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T22:37:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has released the optional KB5014666 Preview cumulative update for Windows 10 20H2, Windows 10 21H1, and Windows 10 21H2. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[502 http code with yay]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmzigm/502_http_code_with_yay/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmzigm/502_http_code_with_yay/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T22:17:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am trying to download libxft-bgra-git. When I do yay -S libxft-bgra-git. I get this error:
 [liam@Zeus ~]$ yay -S libxft-bgra-git :: Checking for conflicts... :: Checking for inner conflicts... [Aur:1] libxft-bgra-git-2.3.4.r147.42c6616-1 1 libxft-bgra-git (Installed) (Build Files Exist) ==> Packages to cleanBuild? ==> [N]one [A]ll [Ab]ort [I]nstalled [No]tInstalled or (1 2 3, 1-3, ^4) ==> N :: (1/1) Downloaded PKGBUILD: libxft-bgra-git 1 libxft-bgra-git (Installed) (Build Files Exist) ==> Diffs to show? ==> [N]one [A]ll [Ab]ort [I]nstalled [No]tInstalled or (1 2 3, 1-3, ^4) ==> N :: (1/1) Parsing SRCINFO: libxft-bgra-git ==> Making package: libxft-bgra-git 2.3.4.r147.42c6616-1 (Tue 28 Jun 2022 05:09:40 PM CDT) ==> Retrieving sources... -> Updating libxft git repo... Fetching origin remote: GitLab is not responding fatal: unable to access 'https://gitlab.freedesktop.org/xorg/lib/libxft.git/': The requested URL returned error: 502 error: could not fetch origin ==> WARNING: Failure while updating libxft git repo -> Found 1.patch ==> Validating source files with md5sums... libxft ... Skipped 1.patch ... Passed ==> Making package: libxft-bgra-git 2.3.4.r147.42c6616-1 (Tue 28 Jun 2022 05:09:41 PM CDT) ==> Checking runtime dependencies... ==> Checking buildtime dependencies... ==> Retrieving sources... -> Updating libxft git repo... 
 Can anyone help me?
    submitted by    /u/l0cky12f  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strange Wifi issue.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmzgou/strange_wifi_issue/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmzgou/strange_wifi_issue/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T22:15:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So, I've recently installed Arch Linux, and set up my Wifi using iwd/iwctl. However, after that, I installed KDE, and switched to using NetworkManager (KDE uses it by default, and it is required for accurate information in the network applet). Weirdly, my Wifi connection will randomly reset while using it, and reconnect under a different name. For example, my connection is normally "wlan0". However, it randomly disconnected me, and reconnected using "wlan1". This has happened multiple times now, and I can't find any mention of it online. What could be a possible cause of this?
    submitted by    /u/notabirb2  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Auricolari Bluetooth TWS ACEFAST T6 ENC: opinione, recensione e prova pratica]]></title>
        <id>3606|20220629000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/cuffie-9543/auricolari-bluetooth-tws-acefast-t6-enc-opinione-recensione-prova-pratica-3606"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ACEFAST è un'azienda cinese fondata nel 2020 che opera nel mercato degli accessori tech con un catalogo piuttosto ampio, che spazia dai caricatori per smartphone ai supporti per notebook, passando per gli auricolari Bluetooth. Ho avuto l'occasione di provare le nuove ACEFAST T6 ENC, cuffiette Bluetooth TWS (True Wireless Stereo) dal design coloratissimo, vendute ad un prezzo che si aggira attorno ai 50 €. Sono un buon acquisto? Vediamolo in questa recensione e prova degli auricolari Bluetooth TWS ACEFAST T6 ENC
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evilnum hackers return in new operation targeting migration orgs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/evilnum-hackers-return-in-new-operation-targeting-migration-orgs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/evilnum-hackers-return-in-new-operation-targeting-migration-orgs/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T21:49:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Evilnum hacking group is showing renewed signs of malicious activity, targeting European organizations that are involved in international migration. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to View and Manage Your TikTok Watch History]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=post-ideas&amp;p=490892</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15398873/view-manage-tiktok-watch-history"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TikTok has easily become one of the most popular social media platforms around the world. Yet, in many ways, the app is still very much in development, with new features being added constantly. One such feature is the ability to see which videos you’ve already watched, aka your TikTok Watch History. This can be an important tool for daily TikTok users, especially when you accidentally refresh your “For You” page or forget to favorite a video.
   

Content

How the TikTok Watch History Feature Works
How to Enable and View Watch History on TikTok
Clearing Your Watch History
What If I Don't Have the Watch History Feature?
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Download TikTok Videos Anywhere
    
How the TikTok Watch History Feature Works
    
TikTok launched its Watch History feature in March 2022. However, like most other features, the platform is slowly releasing it... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Megan Glosson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Firefox privacy feature strips URLs of tracking parameters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-firefox-privacy-feature-strips-urls-of-tracking-parameters/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-firefox-privacy-feature-strips-urls-of-tracking-parameters/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T21:11:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla Firefox 102 was released today with a new privacy feature that strips parameters from URLs that are used to track you around the web. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Install and Move Android Apps to the SD Card]]></title>
        <id>http://www.howtogeek.com/?p=114667</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/114667/how-to-install-android-apps-to-the-sd-card-by-default-move-almost-any-app-to-the-sd-card/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some Android phones don’t have a lot of storage, so you might run out of room for apps. If your device has an SD card slot, you can use that to expand the storage and have more room for apps. However, SD card support is more limited than it used to be.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft 365 now prevents data leaks with new session timeouts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-365-now-prevents-data-leaks-with-new-session-timeouts/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-365-now-prevents-data-leaks-with-new-session-timeouts/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T20:10:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft announced today the general availability of tenant-wide idle session timeout for Microsoft 365 web apps to protect confidential data on shared or non-company devices left unattended. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Check Your Motherboard Model Number on Your Windows PC]]></title>
        <id>http://www.howtogeek.com/?p=208420</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/208420/how-to-check-your-motherboard-model-number-on-your-windows-pc/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you need to update drivers, check hardware compatibility, or you’re just curious, it’s way easier to check your motherboard model number with these simple tricks than to crack open your case to check the board itself. Here’s how to check your motherboard model number from the comfort of your keyboard.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Fitzpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[tiling WM to use with XFCE4]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmw259/tiling_wm_to_use_with_xfce4/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmw259/tiling_wm_to_use_with_xfce4/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T19:48:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I want to use tiling wm with familiar desktop environment, what is the best option in this case? I have little to no experience with tiling wms and hardware from 2009 so I want something fast and simple that won't interfere with anything
    submitted by    /u/AkuBusshu  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[T-Mobile Is Selling Your App Activity: Here’s How to Opt Out]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=814461</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/814461/t-mobile-is-selling-your-app-activity-heres-how-to-opt-out/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T19:31:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[T-Mobile has positioned itself as a better alternative to other carriers over the past few years, but it also plays many of the same tricks as other networks, including selling user data. The network is now targeting advertisements based on app usage data, but there’s a way to opt out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get a Roku Streambar with Voice Remote for Under $100]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=387966</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/14316325/roku-streambar-streaming-media-player"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not interested in Amazon Prime but want Alexa assistance with your streaming. You can stream all of your entertainment, including movies, TV shows, music, podcasts, etc., from a Roku Streambar with Voice Remote and still have Alexa assistance. You can get a streaming media player and premium audio speaker all in one for 24% off.
    
This streaming device has an easy and quick interface with most popular channels and access to free entertainment. Stream it all in HD, 4K, and HDR with a resolution and colors that are optimized for all TVs. Everything you need to get set up is included in the box. Plug it into your TV, connect it to your home Internet, and you’re done!
   
 
   
Four internal speakers on the Roku Streambar provide Dolby Audio calibrated for full sound on your TV. Room-filling audio moves with the action in your entertainment, makes you feel like you’re in the conversations and takes you to another world through the sounds of nature. This is all thanks to advanced audio engineering in the Roku... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fix a Flickering External Screen on a Mac]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=805459</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/805459/mac-flickering-external-screen/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T19:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re using an Apple display with your MacBook or desktop Mac, things are generally flawless. However, non-Apple displays can exhibit weird behavior such as flickering, and it’s not always obvious how to fix it. There are some things you can try, though.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sydney Butler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD GPUOpen Working On A New "gpurt" Open-Source Project]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMD-GPUOpen-gpurt</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMD-GPUOpen-gpurt"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AMD's GPUOpen team quietly setup a new GitHub repository for "gpurt", presumably a new ray-tracing related software effort...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Anyone using Microsoft Edge's Collections feature?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179419</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/28/is-anyone-using-microsoft-edges-collections-feature/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T18:32:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Collections, a way to save content in Edge, is one of the features that distinguishes Microsoft Edge from Google Chrome, its main competitor. Collections work similarly to bookmarks, as the feature's main […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Is Anyone using Microsoft Edge's Collections feature? appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[help]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmu590/help/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmu590/help/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T18:28:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[the "arch-chroot /mnt" doesn't work :chroot failed to run command "/bin/bash": no such file directory . I'm trying to install on a 32 bits PC and I didn't find the solution please help me.
    submitted by    /u/archimen5024  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iwctl stuck in "Waiting for IWD to start"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmu35q/iwctl_stuck_in_waiting_for_iwd_to_start/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmu35q/iwctl_stuck_in_waiting_for_iwd_to_start/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T18:25:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Refer to title. I looked at some other posts here and the solutions there didn't work. I tried systemctl enable --now iwd but that never completes. I checked the logs with systemctl status iwd but I didn't find anything out of the ordinary except Vendor Preset is disabled. I tried looking at my /usr/lib/iwd/iwd but the whole file is in gibberish even though I have my locale set to UTF-8. I tried using leafpad to select a different encoding but every encoding there gives me gibberish. 
 All I really want to do is connect to wifi, if there is an easier way to do it please let me know
    submitted by    /u/Big_Cartographer_676  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Monitor Kubernetes Pod Logs In Real-Time With Stern]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?post_type=devops&amp;p=800723</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/devops/how-to-monitor-kubernetes-pod-logs-in-real-time-with-stern/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T18:25:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stern is an open-source tool that makes it easier to stream real-time Kubernetes logs to your terminal. You can use Stern to monitor logs from multiple containers simultaneously, giving you a combined view of activity inside Pods.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making an Arch install with the Cosmic DE so I made a Plymouth logo .]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmtt6j/making_an_arch_install_with_the_cosmic_de_so_i/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmtt6j/making_an_arch_install_with_the_cosmic_de_so_i/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T18:15:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://imgur.com/a/HHhOclJ
    submitted by    /u/P65B40  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fix: Why Isn’t Linux Detecting My Wi-Fi Adapter?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=806845</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/806845/linux-not-detecting-wi-fi-adapter/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T18:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever installed Linux on a laptop, rebooted, and found it can’t see your Wi-Fi card? It’s pretty deflating. Try these hints. One or more of them might just get it working.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKay</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The M2 MacBook Pro's Base Model Comes with a Disappointing Downgrade]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/121901/the-m2-macbook-pros-base-model-comes-with-a-disappointing-downgrade/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/121901/the-m2-macbook-pros-base-model-comes-with-a-disappointing-downgrade/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T17:57:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple’s new 13-inch MacBook Pro M2 has a lot to offer, but the entry-level model comes with a pretty disappointing downgrade. The base model with 256GB of storage has significantly slower SSD performance speeds than the previous M1 generation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ARM presenta le nuove CPU ARMv9 e le GPU con supporto per il ray-tracing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=ARM-presenta-le-nuove-CPU-ARMv9-e-le-GPU-con-supporto-per-il-ray-tracing_24718</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=ARM-presenta-le-nuove-CPU-ARMv9-e-le-GPU-con-supporto-per-il-ray-tracing_24718"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T17:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ci troviamo nel periodo durante il quale ARM è solita annunciare le novità che debutteranno da qui a un anno sotto forma di prodotti commerciali.La società britannica, che ha visto sfumare l'acquisizione da parte di NVidia e che adesso è nel mirino di una cordata di imprese capeggiata da Qualcomm, ha annunciato la nuova generazione di CPU ARMv9 basate su core Cortex-X3 e Cortex-A715. ARM ha anche annunciato un Cortex-A510 'rinnovato'.

Partendo dalla proposta più performante, il Cortex-X3 è un core focalizzato sulle prestazioni (+22% rispetto agli smartphone Android di punta basati su Cortex-X2). Secondo ARM i SoC basati su Cortex-X3 sarebbero fino al 34% più prestazionali rispetto ad esempio a un Intel Core i7 per notebook (28W).ARM fa riferimento anche a un aumento del valore IPC pari all'11% rispetto al Cortex-X2 che utilizza lo stesso processo produttivo.Non si parlato esplicitamente, in questo caso, di migliorie in fatto di efficienza energetica: l'azienda si è limitata a dire che Cortex-X3 consuma meno energia nella maggior parte dei casi rispetto al Cortex-X2.Il secondo nuovo core, Cortex-A715, raccoglie l'eredità del Cortex-A710: sarà il core 'a media potenza' in questi SoC che usano un'architettura composta da tre cluster fornendo un buon equilibrio tra potenza ed efficienza.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arm Cortex-X3 + Cortex-A715 Announced As Second-Gen Armv9 CPUs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Arm-Cortex-X3-Cortex-A715</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Arm-Cortex-X3-Cortex-A715"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T17:46:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arm today announced their second-generation Armv9 CPU designs with the Cortex-X3 and Cortex-A715. Arm also refreshed the Cortex-A510 to allow for more cores and a power reduction...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vim 9.0 Released With New Vim9 Script For 10~100x Execution Speed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Vim-9.0-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Vim-9.0-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T17:32:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vim 9.0 is out as the first major update in two years for this popular text editor. With Vim 9.0 comes the Vim9 scripting language that offers significantly better performance...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD investigates RansomHouse hack claims, theft of 450GB data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/amd-investigates-ransomhouse-hack-claims-theft-of-450gb-data/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/amd-investigates-ransomhouse-hack-claims-theft-of-450gb-data/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T17:18:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chip manufacturer AMD says they are investigating a cyberattack after threat actors claimed to have stolen 450 GB of data from the company last year. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[After system upgrade X server no longer working?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmseiy/after_system_upgrade_x_server_no_longer_working/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmseiy/after_system_upgrade_x_server_no_longer_working/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T17:17:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I did a paru -Syu but in the middle of it thought it got stuck and stupidly powered off the machine. Now X server encounters fatal errors and I'm not sure what to do. The machine still works and I was able to do another paru -Syu and complete the upgrade. However, I cannot log into the GUI since lightdm can't connect to the X server. Lightdm continously failed. I reinstalled both lightdm and xorg but still run into the issue. I installed SDDM and disabled lightdm. I enabled and started SDDM and it didn't fail but the X server still won't work.
 Here is the log, can anyone offer insight into this issue:
 [ 46200.412] X.Org X Server 1.21.1.3 X Protocol Version 11, Revision 0 [ 46200.413] Current Operating System: Linux arch-pc 5.18.7-arch1-1 #1 SMP PREEMPT_DYNAMIC Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:22:01 +…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nura's New Earbuds Combine Lossless Audio with "Personalized" Sound]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/121878/nuras-new-earbuds-combine-lossless-audio-with-personalized-sound/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/121878/nuras-new-earbuds-combine-lossless-audio-with-personalized-sound/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T17:13:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nura is often lauded for its personalized sound technology, which tests your ears to automatically find optimal EQ settings. But its latest earbuds, the NuraTrue Pro, take things to a new level—they support CD-quality lossless audio.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Force Delete a Folder on Windows 10 and 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=811409</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/811409/force-delete-folder-windows/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T17:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you having trouble deleting a folder from your Windows 10 or Windows 11 PC? If so, that may be a system folder or a folder being used by other apps. We’ll show you how to successfully delete “undeletable” folders on your computer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung's Next Phone Has a Headphone Jack and Removable Battery]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/121885/samsungs-next-phone-has-a-headphone-jack-and-removable-battery/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/121885/samsungs-next-phone-has-a-headphone-jack-and-removable-battery/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T16:32:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung recently confirmed that its next smartphone announcement is coming on July 13th, where it’ll debut the rugged Galaxy XCover 6 Pro. Now, weeks ahead of the event, we’ve received new details confirming it’ll have a large removable battery and a 3.5mm headphone jack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MITRE shares this year's list of most dangerous software bugs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/mitre-shares-this-years-list-of-most-dangerous-software-bugs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/mitre-shares-this-years-list-of-most-dangerous-software-bugs/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T16:29:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MITRE shared this year's top 25 most common and dangerous weaknesses impacting software throughout the previous two calendar years. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Risolvere errore 502 Bad Gateway se un sito non si apre]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2018/10/risolvere-errore-502-bad-gateway-se-un.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2018/10/risolvere-errore-502-bad-gateway-se-un.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T16:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ogni tanto sui siti web troviamo l'errore 502 Bad Gateway: questo è un tipo di errore che si verifica tentando di visitare un sito web ed è legato alla risposta non valida data dal server che agisce da proxy e si collega poi al server web che ospita il sito e dipende, il più delle volte, dal sito stesso.

 Rispetto però la serie di errori 404 o 403, quando compare la pagina con il 502, può darsi...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Have Secret Chats With the iPhone Notes App]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=813110</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/813110/how-to-have-secret-chats-with-the-iphone-notes-app/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T16:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are plenty of messaging apps to choose from when it comes to having private conversations on the iPhone. One that you may not have expected is the good ‘ol Apple Notes app. We’ll show you how it works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[sudo -b replacement with doas]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmq8tp/sudo_b_replacement_with_doas/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmq8tp/sudo_b_replacement_with_doas/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T15:42:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone,
 I'm trying out doas to see if it could fit in my workflow. Everything runs smoothly, apart from one command that runs openconnect.
 The current command is 
 echo $PWD | sudo -b openconnect --background -u AppleseedJ -passwd-on-stdin vpn.company.com 
 I have not been able to work this one out using a mix of doas and nohup (that's why I ended up using the -b switch of sudo back when I wrote the script). The biggest constraint is that the script is run from a terminal that is then killed.
 If anyone has any pointers, I'd be happy to read them.
 ​
 Cheers
    submitted by    /u/noah_boegli  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tradurre testi in italiano nelle app Android]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Tradurre-testi-in-italiano-nelle-app-Android_24716</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Tradurre-testi-in-italiano-nelle-app-Android_24716"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T15:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A meno di non essere poliglotti può capitare di trovarsi in difficoltà nel leggere quanto riportato nelle applicazioni Android. Tante app sono in inglese e chi non è abituato a leggere spesso testi in questa o in altre lingue può realizzare di essere un po’ arrugginito per quello che riguarda la traduzione in italiano.Per tradurre testi nelle app Android, di seguito proponiamo tre possibili soluzioni: le prime due si basano sull'utilizzo di applicazioni sviluppate da Google, la terza fa leva su un'applicazione di terze parti davvero utile e semplice da usare.
Android: tradurre testi in italiano con Google Traduttore
 L'app gratuita Google Traduttore si è da tempo arricchita di una comoda funzionalità chiamata Tocca per tradurre: essa consente di visualizzare una piccola 'bolla' sopra le altre app e di tradurre in italiano i testi presenti in qualunque app che ne consenta la selezione.Per utilizzare lo strumento basta installare il traduttore Google, fare clic sull'icona in alto a destra, scegliere Impostazioni quindi Tocca per tradurre.

A questo punto si devono attivare le opzioni Tocca per tradurre e Mostra icona floating.

L'icona di Google Translate compare sullo schermo: a questo punto si può aprire l'app Android di proprio interesse quindi selezionare il testo e scegliere Copia.

Toccando la 'bolla' del traduttore Google, si può incollare il testo copiato dall'app Android e ottenere immediatamente la traduzione in italiano.

Una volta conclusa l'operazione di traduzione, la 'bolla' di Google Translate può essere disattivata dall'area delle notifiche di Android.L'unico problema, nel caso della soluzione basata su Google Translate, è che l'app Android deve consentire la selezione del testo da tradurre.
Tradurre testi dagli screenshot delle app con Google Lens
 Una soluzione alternativa per ottenere la traduzione in italiano di un testo scritto in un'altra lingua consiste nel creare uno screenshot del contenuto dell'app Android: di solito è possibile farlo premendo Volume giù+tasto accensione.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Atari Launches Two Working 2600 Cartridges for Its 50th Anniversary]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/121866/atari-launches-two-working-2600-cartridges-for-its-50th-anniversary/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/121866/atari-launches-two-working-2600-cartridges-for-its-50th-anniversary/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T15:38:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s been 50 years since Atari sprang to life and kicked off the never-ending video game craze. And to celebrate that anniversary, we’re getting two new limited-edition Atari 2600 cartridges—Missile Command and Adventure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ford Issues F-150 Lightning Recall Over Tire Safety Issue]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/121869/ford-issues-f-150-lightning-recall-over-tire-safety-issue/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/121869/ford-issues-f-150-lightning-recall-over-tire-safety-issue/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T15:38:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to Ford, the new F-150 Lightning electric truck is facing its first recall, and the company has issued a software recall for thousands of vehicles over a tire safety software issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New ZuoRAT malware targets SOHO routers in North America, Europe]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-zuorat-malware-targets-soho-routers-in-north-america-europe/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-zuorat-malware-targets-soho-routers-in-north-america-europe/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T15:33:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A newly discovered multistage remote access trojan (RAT) dubbed ZuoRAT has been used to target remote workers via small office/home office (SOHO) routers across North America and Europe undetected since 2020. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your Roku Now Has Free Local News Channels Built-In]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=814396</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/814396/your-roku-now-has-free-local-news-channels-built-in/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T15:28:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roku streaming devices and TVs have offered free movies, TV shows, and “live” channels for a while now through the pre-installed Roku Channel. Starting today, the Roku Channel now has local news stations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Beautiful Beamer Slides with Emacs]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=477245</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15398417/create-beautiful-beamer-slides-with-emacs"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Emacs is a highly versatile program. Aside from being a text editor, it can be your email client, news reader and even your finances tracker. This is because you can easily adapt Emacs to any purpose and situation. 
    
Beamer is a LaTeX module that allows you to create presentation slides in a similar manner to creating LaTeX documents. Here we will show you how to use it to create presentations inside Emacs.
   

Content

How does Beamer work?
Using Beamer in Emacs
Creating a Basic Presentation in Emacs
Adding Bullets and Symbols to Slides
Adding Images to Slides in Emacs
Adding Tables to Slides in Emacs
Changing the Default Beamer Theme in Emacs
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:5 Hidden Features You Can Use to Improve Emacs
    
How does Beamer work?
   ... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramces Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[User specific daemons?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmpoan/user_specific_daemons/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmpoan/user_specific_daemons/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T15:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I wanted my friking mute button to work and so I installed acpid - and along with some other things configured the mute button. The issue I faced many times is that user specific utilities - notify-send/amixer need to be run with a su <user> -c prefix. I am wondering if this is the actuall way to do it? How does a program know what user I am - for example alsamixer?
    submitted by    /u/Narrow_Farmer_6018  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Time-Saving Google Docs Features You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=810442</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/810442/time-saving-google-docs-features/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T15:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you have a dozen tasks to do before lunchtime, any shortcut to speed things up is welcome. Here are several time-saving features for Google Docs that can help make creating and editing documents go quicker.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New in Mozilla Thunderbird 102]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=814358</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/814358/whats-new-in-mozilla-thunderbird-102/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T14:48:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla Thunderbird is having a resurgence right now, armed with an expanded team of developers and a plan to take over the email world (including Android). The first of several planned updates, Thunderbird 102, is about to start rolling out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FBI: Stolen PII and deepfakes used to apply for remote tech jobs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fbi-stolen-pii-and-deepfakes-used-to-apply-for-remote-tech-jobs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fbi-stolen-pii-and-deepfakes-used-to-apply-for-remote-tech-jobs/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T14:41:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) warns of an increase in complaints that cybercriminals are using Americans' stolen Personally Identifiable Information (PII) and deepfakes to apply for remote work positions. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Miglior processore Intel del momento]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/06/miglior-processore-intel-del-momento.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/06/miglior-processore-intel-del-momento.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T14:41:00.006Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I processori Intel sono senza ombra di dubbio i più potenti e i più richiesti sulle configurazioni PC domestici e per l'utilizzo sui computer da ufficio, ma pochissimi utenti sono in grado di capire se il processore Intel che si trovano davanti è un modello di nuova generazione o un modello vecchio, venduto magari a prezzo di saldo proprio perché uscito fuori supporto. Questo errore deve essere...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roku Now Offers Free Local Channels]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/121861/roku-now-offers-free-local-channels/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/121861/roku-now-offers-free-local-channels/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T14:39:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ever-expanding Roku Channel is about to gain eight local news stations, courtesy of NBCUniversal. These stations provide news coverage in “major U.S. markets” like NYC and LA, though they will be available to all Roku users regardless of their location.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Quickly Switch Kubernetes Contexts With Kubectx and Kubens]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?post_type=devops&amp;p=800736</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/devops/how-to-quickly-switch-kubernetes-contexts-with-kubectx-and-kubens/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T14:24:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kubectx and Kubens are two tools which accelerate your Kubernetes management experience. They address some of the shortcomings of Kubectl by making it quicker and more convenient to switch between cluster environments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Editing file content with pacman hook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmogni/editing_file_content_with_pacman_hook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmogni/editing_file_content_with_pacman_hook/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T14:23:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi,
 I'm trying to create simple pacman hook to clear file contents, for now I have: 
 [Trigger] Operation = Install Operation = Upgrade Operation = Remove Type = Package Target = * [Action] Description = Clear update list file When = PostTransaction Exec = /bin/bash -c '> /tmp/packages_to_update.txt' 
 After system update I get that /tmp/packages_to_update.txt can't be accessed.
 I read that pacman hooks is run by current user, and /tmp should be accessible by anyone. Am I missing something?
    submitted by    /u/silverweaver  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trying to Rust-ify my system as much as possible. Is installing a new shell and a new terminal easy?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmoeph/trying_to_rustify_my_system_as_much_as_possible/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmoeph/trying_to_rustify_my_system_as_much_as_possible/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T14:20:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is it literally just "install mynewshell" "uninstall bash".
 "install alacritty" "uninstall xfce terminal"
 Someone mentioned that "coreutils" has been rewritten in Rust, but "coreutils" is a scary word and "uninstall coreutils" sounds like "bye bye system and all my data".
 Thanks for your help!
    submitted by    /u/Remarkable-River-300  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[App coding: quali le migliori per imparare a sviluppare]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=App-coding-quali-le-migliori-per-imparare-a-sviluppare_24715</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=App-coding-quali-le-migliori-per-imparare-a-sviluppare_24715"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T14:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Un tempo imparare i rudimenti della programmazione era quasi indispensabile. Per sfruttare il potenziale di un elaboratore informatico e adattarne il funzionamento alle proprie necessità era necessario scrivere codice.Come racconta Steve Wozniak, cofondatore di un tempo, i sistemi di maggior successo di una volta erano così attraenti perché sollecitavano subito l'interesse dell'utente che era portato a sviluppare i suoi programmi con la possibilità di comunicare direttamente con l'hardware.Oggi sono disponibili strumenti e servizi che vengono incontro ad ogni possibile esigenza: essi solevano gli utenti dalla necessità di scrivere codice. Esistono anche nuovi strumenti basati sull'intelligenza artificiale che permettono di generare codice funzionante nei vari linguaggi di programmazione scrivendo semplicemente il nome di una funzione o descrivendo ciò che si vuole ottenere: GitHub Copilot e Amazon CodeWhisperer.Non c'è nulla di male: questi strumenti aiutano a concludere più velocemente lo sviluppo di un progetto dispensando il programmatore dallo scrivere codice di base o comunque che si ripete di frequente nei vari progetti.Sviluppare è un'attività stimolante che richiede una dose di logica e di creatività.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>