<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-07-16T02:09:12.799Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["error: failed retrieving file 'package' from 'mirror' : HTTP/2 stream xxx was not closed cleanly before end of the underlying stream" when updating]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w04yuq/error_failed_retrieving_file_package_from_mirror/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w04yuq/error_failed_retrieving_file_package_from_mirror/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T01:45:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm still new to pacman, how do i fix this mirror problem thingy?
    submitted by    /u/Ezzaskywalker_11  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to View Network Adapter Details in Windows]]></title>
        <id>http://maketecheasier.com/?p=66459</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/14182029/view-network-adapter-details-in-windows"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are a network administrator or an advanced user, you probably have multiple network cards in your computer. Digging deep into the device details can be a daunting thought if you want to view network adapter details on all the network cards you have installed, but it’s actually not such a hard thing to do.
    
Here we show you several ways to view the details of your network adapter in Windows: one is integrated into the system, and the other is a great Nirsoft tool called NetworkInterfacesView, which lets you dig a little deeper.
   

Content

1. Using System Information Tool
2. Using the NetworkInterfacesView Tool
3. Device Manager
4. Network Connections
Troubleshoot Network Adapters
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:7 of the Best Dynamic DNS Providers You Can Use for Free
    
1.... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Crystal Crowder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Opening firewall ports for Chiaki on steam deck]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w02efh/opening_firewall_ports_for_chiaki_on_steam_deck/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w02efh/opening_firewall_ports_for_chiaki_on_steam_deck/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T23:36:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I read that I need to open ports 9295, udp 987, 9296 and 9297 to get Chiaki to work on my steam deck. Can someone tell me the command to do so please? Thank you. Also, I did try searching first and my search seemed to be too general because it wasn't getting me the right result.
 https://github.com/thestr4ng3r/chiaki/issues/67
 ​
 This is where I'm coming from
    submitted by    /u/DextersQuest  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wine 7.13 Converts Its USB Driver To PE Format, Brings Theming Improvements]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Wine-7.13-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Wine-7.13-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T22:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wine 7.13 is now available as the newest bi-weekly development release for running Windows games and applications on Linux and other platforms...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[startx failing, can't find displays, help requested]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w00lm7/startx_failing_cant_find_displays_help_requested/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w00lm7/startx_failing_cant_find_displays_help_requested/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T22:10:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[note that I am new to arch linux (a noob) and thus may appear to be a monkey]
 I recently installed arch onto my PC, upon the install everything had been working perfectly (Nvidia, xorg, bspwm, arandr). Thinking everything was great I shutdown (with shutdown command) and went to sleep. Next morning boot up PC and recieved an error message quickly pop up and disappear, continuing I was unable to startx and recieved a fatal error. 
 boot error: "Failed to start NVIDIA Persistence Daemon"
 Xorg log: HTTPS://transfer.sh/GHEz2h/xorg.txt
 the command "Sudo systemctl status nvidia-peristenced" returned some failures I will write them here rather than writing the whole log: "(red x failure symbol) nvidia-persistenced.service -in NVIDIA Persistence Daemon" "Failed to query NVIDIA devices. please ensure that the NVIDIA device files (/dev/nvidia*) exist, and that user 143 has read and write permissions for those files." "nvidia-peristenced.service: Control process exited, code=exited, status=1/FAILURE" "nvidia-persistenced.service: Failed with result 'exit-code'." "Failed to start NVIDIA Persistence Daemon."
 PC specs - Not in a VM - GTX 1060 3gb - Intel i5 - 8gb memory
 Earlier attempts at fixing: - reinstalling "nvidia" "nvidia-utils" through pacman - installing "nvidia-settings" - inserting "Section "Device" Identifier "NVIDIA Card" Driver "nvidia" VendorName "NVIDIA Corporation" BoardName "GeForce GTX 1060" EndSection" to "/etc/X11/xorg.conf.d/20-nvidia.conf" - inserting "MODULES=(nvidia nvidia_modeset nvidia_uvm nvidia_drm)" to "/etc/mkinitcpio.conf" then running "sudo mkinitcpio -p linux"
  
rebooting several times
  
If anyone knows how to fix this, please share, this is causing pain in 4D. Anyhow, thanks for reading this far - have a good day.
    submitted by    /u/KateBinTM  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[trying to fix arch using default fonts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w00gfp/trying_to_fix_arch_using_default_fonts/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w00gfp/trying_to_fix_arch_using_default_fonts/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T22:04:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey all,
 I recently accidentally deleted my /etc/ folder and I'm trying to remake it. I've got it to where pacman/yay works, my desktop works, etc. However, my fonts do not. At least, in certain places. In polybar, everything but one module uses the default font, and I don't know why the wifi module doesn't. They're all supposed to be using the same font. Google chrome also uses a default font. It's pretty dang ugly so any help would be appreciated. Thanks!
    submitted by    /u/24thpanda  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can you remotely update safely?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w00fo8/can_you_remotely_update_safely/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w00fo8/can_you_remotely_update_safely/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T22:03:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm new to linux but wouldn't call myself a complete beginner as I know much of the basics like package managers, the unix filesystem, etc. just haven't really daily driven linux at all. I'm wanting to go with arch but one issue I'm having is the "manual interventions" that you need to do while updating. I have to remote access my computer a lot, sometimes I don't have physical access for weeks at a time, and I'm curious if anyone knows a best way to keep it updated consistently without risking it bricking while I'm away and can't fix it. Right now it seems like a damned if you do damned if you don't situation because if I don't update it while I'm away then I'll come back with potentially several bits of manual intervention I need to do which could cause issues with each other and be a nightmare, or I can try to update regularly and get a few cases of manual intervention, that I may not be able to fix and I'll just be SOL for potentially weeks. 
 I originally considered using an arch derivative like Manjaro but now I'm hearing that Manjaro doesn't actually keep great compatibility with the AUR and has it's own issues so I basically have no idea at this point.
    submitted by    /u/temmiesayshoi  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Questa settimana su TLI (16 luglio 2022)]]></title>
        <id>3621|20220716000001</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/newsletter-turbolab.it-1349/questa-settimana-tli-16-luglio-2022-3621"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T22:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Non hai tempo di leggerci tutti i giorni? nessun problema! ecco a te il riepilogo di quanto proposto da TurboLab.it nel corso della settimana in conclusione.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Different Disks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vzzwf3/using_different_disks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vzzwf3/using_different_disks/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T21:39:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello! I can't figure out how to make a disk (separate to the boot disk) writable so I can put steam games on it. Would anyone be able to tell me how? 
 Thank you!
    submitted by    /u/JJSLAYER_  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Take Advantage of Windows 11’s Improved Accessibility Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=494684</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15433850/windows-accessibility-tools"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 contains various accessibility improvements compared to Windows 10, but the most noticeable is the name change. The feature set known as “Ease of Access” in Windows 10 was transformed into Accessibility in the the latest Windows version. Microsoft even changed the icon into a human-shaped one, which is the recognized Accessibility icon in most parts of the world.
    
In this article, we’ll go through the updated Accessibility offerings in Windows 11, touch on how they can sometime differ from Windows 10, and suggest how these features can be utilized by Windows users.
   

Content

Getting to Your Accessibility Center
Checking Out Your Quick Access Options
Main Accessibility Menu
Options for the Blind/Visually Impaired
Options for the Deaf/Hearing Impaired
Options for Users with Mobility Impairments
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:What Is Windows 11 for ARM and Who Is... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Yoder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ESPN+ Is Raising Prices Again Next Month]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=818713</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/818713/espn-is-raising-prices-again-next-month/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T21:13:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ESPN+ is Disney’s sport-focused streaming service, commonly used in the bundle alongside Disney+ and Hulu. However, if you pay for ESPN+ by itself outside of the Disney+ bundle, your monthly bill is about to go up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make Chrome Use Less RAM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=769906</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/769906/how-to-make-chrome-use-less-ram/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Chrome is a very popular web browser, but people have one common complaint—it uses a lot of RAM. It’s hard to fix the problem completely, but there are some things you can do to reduce Chrome’s memory usage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How can I force bridge to wait for ethernet before LINK STATE UP?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vzyom0/how_can_i_force_bridge_to_wait_for_ethernet/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vzyom0/how_can_i_force_bridge_to_wait_for_ethernet/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T20:43:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm having a problem with my virtual bridge going UP before my ethernet device is configured (Arch automatically renames this physical device eno1). I can restart systemd-networkd to fix the order, but I have to do it every time I boot my Linux. Scoured the docs + Google, found nothing... thinking of making a script run on start to restart networkd but I'd rather fix it than patch.
    submitted by    /u/profile_this  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I need some help with pacman, it keeps saying target error.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vzyboq/i_need_some_help_with_pacman_it_keeps_saying/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vzyboq/i_need_some_help_with_pacman_it_keeps_saying/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T20:27:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello! For a while now I have been trying to install steam and some other things with pacman and it keeps saying “error: target not found”. I have already re-generated a new mirror list and I don’t know what to do next. Any suggestions? Thank you!
    submitted by    /u/JJSLAYER_  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Are Philips Hue Smart Lights so Expensive?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/123257/why-are-philips-hue-smart-lights-so-expensive/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/123257/why-are-philips-hue-smart-lights-so-expensive/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T20:22:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Philips Hue is the most well-known smart lighting brand. But when shoppers realize that Philips Hue costs two or three times the price of its competitors, they often walk away thinking that its products are overpriced. And that’s a shame—Philips Hue is prohibitively expensive, but its pricing makes sense.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Windows 10 or Windows 11 in S Mode?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=354057</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/354057/what-is-windows-10-in-s-mode/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some Windows 10 or Windows 11 PCs, like Microsoft’s Surface Go 3, come with “Windows 10 in S Mode” or “Windows 11 in S Mode.” PCs in S Mode can only install applications from the Microsoft Store. But you’re free to leave S Mode, if you like.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save Up to 35% on a Garmin Venu Sq Music GPS Smartwatch]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=448628</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/14957082/garmin-venu-sq-music-gps-smartwatch"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you still waiting to get started on your summer fitness goals? Kickstart them into gear with a Garmin Venu Sq Music GPS Smartwatch. It’s currently either 30% or 35% off, depending on your color choice, yet has all the features you would want to help you with your fitness and health goals.
    
This bright color display has an always-on mode, which works well when you just need to glance at your phone to check the time or a text notification. You’ll also get call and social media notifications when the smartwatch is paired with a compatible smartphone.
    
The Garmin Venu Sq Music GPS Smartwatch allows you to monitor multiple body metrics, including energy level, respiration, hydration, menstrual cycle, estimated heart rate, stress, and sleep.
   
 
   
Keep moving with more than 20 preloaded sports apps, including cardio, yoga, strength, and Pilates. You can also create your own workout in the Garmin Connect app. If you’re a runner, you’ll enjoy the personal running coach to help you train for your... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Hide and Unhide Sheet Tabs in Google Sheets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=812758</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/812758/hide-sheets-in-google-sheets/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T19:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you have a workbook with many sheets, it can feel tedious to scroll between them. In Google Sheets, you can hide your sheet tabs to see only those you need. Then, unhide them when the time comes to view them again.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Radeon Software for Linux 22.20 Released With Ubuntu 22.04 LTS Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Radeon-Software-Linux-22.20</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Radeon-Software-Linux-22.20"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T18:45:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While AMD is normally fairly good at promptly supporting major new enterprise Linux distribution releases from Red Hat, SUSE, and Canonical (Ubuntu), this time around with Ubuntu 22.04 LTS it's taken just shy of three months since the official release for them to formally release a new packaged driver supporting it...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[audcity 3?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vzw1os/audcity_3/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vzw1os/audcity_3/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T18:45:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I know there was hiccup with telemetry stuff, but it seems to be now sorted out. At least it should be opt-in and self hosted from what I found. Which is not much different from what Firefox is doing if i am right. Is there any Arch relevant discussion on this topic?
    submitted by    /u/sogun123  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This LEGO 'The Office' Set Is a Perfect Gift for Dunder Mifflin Fans]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/123264/this-lego-the-office-set-is-a-perfect-gift-for-dunder-mifflin-fans/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/123264/this-lego-the-office-set-is-a-perfect-gift-for-dunder-mifflin-fans/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T18:23:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest LEGO crossover may be the best one we’ve seen yet. The official LEGO Twitter account just confirmed a new The Office set based on the critically acclaimed NBC show everyone loves. If you’re a fan or know someone that is, this would be the perfect gift.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Enable Macros in Microsoft Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=812574</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/812574/enable-macros-in-excel/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T18:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using Microsoft Excel macros, you can run a prerecorded set of steps to automate many of your repetitive tasks. You’ll have to turn on the feature before you can use it. We’ll show you how to activate macros on a per-spreadsheet basis as well as for all spreadsheets in Excel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two Months After Being Merged, Intel In-Field Scan Marked "Broken" For Linux 5.19]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-IFS-Driver-Broken-Linux</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-IFS-Driver-Broken-Linux"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T17:46:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While there are many shiny new features coming in this next kernel version, the Linux 5.19 cycle hasn't been particularly smooth for Intel. In addition to now needing to deal with their GuC firmare breakage for Alder Lake P "ASAP", their brand new In-Field Scan (IFS) driver set to premiere in Linux 5.19 has been marked as "broken" after it was determined its exposed interface may need some alterations...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Password recovery tool infects industrial systems with Sality malware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/password-recovery-tool-infects-industrial-systems-with-sality-malware/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/password-recovery-tool-infects-industrial-systems-with-sality-malware/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T17:46:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A threat actor is infecting industrial control systems (ICS) to create a botnet through password "cracking" software for programmable logic controllers (PLCs). [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GM May Need to Hit the Brakes on Its Cruise Robotaxis]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/123254/gm-may-need-to-hit-the-brakes-on-its-cruise-robotaxis/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/123254/gm-may-need-to-hit-the-brakes-on-its-cruise-robotaxis/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T17:11:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After years of working on its self-driving Robotaxi fleet of vehicles, GM’s Cruise recently received regulatory approval to drive on select streets in California and charge customers for taxi rides. However, things aren’t off to a good start, and now the platform is under review.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTG Deal Favorites: Save Up to 38% On Stuff We Like]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=818506</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/818506/htg-deal-favorites-save-up-to-38-on-stuff-we-like/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T17:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We made it! Our final edition of How-To Geek Deals for Prime Day is here. To close out the week, we’re featuring a range of sales on some of our team’s favorite gadgets of 2022, all from brands like Samsung, Fitbit, Amazon, and a couple others.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zach Laidlaw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Delete a Sheet in Microsoft Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=810860</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/810860/how-to-delete-a-sheet-in-excel/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T17:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t need a specific worksheet in your spreadsheet anymore? If so, Microsoft Excel offers two easy ways to delete sheets from your workbook. We’ll show you how to use them, as well as what to do if you can’t delete your sheets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[Optimus, Wine] Can't run Wine on integrated GPU when lib32-nvidia-utils installed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vzt1gz/optimus_wine_cant_run_wine_on_integrated_gpu_when/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vzt1gz/optimus_wine_cant_run_wine_on_integrated_gpu_when/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T16:36:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So I have have a laptop with Optimus graphics including Intel HD Graphics 610 and NVidia MX110. I use optimus-manager to switch between them when I need to. Everything works pretty fine except one thing.
 OpenGL works fine in Wine on both Intel and NVidia GPUs when using Mesa. But I have installed lib32-nvidia-utils to use proprietary NVidia driver in Wine for OpenGL apps and it also works fine when running on NVidia GPU. However, when I switch to Intel, Wine doesn't want to run GUI applications at all and says this:
 nodrv_createwindow application tried to create a window, but no driver could be loaded.
 When I uninstall lib32-nvidia-utils, Wine and OpenGL works again on both GPUs. So is there a way to use proprietary NVidia driver in Wine without breaking things for Intel GPU?
    submitted by    /u/TheNightSkyDude  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accidentally disabled cpu boost on Ryzen 5800U]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vzsyv0/accidentally_disabled_cpu_boost_on_ryzen_5800u/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vzsyv0/accidentally_disabled_cpu_boost_on_ryzen_5800u/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T16:33:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I did something to my cpu (ryzen 5800U) at some point and accidentally disabled CPU boost on my arch install. I think it was when I ran powertop --auto-tune. Below is what cpupower frequency-info displays:
 analyzing CPU 0:
 driver: acpi-cpufreq
 CPUs which run at the same hardware frequency: 0
 CPUs which need to have their frequency coordinated by software: 0
 maximum transition latency: Cannot determine or is not supported.
 hardware limits: 1.60 GHz - 4.51 GHz
 available frequency steps: 1.90 GHz, 1.80 GHz, 1.60 GHz
 available cpufreq governors: conservative ondemand userspace powersave performance schedutil
 current policy: frequency should be within 1.60 GHz and 1.90 GHz. The governor "powersave" may decide which speed to use within this range.
 current CPU frequency: Unable to call hardware
 current CPU frequency: 1.41 GHz (asserted by call to kernel)
 boost state support:
 Supported: yes
 Active: no
    submitted by    /u/MaterialisedAutism  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How can I keep my credit card details from being stolen online? [Ask ZDNet]]]></title>
        <id>f967050e-01ff-4278-975f-da97b0e6834a</id>
        <link href="https://www.zdnet.com/article/how-can-i-keep-my-credit-card-details-from-being-stolen-online-ask-zdnet/#ftag=RSSbaffb68"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Got a tech question? Ed Bott and ZDNet's squad of editors and experts probably have the answer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest topics for ZDNet in Windows</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tor Browser risponde alla censura: la nuova versione si connette comunque]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Tor-Browser-risponde-alla-censura-la-nuova-versione-si-connette-comunque_24779</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Tor-Browser-risponde-alla-censura-la-nuova-versione-si-connette-comunque_24779"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T16:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nell'ultimo periodo non si contano i tentativi di bloccare Tor: nel nostro articolo abbiamo spiegato quali espedienti provano a utilizzare alcuni Paesi per impedire ai cittadini la navigazione libera sul Web.Dal momento che Tor Browser aiuta a superare ogni censura il programma e la rete che utilizza sono divenute invise ai regimi totalitari in tante nazioni.Abbiamo visto come funziona Tor Browser: il traffico dati attraversa tre nodi differenti gestiti da volontari. I nodi coinvolti in una comunicazione non hanno visibilità su ciò che avviene sugli altri nodi e i dati scambiati dall'utente con i server remoti sono crittografati a più livelli con uno schema che ricorda la struttura di una cipolla (da qui il nome onion router).Tor Browser 11.5 integra un meccanismo espressamente progettato per superare ogni censura.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come usare il pannello laterale di Chrome]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/07/come-usare-il-pannello-laterale-di.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/07/come-usare-il-pannello-laterale-di.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T16:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tra le novità introdotte da Google Chrome troviamo il pannello laterale (side panel), accessibile tramite apposito pulsante fisso in alto a destra di ogni finestra di Chrome. Molti utenti non hanno apprezzato questa modifica (infatti in basso troviamo anche la guida su come rimuoverla) ma gli utenti più esperti hanno subito imparato tutti i suoi trucchi, così da poterla utilizzare per aumentare la produttività quando lavoriamo dal browser o quando apriamo molte schede contemporaneamente.
 Nella guida che segue vi mostreremo i migliori suggerimenti e trucchi per il pannello laterale di Chrome, una feature che può rivelarsi utile in diversi scenari lavorativi, specie dopo aver appreso quali capacità nasconde al suo interno.
  
LEGGI ANCHE -> Come rimuovere Elenco di lettura e pannello latera…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Cuts Back on In-House Brands Due to Poor Sales]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/123245/amazon-cuts-back-on-in-house-brands-due-to-poor-sales/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/123245/amazon-cuts-back-on-in-house-brands-due-to-poor-sales/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T16:19:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon is reducing the number of products sold under its in-house brands, including AmazonBasics, Amazon Essentials, and Solimo. It’s a major shift in the company’s strategy, and according to the Wall Street Journal, it’s due to poor sales.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft investigates July updates breaking Access applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-investigates-july-updates-breaking-access-applications/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-investigates-july-updates-breaking-access-applications/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T16:06:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft is investigating user reports that MS Access runtime applications stop opening after installing this month's Patch Tuesday Office/Access security updates. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keep getting error while trying to install arch on Virtualbox using archinstall script]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vzs8vo/keep_getting_error_while_trying_to_install_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vzs8vo/keep_getting_error_while_trying_to_install_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T16:02:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is the error. I've tried three times with different internet connection but couldn't solve the problem.
    submitted by    /u/markedfive  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 Common DisplayPort Problems, and How to Fix Them]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=813778</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/813778/how-to-fix-common-displayport-problems/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T16:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DisplayPort is a great option for connecting your monitor and display adapter. But although they are often reliable and stable, DisplayPort connections can sometimes fail in unexpected ways.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Russ Ware</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meglio Google Drive o OneDrive? Differenze tra i due servizi di storage cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Meglio-Google-Drive-o-OneDrive-Differenze-tra-i-due-servizi-di-storage-cloud_24778</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Meglio-Google-Drive-o-OneDrive-Differenze-tra-i-due-servizi-di-storage-cloud_24778"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T15:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Servizi cloud come Google Drive e OneDrive sono tra i più utilizzati in assoluto da utenti privati, professionisti e aziende per salvare file sul cloud e condividerli con i collaboratori, i dipendenti, i colleghi.Quali sono però le principali differenze tra Google Drive e OneDrive? Per quali caratteristiche un servizio brilla rispetto al concorrente?
Sincronizzazione
 La velocità di trasferimento dati è importante: poter aggiornare velocemente file di grandi dimensioni che sono stati caricati sul cloud è un aspetto cruciale.A questo proposito OneDrive utilizza una tecnologia chiamata Block Level Copying: la soluzione per lo storage cloud scompone i file, soprattutto quelli di grandi dimensioni, in frammenti più piccoli e compatti. In questo modo, invece che caricare online un unico pesante file, OneDrive si limita a effettuare l'upload dei frammenti essenziali.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel Might Make Your Next Computer More Expensive]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=818632</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/818632/intel-might-make-your-next-computer-more-expensive/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T15:40:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Global economic inflation is causing nearly everything to creep up in price, from groceries to cars. Intel is now raising prices on its processors and other chips, which could contribute to higher prices for PCs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[File Manager and Arch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vzrmxe/file_manager_and_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vzrmxe/file_manager_and_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T15:36:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone, Arch noob here. 
 I installed arch linux to use it with Awesome WM. So far everything ok. I need a file manager and have both PCManFM and Ranger installed. In both cases I cannot access some folders, as an error signals me "Error opening directory, permission denied". From what I've read around I think it has to do with politi, but I'm not sure. 
 How can I solve it in your opinion? 
 A thousand thanks!
    submitted by    /u/oscarmonteleone  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Emacs to Play Music with EMMS]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=497626</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15433420/use-emacs-to-play-music-with-emms"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Emacs is a brilliant program that can do many things including handling files. With the Emacs Multimedia System (EMMS) package, you can also handle your music in Emacs. You can easily browse music directories, create song playlists and even display lyrics. Here we will show you how to play music in Emacs.
   

Content

What is EMMS and How Does it Work?
Installing EMMS
Configuring EMMS
Starting a Basic EMMS Session
Music Scrobbling in Emacs with GNU FM
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:5 Hidden Features You Can Use to Improve Emacs
    
What is EMMS and How Does it Work?
    
EMMS is an Elisp front-end client for various multimedia players. This means that unlike traditional music players, EMMS only deals with displaying files and it uses external programs to decode those files.
   
 Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramces Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forget Windows 11, Windows 12 Might Be On the Way]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/123238/forget-windows-11-windows-12-might-be-on-the-way/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/123238/forget-windows-11-windows-12-might-be-on-the-way/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T15:24:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It sounds like Microsoft is preparing to reshuffle its entire Windows update release schedule again. While Windows 11 is new and exciting, Windows 12 may arrive in 2024. According to a new report from Windows Central, the company is moving away from yearly feature updates and back to big releases every three years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pacman is throttling on one of my devices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vzr3rl/pacman_is_throttling_on_one_of_my_devices/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vzr3rl/pacman_is_throttling_on_one_of_my_devices/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T15:13:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been a long-time arch user, and this is the first time I've experienced anything like it. My PC is capping pacman download speeds at about a tenth of the limit. However, my laptop (also Arch) is able to download at full speed via pacman.
 Recently, I've also been experiencing this:
 error: failed retrieving file 'qt5-translations-5.15.5+kde+r2-1-any.pkg.tar.zst.sig' from archlinux.thaller.ws : Operation too slow. Less than 1 bytes/sec transferred the last 10 seconds
 I attempted to run Reflector to fix the mirrors, which worked on my laptop but not on the desktop. To be clear, my PC runs everything else at full speed, so this is only a pacman issue. Any help would be appreciated :)
    submitted by    /u/Seraphiel9  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Vapor Chamber Cooling, and Does Your PC Need It?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809377</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809377/what-is-vapor-chamber-cooling/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T15:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Electronics components, particularly computer CPUs and GPUs, need an efficient cooling system to prevent overheating. A vapor chamber is one such cooling system that has gained traction over the last decade. Here’s everything you need to know about it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gaurav Shukla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiplayer 'Wordle' Arrives as an Official Board Game]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/123226/multiplayer-wordle-arrives-as-an-official-board-game/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/123226/multiplayer-wordle-arrives-as-an-official-board-game/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T14:46:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ve talked the talk, but are you ready to prove that you’re the best Wordle player? This October, Wordle: The Party Game launches for just $19. The official board game supports up to four players and lets you go head-to-head with friends or family over and over again.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It looks as if Microsoft could extend Windows 7 Support by another three years]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179752</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/07/15/it-looks-as-if-microsoft-could-extend-windows-7-support-by-three-years/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T14:35:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft ended support for its Windows 7 operating system in 2020. The company offers extended support to organizations and businesses, but not to Home customers. Microsoft's initial plan was to limit extended […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post It looks as if Microsoft could extend Windows 7 Support by another three years appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tor Browser now bypasses internet censorship automatically]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/tor-browser-now-bypasses-internet-censorship-automatically/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/tor-browser-now-bypasses-internet-censorship-automatically/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T14:27:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Tor Project team has announced the release of Tor Browser 11.5, a major release that brings new features to help users fight censorship easier. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come attivare la misurazione costante sulla Mi Band]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/07/come-attivare-la-misurazione-costante.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/07/come-attivare-la-misurazione-costante.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T14:18:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[La Mi Band dispone di sensori molto avanzati per tenere sotto controllo il battito cardiaco e la saturazione del sangue, con un livello di precisione molto buono; questi valori sono molto utili per chi fa molto sport e vuole tenere sotto controllo i parametri durante gli esercizi.
 Quello che pochi utenti sanno è che è possibile attivare la misurazione costante sulla Mi Band e far registrare costantemente il battito cardiaco ed usare altri sensori durante tutto l'arco della giornata, così da poter identificare i momenti in cui abbiamo il battito accelerato senza alcun valido motivo o quando abbiamo un battito troppo basso rispetto all'esercizio che stiamo facendo in quel momento.
 Nella guida che segue vi mostreremo come attivare la misurazione costante sulla Mi Band tramite l'app specific…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wordle Is Now a Board Game, and You Can Pre-order It Now]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=818577</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/818577/wordle-is-now-a-board-game-and-you-can-pre-order-it-now/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T14:04:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wordle is the hit word-based puzzle game that suddenly spiked in popularity earlier this year, and then was purchased by the New York Times. Now, the news organization is taking Wordle to new frontiers: board games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Retro Controllers for PC and Raspberry Pi of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=807828</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/807828/best-retro-controller/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T14:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nothing beats using an old-school style controller when retro gaming, whether you’re on the original hardware, a Raspberry Pi, or even using an emulator. Make sure you get the best retro gaming experience with one of our recommendations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sydney Butler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Cancel Amazon Prime and Get a Refund]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=429020</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/429020/how-to-cancel-amazon-prime/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Prime normally costs $139 per year unless you can score a discounted Prime membership. If you’re ready to give up free two-day shipping, the Amazon Prime Video library, Prime Day, and other perks, here’s how you can quit Prime.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[16 Questions You’re Too Afraid to Ask About Your New MacBook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=814320</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/814320/16-questions-you-are-too-afraid-to-ask-about-your-new-macbook/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re a first-time MacBook owner or are considering buying one, you probably have a lot of questions about the notebooks and ecosystem. We’ve answered some of the most common queries newbies might have to help get you up to speed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sennheiser MOMENTUM True Wireless 3 Review: Good Sound, Poor Noise Cancellation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/122700/sennheiser-momentum-true-wireless-3-review/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/122700/sennheiser-momentum-true-wireless-3-review/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earbud manufacturers typically try to compete with their larger competitors by delivering unique features or a lower price point. Sennheiser, on the other hand, has taken a more head-on approach against its main competition with the MOMENTUM True Wireless 3. The results are decidedly mixed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Loguidice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Booting Linux On A Modern AMD Ryzen 6000 Series Laptop / ThinkPad X13 Gen3]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31308</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31308"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier this week Linux security researcher Matthew Garrett shared that Lenovo's newer AMD Rembrandt laptops with Microsoft's Pluton security co-processor would not boot Linux by default. The issue stems from the third-party UEFI certificate not being enabled by default and it turns out is something Microsoft is seemingly now enforcing. Fortunately, I had a Lenovo ThinkPad X13 Gen3 with Ryzen 7 PRO 6850U on the way and so was now able to test this experience under Linux.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get the Weather on Your Windows 11 Taskbar]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=818441</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/818441/how-to-get-the-weather-on-your-windows-11-taskbar/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know Windows 11 has a Windows 10-style weather widget for its taskbar? If you’ve been using Windows 11 since its release, you might be surprised about that! Here’s how to see the weather on your taskbar.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ASUS Zenbook: tre nuovi notebook OLED disponibili in Italia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=ASUS-Zenbook-tre-nuovi-notebook-OLED-disponibili-in-Italia_24777</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=ASUS-Zenbook-tre-nuovi-notebook-OLED-disponibili-in-Italia_24777"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T12:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ASUS ha annunciato la disponibilità nel nostro Paese di tre nuovi notebook della gamma Zenbook. Si tratta dello Zenbook Pro 16X OLED, il più potente di sempre; Zenbook S 13 OLED che offre massima portabilità, versatilità e potenza in solo 1 kg di peso; ASUS Zenbook 14 OLED, un prodotto che ambisce a diventare un vero e proprio punto di riferimento grazie alle performance di primo livello, a una portabilità estrema, al suono straordinario e design incentrato sull'utente.I laptop delle nuove gamme Zenbook Pro e Zenbook S sono tutti caratterizzati da un design nuovo e moderno e dai più recenti processori ad alte prestazioni Intel Core serie H e GPU NVIDIA GeForce RTX serie 30 nei modelli più costosi.Il look dei nuovi Zenbook è minimal e sofisticato, con bordi che rievocano diamanti con taglio a gradino e il nuovo logo ASUS in monogramma 'A' in rilievo sul telaio.ASUS ha collaborato con NVIDIA per portare tutti i vantaggi di NVIDIA Studio sui nuovi laptop Zenbook, comprese le ottimizzazioni software e i driver NVIDIA Studio preinstallati per migliorare le prestazioni e l'affidabilità di tutte le applicazioni creative preferite dagli utenti.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did You Know? Shift+Ctrl+Alt+Win+L Opens LinkedIn on Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=816348</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/816348/did-you-know-shiftctrlaltwinl-opens-linkedin-on-windows/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T12:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you press Ctrl+Alt+Shift+Win+L in Windows, your default browser opens and loads the LinkedIn social networking website. But why? We’ll get to the bottom of this mystery.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Failed to install packages to new root]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vzmbhk/failed_to_install_packages_to_new_root/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vzmbhk/failed_to_install_packages_to_new_root/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T11:25:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[when i use
 pacstrap /mnt base linux linux-firmware
 it shows me this error
 ​
 ** Please understand that i am a windows user i have no knowledge about Linux **
 Edit: unfortunately, i didn't find any solution for this problem, but i download a gui Edition From archinstallgui.in
    submitted by    /u/H2rw  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[grub: unable to boot root partition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vzmbej/grub_unable_to_boot_root_partition/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vzmbej/grub_unable_to_boot_root_partition/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T11:25:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HI everybody, I just installed archlinux and wanted to setup an encrypted root partition (with not encrypted boot). I followed the guide but when I reboot grub goes into rescue mode telling me:
 error: no such device: 55740d88-7246-4c78-b509-577ca218f96f grube rescue> 
 Relevant partitions:
 sda ├─sda1 ext4 1.0 BOOT 55740d88-7246-4c78-b509-577ca218f96f (unencrypted BOOT partition) └─sda2 crypto_LUKS 2 b7ac4924-bbea-44c5-a8ec-b832de1d6522 (encrypted ROOT partition) nvme0n1p1 vfat FAT32 F83B-B19A (EFI partition) 
 Here is my /etc/default/grub:
 # GRUB boot loader configuration GRUB_DEFAULT=0 GRUB_TIMEOUT=5 GRUB_DISTRIBUTOR="Arch" GRUB_CMDLINE_LINUX_DEFAULT="loglevel=3 cryptdevice=b7ac4924-bbea-44c5-a8ec-b832de1d6522:root root=/dev/mapper/root nvidia-drm.modeset=1" GRUB_CMDLINE_LINUX="" # Pre…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Little-Known Gmail Features You Should Try]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=813437</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/813437/gmail-features-you-should-try/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T11:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes you read about new features for applications you use daily, like Gmail, but forget to try them out. Before you know it, those features are no longer new, and fresher features get your attention. Here are several desktop Gmail features you might have missed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What can I do to try and fix extremely slow internet in Arch Linux?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vzlq06/what_can_i_do_to_try_and_fix_extremely_slow/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vzlq06/what_can_i_do_to_try_and_fix_extremely_slow/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T10:51:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So I just finished my first Linux installation outside of a virtualmachine, and I know Arch may not have been the best choice but out of all the ones I tried in VMs it is by far my favourite, but I have noticed that my computer gets extremely slow internet now.
 I've spent quite a few hours looking over reddit, stackoverflow and a lot of other websites and so far I have found not many things that have actually helped.
 Before I mention all the things that I have already tried, I'll just put in some basic information. So I am using the built in ethernet controller on the ASRock B450 Steel Legend motherboard, which is the RTL8111H controller. On windows, I get around 30Mbits/s but on Arch I could barely top 20kbits/s.
 So the first thing I tried was switching drivers. This is actually listed…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to grep Search for Filenames Instead of Content in Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?post_type=devops&amp;p=800697</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/devops/how-to-grep-search-for-filenames-instead-of-content-in-linux/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T10:40:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[grep is a Linux tool usually used for searching text files for specific content. However, it’s often useful to search directories for file names instead of file contents, and this can be done with grep and other Linux command line utilities]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Heddings</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come attivare una PEC gratis per sempre (in ricezione)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/07/come-attivare-una-pec-gratis-per-sempre.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/07/come-attivare-una-pec-gratis-per-sempre.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T10:36:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chi necessita di attivare una PEC per fare i concorsi pubblici o per contattare la pubblica amministrazione sa benissimo che non è possibile usufruire di una PEC totalmente gratuita, visto che i vari provider autorizzati si fanno pagare una quota annuale per poter mantenere la casella di posta elettronica certificata.
 Per fortuna Namirial ha deciso di andare contro corrente e di offrire, a tutti i possessori di SPID, la possibilità di attivare una casella PEC gratuita in ricezione, gratis per sempre e senza nessun costo nascosto (paghiamo solo eventuali invii ad un prezzo molto contenuto).
 Se siamo interessati ad attivare una PEC gratuita, siamo nella guida giusta: nei capitoli che seguono vi mostreremo cosa è SpidMail, quali sono i limiti di questa casella di posta elettronica e come at…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 12 in arrivo entro ottobre 2024: Microsoft passa ai rilasci triennali?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-12-in-arrivo-entro-ottobre-2024-Microsoft-passa-ai-rilasci-triennali_24776</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-12-in-arrivo-entro-ottobre-2024-Microsoft-passa-ai-rilasci-triennali_24776"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T10:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Con la pubblicazione della versione finale di Windows 11 il 5 ottobre 2021, Microsoft ha comunicato che non avrebbe più rilasciato due feature update l'anno. I feature update sono gli aggiornamenti per Windows che introducono anche nuove funzionalità nel sistema operativo.Sia per Windows 11 che per Windows 10, supportato fino al 14 ottobre 2025, Microsoft ha scelto per il rilascio di un solo feature update l'anno.Fonti vicine a Microsoft rivelano che questo schema di rilascio potrebbe cambiare a breve: l'azienda di Redmond sarebbe infatti intenzionata a distribuire una nuova versione di Windows ogni tre anni. Ciò confermerebbe l'ipotesi di un Windows 12 già in fase di sviluppo con la nuova major release del sistema operativo che potrebbe debuttare entro ottobre 2024, a distanza di tre anni esatti dal lancio di Windows 11.Cosa ne sarà dei feature update? Microsoft sarebbe intenzionata a puntare principalmente sul rilascio di aggiornamenti cumulativi attraverso Windows Update.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TUXEDO Computers Announces Water-Cooled Linux Laptop Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=TUXEDO-Aquaris-Linux-Water</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=TUXEDO-Aquaris-Linux-Water"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T09:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier this year TUXEDO Computers announced their Stellaris 15 Gen4 laptop that when stationary could be water-cooled using their TUXEDO Aquaris water-cooling solution. Oddly for this Bavarian Linux PC retailer that was a Windows-only feature, but today they have announced Linux support for this laptop water cooling solution...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xfce's Xfwm4 Sees Wayland Port With Wlroots]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Xfce-Xfway-wlroots-Wayland</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Xfce-Xfway-wlroots-Wayland"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T09:36:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer "adlo" announced to Wayland developers today the work on porting Xfce's Xfwm4 window manager code to Wayland and this new "Xfway" compositor is being brought up using the wlroots library that is becoming increasingly common among the smaller Wayland compositors...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[openSUSE Announces "First Class" Support For The Nim Programming Language]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=openSUSE-First-Class-Nim</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=openSUSE-First-Class-Nim"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T09:16:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The openSUSE project is talking up their first-class support for the Nim programming language in joining Arch Linux for shipping up-to-date packages for this compiled programming language...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Chrome non memorizza le password: come risolvere]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Google-Chrome-non-memorizza-le-password-come-risolvere_24775</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Google-Chrome-non-memorizza-le-password-come-risolvere_24775"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T09:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Come i principali browser concorrenti anche Chrome integra un password manager ovvero un modulo per la gestione delle credenziali di accesso ai siti Web via via visitati. Come nel caso degli altri browser, un utente con accesso fisico alla macchina può trovare le password salvate. Per questo il consiglio migliore è quello di proteggere i dati memorizzati su disco con BitLocker e un PIN all'avvio oppure servirsi di soluzioni alternative come VeraCrypt.Nulla vieta comunque a un programma malevolo in esecuzione sul sistema di recuperare le password da tutti i vari browser installati.Per questo motivo è bene orientarsi sull'utilizzo di programmi come Keepass e derivati per salvare in sicurezza nomi utente e password sincronizzandoli tra più dispositivi.Il gestore password di Chrome resta tuttavia uno degli strumenti più utilizzati per conservare le proprie credenziali e accedere velocemente su siti Web, servizi e applicazioni online.
Chrome non memorizza le password: cosa fare
 Ogni volta che si effettua un accesso su qualunque sito Web Chrome mostra un messaggio in alto a destra nell'interfaccia del browser con cui chiede se l'utente voglia memorizzare le credenziali in locale (Salva solo su questo dispositivo) oppure all'interno dell'account Google in uso.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IO_uring User-Space Block Driver Coming For Linux 5.20]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.20-User-Space-Block-Drv</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.20-User-Space-Block-Drv"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T09:05:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coming for the Linux 5.20 cycle is a IO_uring user-space block driver developed by a Red Hat engineer...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMDGPU Driver Reverting The Buddy Allocator For Linux 5.19]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMDGPU-Reverts-Buddy-Allocator</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMDGPU-Reverts-Buddy-Allocator"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T08:49:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AMDGPU kernel graphics driver had been preparing to make use of the buddy allocator started by the Intel Linux graphics driver. But now with today's batch of DRM fixes that AMDGPU support is being reverted for Linux 5.19 due to it causing garbled screens for some users...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Started Writing Helm Charts for Your Kubernetes Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?post_type=devops&amp;p=800698</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/devops/how-to-get-started-writing-helm-charts-for-your-kubernetes-applications/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T08:04:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Helm is a package manager for Kubernetes workloads. Creating a Helm chart for your application simplifies reproducible deployments into a Kubernetes cluster. Users can install the whole chart with one command, instead of manually applying individual component manifests with Kubectl.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung presenta le nuove memorie DRAM GDDR6 a 24 Gbps per le schede grafiche]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Samsung-presenta-le-nuove-memorie-DRAM-GDDR6-a-24-Gbps-per-le-schede-grafiche_24774</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Samsung-presenta-le-nuove-memorie-DRAM-GDDR6-a-24-Gbps-per-le-schede-grafiche_24774"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T08:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung ha annunciato di aver concluso lo sviluppo delle sue nuove memorie DRAM GDDR6 capaci di raggiungere una velocità di trasferimento dati di 24 Gbps.Una scheda grafica top di gamma che userà i nuovi chip Samsung potrà quindi assicurare una velocità di elaborazione dati fino a 1,1 Terabyte al secondo. Essa equivale all'elaborazione di 275 film con risoluzione Full HD in un secondo.Il colosso sudcoreano spiega che le DRAM GDDR6 sono composte da chip da 16 Gb che utilizzano il processo costruttivo a 10 nm di terza generazione. In fase di produzione è stato fatto ricorso alla litografia ultravioletta estrema (EUV) e ad alcune soluzioni architetturali per fare sì che il gate mantenga più carica.Samsung afferma che una soluzione del genere ha permesso di ottenere una DRAM di ultima generazione che funziona a una velocità superiore al 30% rispetto alla DRAM GDDR6 da 18 Gbps.La DRAM segue gli ultimi standard stabiliti dal JEDEC, l'organismo che si occupa della definizione degli standard per i chip di memoria, in modo che i fornitori di hardware per l'intelligenza artificiale e i produttori di acceleratori grafici possano servirsene facilmente nei loro prodotti.Samsung ha precisato di aver anche applicato la tecnica del dynamic voltage switching (DVS) per aumentare l'efficienza energetica della DRAM.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Attackers scan 1.6 million WordPress sites for vulnerable plugin]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/attackers-scan-16-million-wordpress-sites-for-vulnerable-plugin/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/attackers-scan-16-million-wordpress-sites-for-vulnerable-plugin/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T07:28:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security researchers have detected a massive campaign that scanned close to 1.6 million WordPress sites for the presence of a vulnerable plugin that allows uploading files without authentication. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Corrupted user journals, anyone?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vzhmnw/corrupted_user_journals_anyone/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vzhmnw/corrupted_user_journals_anyone/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T06:23:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm seeing a lot of corrupted journal files:
 Journal file /var/log/journal/592150cf5ad44523af127588741e363c/user-1000@c1c3d1e59afc4735b7e0ce6b9692359a-0000000000000000-0000000000000000.journal corrupted, ignoring file. 
 Before I start digging deeper and/or filing a bug, I'd like to know: anyone else currently experiencing this issue?
 The machine runs 24/7 so it's not a matter of file corruption due to unclean shutdown.
    submitted by    /u/lynix48  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do trim work on all partions that are in the fstab?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vzhi8v/do_trim_work_on_all_partions_that_are_in_the_fstab/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vzhi8v/do_trim_work_on_all_partions_that_are_in_the_fstab/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T06:15:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I replaced my dying HDD with an SSD in laptop.It's a 240GB one(222.6GB usable).Is it possible to create partition of 600mb(Boot),72GB(Root) and use the remaining 150GB to store my music collection and some movies?
 This is the how I've thought of mounting before generating fstab
 For / partition mount /dev/sda2 /mnt
 For efi partition mkdir -p /mnt/boot/efi mount /dev/sda1 /mnt/boot/efi
 Remaining 150GB mkdir -p /mnt/MyFiles mount /dev/sda3 /mnt/MyFiles
 swapfile Create a swapfile and add it to fstab.
 I know that SSD should always have 20% of free space.My main question is does trim work on all the partions in the fstab file or do i have to automount it(150GB partition) for fstrim.timer to work.
 Thanks in advance.
    submitted by    /u/mysuravnu  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Accelerate Docker Builds and Optimize Caching With “COPY –link”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?post_type=devops&amp;p=800706</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/devops/how-to-accelerate-docker-builds-and-optimize-caching-with-copy-link/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T06:02:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[COPY --link is a new BuildKit feature which could substantially accelerate your Docker image builds. It works by copying files into independent image layers that don’t rely on the presence of their predecessors. You can add new content to images without the base image even existing on your system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google releases Chrome OS Flex for PCs and Macs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179747</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/07/15/google-releases-chrome-os-flex-for-pcs-and-macs/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T04:48:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome OS Flex is a special version of Google's Chrome OS that is bringing the operating system to Windows PCs and Apple Macs. Several Windows and Mac operating systems will run out […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Google releases Chrome OS Flex for PCs and Macs appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Graphics issues , new Dell XPS 9720 with RTX 3050 graphics.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vzfot4/graphics_issues_new_dell_xps_9720_with_rtx_3050/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vzfot4/graphics_issues_new_dell_xps_9720_with_rtx_3050/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T04:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anyone have a similar setup that has working graphics? I know this is fairly new laptop and support is not the best on new stuff but i thought i would take a chance. I am having graphics issues where the screen does not refresh unless the mouse moves over the location, also when moving the mouse, i get wild glitchy graphics that produces horizontal lines across the whole screen and the screen sort of jumps all around. 
 Its got a UHD 3840 x 2400 touch screen if that may be causing issues too. 
 Anyone have a similar setup working, and what you might have done to get it working?
 Thanks.
    submitted by    /u/burrfree  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Live USB reboots midway during boot process]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vzdjj7/live_usb_reboots_midway_during_boot_process/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vzdjj7/live_usb_reboots_midway_during_boot_process/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T02:40:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/betacollector64  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PSA: libnotify update breaks gnome-tweaks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vzc13m/psa_libnotify_update_breaks_gnometweaks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vzc13m/psa_libnotify_update_breaks_gnometweaks/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T01:25:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Workaround and bug report
    submitted by    /u/ukbeast89  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What i need instead of a DM ?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vzbaj9/what_i_need_instead_of_a_dm/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vzbaj9/what_i_need_instead_of_a_dm/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T00:48:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So, i have my arch vanilla installed. What do i need instead of installing a desktop environment ?
 - File Manager (Caja, Thunar, Nautilus etc.)
 - Status Bar (Polybar, i3bar etc.)
 - Terminal (Kitty, Alacritty etc.)
 - Window Manager (i3, sway, xmonad etc.)
 - Display manager (nodm for example)
 (+ X11, graphic driver, compositor and apps but don't mind for that)
 Do i miss something to make the system work properly on GUI ?
    submitted by    /u/Geomian  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 Sites and Extensions to Make Google Maps Even Better]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=496280</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15432068/extensions-sites-for-google-maps"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Maps is by far the most popular online mapping service used today. People love how easily they can look up directions or search around a specific location. On top of that, Google Maps is now also integrated with many other popular sites and services we use. However, there are ways to make Google Maps even better with these eight extensions and websites.
   

Content

1. Routora (Chrome Extension)
2. Scribble Maps (Website)
3. Google Maps Select and Search (Extension)
4. Top-Rated Online (Website)
5. EZ Maps (Website)
6. Snazzy Maps (Website)
7. Send To Google Maps (Extension)
8. Fuel Cost for Google Maps (Extension)
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:12 of the Best Google Maps Alternatives You Should Try
    
1. Routora (Chrome Extension)
    
If you plan out a multi-stop trip within Google Maps, it will only give... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Megan Glosson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can't access encrypted root after full system upgrade.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vz9ovq/cant_access_encrypted_root_after_full_system/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vz9ovq/cant_access_encrypted_root_after_full_system/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T23:31:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Took a picture.
 Did a full system upgrade, rebooted, and now whenever I enter the passphrase, this happens.
 All I have to possibly access and fix this is a ventoy drive with an arch iso.
    submitted by    /u/skqstns  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More Radeon RDNA3 Enablement, SubVP Feature Added To AMDGPU For Linux 5.20]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=More-RDNA3-SubVP-Linux-5.20</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=More-RDNA3-SubVP-Linux-5.20"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T23:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A final batch of feature updates for the AMDGPU/AMDKFD drivers were mailed in this afternoon to DRM-Next for queuing ahead of the Linux 5.20 merge window opening later this month...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft links Holy Ghost ransomware operation to North Korean hackers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-links-holy-ghost-ransomware-operation-to-north-korean-hackers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-links-holy-ghost-ransomware-operation-to-north-korean-hackers/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T23:10:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For more than a year, North Korean hackers have been running a ransomware operation called HolyGhost, attacking small businesses in various countries. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Ilascu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Holy Ghost ransomware operation linked to North Korean hackers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/holy-ghost-ransomware-operation-linked-to-north-korean-hackers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/holy-ghost-ransomware-operation-linked-to-north-korean-hackers/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T23:10:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For more than a year, North Korean hackers have been running a ransomware operation called HolyGhost, attacking small businesses in various countries. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Ilascu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 8 Xbox Accessories You Can’t Live Without]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=283887</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/10948201/best-xbox-one-x-accessories"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s tough to choose the best Xbox accessories, as there are many peripherals and accessories that are compatible with your Xbox. You can choose from various headsets, gaming monitors, hard drive, and more to make your console gaming experience better. If you’re looking for the best Xbox accessories, this list covers a variety of options to help you choose.
   

Content

1. Xbox One Elite Wireless Controller Series 2
2. SteelSeries Arctis 1 Wireless for Xbox
3. Asus ROG Strix Xbox Edition Gaming Monitor XG43UQ 43”
4. Toshiba Canvio Basics 1TB
5. Razer Universal Quick Charging Stand for Xbox
6. Xbox Live Gold Subscription
7. Turtle Beach Battle Buds In-Ear Gaming Headset
8. Logitech G920 Driving Force Racing Wheel for Xbox One
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Connect an Xbox One Controller to Your Android Device
    
1.... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Natalie dela Vega</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Fuel-Efficient Routes in Google Maps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=761925</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/761925/how-to-use-fuel-efficient-routes-in-google-maps/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are a couple of things to consider when choosing a navigation route: Which one will be the fastest? Which one is the fewest miles? Google Maps can also show you which route will save the most gas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google and Android App Developers Are Fighting, and We’re Losing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=818439</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/818439/google-and-android-app-developers-are-fighting/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T20:28:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Epic Games’ legal battles with Apple and Google over in-app purchases in Fortnite have been ongoing since August 2020. Over the past few months, more companies have pushed back against Google, impacting how people can (or can’t) spend money in Android apps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Minecraft is crushing so much in Arch Linux?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vz5gxy/why_minecraft_is_crushing_so_much_in_arch_linux/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vz5gxy/why_minecraft_is_crushing_so_much_in_arch_linux/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T20:25:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Minecraft lately crushes all the time i think it may be a RAM issue but one time i had Minecraft opened and I changed a setting and it crushed right away. If anyone knows a solution please help.
    submitted by    /u/Axolotl_King2007  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Laptop freezes when doing startx with i3]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vz5fpe/laptop_freezes_when_doing_startx_with_i3/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vz5fpe/laptop_freezes_when_doing_startx_with_i3/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T20:24:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've tried installing arch ~5 times using archinstall and 2 times manually. I'm using an NVIDIA RTX3050 mobile so that's probably the culprit.
 Xorg logs don't show anything peculiar. Journalctl also shows completely normal logs. Using nvidia-xconfig does nothing. Deleting /etc/X11/xorg.conf does nothing. Deleting the entire /etc/X11/xorg.d/ does nothing. Following the wiki about using an NVIDIA card for everything without care of power does nothing. (did everything word for word as was suggested in the wiki 2 times with no luck).
 Anyway, doing startx freezes my laptop and the fans ramp up. I also tried just leaving it like that for an hour with no change. Only the poweroff button has any effect (shell complains that it doesn't understand the input). I still couldn't get any inputs in. For example, ctrl+alt+fx did nothing.
 I've installed arch ~10 times in virtual machines and different desktops and laptops. I've used arch for years and I've never seen anything like this. Google doesn't give any helpful results either. I tried every possible fix the first two google pages recommended. I've never dealt with NVIDIA cards so I believe this is something exclusive to them.
 Also, I'm using an Acer Nitro 5 with an RTX3050 and an 11th gen i5 CPU if that has anything to do with this issue.
 If anyone has a fix or could help me, please let me know. I would hate to install an inferior, glowing operating system to my laptop.
    submitted by    /u/_Meisteri  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A solution to mce hardware error reboots on AMD hardware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vz5apu/a_solution_to_mce_hardware_error_reboots_on_amd/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vz5apu/a_solution_to_mce_hardware_error_reboots_on_amd/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T20:18:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So, this seems to be a common issue on AMD hardware on Linux and I haven't really found a post on the internet that describes a clear cause and solution for this issue, so I decided to make this post.
 First, I want to describe the issue. If under gaming load, your PC randomly reboots due to an error similar to this:
 Jul 13 20:35:56 archlinux kernel: mce: [Hardware Error]: Machine check events logged Jul 13 20:35:56 archlinux kernel: mce: [Hardware Error]: CPU 0: Machine Check: 0 Bank 27: faa000000000080b Jul 13 20:35:56 archlinux kernel: mce: [Hardware Error]: TSC 0 MISC d012000200000000 SYND 5d000000 IPID 1002e00000500 Jul 13 20:35:56 archlinux kernel: mce: [Hardware Error]: PROCESSOR 2:a20f10 TIME 1657740954 SOCKET 0 APIC 0 microcode a201016 Jul 13 20:35:57 archlinux kernel: MCE: In-ke…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Find Your Windows 10 Product Key Using the Command Prompt]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=660517</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/660517/how-to-find-your-windows-10-product-key-using-the-command-prompt/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re looking for your Windows 10 product key, you can find it by entering a quick command in the Command Prompt. Here’s how—plus a neat little trick for finding the product key using a Windows Registry method.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marshall Gunnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[wxWidgets 3.2 update may need manual intervention]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vz48m3/wxwidgets_32_update_may_need_manual_intervention/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vz48m3/wxwidgets_32_update_may_need_manual_intervention/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T19:32:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/my_coll_cont_bot  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save $300 on a Gigabyte G5 GD Gaming Laptop with Windows 11 Home]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=505971</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15431755/gigabyte-g5-gd-gaming-laptop-2"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are certain things you need when gaming, and the Gigabyte G5 GD Gaming Laptop has it. It even has things you’d desire but don’t need, such as Windows 11 Home. While Amazon Prime Days are over, this deal is still running hot, saving you $300.
    
The laptop does more than just partner with you in your gaming – it’s also great for working, streaming TV and movies, and more. Its 10th Gen Intel Core i5 processor helps you multitask, whether you’re working or just having fun. You can record your gaming with other apps running in the background. And of course, let’s not forget that you also get Windows 11 Home built in.
   
 
   
NVIDIA’s 2nd gen RTX powers this Gigabyte gaming laptop, with the RTX 30 Series laptop GPUs providing support for real-time ray tracing to bring a high-quality rendering into your gaming. The GPUs in the Gigabyte laptop also bring AI rendering that boosts frame rates.
    
The 15.6″ 144Hz screen helps you see everything smoothly in... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[wxWidgets 3.2 update may need manual intervention]]></title>
        <id>tag:archlinux.org,2022-07-14:/news/wxwidgets-32-update-may-need-manual-intervention/</id>
        <link href="https://archlinux.org/news/wxwidgets-32-update-may-need-manual-intervention/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T19:20:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[wxWidgets 3.2 provides a Qt frontend in addition to the GTK3 one, so packages have been renamed from wxgtk- to wxwidgets-.
The GTK2 frontend is no longer provided. If you have wxgtk2 installed, the upgrade will fail with
error: failed to prepare transaction (could not satisfy dependencies)
:: removing wxgtk-common breaks dependency 'wxgtk-common' required by wxgtk2
In such case, uninstall wxgtk2 first and then proceed with the upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antonio Rojas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Copy a Formula in Microsoft Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=810735</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/810735/how-to-copy-a-formula-in-excel/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T19:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’d like to use the same formula across multiple cells, copy the formula instead of typing it individually in each cell. You can use both dynamic cell reference and absolute cell reference while doing this, and we’ll show you how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch Linux and Linux Live Kit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vz383b/arch_linux_and_linux_live_kit/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vz383b/arch_linux_and_linux_live_kit/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T18:48:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi all! Sorry if my post was sent to the wrong reddit, but I have a question. Can I make my distribution on Arch Linux using Linux Live Kit? Has anyone checked?
    submitted by    /u/egor8799  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oh GuC: Intel ADL-P Graphics On Linux 5.19 Will Break Unless You Also Upgrade Firmware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=GuC-Firmware-ADL-P-Linux-5.19</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=GuC-Firmware-ADL-P-Linux-5.19"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T18:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a public service announcement for those who already have bought an Alder Lake P laptop or thinking of getting one, with kernel upgrades you need to be cautious/aware now of breaking accelerated graphics support due to versioned firmware requirements around the GuC micro-controller. While I am surprised Linus Torvalds allows this or wonder if he even is aware of it given his past statements on Linux kernel updates not breaking user-space, the Intel GuC firmware handling being versioned and not supporting backwards compatibility can throw a wrench into your upgrade experience like with the upcoming Linux 5.19 kernel...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung Galaxy S21 Owners Report Audio Cutouts on Verizon Networks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/123172/samsung-galaxy-s21-owners-report-audio-cutouts-on-verizon-networks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/123172/samsung-galaxy-s21-owners-report-audio-cutouts-on-verizon-networks/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T18:09:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If calls keep cutting in and out on your Samsung Galaxy S21, you’re not alone. Dozens of Galaxy S21 owners report audio cutouts on Verizon networks, and according to Verizon’s tech support, the problem is “widespread.” Some AT&T and T-Mobile customers also seem to experience this issue, though not to the degree of Verizon users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PayPal phishing kit added to hacked WordPress sites for full ID theft]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/paypal-phishing-kit-added-to-hacked-wordpress-sites-for-full-id-theft/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/paypal-phishing-kit-added-to-hacked-wordpress-sites-for-full-id-theft/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T18:09:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A newly discovered phishing kit targeting PayPal users is trying to steal a large set of personal information from victims that includes government identification documents and photos. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Format a USB Drive on Linux That Works With Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=810669</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/810669/how-to-format-a-usb-drive-on-linux-that-works-with-windows/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T18:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes Linux users need to exchange files with computers running other operating systems, such as Windows or macOS. That’s simple enough with a USB drive—as long as it is formatted correctly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKay</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel Core i7 1280P "Alder Lake P" Linux Laptop Performance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31299</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31299"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Launched earlier this year was Alder Lake P series for modern Intel laptops with up to 14 cores / 20 threads for modern Intel laptops. Many Phoronix readers have been inquiring about Alder Lake laptop support and performance under Linux and recently I finally got my hands on an Alder Lake P device in the form of the MSI Prestige 14Evo A12M-231 that features the flagship ADL-P model of the Core i7 1280P. Today's article is focused on the Linux performance of that flagship Core i7 1280P compared to other AMD and Intel laptop processors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Return Amazon Items Painlessly]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/123157/how-to-return-amazon-items-painlessly/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/123157/how-to-return-amazon-items-painlessly/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T17:50:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Purchasing items on Amazon is about as easy as it gets, but it’s not always as simple to return Amazon orders. So, here are the best ways: whether you made an impulse buy on Prime Day or Black Friday or need to return an Amazon order without a box.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux Mint 21 "Vanessa" Beta Released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-Mint-21-Beta</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-Mint-21-Beta"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T17:30:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Out today is the beta of the upcoming Linux Mint 21 "Vanessa" desktop-oriented Linux distribution that is built off Ubuntu 22.04 LTS...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome OS su vecchi PC e Mac con il nuovo progetto Google]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Chrome-OS-su-vecchi-PC-e-Mac-con-il-nuovo-progetto-Google_24145</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Chrome-OS-su-vecchi-PC-e-Mac-con-il-nuovo-progetto-Google_24145"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T17:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A dicembre 2020 Google aveva annunciato l'acquisizione di Cloudready, un progetto che permetteva di installare Chrome OS su PC e Mac. I detrattori avevano ipotizzato un'imminente chiusura del progetto da parte di Google, probabilmente non disposta a tollerare un'iniziativa come quella portata innanzi dagli sviluppatori di Neverware.In realtà Cloudready non soltanto non è morto ma da oggi evolve in un progetto di più ampio respiro. Chiamato Chrome OS Flex si tratta di una nuova versione del sistema operativo Google espressamente progettata per le aziende e per le scuole.Chrome OS Flex ricalca il funzionamento di Chrome OS su un Chromebook con la differenza che esso nasce come piattaforma installabile su vecchi PC e Mac.Come sottolinea Google il sistema può essere 'installato in pochi minuti' e permette di ridare vita a computer ormai superati.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTG Deals: Google Pixel 6 Pro Hits Lowest Price Ever, Plus More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=818428</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/818428/htg-deals-google-pixel-6-pro-hits-lowest-price-ever-plus-more/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T17:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Only two days remain in Amazon’s Prime Day sales extravaganza, and we’ve got the details on the hottest items you can buy right now. Click to claim the most savings ever on the Google Pixel 6 Pro, and enjoy additional deals on a Nest Wi-Fi bundle, one of our favorite smart TVs of the year, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zach Laidlaw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome and Firefox Killed FTP Support: Here’s an Easy Alternative]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=744569</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/744569/chrome-and-firefox-killed-ftp-support-heres-an-easy-alternative/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T17:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you rely on Google Chrome or Mozilla Firefox to browse FTP sites, you may have noticed that it doesn’t work anymore. Both browsers disabled their built-in FTP clients in 2021. Here’s why—and what you can do instead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LinkedIn: chi ha visitato il profilo e come navigare in privato]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=LinkedIn-chi-ha-visitato-il-profilo-e-come-navigare-in-privato_24773</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=LinkedIn-chi-ha-visitato-il-profilo-e-come-navigare-in-privato_24773"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T16:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LinkedIn è il social network acquisito da Microsoft a metà 2016 che viene ampiamente utilizzato soprattutto per sviluppare una rete di contatti professionali e diffondere contenuti relativi al mondo del lavoro.Secondo Statista nel 2021 erano registrati su LinkedIn circa 775 milioni di utenti a livello mondiale: entro il 2025, stando alle stime, verrà superato il miliardo di utenti.Chi utilizza LinkedIn avrà certamente notato che la piattaforma informa sugli utenti che visitano il proprio profilo. Accedendo alla pagina Chi ha visitato il tuo profilo? LinkedIn mostra nomi, cognomi e informazioni principali di ogni utente che ha consultato la pagina.La stessa pagina Chi ha visitato il tuo profilo? è accessibile cliccando sulla propria immagine quindi selezionando Visualizzazioni del profilo nel riquadro Analisi.Nel piano di abbonamento base LinkedIn mostra solo alcuni degli utenti che accedono al contenuto del profilo; per ottenere la lista completa viene chiesto di attrivare un abbonamento Premium a pagamento.LinkedIn non permette più di accedere ai profili di altri utenti senza aver prima effettuato il login sulla piattaforma utilizzando un account valido.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rimuovere programmi preinstallati e bloatware su Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/07/rimuovere-programmi-preinstallati-e.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/07/rimuovere-programmi-preinstallati-e.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T16:35:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In commercio troviamo ancora molti notebook con Windows 11 dotati di programmi preinstallati dal produttore del computer, spesso totalmente inutili e fastidiosi (visto che si avviano insieme al sistema operativo). Anche se il computer è nuovo e veloce, conviene agire subito rimuovendo i programmi preinstallati e le app catalogate come bloatware su Windows 11, utilizzando sia la procedura di...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome OS Flex Exits Early Access, Offering Upgrades for More PCs and Macs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/123126/chrome-os-flex-exits-early-access-offering-upgrades-for-more-pcs-and-macs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/123126/chrome-os-flex-exits-early-access-offering-upgrades-for-more-pcs-and-macs/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T16:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After just a few months of Early Access, the Chrome OS Flex software is graduating to Google’s “stable” release channel. It’s now certified for over 400 devices, and businesses hit by ransomware can now join a “rapid release program” to install Chrome OS flex on affected machines without losing access to Windows apps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome OS Flex Is Ready to Turn Old PCs Into Chromebooks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=818187</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/818187/chrome-os-flex-is-ready-to-turn-old-pcs-into-chromebooks/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T16:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google released the first preview version of Chrome OS Flex earlier this year, which is a customized build of Chrome OS that can run on traditional PCs (and some old Mac computers). Starting today, Chrome OS Flex is ready for everyone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Compress Videos on Android]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=816550</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/816550/how-to-compress-videos-on-android/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s pretty awesome to have the ability to record 4K videos with your Android phone, but sometimes the highest quality is just too much. To reduce the size of a video, your best option is to compress it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bridget Todd, the new host of Mozilla’s IRL podcast, on online communities, The X-Files & raising marginalized voices]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.mozilla.org/?p=69385</id>
        <link href="https://blog.mozilla.org/en/mozilla/bridget-todd-irl-podcast-host-interview/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here at Mozilla, we are the first to admit the internet isn’t perfect, but we are also quick to point out that the internet is pretty darn magical. The internet opens up doors and opportunities, allows for people to connect with others, and lets everyone find where they belong — their corners of the internet. […]
The post Bridget Todd, the new host of Mozilla’s IRL podcast, on online communities, The X-Files & raising marginalized voices appeared first on The Mozilla Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rebecca Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save Up To 44% on Roborock’s Robot Vacuums Through Prime Day]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=815542</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/815542/save-up-to-44-on-roborocks-robot-vacuums-through-prime-day/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T15:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon’s Prime Day sales extravaganza is well underway, and our friends at Roborock have unleashed their own torrent of discounts for your buying pleasure. Valid through July 16, you can save up to 44% on some of the hottest robot vacuums on the planet, but each sale happens during specific days, so be watchful as you seek out your savings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zach Laidlaw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mantis botnet behind the record-breaking DDoS attack in June]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/mantis-botnet-behind-the-record-breaking-ddos-attack-in-june/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/mantis-botnet-behind-the-record-breaking-ddos-attack-in-june/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T15:53:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The record-breaking distributed denial-of-service (DDoS) attack that Cloudflare mitigated last month originated from a new botnet called Mantis, which is currently described as "the most powerful botnet to date." [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rivian Isn't Interested In Bringing Android Auto or CarPlay to Its EVs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/123153/rivian-isnt-interested-in-bringing-android-auto-or-carplay-to-its-evs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/123153/rivian-isnt-interested-in-bringing-android-auto-or-carplay-to-its-evs/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T15:48:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re waiting for Rivian to announce Android Auto and Apple CarPlay support, don’t hold your breath. In an email to a customer, Rivian explains that its bespoke software platform is “the better path,” and that future updates will focus on improving the current Rivian software experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 Insider Preview Build 25158 introduces a large Search the Web shortcut on the Taskbar]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179715</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/07/14/windows-11-insider-preview-build-25158/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T15:47:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 Insider Preview Build 25158 has been released for testers who have opted in to the Developer Channel of the Insider Program. It introduces a couple of controversial changes to the […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Windows 11 Insider Preview Build 25158 introduces a large Search the Web shortcut on the Taskbar appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The M2 MacBook Air Shares the New MacBook Pro’s SSD Problem]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=818350</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/818350/the-m2-macbook-air-shares-the-new-macbook-pros-ssd-problem/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T15:41:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple revealed the new MacBook Air during last month’s WWDC event, with a larger screen, faster M2 chip, and a MagSafe connector. However, it does fall short of the model it replaced in one critical area: the SSD.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rumor: Microsoft plans to release new major Windows versions every three years]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179743</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/07/14/rumor-microsoft-plans-to-release-new-major-windows-versions-every-three-years/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T15:33:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The following information needs to be taken with a grain of salt, as it has not been confirmed by Microsoft at this point. According to Windows Central,  Microsoft plans to move from […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Rumor: Microsoft plans to release new major Windows versions every three years appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rocky Linux 9.0 Released As Free RHEL 9.0 Alternative]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Rocky-Linux-9.0-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Rocky-Linux-9.0-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T15:30:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rocky Linux 9.0 was officially released today that joins the likes of AlmaLinux 9.0 and Oracle Linux 9.0 as free alternatives to Red Hat Enterprise Linux 9.0...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make Your Android Phone Look Like a Google Pixel Without Rooting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=170374</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/4904802/turn-android-device-to-google-pixel"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Pixel phones run stock Android with minimal customizations as to give users the purest Android experience possible. In contrast, a lot of Android phones come with customized skin (such as MIUI, One UI, and ColorOS etc) which tend to irritate a lot of users. While you can’t change these skins without rooting, you can still make your Android phone look like a Google Pixel, with the help of a few third-party apps, widgets, and launchers. It’s pretty easy to do, so follow along in this guide to learn how.
   

Content

Advantages of the Google Pixel Interface
Things to Know Before Turning Your Android Phone into a Pixel
1. Download and Install a Third-Party Launcher
2. Install a Material-Based Icon Pack
3. Get the Google Feed
4. Set Google Wallpapers
5. Download Google Apps (optional)
6. Get Pixel Exclusive Goodies
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Customize Your Android’s... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anurag</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hyundai Ioniq 6 Doubles as a "Mobile Studio" and Packs Plenty of Range]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/123149/hyundai-ioniq-6-doubles-as-a-mobile-studio-and-packs-plenty-of-range/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/123149/hyundai-ioniq-6-doubles-as-a-mobile-studio-and-packs-plenty-of-range/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T15:24:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week Hyundai hosted its global premiere event for the Ioniq 6 electric vehicle, and there’s a lot to like. The South Korean brand revealed several impressive specs, including its Tesla-challenging range, not to mention a “personal mobile studio” inside that’ll double as a home office.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Archinstall command]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vyy289/archinstall_command/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vyy289/archinstall_command/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T15:05:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello I’ve followed the instructions from the arch linux website to install arch with the command “archinstall” and when I finish installing it with the command and rebooted nothing happened, i was expected to load the grub menu and it didn’t work 🤦🏻‍♂️. Did i do something wrong? I’ve the instructions and didn’t work☹️
    submitted by    /u/RevolutionaryLunch28  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Does My Wi-Fi Keep Going Out?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=811903</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/811903/why-does-my-wi-fi-keep-going-out/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Inconsistent Wi-Fi performance is a frustrating problem to have. With so many variables, it can be hard to know where to begin. Here are some things you can try to rid yourself of dropouts and unresponsive wireless networking.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix's Cheaper Membership Is Coming Soon, Courtesy of Microsoft]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/123147/netflixs-cheaper-membership-is-coming-soon-courtesy-of-microsoft/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/123147/netflixs-cheaper-membership-is-coming-soon-courtesy-of-microsoft/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T14:43:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After losing a massive number of subscribers earlier this year, Netflix is finally trying to launch a cheaper ad-supported plan. And the streaming service is fast-tracking this new membership tier with a new advertising partner—Microsoft.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I've created an AUR package for Gnome mutter with screen auto-rotation fixed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vyxezb/ive_created_an_aur_package_for_gnome_mutter_with/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vyxezb/ive_created_an_aur_package_for_gnome_mutter_with/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T14:37:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you have a "2-in-1" style laptop (like Lenovo Yoga), and is missing that feature, feel free to check it out. I'm using the package for some months now and didn't have any problems.
 Reasoning for the package is the first pinned comment in AUR.
 https://aur.archlinux.org/packages/mutter-auto-rotation
    submitted by    /u/parcimonic  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migliori router con copertura Wi-Fi massima]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/07/migliori-router-con-copertura-wi-fi.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/07/migliori-router-con-copertura-wi-fi.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T14:34:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chi possiede una casa molto grande (anche su più piani) sa quando sia difficile trovare un modem o un router in grado di coprire una casa di dimensioni superiori ai 120 metri quadrati. In questi scenari dovremo spesso puntare su ripetitori Wi-Fi, Powerline o altri trucchi per portare Internet in tutte le stanze, mantenendo una buona velocità di connessione ovunque ci troviamo. 
Per fortuna sono...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Retbleed: cos'è la nuova falla di sicurezza presente nei processori Intel e AMD]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Retbleed-cos-e-la-nuova-falla-di-sicurezza-presente-nei-processori-Intel-e-AMD_24772</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Retbleed-cos-e-la-nuova-falla-di-sicurezza-presente-nei-processori-Intel-e-AMD_24772"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T14:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A inizio 2018 la scoperta di alcune vulnerabilità di sicurezza battezzate Spectre e Meltdown ha fatto da apripista per i successivi attacchi side channel che fanno leva su tutta una serie di debolezze delle moderne CPU. Queste lacune di sicurezza hanno portato i ricercatori a intensificare gli studi sul funzionamento dei processori: negli anni seguenti sono infatti venute a galla molteplici vulnerabilità alle quali i produttori hardware e software hanno risposto in maniera differente.Sono state infatti realizzate patch che agiscono a livello di microcodice, kernel, driver, sistema operativo e persino lato applicativo per ridurre al minimo la superficie di attacco.In mancanza delle patch correttive, un aggressore che interagisce con i meccanismi di branch prediction della CPU o misura il tempo di esecuzione delle istruzioni in alcuni casi può recuperare dati personali e informazioni riservate, comprese password e chiavi di decodifica.Per lungo tempo (e in parte ancora oggi) gli attacchi come Spectre, Meltdown così come tutte le varianti successivamente emerse, sono stati considerati di grande interesse ma di scarsa valenza pratica.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 Might Get the Search Bar From Windows 10]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=818338</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/818338/windows-11-might-get-the-search-bar-from-windows-10/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T14:26:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has been testing a few possible design changes for Windows 11 recently, such as widgets on the desktop, and now the company is experimenting with bringing back a feature from Windows 10.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch takes way longer than normal to boot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vyx571/arch_takes_way_longer_than_normal_to_boot/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vyx571/arch_takes_way_longer_than_normal_to_boot/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T14:25:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since yesterday, my Arch machine takes more than 3 minutes to boot, when it usually booted in under 20 seconds. The system still boots fine, but it gets stuck for most of the boot process in "A start job is running for Wait for udev To Complete Device Initialization (58s 2min 59s)", which then fails and the boot process finishes and the login screen pops up.
 Screenshots: https://www.reddit.com/r/u_MonkeEnthusiast8420/comments/vyx3p1/screenshots/
    submitted by    /u/MonkeEnthusiast8420  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Audiobooks to Make You Smarter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/122066/10-audiobooks-to-make-you-smarter/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/122066/10-audiobooks-to-make-you-smarter/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T14:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I read a lot of audiobooks, usually two or three a week. I’ve waded through reams of questionable analysis, mediocre prose, and unsatisfying conclusions. But, I occasionally come across a book that blows my mind and think it was all worth it for that knowledge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Chadwick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>