<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-06-27T02:03:37.348Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Debugging Your AWS Bill With Cost Explorer and Billing Tags]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?post_type=devops&amp;p=800740</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/devops/debugging-your-aws-bill-with-cost-explorer-and-billing-tags/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T01:48:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS’s billing is notoriously complicated, and misconfigurations in your network can lead to excess data or resource use that can pile up unnoticed. AWS provides many solutions for debugging your bill before it hits your wallet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Heddings</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Losing permissions on external disks.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vljpyh/losing_permissions_on_external_disks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vljpyh/losing_permissions_on_external_disks/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T01:33:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the title say, I am consistantly losing permission to write on any external disks, even those formated with the system. Only started doing that about a week ago, and even with sudo I can change permissions.
 Any clue what could be the "root" cause of this ?
 Edit: I have 3 computers all running Archlinux, and an Ipad, I have a suspission that the Ipad has something to do with it since it was only recently added to the house and I have been using my portable drives with it too.
    submitted by    /u/Bender248  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Plex Media Server "target not found" even though Multilib is enabled (Arch 5.18.6-arch1-1)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlgvfj/plex_media_server_target_not_found_even_though/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlgvfj/plex_media_server_target_not_found_even_though/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T23:03:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello!
 I switched to Arch as my 24/7 OS about 2 weeks ago, I've had Plex Media Server installed as a snap package and it was causing issues so I removed it and now im trying to download PMS through the AUR. I know multilib is required so I went into my pacman.conf and enabled them...
 # If you want to run 32 bit applications on your x86_64 system, enable the multilib repositories as required here. [multilib-testing] Include = /etc/pacman.d/mirrorlist [multilib] Include = /etc/pacman.d/mirrorlist 
 Afterward I ran pacman -Syu to update everything, went to do pacman -S plex-media-server and it comes up with...
 error: target not found: plex-media-server 
 Even though its RIGHT HERE in the AUR. https://aur.archlinux.org/packages/plex-media-server
 I am stumped. I can find no other steps people have had to take other than enabling multilib and pacman-ing "plex-media-server". In fact thats exactly how I did it on Manjaro a few months ago.
 Any help would be appreciated.
    submitted by    /u/bactaholic  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Custom ISOs?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlgpym/how_to_build_custom_isos/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlgpym/how_to_build_custom_isos/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T22:56:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I wanted to try building my own ISO to more easily install Arch and my software without using archinstall or doing it manually, but everything I try just keeps failing. I've tried using archiso, tried using some old programs like Linux Live Kit and I even tried building Arcolinux ISOs because they're supposed to be "easier". I also (obviously) read the wiki pages for building ISOs and older Reddit posts on the topic, but it still is extremely confusing and I don't really know what I'm doing wrong, I just followed the wiki and later some tutorial videos on the subject. I consider myself an advanced user and have been using Linux for the past two years as my main OS. 
 I wanted an Arch ISO running Cinnamon with some custom themes, pamac and the Calamares Installer. Do you have any suggestions on where to begin my search, like more documentation, tutorial videos or the like?
    submitted by    /u/AugustBrasilien  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Problem with wifi keeps disconnecting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlftdc/problem_with_wifi_keeps_disconnecting/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlftdc/problem_with_wifi_keeps_disconnecting/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T22:11:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently I have had this issue with wifi, it keeps disconnecting and reconnecting. I tried switching to networkmanager from iwd, but that didn’t help
 this is what journalctl is saying
  Jun 20 11:10:39 nyly-arch kernel: Linux version 5.15.48-1-lts (linux-lts@archlinux) (gcc (GCC) 12.1.0, GNU ld (GNU Binutils) 2.38) #1 SMP Thu, 16 Jun> Jun 20 11:10:39 nyly-arch kernel: Command line: BOOT_IMAGE=/boot/vmlinuz-linux-lts root=UUID=39713201-b74b-4c19-8f53-aace43e5c1c2 rw loglevel=3 quiet Jun 20 11:10:39 nyly-arch kernel: x86/fpu: Supporting XSAVE feature 0x001: 'x87 floating point registers' Jun 20 11:10:39 nyly-arch kernel: x86/fpu: Supporting XSAVE feature 0x002: 'SSE registers' Jun 20 11:10:39 nyly-arch kernel: x86/fpu: Supporting XSAVE feature 0x004: 'AVX registers' Jun 20 11:10:39 nyly-arc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux 5.19-c4 - A Bit Bigger, Also Fixes A Previously Reported Performance Regression]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-rc4-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-rc4-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T22:07:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linus Torvalds just released Linux 5.19-rc4 as the newest weekly test candidate. There are more patches this week than in the prior Linux 5.19-rc versions but nothing too scary as well as having some notable patches in tow...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Connecting to internet during installation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlfmyu/connecting_to_internet_during_installation/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlfmyu/connecting_to_internet_during_installation/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T22:02:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I need some help conecting to the internet during the installation process. I ran the command Iwctl device list but it just showed an empty table. Acording to ip link, the system detects the wlan0 adapter but for some reason i'm not able to connect to it. Any help would be greatly appreciated.
 Ip link:wlan0:
 <NO-CARRIER,BROADCAST,MULTICAST,UP> mtu 1500 qdisc fq_code1 state DOWN mode DEFAULT group default qlen 1000 link/ether brd ff:ff:ff:ff:ff:ff
 lsusb | grep WLAN:
 Realtek Semiconductor Corp. RTL8191SU 802.11n WLAN Adapter
    submitted by    /u/veganbtw6969  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come evitare le tre domande di sicurezza quando create un account locale]]></title>
        <id>3607|20220627000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/password-174/come-evitare-tre-domande-sicurezza-quando-create-account-locale-3607"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quando create un account locale in un computer, e gli mettete una password, siete obbligati a scegliere tre domande e risposte per il recupero della password quando la dimenticate. Il problema è che queste domande/risposte, a meno di scriverle da qualche parte, dopo cinque minuti dal loro inserimento è probabile che le avrete dimenticate se avete inserito dei dati a caso, se invece utilizzate delle risposte vere, fornendo dei dati personali, non va bene perché possono essere recuperati anche da altre persone che hanno accesso a quel computer.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best alternative to MuQSS?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlf5jo/best_alternative_to_muqss/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlf5jo/best_alternative_to_muqss/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T21:39:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello,
 Apologies if similar questions have been asked, but I'm just curious if there is a similar alternative to CK's MuQSS. I still have the last available kernel release in my secondary slot, which I bounce to when suspend issues come up, and have been using graysky's build for the hrtimer tweaks for the up-to-date kernel releases.
 Just checking in to see what the consensus is on the "best" maintained scheduler (or desktop kernel builds in general), and if anything out there plays a similar role. My current laptop is quite the potato, so I'd like to think tailored kernels are the way to go in my use case. Maybe I should just use zen from the official repo?
 Thanks!
    submitted by    /u/entheogenetica  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[how to rename a command]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlew42/how_to_rename_a_command/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlew42/how_to_rename_a_command/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T21:26:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[there is a thing in arch that will rename a command for example instead of me writing ls for the list i can change it to l but i forgot the name of it and how to use it
    submitted by    /u/zarnackreddit  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can't boot into windows 11 after installing arch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlej25/cant_boot_into_windows_11_after_installing_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlej25/cant_boot_into_windows_11_after_installing_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T21:09:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have just installed arch linux taking making sure to not touch the windows install. I also have disabled secure boot etc but now windows isn't being detected by my bios, os-prober or efibootmgr even when mounted. I can see all my files there etc. I'll attach outputs of lsblk and efibootmgr -v below and os-prober returns nothing. Windows is installed in UEFI mode.
 efibootmgr -v
 BootCurrent: 0003 Timeout: 1 seconds BootOrder: 0003 Boot0003* GRUB HD(1,GPT,c5d1c8be-3300-4e7e-bae0-250c0a18c80d,0x800,0x96000)/File(\EFI\GRUB\grubx64.efi) 
 lsblk
 NAME MAJ:MIN RM SIZE RO TYPE MOUNTPOINTS sda 8:0 0 119.2G 0 disk |-sda1 8:1 0 300M 0 part /boot `-sda2 8:2 0 118.9G 0 part /home / sdb 8:16 0 558.9G 0 disk |-sdb1 8:17 0 16M 0 part |-sdb2 8:18 0 558.3G 0 part /run/media/volt/9E8EDE668EDE368D `-sdb3 8:19 0 580M 0 part sdc 8:32 0 1.8T 0 disk `-sdc1 8:33 0 1.8T 0 part sdd 8:48 0 3.6T 0 disk |-sdd1 8:49 0 16M 0 part `-sdd2 8:50 0 3.6T 0 part zram0 253:0 0 8G 0 disk [SWAP] 
 Windows is installed on /dev/sdb and arch is installed on /dev/sda with btrfs etc. sdc and sdd are just large drives for storage.
 Any other information needed just ask and I will provide it. This has been a common theme with installing linux distros with most of them just not letting me boot into windows after installation.
 Any help is appreciated thank you!
    submitted by    /u/voltaf4  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does Your Android Phone Need an Antivirus App?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=793462</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/793462/does-your-android-phone-need-an-antivirus-app/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may be surprised to learn that Android is the most popular operating system on the planet—even bigger than Windows. That makes it a target for malicious attacks. But do you actually need antivirus apps on your Android phone?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google's Pixel 7 Pro Screen Could Be a Lot Better Outdoors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/121686/googles-pixel-7-pro-screen-could-be-a-lot-better-outdoors/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/121686/googles-pixel-7-pro-screen-could-be-a-lot-better-outdoors/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T20:04:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While Google already teased the Pixel 7 and Pixel 7 Pro back in May, the phones won’t arrive until later this year. Still, that hasn’t stopped a slew of leaks and rumors from emerging. Now, the latest leak suggests the Pixel series will finally have a much brighter display.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Silence Unknown Callers to Stop Robocall Spam on iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=772148</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/772148/how-to-silence-unknown-callers-to-stop-robocall-spam-on-iphone/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tired of getting robocalls all day long on your iPhone? Your iPhone lets you silence the harassment by turning on a feature called “Silence Unknown Callers” in Settings. Here’s how to do it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[how do I permanantly disable a virtual core pointer?I want to disable the wacom one as I use opentablerdriver I dont need it]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlcrzq/how_do_i_permanantly_disable_a_virtual_core/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlcrzq/how_do_i_permanantly_disable_a_virtual_core/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T19:47:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://imgur.com/a/TLw7hA5
    submitted by    /u/DrWeird31  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 Ways to Easily Send Text Messages (SMS) from Your PC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=295664</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/11255842/send-sms-from-pc"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Text messaging has become one of the most popular ways to carry on conversations in our world today. The convenience of using SMS is universally known. Sometimes, though, for one reason or another, you may prefer to have access to text messaging on your computer.
    
No matter your reason, if this is something you want to do, follow one of these texting methods that do not require the use of the messaging app on your phone.
   

Content

1. Google Voice
2. Your Email Account
3. Windows App
4. Chrome Extension
5. Free Websites
6. Text Sync Apps
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Use Google Messages on Desktop
    
1. Google Voice
    
Google Voice isn’t talked about much, but this handy service gives you a free virtual phone number that you can use to make calls and send texts.... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Crystal Crowder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unable to connect to a wifi network after installing arch in virtualbox]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlc4rt/unable_to_connect_to_a_wifi_network_after/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlc4rt/unable_to_connect_to_a_wifi_network_after/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T19:16:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(English is not my native language so there might be some errors sorry)
 I finished to install arch on virtualbox and everything seemed to work just fine until I realized I didn't have any internet connection. I use a laptop without any ethernet port so I have to use a wireless connection. The thing I don't understand is that during the install process (logged in as root), I was able to download all the packages I wanted using pacman but after booting the system for the first time, I just couldn't install anything nor ping any website (it returns "Temporary failure in name resolution"). After looking up some forum posts I tried to use iw which didn't work since I didn't install it during the installation process, then I tried to use netctl and wifi-menu but it didn't bring any results either even though I had access to them. I also tried to activate the dhcpcd client with sudo systemctl start dhcpcd since i thought it was the problem but it returns "Unit dhcpcd.service not found.". I am a complete beginner regarding arch linux so I would really really appreciate it if someone took the time to give me some paths that could lead me to a solution.
    submitted by    /u/NoOil3540  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add Gmail to Your iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=810864</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/810864/how-to-add-gmail-to-iphone/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T19:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google makes it super easy to add your Gmail account to your iPhone. This way, you can access your Gmail emails in your iPhone’s Mail app as well as the Gmail app. We’ll show you how to perform this integration on your device.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[error message in local.conf]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlbbme/error_message_in_localconf/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlbbme/error_message_in_localconf/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T18:39:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I can't update any font packages because it shows the same error: Fontconfig error: "/etc/fonts/local.conf", line 1: XML declaration not well-formed.
 ​
 but i haven't changed anything since i installed it yesterday
 ​
 ​
 <?xml version=1.0?>
 <!DOCTYPE fontconfig SYSTEM fonts.dtd>
 <fontconfig>
 <alias>
 <family>sans-serif</family>
 <prefer>
 <family>Noto Sans</family>
 <family>Noto Color Emoji</family>
 <family>Noto Emoji</family>
 <family>DejaVu Sans</family>
 </prefer>
 </alias>
 ​
 <alias>
 <family>serif</family>
 <prefer>
 <family>Noto Serif</family>
 <family>Noto Color Emoji</family>
 <family>Noto Emoji</family>
 <family>DejaVu Serif</family>
 </prefer>
 </alias>
 ​
 <alias>
 <family>monospace</family>
 <prefer>
 <family>Noto Mono</family>
 <family>Noto Color Emoji</family>
 <family>Noto Emoji</family>
 <family>DejaVu Sans Mono</family>
 </prefer>
 </alias>
 </fontconfig>
    submitted by    /u/OmgGass  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I feel in love with pacman!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlamig/i_feel_in_love_with_pacman/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlamig/i_feel_in_love_with_pacman/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T18:06:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Look, I've used other package managers before like dnf, apt, and pkg. Its main pro, though, is that once you've learned it, pacman does exactly what you tell it to do. I feel more in control of my system due to it.
    submitted by    /u/Mr_Foggy_Glasses  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Import Bookmarks From Chrome to Firefox]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=810747</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/810747/import-chrome-bookmarks-to-firefox/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T18:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla Firefox makes it easy to import bookmarks from other web browsers. If you’re switching from Google Chrome to Firefox, this guide will show you how to get all your Chrome bookmarks moved to your Firefox browser.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Overwatch' Will Stop Working When Its Sequel Arrives This October]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/121687/overwatch-will-stop-working-when-its-sequel-arrives-this-october/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/121687/overwatch-will-stop-working-when-its-sequel-arrives-this-october/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T17:13:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It seems that Overwatch 2 is more than just a flashy sequel. Instead, it’s a full on replacement for the seven-year-old Overwatch, which will stop working when Overwatch 2 arrives on October 4th. Given previous news, this isn’t much of a surprise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Check Your Computer’s Specifications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=810321</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/810321/how-to-check-computer-specs/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T17:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using just the built-in tools on Windows 10 and Windows 11, you can check your PC’s specs, like the processor type, RAM, graphics card model, storage type (SSD or HDD), network adapter model, and more. We’ll show you how to find that information on your machine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[flutter set up for arch linux (without installing android studio)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vl87ew/flutter_set_up_for_arch_linux_without_installing/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vl87ew/flutter_set_up_for_arch_linux_without_installing/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T16:15:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I want to install the android sdk and be able to use the android emulator without android studio.
 My current flutter doctor output:
 Doctor summary (to see all details, run flutter doctor -v): [!] Android toolchain - develop for Android devices (Android SDK version 33.0.0) ✗ Android license status unknown. Run `flutter doctor --android-licenses` to accept the SDK licenses. See https://flutter.dev/docs/get-started/install/linux#android-setup for more details. [✓] Chrome - develop for the web [✓] Linux toolchain - develop for Linux desktop [!] Android Studio (not installed) [✓] Connected device (2 available) [✓] HTTP Host Availability ! Doctor found issues in 2 categories. 
 There are several written tutorials online for how to do this such as this one: https://www.rockyourcode.com/how-to-get-flutter-and-android-working-on-arch-linux/
 but I can't tell which ones are up to date, so if you have it all set up on your machine matching the criteria I mentioned above, I would appreciate some step-by-step instructions on how you did it.
 This is what i have in my .bashrc:
 export JAVA_HOME='/usr/lib/jvm/java-18-openjdk' export JAVA_OPTS='-XX:+IgnoreUnrecognizedVMOptions --add-modules java.se.ee' export ANDROID_SDK_ROOT='/opt/android-sdk' export PATH=$JAVA_HOME/bin:$PATH export PATH=$PATH:$ANDROID_SDK_ROOT/platform-tools/ export PATH=$PATH:$ANDROID_SDK_ROOT/tools/bin/ export PATH=$PATH:$ANDROID_SDK_ROOT/tools/emulator export PATH=$PATH:$ANDROID_SDK_ROOT/tools/ 
 I tried to create an emulator with avdmanager create avd -n my_em -k "system-images;android-25;google_apis;x86" but I got this error:
 Error occurred during initialization of boot layer java.lang.module.FindException: Module java.se.ee not found 
 flutter doctor --android-licenses yielded the same error.
 I saw online that it is probably needing to downgrade my java version, so I tried to downgrade my jdk-openjdk package but I couldn't because it would break dependencies.
    submitted by    /u/Righteous_Warrior  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[liburing 2.2 Released For Easier IO_uring Usage On Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=liburing-2.2</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=liburing-2.2"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T16:07:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jens Axboe, Linux storage expert and IO_uring lead developer, released liburing 2.2 this weekend as the newest version of this helper library that makes it easier for user-space software to make use of the Linux kernel's IO_uring support...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multicharacter Glyph has wrong width in terminal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vl7zql/multicharacter_glyph_has_wrong_width_in_terminal/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vl7zql/multicharacter_glyph_has_wrong_width_in_terminal/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T16:05:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am using dwm/alacritty|st and when I copy a icon from nerdfont's cheatsheet online it seems to have a wrong width on paste and causes for example the terminal string to get erased when moving the cursor. I use the Hack patched NerdFont. Xclip pasting works and correctly gets pasted into terminal output. Does anybody have a similar issue?
    submitted by    /u/Narrow_Farmer_6018  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LGBTQ+ community warned of extortionists abusing dating apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/lgbtq-plus-community-warned-of-extortionists-abusing-dating-apps/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/lgbtq-plus-community-warned-of-extortionists-abusing-dating-apps/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T16:04:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Federal Trade Commission (FTC) has warned this week of extortion scammers targeting the LGBTQ+ community by abusing online dating apps like Grindr and Feeld. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything You Need to Know About Your Apple Watch Move Goal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=807795</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/807795/everything-you-need-to-know-about-your-apple-watch-move-goal/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T16:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you don’t fully understand how your Apple Watch Move goal works, what it should be set at, and how to fill your rings, it can be hard to use it as a motivational tool. Here are some tips to help you master your fitness-oriented wearable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spotify Now Uses Your Listening Habits to Find Concert Tickets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/121694/spotify-now-uses-your-listening-habits-to-find-concert-tickets/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/121694/spotify-now-uses-your-listening-habits-to-find-concert-tickets/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T15:23:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spotify has completely revamped its Concerts Hub, turning it into a powerful concert-finding tool called Live Events. This feed, which you can find by searching “Live Events” on Spotify, uses your listening habits to find concert tickets and information on upcoming shows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chroot into Encrypted Btrfs on Luks to repair fstab]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vl6uj2/chroot_into_encrypted_btrfs_on_luks_to_repair/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vl6uj2/chroot_into_encrypted_btrfs_on_luks_to_repair/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T15:12:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[*Obligatory Noob Preface*: I know I probably should've just used snapshots, but I'm a noob have been procrastinating on learning how to properly use BTRFS' features. I'll do so after resolving this.
 ​
 I recently edited my /etc/fstab to try to access an internal hard drive, and after rebooting, when I attempt to decrypt my arch installation, it times out. After this message it attempts to enter emergency mode but I'm unable to do anything in emergency mode because I have no root user set.
 I did make a backup of my fstab, and now I'm trying to chroot into my installation (via live USB) to restore the fstab backup.
 My Disk Layout:
 DEVICE SIZE TYPE /dev/nvme0n1p1 511M EFI System /dev/nvme0n1p2 931G Linux filesystem 
 What I've tried so far:
 cryptsetup luksOpen /dev/nvme0n1p2 arch mkdir -p /mnt/ mount /dev/mapper/arch /mnt mkdir -p /mnt/root/boot mount /dev/nvme0n1p1 /mnt/root bash chroot /mnt/root cp /etc/fstab.bak /etc/fstab 
  
At this point I get the error: "chroot: failed to run command cp: No such file or directory"
  
Any pointers?
    submitted by    /u/TheBlackChamber  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fake copyright infringement emails install LockBit ransomware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fake-copyright-infringement-emails-install-lockbit-ransomware/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fake-copyright-infringement-emails-install-lockbit-ransomware/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T15:05:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LockBit ransomware affiliates are using an interesting trick to get people into infecting their devices by disguising their malware as copyright claims. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Run Multiple Services In One Docker Container]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?post_type=devops&amp;p=800747</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/devops/how-to-run-multiple-services-in-one-docker-container/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T15:03:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Docker is a technology for packaging components of your stack as isolated containers. It’s common practice to run each of your processes in its own container, creating a clean divide between components. This enhances modularity and lets you access the scalability benefits of containerization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What to Look for in a Gaming Monitor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=803895</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/803895/what-to-look-for-in-a-gaming-monitor/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T15:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A good gaming monitor can improve your gameplay right away. They have key features that can help you see and react to your opponents faster, but they’re also useful for any activity. Here are the specs to look for.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Nguyen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clever phishing method bypasses MFA using Microsoft WebView2 apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/clever-phishing-method-bypasses-mfa-using-microsoft-webview2-apps/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/clever-phishing-method-bypasses-mfa-using-microsoft-webview2-apps/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T14:12:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A clever, new phishing technique uses Microsoft Edge WebView2 applications to steal victim's authentication cookies, allowing threat actors to bypass multi-factor authentication when logging into stolen accounts. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best TVs of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=740812</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/740812/best-tvs-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are some great TVs on the market, but how do you separate the best from the rest? That’s where our recommendations can help. We’ve picked out favorite sets for a range of different uses and budgets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What to install for default dark theming?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vl59qm/what_to_install_for_default_dark_theming/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vl59qm/what_to_install_for_default_dark_theming/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T13:56:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I always seem to forget what I need to add to my Arch install if I want to use a dark theming. For instance, on my current setup (after a recent Arch re-install) I have some programs that are BLINDING white!
 I just installed KDE Plasma and Cinnamon and I sort of have everything that I need but I didn't want to have to install those 2 DEs just to get the theming I want. Some things are looking better after the 2 DE installs (File manager is dark themed after going through the Look and Feel application and choosing the theming I want) but things like LibreOffice is still blinding me.
 I know some applications require different theming protocols in order to get things looking the way I want them to look.
 EDIT: Now LibreOffice has a dark mode in it's Options settings so I've fixed that. I'm going to play around a bit and see if anything opens and stabs me in the eyes with bright white still. :)
 If anyone knows the packages I need to install to make these changes on initial install/startup, I'd greatly appreciate it. I can add that to my script of software to install for new Arch installs.
    submitted by    /u/Phydoux  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PicPick screen capturing software update adds Screen Recorder]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179364</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/26/picpick-screen-capturing-software-update-adds-screen-recorder/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T13:52:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PicPick is one of my favorite screen capturing tools for Windows. It is a professional application that is free for non-commercial use. The program lacked screen recording support, which was my biggest […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post PicPick screen capturing software update adds Screen Recorder appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gnome battery indicator does not update.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vl4jwr/gnome_battery_indicator_does_not_update/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vl4jwr/gnome_battery_indicator_does_not_update/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T13:18:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have noticed that after a couple hours of up time the battery indicator stops updating. 
 Running "acpi" will return the current battery status, but "upower --monitor-detail" shows nothing. I didn't see anything that looked relevant in dmesg or journalctl.
 The computer is a Dell Inspiron 13 7391 with Intel i7-10510U running the linux-lts kernel. The same thing happens with the regular kernel.
    submitted by    /u/ElectronPunt  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NetSec Goggle shows search results only from cybersecurity sites]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/netsec-goggle-shows-search-results-only-from-cybersecurity-sites/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/netsec-goggle-shows-search-results-only-from-cybersecurity-sites/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T13:14:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new Brave Search Goggle modifies Brave Search results to only show reputable cybersecurity sites, making it easier to search for and find security information. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biometric Security Isn’t As Strong as You Think, Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=805458</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/805458/biometric-security-isnt-as-strong-as-you-think-heres-why/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T13:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Biometric authentication using your face or fingerprints is super-convenient and feels futuristic and secure. However, that may be a false sense of security thanks to weaknesses biometric systems have. If you know what they are, you can use biometrics responsibly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sydney Butler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Raspberry Pi 4 Alternatives]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/121592/the-best-raspberry-pi-4-alternatives/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/121592/the-best-raspberry-pi-4-alternatives/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T13:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Raspberry Pi 4 is a wonderful device. It’s the latest and greatest from a series of computers that have gotten millions into coding, and it forms the basis for a multitude of DIY electronics projects. The catch is, they’re impossible to get hold of, at least not at MSRP.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McQuilling</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Always having trouble with qt5 updates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vl3vnj/always_having_trouble_with_qt5_updates/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vl3vnj/always_having_trouble_with_qt5_updates/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T12:40:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whenever there is an update for qt5 packages it breaks programs like keepassxc.
 I usually have to wait for a couple weeks for other updates to fix it. So i usually just downgrade back and wait for that update.
 It's this error I am getting "Cannot mix incompatible Qt library (5.15.4) with this library (5.15.5)"
 qt5-styleplugins I use from AUR. 
 Is there a way I can fix this properly?
    submitted by    /u/therumble9  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulkan not working after update (AMD)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vl3opf/vulkan_not_working_after_update_amd/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vl3opf/vulkan_not_working_after_update_amd/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T12:29:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey, I can't get Vulkan to work after updating. Running vulkaninfo outputs an error: 
 ERROR: [Loader Message] Code 0 : loader_scanned_icd_add: Could not get 'vkCreateInstance' via 'vk_icdGetInstanceProcAddr' for ICD libGLX_nvidia.so.0 
 I thought it was weird that it was looking for an Nvidia library since I have AMD, so I tried uninstalling nvidia-utils and lib32-nvidia-utils which were installed for some reason. After that (and a reboot), vulkaninfo outputs nothing and just hangs. 
 I have vulkan-radeon, lib32-vulkan-radeon, amdvlk, and lib32-amdvlk installed. My GPU is RX 6700 XT. I'm positive it's not a hardware issue, because timeshifting to back before the system update fixes it. 
 I'm pretty confused about this whole thing so a little help would be appreciated.
    submitted by    /u/neuro_convergent  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s the Difference Between Em Dash, En Dash, and Hyphen?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=812094</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/812094/whats-the-difference-between-em-dash-en-dash-and-hyphen/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T12:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the world of typography, a humble horizontal line can mean at least seven different things depending on its length and the context in which it gets used. Generally, the most confusing of these are the hyphen, en dash, and em dash. We’ll explain the differences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Significato delle 100 emoji più usate]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/06/significato-delle-100-emoji-piu-usate.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/06/significato-delle-100-emoji-piu-usate.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T11:55:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Le emoji sono probabilmente la forma di comunicazione più diffusa su Internet, grazie alla diffusione massiccia delle app di messaggistica (come WhatsApp o Telegram). Tutti i giorni utilizziamo almeno una emoji, magari senza conoscere il suo vero significato, rischiando di inviare un messaggio sbagliato rispetto a quello che volevamo realmente inviare. 
Per evitare errori e diventare dei veri...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Much Does It Cost to Recharge a Battery?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=811727</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/811727/how-much-does-it-cost-to-recharge-a-battery/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From smaller devices like an Xbox controller to bigger devices like a battery-powered leaf blower or even a car, here’s how to figure out how much it costs to recharge the batteries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Fitzpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NVIDIA Lands AV1 VDPAU Hardware Acceleration In FFmpeg]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=NVIDIA-AV1-VDPAU-FFmpeg</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=NVIDIA-AV1-VDPAU-FFmpeg"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T09:44:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NVIDIA has contributed support to the FFmpeg multimedia library for being able to take advantage of AV1 GPU-accelerated video decoding by way of the VDPAU API when using the latest-generation NVIDIA RTX 30 "Ampere" GPUs...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft's CBL-Mariner 2.0 Linux Distro Now Supports Kernel Live Patching, PXE Boot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=CBL-Mariner-2.0-June-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=CBL-Mariner-2.0-June-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T09:14:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last month Microsoft issued the first production release of CBL-Mariner 2.0, its in-house Linux distribution used for powering services from Microsoft Azure to WSL use-cases and more. CBL-Mariner 2.0 this weekend saw a rather large monthly update with a number of fixes, package updates, and new additions to this "Common Base Linux" platform...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Play YouTube Shorts like normal YouTube videos]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179360</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/26/play-youtube-shorts-like-normal-youtube-videos/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T09:11:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[YouTube Shorts brings short-form videos to YouTube. The integrated service resembles what other short-form video services, such as TikTok, bring to the table: time-limted videos in portrait mode. Google's been late to […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Play YouTube Shorts like normal YouTube videos appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shotcut 22.06 Video Editor Adds Support For Lottie Animations, Filter Improvements]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Shotcut-22.06-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Shotcut-22.06-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T09:07:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shotcut remains one of the leading open-source, cross-platform video editors built atop the MLT Multimedia Framework with FFmpeg. Out this week is Shotcut 22.06 as the newest feature update to this non-linear video editing solution...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[nvidia stuff]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vkzr8a/nvidia_stuff/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vkzr8a/nvidia_stuff/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T08:07:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi ! I've been using arch since 6 months with nvidia drivers (latest version that work : 510, and I have GeForce RTX 3050 Ti Mobile). Lately I update my system and it broke (kernel panic), it took me some time (i'm a archlinux newbie) but I found out that it was because of nvidia 515. I'm really tired to manage this fuc***g driver so I would like to have your thought on this, should I use nouveau ? Wait for a stable update and rolled back to 510 until then? Or get another GPU that does not use nvidia ?
    submitted by    /u/metaxiii_fr  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[keyboard stops working after a period of time]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vkyw8w/keyboard_stops_working_after_a_period_of_time/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vkyw8w/keyboard_stops_working_after_a_period_of_time/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T07:06:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I use a dell xps 13 (9343). After a period of time the laptop's keyboard enter, space, backspace and certain function keys stop working. I've tried "sudo modprobe -r atkbd; sudo modprobe atkbd", which doesn't work. 
 When the laptop overheats, it seems that the system thinks the insert key is being continuously held down. Rebooting doesn't solve the issue. Sometimes the keyboard will randomly start working again.
    submitted by    /u/ryanng561  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[PSA] Having trouble with mpv/smplayer? Recently upgraded?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vkvwzu/psa_having_trouble_with_mpvsmplayer_recently/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vkvwzu/psa_having_trouble_with_mpvsmplayer_recently/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T03:52:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently upgraded mpv-git to version 0.34.0_351_g45ff20986d-1, which led to video output not working; specifically, the video in mpv/smplayer only showed a blank screen with audio. I'm using KDE Plasma 5.25.1; I don't know if that makes a difference.
 Anyway, I changed the following packages, which fixed the problem: 
 mpv-git to regular mpv, version 0.34.1 libplacebo-git to regular libplacebo, version 4.192.1-3 
 Now, video works again as normal. Hopefully this helps if someone else is having the same problem. 
 Edit: I was using mpv-git, not regular mpv. Using the non-git version of mpv seems to have solved the problem.
    submitted by    /u/PoliteSarcasticThing  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Issue with rsync autocompletion in zsh]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vkrye6/issue_with_rsync_autocompletion_in_zsh/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vkrye6/issue_with_rsync_autocompletion_in_zsh/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-26T00:05:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm not sure where this bug originates: if it's in rsync, zsh, some plugin for zsh or the arch packaging of any of these, but there's a problem with the auto-complete when auto-completing remote paths while rsyncing between my two arch machines. I seems to stem from a recent change in rsync behaviour I think.
 Before you had to prepend \\ to all your escapes when dealing with remote files in rsync, this in order to send the escapes to the remote machine. So if you had a machine machine with a file my file you wanted to copy, you would use rsync -Parch machine:my\\\ file ..
 However now I get an error saying rsync: [sender] link_stat "/home/machine/my\ file" failed: No such file or directory (2), and the way to fix it is to remove the escaped \: rsync -Parch machine:my\ file ..
 Anyone else have this problem? Is there a way to fix this?
    submitted by    /u/qhxo  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch installation crashing before even reaching the first root prompt]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vkqor9/arch_installation_crashing_before_even_reaching/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vkqor9/arch_installation_crashing_before_even_reaching/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-25T22:58:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi there! I'm trying to dual boot Windows 10 with Arch on a HP Victus 16 laptop. I have Windows already installed and secure boot disabled, but when booting from the live USB, the whole system crashes and restarts. This happens before the root prompt appears, and the last message that I get to see usually changes. The one I have seen the most has something about the backlight, but I haven't managed to fully read it.
 The laptop has an RTX 3050, which might be the problem. Any suggestions?
    submitted by    /u/dani-lp  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GRUB theming is broken in arch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vkonr4/grub_theming_is_broken_in_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vkonr4/grub_theming_is_broken_in_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-25T21:17:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm trying to make a GRUB theme, the strange thing that when you add labels or change fonts, GRUB crashes when you select/open the grub prompt. The issue doesn't happen in debian and its derivatives distros. Could it be an arch issue?
 Much thanks.
    submitted by    /u/KamaKazeh  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Should You Buy a Drone?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=796188</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/796188/should-i-buy-a-drone/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-25T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Drones are more accessible than ever before and now come in a range of sizes and price points. But before you reach for your wallet, there are a few things you might want to mull over.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A YouTuber Just Created the First "PS5 Slim," Kinda]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/121695/a-youtuber-just-created-the-first-ps5-slim-kinda/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/121695/a-youtuber-just-created-the-first-ps5-slim-kinda/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-25T20:04:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Playstation 5 is one of the biggest consoles around, but eventually, Sony will likely release a slim version. However, one DIY YouTuber didn’t want to wait several years for it, so he made his own “PS5 Slim.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Paste Text Without Formatting Almost Anywhere]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=679956</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/679956/how-to-paste-text-without-formatting-almost-anywhere/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-25T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Copy-and-paste moves more than just text around. It often brings along formatting from web pages and other documents. You can paste without formatting in nearly any application to get just the text without the extra formatting. Use this keyboard shortcut.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fedora CoreOS Hopes To Become An Official Edition With Fedora 37]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Fedora-CoreOS-Promotion-Hopes</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Fedora-CoreOS-Promotion-Hopes"/>
        <updated>2022-06-25T19:54:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the Fedora 37 cycle Fedora CoreOS is hoping to be promoted to an official release "edition" alongside the likes of Fedora Workstation and Fedora Server...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Huion H950P works at times, but doesn't most of the time, log included]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vkmqdn/huion_h950p_works_at_times_but_doesnt_most_of_the/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vkmqdn/huion_h950p_works_at_times_but_doesnt_most_of_the/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-25T19:43:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I remember using the drawing tablet in the past (like a year ago?) and it worked perfectly fine. Now, it works until it just stops working, stops working as in doesn't register inputs, can't even move the cursor. Replugging sometimes helps, most of the time does not. It's seemingly random.
 Note: there's power delivered to the device, there's a little indicator on the tablet and it also reacts when I use the pen like normal. I also tried it on windows 10 (dual booted) -- same everything, same usb slot, and works perfectly there.
  
tablet model: Huion H950P
 kernel: 5.18.6-arch1-1
 cpu: amd 3600x
 gpu: nvidia 2060
 de: kde plasma 5.25
  
Log: https://pastebin.com/fQJiigCJ
 Any idea what's happening?
    submitted by    /u/ReasonableFrog  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set up and Use a Ram Drive in Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=post-ideas&amp;p=262047</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/9643317/setup-ram-disk-windows"/>
        <updated>2022-06-25T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A RAM drive is a hard drive made up of your computer’s RAM. It can’t save data permanently, but it’s incredibly fast. If you want to try it out, you can create a RAM drive with free software and without a single computer upgrade. This article will walk through how you can set up and use a RAM drive on Windows 10 and Windows 11.
   

Content

Using ImDisk Toolkit
Using Your RAM Drive
Precautions and Recommendations
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Find the Maximum RAM Capacity of Your Computer
    
Using ImDisk Toolkit
    
ImDisk Toolkit is an application for managing virtual drives. It also includes a utility that allows the creation of RAM drives.
    
Download ImDisk from Sourceforge.net.
   
 Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sayak Boral</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Im using an Acer Aspire 5 2020, i have Arch installed with BTRFS and my Touchpad isnt working]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vkm0ga/im_using_an_acer_aspire_5_2020_i_have_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vkm0ga/im_using_an_acer_aspire_5_2020_i_have_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-25T19:07:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The libinput package is alredy installed and im using Gnome
 But the touchpad of my notebook isnt working
 And the why i said "I have Arch installed with BTRFS", thats because i wasnt having this problem when i was using my system before with ext4
 But after i reinstalled my Arch system changing from ext4 to BTRFS, my touchpad stopped working
    submitted by    /u/I7sReact  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Clear the Recent Files List in Adobe Photoshop]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=810800</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/810800/how-to-clear-the-recent-files-list-in-adobe-photoshop/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-25T19:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve been using Adobe Photoshop and you don’t want to leave your recent work visible on the opening Home page when you launch the app, you have a few options for clearing the list or hiding it. We’ll show you how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trouble with AMD GPU]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vkkonp/trouble_with_amd_gpu/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vkkonp/trouble_with_amd_gpu/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-25T18:04:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello!
 I have an AMD FirePro M6100 that when in arch, I can't seem to get to work but in other distros (Like Manjaro) seem to work fine.
 Under arch, my install doesn't even seem to be detecting it. I even looked through the boot logs to make sure it is at least throwing an error and there is nothing referencing amdgpu or radeon (This is South Island based/GCN 2.0 so it supports amdgpu)
 And yes, Ive read the wiki and can't seem to wrap my head around it (Its instructions seem vaige to me) so if anyone can provide any help; it would be very much appreciated
 Thanks!
    submitted by    /u/PentiumCentrino  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Restart Windows 10]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=811420</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/811420/how-to-restart-windows-10/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-25T18:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Restarting your Windows 10 PC is as easy as clicking a few options or running a command from Command Prompt. We’ll show you the options available to you to turn your PC off and then back on.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Instagram Wants a Video Selfie From Your Teen]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/121674/instagram-wants-a-video-selfie-from-your-teen/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/121674/instagram-wants-a-video-selfie-from-your-teen/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-25T17:13:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Instagram this week announced it’s testing several new systems for age verification. This includes recording a video selfie and submitting it to an AI-powered facial recognition tool. The goal is for teenagers to verify their age and comply with platform rules.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Multiple Accounts With Discord]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=808489</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/808489/discord-multiple-accounts/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-25T17:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you manage multiple Discord accounts, the platform’s desktop and web app allow you to add all your accounts into the app and then switch between them with ease. If this sounds like something you want to do, we’ll show you how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Right click issue with pcmanfm-gtk3]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vkiyr5/right_click_issue_with_pcmanfmgtk3/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vkiyr5/right_click_issue_with_pcmanfmgtk3/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-25T16:41:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Couldn't find a place to ask specific to pcmanfm/If there's a better place let me know.
 If I have pcmanfm installed my right click works fine on folders and files using the touchpad or a connected mouse but if I use pcmanfm-gtk3 I can no longer right click. The 3 finger middle click still works.
 Both pcmanfm and gtk3 are version 1.3.2-1 and both from the arch community repository and only other packages that change are libfm-gtk2 to libfm-gtk3.
 System is fully updated, running swaywm so maybe a wayland issue? I don't have the full xorg suite installed but do have xorg-xwayland. Tried figuring out if it was a known bug but having trouble navigating the source forge repo.
    submitted by    /u/Marty1820  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How is game dev on arch linux?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vkixzp/how_is_game_dev_on_arch_linux/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vkixzp/how_is_game_dev_on_arch_linux/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-25T16:40:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[hey i have been going back and forth with arch linux and i have been curious can you work on game dev on arch?
    submitted by    /u/Drebthedope69  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Rid of Bloatware on Your Android Phone]]></title>
        <id>http://www.howtogeek.com/?p=115533</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/115533/how-to-disable-or-uninstall-android-bloatware/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-25T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manufacturers and carriers often pre-install a bunch of apps on Android phones. If you don’t use them, they just clutter your system and drain your battery in the background. Take control of your device and stop the bloatware.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PyPi python packages caught sending stolen AWS keys to unsecured sites]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/pypi-python-packages-caught-sending-stolen-aws-keys-to-unsecured-sites/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/pypi-python-packages-caught-sending-stolen-aws-keys-to-unsecured-sites/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-25T15:32:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Multiple malicious Python packages available on the PyPI repository were caught stealing sensitive information like AWS credentials and transmitting it to publicly exposed endpoints accessible by anyone. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[pacman hook for setting `NoDisplay=true` for specified list of desktop entries?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vkhecc/pacman_hook_for_setting_nodisplaytrue_for/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vkhecc/pacman_hook_for_setting_nodisplaytrue_for/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-25T15:26:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I want my application clean. 
 So, I do hide unwanted ones by setting NoDisplay=true for their desktop entries. 
 And I have to do it after every update of the package.
 A possible solution is to set these entries' path as NoExtract in pacman.conf. But I don't think that's a viable solution.
 So, I wonder if there's any pacman hook or something, then I set which entries I wanted to hide.
  
Thank you
    submitted by    /u/mishab_mizzunet  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The iOS 16 Beta Hints at a New Apple TV Box]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/121678/the-ios-16-beta-hints-at-a-new-apple-tv-box/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/121678/the-ios-16-beta-hints-at-a-new-apple-tv-box/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-25T15:23:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The iOS 16 beta launched earlier this month, and oddly enough, its code references both “WirelessRemoteFirmware.4” and “SiriRemote4.” These names don’t correspond to any existing Apple products, and notably, Apple has only released three generations of the Siri Remote.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Does Shift+Enter Do in Word?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=811092</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/811092/what-does-shift-enter-do-in-word/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-25T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you press Enter in Microsoft Word, by default, your cursor will jump ahead two lines. But why does it do this, and is there any way to make it only move ahead one line instead? We’ll show you the answers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft: Exchange Server 2013 reaches end of support in 9 months]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-exchange-server-2013-reaches-end-of-support-in-9-months/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-exchange-server-2013-reaches-end-of-support-in-9-months/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-25T14:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has reminded customers that the Exchange Server 2013 mail and calendaring platform will reach its extended end-of-support date roughly nine months from now, on April 11, 2021. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>