<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-05-13T02:00:34.930Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[`xdg-open` has been complaining because it tries to run`kde-config`, which isn't installed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uogwpv/xdgopen_has_been_complaining_because_it_tries_to/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uogwpv/xdgopen_has_been_complaining_because_it_tries_to/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T01:52:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[/usr/bin/xdg-open: line 501: test: : integer expression expected /usr/bin/xdg-open: line 502: test: : integer expression expected /usr/bin/xdg-open: line 503: test: : integer expression expected 
 and those lines are the three tests in
 kfmclient_fix_exit_code() { version=`LC_ALL=C.UTF-8 kde-config --version 2>/dev/null | grep '^KDE'` major=`echo $version | sed 's/KDE.*: \([0-9]\).*/\1/'` minor=`echo $version | sed 's/KDE.*: [0-9]*\.\([0-9]\).*/\1/'` release=`echo $version | sed 's/KDE.*: [0-9]*\.[0-9]*\.\([0-9]\).*/\1/'` test "$major" -gt 3 && return $1 test "$minor" -gt 5 && return $1 test "$release" -gt 4 && return $1 return 0 } 
 . . . and (a) I can't find the kde-config command or anything like it anywhere and (b) xdg-open doesn't source anything I can see.
 So I'm getting the impression I'm missing something idiotic but, well, so be it.
 Is this just some command that's gone now and I should just hack up a substitute? It looks as if ln -s /usr/bin/kdeinit5 ~/bin/kde-config does the trick but that feels unclean.
    submitted by    /u/jthill  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How can I find out my laptop charging rate?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uofcpb/how_can_i_find_out_my_laptop_charging_rate/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uofcpb/how_can_i_find_out_my_laptop_charging_rate/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T00:27:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have a 100w GaN charger and want to know if it is actually charging at 100w
    submitted by    /u/theguysk21  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[15 Safe Websites for Downloading Windows Software]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=152689</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/3459316/websites-download-windows-software"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows has tons of free software, and of course, there are so many websites where you can download it. The challenge is that a lot of these freeware download sites, each claiming to be the best, routinely saddle the software with custom installers, adware, crapware, and bloatware. 
    
However, there are still quite a few reliable software download websites which don’t complicate the core installer with crapware. The following updated list comprises an exhaustive collection of sites where you can download Windows software, minus the bad stuff.
   

Content

Our Criteria to Assess a Source's Safety for Software Downloads
1. Microsoft.com
2. Microsoft Store 
3. Developer's Website 
4. SourceForge
5. AlternativeTo
6. GitHub
7. Steam
8. Epic Games
9. Filepuma
10. Ninite
11. Softpedia
12. DownloadCrew
13. FileHorse
14. Chocolatey
15. DeviantArt
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Install Unsigned Drivers in Windows
  ... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sayak Boral</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Need to restart `pulseaudio` every time I open browser to play video]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uoec8a/need_to_restart_pulseaudio_every_time_i_open/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uoec8a/need_to_restart_pulseaudio_every_time_i_open/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T23:33:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This happened after an update and a reboot. Basically, I need to restart pulseaudio everytime I want to play a video on a browser or hear audio in general.
  systemctl restart --user pulseaudio  Even if you already restarted pulseaudio, the problem happens again when opening another YouTube tab or closing/reopening browser.
    submitted by    /u/MISTREAPERf  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AUR is down?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uodmbb/aur_is_down/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uodmbb/aur_is_down/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T22:57:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Can't seem to access the AUR right now. Is this happening to anyone else?
    submitted by    /u/Prizefighter-Mercury  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come risolvere le problematiche relative all’audio quando lavorate da remoto]]></title>
        <id>3570|20220513000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/audio-30/come-risolvere-problematiche-relative-allaudio-quando-lavorate-remoto-3570"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Una delle principali problematiche, per l’utente che lavora da casa su sistemi aziendali, è quella relativa all’audio delle telefonate, fatte o ricevute, con i clienti. Audio mancante, gracchiante, incompleto, il microfono che non funziona, sono tra i principali difetti. Vediamo come cercare di risolvere questi problemi, perché, almeno in alcuni casi le soluzioni sono molto semplici.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tried to use the new Install script but it failed and I'm not really sure what happened?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uocepw/tried_to_use_the_new_install_script_but_it_failed/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uocepw/tried_to_use_the_new_install_script_but_it_failed/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T21:59:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Could someone please explain what exactly is causing this to fail?
 To me it looks like it is looking for the drive at /dev/sda instead of /dev/nvme0n1 but im not 100% sure.
 Hardware model detected: Eluktronics Inc. MAX-15; UEFI mode: True Processor model detected: Intel(R) Core(TM) i7-10870H CPU @ 2.20GHz Memory statistics: 15473192 available out of 16210456 total installed Could not detect virtual system: ['/usr/bin/systemd-detect-virt'] exited with abnormal exit code [256]: b'none\r\n' System is not running in a VM: ['/usr/bin/systemd-detect-virt'] exited with abnormal exit code [256]: b'none\r\n' Virtualization detected: None; is VM: None Graphics devices detected: dict_keys(['Intel Corporation CometLake-H GT2 [UHD Graphics] (rev 05)', 'NVIDIA Corporation TU104BM [GeForce RTX 2070 SUP…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 of the Best VPN Apps for iPhone and Android]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=473562</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15291293/best-mobile-vpn-apps"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly everyone uses the internet daily at this point, there’s almost no way around it. Between cybercriminals, phishing emails, and targeted ads, though, many people are looking for ways to protect themselves while they use the internet. This is where VPN apps come in handy, since they can help protect your browsing habits and data on virtually any device.
   

Content

What Is a VPN?
What About Mobile VPNs?
The Benefits of Having VPN Apps on Your Mobile Device
1. NordVPN
2. Surfshark
3. ExpressVPN
4. Datacappy
5. CyberGhost
6. Windscribe
7. ProtonVPN
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Spot a Facebook Phishing Email and Similar Scams
    
What Is a VPN?
    
A virtual private network, or VPN for short, is essentially a service that protects your online privacy. These virtual networks create a sort of encrypted tunnel... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Megan Glosson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ukrainian imprisoned for selling access to thousands of PCs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ukrainian-imprisoned-for-selling-access-to-thousands-of-pcs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ukrainian-imprisoned-for-selling-access-to-thousands-of-pcs/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T21:10:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Glib Oleksandr Ivanov-Tolpintsev, a 28-year-old from Ukraine, was sentenced today to 4 years in prison for stealing thousands of login credentials per week and selling them on a dark web marketplace. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaFX install help]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uob9ly/javafx_install_help/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uob9ly/javafx_install_help/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T21:09:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am studying a BSc at University of the people, and the unit I'm working on now works with JavaFX. However, I'm having trouble getting JavaFX to work at all, and as you can tell it's quite important I get it to work, otherwise I can't get my work done.
 Any guide or general information of what I'm doing wrong will really help. I'm fairly new at using Linux so treat me like a beginner.
 If this will help I get get these errors when I run Main.java from a new javafx project:
 ​
 Graphics Device initialization failed for : es2, sw
 Error initializing QuantumRenderer: no suitable pipeline found
 java.lang.RuntimeException: java.lang.RuntimeException: Error initializing QuantumRenderer: no suitable pipeline found
 at [javafx.graphics](https://javafx.graphics)@18.0.1/com.sun.javafx.tk.quantum.Q…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Install Free HEVC Codecs on Windows 10 (for H.265 Video)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=680690</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/680690/how-to-install-free-hevc-codecs-on-windows-10-for-h.265-video/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 10 supports video files encoded with High-Efficiency Video Coding (HEVC), also known as H.265 video. However, Microsoft charges for its official codecs and doesn’t include them in Windows 10. You can get them for free without busting out the credit card and spending $0.99.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Initial Performance Of NVIDIA's R515 Open-Source Linux GPU Kernel Driver]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31119</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31119"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As outlined in yesterday's extensive article about NVIDIA's new open-source Linux kernel GPU driver, currently for consumer GeForce RTX GPUs the driver is considered of "alpha quality" while NVIDIA's initial focus has been on data center GPU support. In any event with having lots of Turing/Ampere GPUs around, I've been trying out this new open-source Linux kernel driver on the consumer GPUs. In particular, I've been curious about the performance of using this open-source kernel driver relative to the default, existing closed-source kernel driver. Here are some early benchmarks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia Releases Open-Source Linux GPU Drivers, With a Catch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=805004</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/805004/nvidia-releases-open-source-linux-gpu-drivers-with-a-catch/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T20:32:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gaming on Linux has always been a bit more complicated than on Windows (or game consoles), and one reason for that is Nvidia’s poor driver support on Linux. That’s now changing, though it’s unclear how much the situation will improve.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Subscription Boxes for Gardeners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/13463/the-best-subscription-boxes-for-gardeners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/13463/the-best-subscription-boxes-for-gardeners/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gardening is a satisfying hobby for so many reasons—your outdoor space looks great, you’ve helped cultivate new life, and you even get some crops or flowers in return. We’ve checked out the best subscription boxes for gardeners so that your green finger endeavors are even more successful.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Allen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Any clue why my programs are using English instead of default language?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uoa0b7/any_clue_why_my_programs_are_using_english/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uoa0b7/any_clue_why_my_programs_are_using_english/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T20:16:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since some days ago... I have been experiencing something really weird. 
 All my programs run in English, unless I manually override their specific configuration. 
 I have tried locale command, and everything looks good. LC_ALL is empty which I have read it is the way, as it should only be used for specific cases where you want to quickly override all languages for a specific task. 
 locale -a also seems to output the expected, and my KDE Plasma also has the proper configuration in the language section of their settings. 
 Here is my system data. 
  Operating System: Arch Linux KDE Plasma Version: 5.24.5 KDE Frameworks Version: 5.93.0 Qt Version: 5.15.3 Kernel Version: 5.17.6-zen1-1-zen (64-bit) Graphics Platform: Wayland 
 Examples of programs that have switched to English: - Dolphin - Kate - FreeTube - Gnome Boxes - GIMP
 Examplees of programas that use the correct language: - The Plasma settings are half in my language, half not. Weird. - locale seems to speak in my language too.
    submitted by    /u/anotheruser123123  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Just made my first package on the AUR, rofi-checklist-git!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uo9yi8/just_made_my_first_package_on_the_aur/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uo9yi8/just_made_my_first_package_on_the_aur/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T20:13:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was surprised how easy it was to get stuff on the AUR. I made a small little shell script for rofi that works as a checklist, if anyone wants to check it out (GitHub, AUR). It's not much, but I find it useful and I hope somebody else does too. I'm pretty new to bash scripting so they script itself is kind of messy and bodged together, but it works. That's all, just wanted to share.
    submitted by    /u/ElnuDev  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Clear Your Computer’s CMOS to Reset BIOS Settings]]></title>
        <id>http://www.howtogeek.com/?p=131623</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/131623/how-to-clear-your-computers-cmos-to-reset-bios-settings/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your computer stores low-level settings like the system time and hardware settings in its CMOS. These settings are configured in the BIOS or UEFI setup menu. If you’re experiencing a hardware compatibility issue or another problem, you may want to try clearing the CMOS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Undone replacement of pipewire-media-session with wireplumber]]></title>
        <id>tag:archlinux.org,2022-05-12:/news/undone-replacement-of-pipewire-media-session-with-wireplumber/</id>
        <link href="https://archlinux.org/news/undone-replacement-of-pipewire-media-session-with-wireplumber/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T19:48:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two days ago the wireplumber package was made to replace pipewire-media-session as the latter session manager for PipeWire is considered dead upstream and will see no more releases. Unfortunately, this step was premature.
Our pipewire audio packages (pipewire-alsa, pipewire-jack and pipewire-pulse) ship configuration that prompt media-session to activate PipeWire's audio features. When these packages are not installed and the configuration is missing, PipeWire can be used for screen recording without interfering with ALSA or PulseAudio.
WirePlumber disregards this mechanism and always configures PipeWire to grab audio devices, meaning users of PulseAudio or bare ALSA experience broken audio.
The replacement has been reverted while we attempt to look for a better solution switching to WirePlumber. If you are currently not using PipeWire for audio and wireplumber got installed on your system, please reinstall pipewire-media-session and reboot to restore audio functionality.
pacman -Syu pipewire-media-session]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jan Alexander Steffens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will fire jail propagate to subprocesses?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uo9dnr/will_fire_jail_propagate_to_subprocesses/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uo9dnr/will_fire_jail_propagate_to_subprocesses/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T19:46:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anyone know if I run a bash script that executes other commands like a Python script or another shell script if the options I passed to firejail will propagate to the subprocesses?
 E.g.
 firejail --net=none launcher.sh 
 Where launcher.sh might run a couple of python scripts and a shell script?
    submitted by    /u/krisclarkdev  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[cron isn't removing files at startup]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uo97o4/cron_isnt_removing_files_at_startup/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uo97o4/cron_isnt_removing_files_at_startup/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T19:39:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On some computers I administer, I would like to have the Desktop cleared for the student user at reboot. I've tried doing this with cron, but it isn't working and I can't figure out why. Here is what I've tried:
 $ crontab -e @reboot /usr/bin/rm -rf /home/student/Desktop/* 
 I've tried that as the 'student' user as well as on root and the files remain after reboot. I've also tried it with just 'rm' instead of the full path. No dice. Any ideas why it isn't working?
    submitted by    /u/LorenWard  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open 3D Engine 22.05 Released With New Features]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=O3DE-22.04-Open-3D-Engine</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=O3DE-22.04-Open-3D-Engine"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T19:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In addition to a new development release of Godot 4.0 out today, the other high profile open-source 3D game engine is Open 3D Engine (O3DE) that started last year from Amazon's Lumberyard Engine and now under the Linux Foundation's Open 3D Foundation. Out today is O3DE 22.05 for this high profile free software 3D game engine...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save $70 on an Apple Watch Series 7]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=467477</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15103583/apple-watch-series-7"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may be looking forward to all the great fitness you’ll be doing in the great weather this summer. Get some help with that by buying an Apple Watch Series 7. It’s now available for $70 off (its lowest ever!) in certain colors with a 41mm sport band and GPS.
    
The Watch features the Always-On Retina display for almost 20% more screen real estate than the previous model, which makes it easier to see your messages, fitness counter, health information, etc. This information is under the most crack-resistant front crystal yet for an Apple Watch. It also sports IP6X dust resistance and is swim-proof to boot.
    
This particular version of the Apple Watch Series 7 is non-cellular, meaning you will have to remain connected to your iPhone for you to take calls, use the health and fitness features, or do anything Internet-related while using the Watch.
    

    
You can check your heart rhythm with the ECG app anytime and anywhere and get high and low heart rate and irregular heart... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eternity malware kit offers stealer, miner, worm, ransomware tools]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/eternity-malware-kit-offers-stealer-miner-worm-ransomware-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/eternity-malware-kit-offers-stealer-miner-worm-ransomware-tools/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T19:18:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors have launched the 'Eternity Project,' a new malware-as-a-service where threat actors can purchase a malware toolkit that can be customized with different modules depending on the attack being conducted. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fix “Network Blocking Encrypted DNS Traffic” on iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=785617</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/785617/how-to-fix-network-blocking-encrypted-dns-traffic-on-iphone/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T19:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your iPhone can encrypt DNS traffic so that the names of websites and servers you access cannot be seen by third parties. Occasionally your iPhone may display a warning that encrypted DNS traffic is being blocked. Learn what it means and how to resolve it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pixel Watch Is Google’s Long-Awaited Apple Watch Competitor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=804871</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/804871/pixel-watch-is-googles-long-awaited-apple-watch-competitor/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T18:35:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google held its yearly Google I/O event on Wednesday, and among the sea of new software and hardware announcements, we got our first look at the long-awaited Pixel Watch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[virtualbox-host-dkms error when compiling kernel modules (solved)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uo7jrl/virtualboxhostdkms_error_when_compiling_kernel/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uo7jrl/virtualboxhostdkms_error_when_compiling_kernel/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T18:23:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I did a pacman -Syu today and Virtualbox stopped working. I narrowed down the issue to the kernel modules not compiling. When installing virtualbox-host-dkms I get the error Error! Bad return status for module build on kernel: $kernelname. It also spits out "exit: 10".
 The solution was to downgrade gcc from 12.1 to 11.2. I navigated to /var/cache/pacman/pkg and ran sudo pacman -U gcc-11.2.0-4-x86_64.pkg.tar.zst gcc-libs-11.2.0-4-x86_64.pkg.tar.zst lib32-gcc-libs-11.2.0-4-x86_64.pkg.tar.zst and then the kernel modules compiled properly.
 Just putting this out there because googling the issue didn't result in much useful info, so maybe newer users will come across this if they experience this issue
    submitted by    /u/pinephreak  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zyxel silently fixes critical RCE vulnerability in firewall products]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/zyxel-silently-fixes-critical-rce-vulnerability-in-firewall-products/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/zyxel-silently-fixes-critical-rce-vulnerability-in-firewall-products/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T18:13:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat analysts who discovered a vulnerability affecting multiple Zyxel products report that the network equipment company fixed it via a silent update pushed out two weeks ago. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s Pixel Buds Pro Will Have Incredible Battery Life]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=804964</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/804964/googles-pixel-buds-pro-will-have-incredible-battery-life/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T18:02:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has released a few pairs of wireless earbuds at this point, and the company revealed the a new pair on Wednesday during the Google I/O main keynote. The Pixel Buds Pro aims to be one of the best wireless earbuds ever, and that might just be true.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Is My Microphone Quiet in Windows 11? 5 Fixes to Try]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=802204</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/802204/why-is-my-microphone-quiet-in-windows-11-5-fixes-to-try/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s happened to all of us. You’re in a video call, and someone says “you sound quiet.” There are a surprising number of things that could be causing this in Windows 11. Let’s figure out what’s going on.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rivian R1T Electric Truck Recalled Over Dangerous Child Safety Issue]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117766/rivian-r1t-electric-truck-recalled-over-dangerous-child-safety-issue/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117766/rivian-r1t-electric-truck-recalled-over-dangerous-child-safety-issue/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T17:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, Rivian issued its first recall on the popular new R1T electric truck over a critical safety issue affecting over 500 vehicles. According to the NHTSA, defective airbag sensors may not deactivate when a child is in the passenger seat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOOGEE S98 Smartphone Review: Rugged and Innovative]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=482006</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15291028/doogee-s98-smartphone"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T17:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With so many Android devices on the market, sometimes it’s hard to find the best option for your needs. For those with active lifestyles that need a durable phone with innovative features, the DOOGEE S98 could be the perfect solution. With a brand philosophy of “Our spirit is to have the courage to keep challenging and exploring,” you’d expect an impressive device. I recently had the pleasure of seeing just how well the DOOGEE S98 smartphone lives up to the brand’s promises.
    
This is a sponsored article and was made possible by DOOGEE. The actual contents and opinions are the sole views of the author who maintains editorial independence even when a post is sponsored.
    
Overview of Features
    
Straight away, the DOOGEE S98 has an incredible feature set, along with accessories, that you won’t find on most major smartphones. Even when you lift it for the first time, you can tell it’s designed to be more durable and rugged than the competition.
    
The phone has a 6.3 in. LCD FHD+ waterdrop screen. The 1080 x 2340 resolution screen is heavily protected from drops... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Crystal Crowder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sony's WH-1000XM5 Arrive With a Refined Design at a Higher Price]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117753/sonys-wh-1000xm5-arrive-with-a-refined-design-at-a-higher-price/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117753/sonys-wh-1000xm5-arrive-with-a-refined-design-at-a-higher-price/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T17:09:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After several recent leaks, Sony unveiled its new premium WH-1000XM5 headphones with an all-new refined design and countless upgrades. While everything is a little better than the previous generation, they cost $399, a $50 price increase over the 1000XM4s.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BPFdoor: Stealthy Linux malware bypasses firewalls for remote access]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/bpfdoor-stealthy-linux-malware-bypasses-firewalls-for-remote-access/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/bpfdoor-stealthy-linux-malware-bypasses-firewalls-for-remote-access/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T17:07:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recently discovered backdoor malware called BPFdoor has been stealthily targeting Linux and Solaris systems without being noticed for more than five years. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Ilascu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s a POAP? How Memories Are Being Transformed in Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=800246</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/800246/whats-a-poap-how-memories-are-being-transformed-in-web3/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[POAPs are used to mark participation or attendance at an event. Just like you might save ticket stubs from concerts or movies, buy pins at a sporting event or festival, or collect matches from restaurants or hotels, a POAP is a digital version of that same notion, satiating our desire to collect items that mark our experiences throughout life.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Colin Brightfield</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come condividere lo stesso abbonamento Netflix per pagare meno]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2016/01/si-puo-dividere-il-prezzo-di-netflix.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2016/01/si-puo-dividere-il-prezzo-di-netflix.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T16:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix è il miglior servizio per vedere in streaming film e serie TV, vista anche l'elevata qualità audio e video offerta dai contenuti, in particolare se attiviamo l'abbonamento più costoso (che sblocca il 4K con HDR, una qualità impensabile per un flusso in streaming via Internet).

 I costi dell'abbonamento di Netflix vanno da 7,99 € a 17,99 € al mese, in base alla qualità che vogliamo...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[two dams can be found on my login screen but I don’t know how to delete them, where could they be?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uo59r0/two_dams_can_be_found_on_my_login_screen_but_i/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uo59r0/two_dams_can_be_found_on_my_login_screen_but_i/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T16:39:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/9934d  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD's Xilinx Posts New Linux DRM Display Driver]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Xilinx-2022-DRM-Driver</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Xilinx-2022-DRM-Driver"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T16:19:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AMD-owned Xilinx posted a new patch series today implementing a new DRM display driver for supporting their soft MIPI DSI Tx subsystem IP...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LEGO Optimus Prime Is Ready to Roll Out]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117736/lego-optimus-prime-is-ready-to-roll-out/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117736/lego-optimus-prime-is-ready-to-roll-out/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T16:17:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Move over Batmobile; LEGO just announced its best 80s nostalgia set yet: Optimus Prime. And if just the name of the set isn’t enough to make you instantly pull out $169.99 to buy it, you should know this set actually transforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Hendrickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Android TV 13 Will Upgrade Picture-in-Picture Mode]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=804506</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/804506/android-tv-13-will-upgrade-picture-in-picture-mode/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T16:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Android TV powers many different smart TVs, cable boxes, and some of the best streaming devices, and a customized version called Google TV has appeared on some devices. Google has now shared more information about the next major update, Android TV 13.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There's Now a Wordle Game for Food Lovers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lifesavvy.com/128798/theres-now-a-wordle-game-for-food-lovers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lifesavvy.com/128798/theres-now-a-wordle-game-for-food-lovers/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T16:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By now, you’ve likely played Wordle at least once. The Hangman-esque game took the internet by storm earlier this year, and now there are all kinds of iterations, including one for foodies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shea Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is the Line Under the Battery on the iPhone Lock Screen?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=802975</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/802975/what-is-the-line-under-the-battery-on-the-iphone-lock-screen/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T16:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The iPhone has a pretty simple and intuitive interface, but there are still some things that appear with no explanation. One such thing is the line under the cell signal, Wi-Fi, and battery icons on the lock screen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We take a closer look at Suggested Actions in Windows 11, and show you how to disable it]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178538</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/05/12/we-take-a-closer-look-at-suggested-actions-in-windows-11-and-show-you-how-to-disable-it/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T15:52:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft released Windows 11 Insider Preview Build 25115 to the Dev Channel. It introduced a new feature called Suggested Actions. Microsoft showcased it with two screenshots. We take a closer look at […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post We take a closer look at Suggested Actions in Windows 11, and show you how to disable it appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ghacks Deals: The Jumbo 2022 Javascript Bundle]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178549</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/05/12/ghacks-deals-the-jumbo-2022-javascript-bundle/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T15:50:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript is one of the most popular programming languages; if you want to get started with the language or finetune your skills, you may find the Jumbo 2022 JavaScript Bundle perfectly suited […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Ghacks Deals: The Jumbo 2022 Javascript Bundle appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smart Lock Google: cos'è e come funziona]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Smart-Lock-Google-cos-e-e-come-funziona_24508</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Smart-Lock-Google-cos-e-e-come-funziona_24508"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T15:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ogni dispositivo mobile è una vera e propria miniera di dati personali e informazioni riservate. Ciò che custodisce va mantenuto protetto nei confronti di terzi sia evitando l'installazione di app che possono trasferire dati personali a soggetti sconosciuti, sia impostando lo sblocco del dispositivo mediante impronta digitale, un PIN o una password complessi.La sequenza grafica viene comunemente utilizzata per proteggere il dispositivo ma è necessario sceglierne una articolata e assicurarsi che qualcuno, nelle vicinanze, non la lista di fatto memorizzando.Una delle funzioni meno conosciute di Android, nonostante sia stata introdotta già ai tempi della release 5.0 Lollipop (2014), è Smart Lock: essa permette di mantenere lo smartphone sbloccato quando si ha il telefono con sé, se ci si trova a casa o in un altro luogo affidabile ('Luoghi attendibili'), se nelle immediate vicinanze ci fosse un proprio dispositivo Bluetooth (uno smartwatch, una smart band, un PC,...).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Future Rivian EV Pre-Orders Will No Longer Guarantee a Price]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117735/future-rivian-ev-pre-orders-will-no-longer-guarantee-a-price/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117735/future-rivian-ev-pre-orders-will-no-longer-guarantee-a-price/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T15:43:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in March, Rivian announced large price increases for its popular R1T and R1S electric truck and SUV, affecting all orders. However, it quickly rolled back that decision after backlash and honored the original pre-order price for early buyers. And while that still stands, upcoming orders will lose the price guarantee.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox crashing on system restart]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uo3rj9/firefox_crashing_on_system_restart/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uo3rj9/firefox_crashing_on_system_restart/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T15:31:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey!
 Over the last few days I am running into a new issue with Firefox that I have no idea how to debug. When I boot up the computer, Firefox would usually restore the windows and tabs from the last session. But in the last few days, I am running into a new issue where Firefox doesn't open properly when it tries to restore the windows from the previous session. Here is a screenshot of what it looks like. The black window on the left is supposedly Firefox, but it's not responsive at all. The black is also from the KDE login splash screen (you can kind of see the logo). When I close that window from the task bar and reopen Firefox, it doesn't open any previous tabs, even pinned tabs. Another weird thing is that it logs me out of some sites, such as Reddit, which is weird and leads me to think some local data is getting wiped. This whole issue only happens sometimes, but more often than not and has only started in the last few days. I am guessing it started after a recent update.
 Any pointers on how I can dig into this further to figure out what's causing it?
 I am running KDE Plasma (X11), NVIDIA 3070 TI with nvidia driver package.
    submitted by    /u/Probotect0r  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Beginner’s Guide to Git]]></title>
        <id>http://maketecheasier.com/?p=13394</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/14185817/beginners-guide-to-git"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T15:25:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git is a wonderful program. It is a version control utility that allows you to seamlessly manage a file’s edit history. While this might seem simple and unimpressive, Git’s strength lies in the fact that you can extend this history to entire groups of files and directories.
    
This means that it is possible to use Git to track every change in every file for every directory. This is highly useful if you are doing a project where you want to have a rolling snapshot of everything that you are doing.
   

Content

What is Git?
Installing Git
Using Git for a Local Project
Using Git for Online Projects
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Determine Whether a Website Is Legit and Safe to Use
    
What is Git?
    
At its... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramces Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up Appointment Schedules in Google Calendar]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=800079</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/800079/google-calendar-appointment-schedules/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T15:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you have a business or service where you want to allow clients and customers to book appointments with you, take a look at the Appointment Schedules feature in Google Calendar.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Drive Will "Delete" Your Duplicate Files]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117729/google-drive-will-delete-your-duplicate-files/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117729/google-drive-will-delete-your-duplicate-files/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T14:56:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an effort to streamline Google Drive and help optimize your storage space, Google is rolling out a feature that is sure to be divisive among its users. Soon, it will replace all of your files and folders stored in multiple locations with shortcuts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzanne Humphries</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Steam Deck Update Includes the Feature You Asked For]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117726/new-steam-deck-update-includes-the-feature-you-asked-for/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117726/new-steam-deck-update-includes-the-feature-you-asked-for/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T14:51:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After the last Steam Deck update unlocked system-wide performance settings, gamers asked for the option to save these settings to individual games. And Valve listened—today’s update introduces per-game performance settings that you can quickly program through the Quick Access menu.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s Pixel Tablet Arrives in 2023 to Battle the iPad]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=804749</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/804749/googles-pixel-tablet-arrives-in-2023-to-battle-the-ipad/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T14:47:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s interest in Android tablets has gone up and down over the years (mostly down), but at Google I/O on Wednesday, the company revealed there will be a Pixel-branded tablet sometime in 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why does Debian use so much more memory than Arch?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uo2lyk/why_does_debian_use_so_much_more_memory_than_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uo2lyk/why_does_debian_use_so_much_more_memory_than_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T14:39:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been experimenting with putting together a desktop environment my brother can run on his crappy old laptop (2G ram single core). The first one I built on a base Arch install and the second on a Debian server install. I used the same packages, or if I couldn't find an exact match I was careful to install packages with the same memory footprint. I also disabled all the services that Debian was using and Arch was not. The result was the Arch system idles at 230 MB of ram and Debian idles at 445 MB. It may not seem like much, but with 2 gigs of ram it can make a difference. The Arch system is a lot more responsive, things happen like right freaking now while the Debian system is quite a bit more sluggish. Why is that?
    submitted by    /u/pressman57  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Arch Linux paradox noone seems to talk about]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uo2lms/the_arch_linux_paradox_noone_seems_to_talk_about/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uo2lms/the_arch_linux_paradox_noone_seems_to_talk_about/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T14:39:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The paradox that says
 "You will never complete the installation of Arch Linux"
 I started installing Arch linux about 3yrs ago and I got it to a point of working in about 45mins(much of that has to do with internet speed). Yet, every time I have to do something unique, I have to install more packages in the system to make it more complete. What I believed to be a complete installation of Arch Linux 3yrs ago, now I realise is very incomplete.
 And the fact that there are always new things coming. What wasnt possible in linux then is now being possible thanks to many people writing and improving free software to do real work. Means more puzzle pieces you stumble upon to make your system more complete, means there is always more steps to do.
 I think its better related to with the big bang, that thing which initialized the universe. We have a date when it started but not when big bang end. Why? Because it is still going on. Big Bang will end only when the universe ends. Same thing with Arch Linux. Your Arch Linux installation will be complete only after the death of technology.
    submitted by    /u/cy_narrator  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tutti i metodi per sospendere correttamente Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/05/se-dobbiamo-allontanarci-dalla.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/05/se-dobbiamo-allontanarci-dalla.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T14:36:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Se dobbiamo allontanarci dalla postazione PC per la pausa pranzo o solo per pochi minuti conviene metterlo in modalità sospensione, così da risparmiare energia o, nel caso dei computer portatili, aumentare la durata della batteria. La modalità sospensione consente di riprendere rapidamente da dove eravamo rimasti senza spegnere completamente il computer: avremo tutti i nostri file e programmi...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NVIDIA has open-sourced its Linux GPU kernel drivers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/linux/nvidia-has-open-sourced-its-linux-gpu-kernel-drivers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/linux/nvidia-has-open-sourced-its-linux-gpu-kernel-drivers/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T14:31:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NVIDIA has published the source code of its kernel modules for the R515 driver, using a dual licensing model that combines the GPL and MIT licenses, making the modules legally re-distributable. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cannot write password on lock screen after putting laptop to sleep]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uo2f1n/cannot_write_password_on_lock_screen_after/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uo2f1n/cannot_write_password_on_lock_screen_after/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T14:30:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have a problem with getting past lock screen after putting laptop to sleep. When I wake it up password field is write protected ( basically i can't type anything in it ), and it's not keyboard fault because when click CapsLock it notifies me about clicking it, and also i can get to tty. My display manager is Lightdm with gtk greeter and my DE is xfce4. Also I think that this started happening after I installed deepin DE for fun and then removed it. If anyone knew how I could tell me how I could fix it I would be grateful.
    submitted by    /u/Kuba_CXD  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kovol Sprint 120W Desktop Charger Review: Compact and Speedy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117285/kovol-sprint-120w-desktop-charger-review/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117285/kovol-sprint-120w-desktop-charger-review/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T14:24:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you start buying new smartphones, gaming handhelds, and tablets, you will eventually realize that there aren’t enough USB ports to go around when you need them. The Kovol Sprint 120W Desktop Charger is worth investing in to keep all of your devices juiced up and ready to roll at the same time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arnold Carreiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Historic Hotel Stay, Complementary Emotet Exposure included]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/historic-hotel-stay-complementary-emotet-exposure-included/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/historic-hotel-stay-complementary-emotet-exposure-included/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T14:02:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Historic Hotel of America serving up modern malware to their guests.  Why securing your inbox with more than just anti-malware engines is needed to prevent cybercrime attacks. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sponsored by InQuest</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Apple Watch Bands of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=750136</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/750136/the-best-apple-watch-bands-of-2021-for-any-activity/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are lots of bands available for your Apple Watch, and finding the right one can be tricky. Whether you need one for everyday wear, working out, or a classy affair, we’ve highlighted the best Apple Watch bands that we think you’ll love!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Max Buondonno</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Pixel 6a: praticamente uno smartphone Pixel 6 a 459 euro]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Google-Pixel-6a-praticamente-uno-smartphone-Pixel-6-a-459-euro_24507</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Google-Pixel-6a-praticamente-uno-smartphone-Pixel-6-a-459-euro_24507"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T13:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In occasione della sua Google I/O 2022 l'azienda fondata da Larry Page e Sergey Brin ha annunciato anche il nuovo smartphone Pixel 6a, un dispositivo piuttosto interessante considerato che gli aggiornamenti sono gestiti direttamente dalla società.Nel complesso Pixel 6a è sostanzialmente sovrapponibile con il Pixel 6 anche se il prezzo sarà ridotto a 459 euro. Sarà disponibile anche in Italia a partire dalla prossima stagione estiva. Visto che il Pixel 6 è stato ribassato a 579 euro, Pixel 6a rappresenta comunque un buon risparmio e non è escluso che la richiesta possa abbassarsi ulteriormente in futuro.

Rispetto al 'fratello maggiore' Pixel 6a monta un display leggermente più piccolo (15,5 cm).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[yay compilation spawning too many processes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uo0sgi/yay_compilation_spawning_too_many_processes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uo0sgi/yay_compilation_spawning_too_many_processes/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T13:13:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So I was installing sqlitestudio today, via yay. Much to my surprise, after a few seconds my PC went bonkers, running out of memory (16 GB). So I created an 8 GB swapfile, which also was not enough, and then proceeded with 32 GB, which succeeded. 
 I noticed there were up to 130 gcc processes spawned while compiling, or more because it was changing and my PC wasn't exactly responsive doing all that. Nonetheless, that's just a few too many I'd say, given I have a Ryzen 5600X for which nproc returns 12. My /etc/makepkg.conf isn't weird, it's just good old MAKEFLAGS="-j${nproc}" too. Still, it looks like maybe somewhere 12 is multiplied by 12 when choosing how many g++ processes to spawn, and I would like to know where could this be happening.
 I downloaded the source from github and tried compiling it myself with make -j${nproc}, it all went normal with 12 processes spawned. 
 PKGBUILD looks normal to me, although I'm definitely not an expert. 
 So any ideas as to what could be causing this? I didn't notice any issues with other builds, but I also don't build too many C++/Qt apps via yay.
    submitted by    /u/pooerh  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How can i change rgb TUF-GAMING A15]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uo0r02/how_can_i_change_rgb_tufgaming_a15/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uo0r02/how_can_i_change_rgb_tufgaming_a15/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T13:11:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been using arch linux for 3 months and i totally love it and doesn't intend to move back to Window. But there is one problem that i'm now using asus tuf gaming a15 laptop and by default as i remember i can fix my rgb keyboard by "armory crate". How can i install this application or is there any applications similar to this in arch linux? Please show me the way or comment a link with detail instruction \cry\ . I'm an Arch beginner
    submitted by    /u/ON_NO_  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roku Now Bundles Its Best Streaming Box with Its Best Remote]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117638/roku-now-bundles-its-best-streaming-box-with-its-best-remote/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117638/roku-now-bundles-its-best-streaming-box-with-its-best-remote/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T13:02:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roku products offer a premium experience at a low price. But if you want the best Roku products, meaning the Roku Ultra and the Voice Remote Pro, you need to buy them separately for $120. That’s just silly, so Roku is now bundling these devices together for $99.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forget Audible, Get a Library Card]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/116619/forget-audible-get-a-library-card/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/116619/forget-audible-get-a-library-card/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T13:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re paying for a monthly audiobook subscription to a service like Audible or Kobo Books, you may not have to. Public libraries are still a thing, and they’ve arrived in the digital age with apps that may enable you to save money by delivering thousands of audiobooks and other media for free.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Chadwick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 Cleaning Hacks for Removing Pet Stains and Odors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lifesavvy.com/127553/6-cleaning-hacks-for-removing-pet-stains-and-odors/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lifesavvy.com/127553/6-cleaning-hacks-for-removing-pet-stains-and-odors/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T13:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every pet owner has been there: an unexpected stain or odor left behind by your furry BFF. With just a few easy tips and common household products, though, you can take the hassle out of cleanup and keep your home looking (and smelling) fresh.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amanda Prahl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Starlink Internet, and Should You Use It?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=796749</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/796749/what-is-starlink-internet-and-should-you-use-it/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T13:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you live in a rural or remote area with unreliable or non-existent internet connectivity, Starlink is often touted as a solution for all your broadband woes. But what is it, and does it even make sense for you?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gaurav Shukla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grub theme boot error]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uo0cjx/grub_theme_boot_error/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uo0cjx/grub_theme_boot_error/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T12:51:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I just downloaded the "Xenlism Grub Theme" and installed it, without modifying anything. But, when I reboot, the following error is printed:  error: ../../grub-core/video/bitmap.c:70:invalid argument. 
 I searched everywhere on internet, but it's like nobody had this problem before. And the error itself don't help me very much.
 Does anyone already seen it?
    submitted by    /u/Kyre1a  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple abbandonerà Lightning in favore di USB-C nel 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Apple-abbandonera-Lightning-in-favore-di-USB-C-nel-2023_24506</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Apple-abbandonera-Lightning-in-favore-di-USB-C-nel-2023_24506"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T12:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Conosciamo la 'crociata' che l'Unione Europea ha avviato per far sì che l'industria utilizzi un caricabatterie universale e un'unica interfaccia. La scelta è ricaduta su USB-C che dovrà essere utilizzato su tutti gli smartphone, tablet, fotocamere digitali, console per videogiochi portatili, cuffie e auricolari venduti in Europa.Molto difficile, se non quasi impossibile, che il legislatore possa disporre uno standard per i sistemi di ricarica rapida: ogni produttore ne utilizza uno proprietario che non è compatibile con gli altri.Piuttosto che utilizzare USB-C sui suoi iPhone sembrava che Apple fosse orientata a rimuovere del tutto la porta usando esclusivamente la ricarica wireless.Stando a fonti vicine all'azienda di Cupertino e a quanto riferisce all'analista Ming-Chi Kuo, il 2023 potrebbe essere l'anno in cui Apple sostituirà la porta Lightning con USB-C.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rsync hanging on full backup]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/unzz9w/rsync_hanging_on_full_backup/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/unzz9w/rsync_hanging_on_full_backup/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T12:31:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, i am relatively new to Linux so bare with me. i am trying to clone my arch install to my USB flash drive but i'm having trouble. 
 i have tried the following -
 sudo mkfs.ext4 /dev/sdc1 (USB DRIVE)
 then mounting the drive under /media
 and finally running - 
 rsync -aAXHv --progress --exclude={"/dev/*","/proc/*","/sys/*","/dev/nvme0n1p2/*","/var/lib/dhcpcd/*","/tmp/*","/run/*","/mnt/*","/media/*","/lost+found"} / /Place/for/Backup
 Every time i do this the transfer rate eventually drops from MB/s to KB/s and its always different files so its not a file causing the issue and eventually it just hangs indefinitely, its almost as if it times out. 
 i have excluded the swap partition too. is the problem one of the flags i'm using? 
 my end goal is to have a copy of my install on a portable USB drive
 any help is appreciated!
    submitted by    /u/PWICHex  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD Graphics Driver Surpassing 4 Million Lines Of Code In Linux 5.19, NVIDIA Opens Up At 1 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMDGPU-4-Million</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMDGPU-4-Million"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Given the NVIDIA open-source kernel driver code announcement from yesterday and also the Linux 5.19 merge window coming up soon with a host of AMDGPU/AMDKFD kernel driver improvements and starting to prepare support for RDNA3, it's time for some fun with numbers around driver sizes...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come funziona davvero un Router?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2013/02/come-funziona-un-router.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2013/02/come-funziona-un-router.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T12:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[L'evoluzione di Internet ha cambiato profondamente il mondo, la tecnologia e le persone ed è difficile immaginarsi una vita senza Internet. Il dispositivo che rende possibile tutto questo si chiama Router, quella piccola scatola collegata alla presa a muro, con sopra diverse porte e lucette, che permette a tutti i dispositivi di connettersi contemporaneamente a Internet.

 Senza di esso, non...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Share Your Screen Using FaceTime]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=804184</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/804184/how-to-share-your-screen-using-facetime/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T12:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’d like to share what you’re looking at on your iPhone, iPad, or Mac’s screen with a friend who is far away, it’s as easy as making a FaceTime call now thanks to the built-in Share Screen feature. Here’s how to use it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[AMDGPU] Screen goes black with only cursor before losing display signal completely]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/unzdwg/amdgpu_screen_goes_black_with_only_cursor_before/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/unzdwg/amdgpu_screen_goes_black_with_only_cursor_before/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T11:58:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently got a new AMD card to replace my old 1660 Ti. Over the 2 months I've had the card, I've had about 4 or 5 occasions where the screen goes black and only the cursor shows, before I lose display signal completely. Attempting to wake it up by keyboard or mouse does not work. I have not tried resetting the monitor (i.e powering it off and back on). I am forced to reset the computer.
 I assume this is likely a driver issue due to AMDGPU reporting errors in dmesg.
 System info:
 GPU: AMD RX 6600 XT
 Mesa (AMDGPU) version: 22.0.3-1
 Display Manager: Xorg 21.1.3-6
 DE: KDE Plasma 5.24.5-1
 Window Manager: kwin 5.24.5-1
 Motherboard: Gigabyte B550M DS3H AC
 Display Output/Input: Male DP (GPU) to Male HDMI (monitor)
 Monitor: 1920x1080, 60Hz
 Kernel: linux-lts 5.15.37-1
    submitted by    /u/toast_ghost12  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Godot 4.0 Alpha 8 Game Engine Released With Some Nice Improvements]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Godot-4.0-Alpha-8</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Godot-4.0-Alpha-8"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T11:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Godot 4.0 continues working its way towards release as the most acclaimed open-source game engine. Godot 4.0 brings Vulkan rendering, OpenXR support, and a ton of other features covered in the past few years for making it more competitive with commercial game engines. Out this morning is Godot 4.0 Alpha 8 with a few more improvements worth noting...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Wi-Fi for Everything? Here’s Why You Shouldn’t]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=800329</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/800329/using-wi-fi-for-everything-heres-why-you-shouldnt/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T11:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wi-Fi is ubiquitous at this point but that doesn’t mean you should default to using it exclusively. Here’s why you should skip using Wi-Fi in favor of Ethernet where you can.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Fitzpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More AMD RDNA3 Code Prepared For Linux 5.19, RADV Begins Landing Task Shaders]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMD-RDNA3-More-5.19-Tasks-RADV</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMD-RDNA3-More-5.19-Tasks-RADV"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T10:39:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While open-source fans this morning are celebrating NVIDIA finally publishing open-source kernel driver code as a step to opening up their driver, open-source AMD Radeon driver developers are proceeding as normal and undeterred by NVIDIA's open kernel-only approach. Another batch of AMD graphics code was sent in this morning to DRM-Next and then over in user-space Mesa's RADV Vulkan driver has landed more task shader code...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MSI Clutch GM41 Lightweight Wireless Mouse Review: Versatile Featherweight]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=798503</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/798503/msi-clutch-gm41-wireless-gaming-mouse-review/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T10:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MSI’s Clutch GM41 Lightweight Wireless mouse stands out from the crowd as an impressively versatile option for premium PC gaming, portability, and critical customization. With extensive battery life and few complaints to its name, the Clutch GM41 Lightweight Wireless is a serious setup contender.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arnold Carreiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thunderbird 102 to include an improved Import Tool]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178535</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/05/12/thunderbird-102-to-include-an-improved-import-tool/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T09:54:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The team that is developing the Thunderbird email client has been working on the next major release of Thunderbird for some time. One of the new features of Thunderbird 102 is an […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Thunderbird 102 to include an improved Import Tool appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It's normal that the bluetooth is spending 2W ?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/unxgbr/its_normal_that_the_bluetooth_is_spending_2w/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/unxgbr/its_normal_that_the_bluetooth_is_spending_2w/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T09:50:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi! 
 Is this normal this usage of battery of btusb? I'm using a MX Master 3 mouse. 
 Here an image: https://imgur.com/a/Ciy0FTJ
 ​
 Have a nice day!
    submitted by    /u/jcfitn  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Releases CBL-Mariner 1.0 May 2022 Linux Distro Update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=CBL-Mariner-1.0-May-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=CBL-Mariner-1.0-May-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T09:41:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While this week Microsoft issued a production release of CBL-Mariner 2.0 as its in-house Linux distribution, they are continuing to maintain CBL-Mariner 1.0 for the time being and have overnight issued its newest monthly release...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[systemd-oomd]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/unxbb9/systemdoomd/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/unxbb9/systemdoomd/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T09:39:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi,
 The documentation for systemd-oomd is not very great. (Or maybe I can't understand it.)
 Could someone please give me instructions on how to set it up?
 Also, should I setup oomd? What happens is that once in a week, my system completely hangs. Just straight up unresponsive. Only way I can end this is to just forcefully turn it off. I do have 8 GB swap with 8GB RAM.
 Thanks.
    submitted by    /u/abrattic  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NVIDIA CUDA 11.7 Brings Lazy Loading, Open GPU Kernel Driver Compatibility]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=NVIDIA-CUDA-11.7</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=NVIDIA-CUDA-11.7"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T09:16:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Released on Wednesday alongside the R515 NVIDIA Linux driver beta and the open-source NVIDIA GPU kernel driver announcement was the launch of CUDA 11.7...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google I/O: novità RCS, Wallet, Workspace e Meet, ricerca multipla e Assistant]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Google-I-O-novita-RCS-Wallet-Workspace-e-Meet-ricerca-multipla-e-Assistant_24504</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Google-I-O-novita-RCS-Wallet-Workspace-e-Meet-ricerca-multipla-e-Assistant_24504"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T08:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Android è il sistema operativo più popolare al mondo: sono oltre tre miliardi i dispositivi che risultano attivi su base mensile e che si servono della piattaforma Google. Solo nell'ultimo anno sono stati attivati ​​più di un miliardo di nuovi smartphone Android. Cresce però anche l'utilizzo in ambito automotive, sulle smart TV, sugli smartwatch e su altri dispositivi intelligenti.Così, Android non poteva non essere al centro dell'attenzione durante l'evento Google I/O di quest'anno.
Aggiornamenti a Google Messaggi con supporto RCS
 I messaggi basati sull'utilizzo del protocollo RCS (Rich Communication Services) rappresentano l'evoluzione dei vecchi SMS, il cui utilizzo è ormai ridotto ai minimi termini.L'idea di Google è quella di usare uno standard condiviso per trasferire i messaggi tra gli utenti svincolandosi sempre di più dalle app di messaggistica proprietarie (in questo segmento l'azienda guidata da Sundar Pichai ha fallito ripetutamente…).Google racconta di aver lavorato a stretto contatto con gli operatori di telecomunicazioni per estendere il supporto a livello globale e portare la compatibilità con RCS sulle reti dei singoli provider.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Maps Immersive View: cos'è e come funziona]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Google-Maps-Immersive-View-cos-e-e-come-funziona_24503</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Google-Maps-Immersive-View-cos-e-e-come-funziona_24503"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T07:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[L'utilizzo delle tecnologie per la generazione in tempo reale di modelli 3D è sempre più utilizzata su Android. Si pensi agli animali 3D Google che prendono forma nel browser e grazie alla realtà aumentata si integrano e interagiscono con l'ambiente reale.Alla base della 'magia' c'è la tecnologia ARCore che Google ha progressivamente affinato nel corso degli ultimi anni e che è pronta per nuove coinvolgenti 'sfide'.Durante l'evento Google I/O 2022 l'azienda di Mountain View ha presentato Immersive View, una modalità che presto sarà attivabile dagli utenti di Google Maps che dispongono di dispositivi compatibili con la tecnologia ARCore. Immersive View permette di ottenere una fedele rappresentazione delle principali città del mondo realizzata combinando le informazioni provenienti dagli archivi di Street View con le immagini satellitari e le foto aeree che Google conserva nei suoi server.Il risultato lascia davvero a bocca aperta: la modellazione 3D delle città appare perfetta e l'utente può guardare da qualunque prospettiva effettuando zoom, optando per una vista più panoramica e concentrandosi sulla disposizione di monumenti e punti d'interesse.Il bello è che Immersive View si integra con tutti gli altri strumenti forniti da Google Maps: è quindi possibile visualizzare le informazioni di traffico in tempo reale, la disposizione di negozi, bar, ristoranti e altre attività, accedere agli ambienti interni di tanti locali e così via.Per rendervi conto della portata della novità, date un'occhiata a questo breve video dimostrativo che Google ha diffuso in queste ore.Nella fase di lancio, Immersive View sarà disponibile soltanto per le città di Los Angeles, Londra, New York, San Francisco e Tokyo.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft: May Windows updates cause AD authentication failures]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-may-windows-updates-cause-ad-authentication-failures/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-may-windows-updates-cause-ad-authentication-failures/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T07:11:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft is investigating a known issue causing authentication failures for some Windows services after installing updates released during the May 2022 Patch Tuesday. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Windows 11 version 23H2 build released with Suggested Actions feature]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178532</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/05/12/first-windows-11-version-23h2-build-released-with-suggested-actions-feature/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T04:23:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft released two new Insider builds for the company's Windows 11 operating system this week. The first, Windows 11 build 25115, marks the beginning of the development of the 2023 feature update […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post First Windows 11 version 23H2 build released with Suggested Actions feature appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Help test nvidia-open]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/unpt7t/help_test_nvidiaopen/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/unpt7t/help_test_nvidiaopen/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T01:53:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After quite a long evening, we finally managed to package the new nvidia-open drivers. They are now in [testing] and I'd like for some extra opinions with these drivers as they are quite experimental. I packaged them to the best of my knowledge but again, they might be unusable for most purposes. Those with compatible hardware (fairly recent hardware) can install the package and give it a spin. Keep in mind that they are at the moment severely limited as opposed to the blob drivers.
 Take special note of the post install note:
  
In order to boot this on non-datacenter cards, you currently need to set NVreg_OpenRmEnableUnsupportedGpus=1 during module load You can try it like this: modprobe nvidia NVreg_OpenRmEnableUnsupportedGpus=1 but you should likely set it in a /etc/modprobe.d file to make it permanent.
  
I'd like to collect some feedback directly in this thread.
    submitted by    /u/Svenstaro  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 to show suggested actions when copying data to the clipboard]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-to-show-suggested-actions-when-copying-data-to-the-clipboard/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-to-show-suggested-actions-when-copying-data-to-the-clipboard/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T00:38:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft is testing a new 'Suggested Actions' feature in Windows 11 Dev builds where the operating system suggests actions you can take with data you copy into the clipboard. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use Access Dots to Find Out If Apps Are Using Microphone and Camera in the Background]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=357710</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/13775856/prevent-android-apps-using-microphone-camera-background"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even if you absolutely love Android, sometimes iOS adds a feature you would love to have, such as extra security features. Since iOS 14, there is an alert feature in the form of a small dot that lets users know whenever apps are using the microphone or camera. You don’t have to switch to an iPhone, though. Android users just need the free app Access Dots for similar security alerts on Android 12.
   

Content

Why You Need Alerts
Determining App Permissions
Purpose of Access Dots
Using Access Dots
Troubleshooting
Using Access Dots in Android 12
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Customize Your Android’s Lock Screen
    
Why You Need Alerts
    
Apps initially have to ask permission to gain access to your camera and/or microphone. There’s just one problem with that, though. Once permission is granted, apps can use your microphone or... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Crystal Crowder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GDM proxying all journal writes for non-Gnome Sessions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uno27v/gdm_proxying_all_journal_writes_for_nongnome/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uno27v/gdm_proxying_all_journal_writes_for_nongnome/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T00:22:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GDM redirects stdout and stderr for processes launched in a session to the systemd journal. When starting an alternative (i.e. not Gnome) session from GDM (in my case, awesomewm) all of the journal entries show as logged from `gdm-x-session. When running Gnome, the entries are correctly attributed to their application.
 How can I ensure that the correct originating application is passed through to the journal when not running Gnome?
 Edit: Yes, I realize that this isn't necessarily Arch specific; however, it's not clear where else I could conceivably ask. r/gnome is likely to go down the rabbit hole of, "Why would you use gdm if you're not using Gnome?" which isn't going to get me anywhere.
    submitted by    /u/nalthien  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aggiungiamo affascinanti background al nostro Linux Mint Cinnamon]]></title>
        <id>3565|20220512000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/linux-27/aggiungiamo-affascinanti-background-linux-mint-cinnamon-3565"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Utilizzando Linux Mint sempre più assiduamente ho avuto modo di apprezzare sin da subito la possibilità di apportare una enormità di personalizzazioni all'ambiente scelto, Cinnamon nel caso specifico. Occorre premettere che ogni uscita di Linux Mint porta con sé una serie di sfondi del desktop particolarmente accattivanti e affascinanti, ma soltanto delle edizioni più recenti, ossia abbandonando i background delle versioni più datate, succedutesi nel tempo. Con questo articolo vedremo invece come "recuperare" i background di alcune "vecchie" edizioni di Linux Mint, Tara e Tessa in particolare.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 KB5013943 update causes 0xc0000135 application errors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-kb5013943-update-causes-0xc0000135-application-errors/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-kb5013943-update-causes-0xc0000135-application-errors/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T21:38:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 users are receiving 0xc0000135 errors when attempting to launch applications after installing the recent Windows 11 KB5013943 cumulative update. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Unlock Android Phone’s Safe Folder]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=345215</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/13532762/unlock-android-phones-safe-folder"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you have files on your Android phone that you don’t want others to view, then you should use what is known as a Safe folder. This allows you to encrypt and hide your private files using a pattern or PIN.  Follow the methods below to unlock your Android Safe folder and move your private files to it.
   

Content

What Is the Android Safe Folder?
Create Safe in Android Phone Using "Files by Google" App
Temporary Safe in Android: Create and View Secret Folders 
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:5 Best Privacy-Focused Browsers for Android and iOS
    
What Is the Android Safe Folder?
    
An Android Safe folder is a hidden and allows you to securely store your private files and folders using a PIN, pattern, or password, as if it were a digital vault. Only certain Android phone models... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sayak Boral</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NVIDIA Releases Open-Source GPU Kernel Modules]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/unjym5/nvidia_releases_opensource_gpu_kernel_modules/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/unjym5/nvidia_releases_opensource_gpu_kernel_modules/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T21:04:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/w0330  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s the Best Antivirus for Windows 10 and 11? (Is Microsoft Defender Good Enough?)]]></title>
        <id>http://www.howtogeek.com/?p=225385</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/225385/what%e2%80%99s-the-best-antivirus-for-windows-10-is-windows-defender-good-enough/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 10 and Windows 11 won’t hassle you to install an antivirus like Windows 7 did. Since Windows 8, Windows now includes a built-in free antivirus called Microsoft Defender. But is it really the best for protecting your PC — or even just good enough?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lowell Heddings</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Noob here, I removed pacman for some reason, how can I get it back?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/unjqmn/noob_here_i_removed_pacman_for_some_reason_how/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/unjqmn/noob_here_i_removed_pacman_for_some_reason_how/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T20:55:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I did pacman -Rdd pacman 
 Edit: Solved! Thank you guys ;)
    submitted by    /u/Dovahkiin3641  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung Apparently Won’t Redesign the Galaxy Z Flip for 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=804622</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/804622/samsung-apparently-won%e2%80%99t-redesign-the-galaxy-z-flip-for-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T20:45:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Galaxy Z Fold and Flip are some of the best Android phones right now, at least in terms of uniqueness. The next Galaxy Z Flip phone just leaked, and despite rumors to the contrary, it looks pretty much exactly like the current Flip.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Awesome Ford F-150 Lightning Electric Truck Features]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117468/7-awesome-ford-f-150-lightning-electric-truck-features/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117468/7-awesome-ford-f-150-lightning-electric-truck-features/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T20:42:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While Tesla and newcomers like Rivian have dominated the electric vehicle news lately, it’s time for America’s best-selling pickup to shine. We’re talking about the F-150 Lightning, Ford’s new all-electric truck.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s Pixel 6a And Pixel 7 Look Like Its Best Phones Yet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=804697</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/804697/googles-pixel-6a-and-pixel-7-look-like-its-best-phones-yet/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T20:14:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google had its yearly I/O event on Wednesday, where the company showed off a bunch of new hardware products and software features. Perhaps the most exciting reveals were the Google Pixel 6a and Pixel 7 series, which are coming later this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bizarre sound issue]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/unis3j/bizarre_sound_issue/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/unis3j/bizarre_sound_issue/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T20:11:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently started having this issue, for seemingly no particular reason, where I had no sound after booting. However, there is sound at boot. The sound works fine until I see my cursor loading something and stops. I've come to realize I can extend how long it takes for it to stop working by immediately starting a task that uses sound at startup, like spotify, but as soon as it is closed, the sound deactivates.
 Also, while the sound doesn't work, neither does music playback on spotify (music fails to load at all), nor does youtube video playback.
 Anybody know anything about this bizarre issue?
    submitted by    /u/Gwynsaov  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NVIDIA Transitioning To Official, Open-Source Linux GPU Kernel Driver]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31114</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31114"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T20:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The day has finally come: NVIDIA IS PUBLISHING THEIR LINUX GPU KERNEL MODULES AS OPEN-SOURCE! To much excitement and a sign of the times, the embargo has just expired on this super-exciting milestone that many of us have been hoping to see for many years. Over the past two decades NVIDIA has offered great Linux driver support with their proprietary driver stack, but with the success of AMD's open-source driver effort going on for more than a decade, many have been calling for NVIDIA to open up their drivers. Their user-space software is remaining closed-source but as of today they have formally opened up their Linux GPU kernel modules and will be maintaining it moving forward. Here's the scoop on this landmark open-source decision at NVIDIA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Releases Flutter 3.0 for Creating Cross-platform Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=803764</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/803764/google-releases-flutter-3.0-for-creating-cross-platform-apps/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T20:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s ‘Flutter’ framework allows software developers to create applications that run on mobile devices, macOS, Windows, Linux, and even web browsers. Flutter 3.0 was just announced, which might power more of your apps in the near future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your Next Android App Purchase May Only Cost 5 Cents]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117562/your-next-android-app-purchase-may-only-cost-5-cents/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117562/your-next-android-app-purchase-may-only-cost-5-cents/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T20:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re knee-deep in Google’s I/O developer conference, and the company has announced some odd changes for the Play Store. Some of these changes focus on security, while others simply help app developers eke more money out of customers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Cracks Down on Android Game Cheating With New API]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=804045</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/804045/google-cracks-down-on-android-game-cheating-with-new-api/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T20:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cheating is an ever-present problem for many games, especially on platforms like PC and Android where it’s easier to modify a game’s files. Google is now rolling out the Play Integrity API on Android, aimed specifically at limiting cheats and other modifications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Pixel Watch Arrives This Fall with Fitbit Integration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117662/the-pixel-watch-arrives-this-fall-with-fitbit-integration/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117662/the-pixel-watch-arrives-this-fall-with-fitbit-integration/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T19:56:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After years of leaks and rumors, Google has finally announced its first smartwatch. The Pixel Watch arrives this fall alongside the Pixel 7 smartphone. Details are still a bit scarce, but Google tells us some interesting things about the Pixel Watch, including its Fitbit integration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US charges hacker for breaching brokerage accounts, securities fraud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-charges-hacker-for-breaching-brokerage-accounts-securities-fraud/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-charges-hacker-for-breaching-brokerage-accounts-securities-fraud/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T19:51:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Department of Justice (DoJ) has charged Idris Dayo Mustapha for a range of cybercrime activities that took place between 2011 and 2018, resulting in financial losses estimated to over $5,000,000. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Teased a Pixel 7 Series and Pixel Tablet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117667/google-teased-a-pixel-7-series-and-pixel-tablet/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117667/google-teased-a-pixel-7-series-and-pixel-tablet/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T19:39:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At today’s Google’s I/O 2022 conference, the company announced a ton of fantastic-looking new hardware, including the upcoming flagship Pixel 7 and Pixel 7 Pro phones, and even an Android-based Pixel tablet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzanne Humphries</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save Up to $500 on Bluetti Power Station Deals]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=488033</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15288940/bluetti-power-station-mothers-day"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While you’re prepping for your summer plans, you may be worried about how you will power all your devices while you camp, have outdoor parties, etc. This is a great time to check out Bluetti Power Stations. They can power all your devices and even some appliances and will recharge via AC power, a car charger, or solar panels. These deals can save you up to $500 and will be valid through May 12. Also check out the Bluetti Instagram page and share a photo and a story about your mom to celebrate her for a few more days and a chance to win your own power station.
    
Bluetti AC300 + B300 Combo
    

    
Up to four B300 battery modules can be attached to the modular Bluetti AC300 to equal 12,288Wh total power. Pick up this expandable power center, and you’re already partway there with one module. The combo can work with solar power as well, with the battery module charging up completely in just 1.5 hours. You’ll be all set whether you’re looking... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Unveils Pixel Buds Pro With ANC And All-Day Battery]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117654/google-unveils-pixel-buds-pro-with-anc-and-all-day-battery/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117654/google-unveils-pixel-buds-pro-with-anc-and-all-day-battery/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T19:21:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, at its annual I/O developer event, Google announced a new set of earbuds, the Pixel Buds Pro. These are Google’s first premium set of earbuds and look to take on Apple’s AirPods Pro with many pro-level features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Pixel 6a Arrives at an Awesome Price]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117645/the-pixel-6a-arrives-at-an-awesome-price/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117645/the-pixel-6a-arrives-at-an-awesome-price/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T19:12:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As expected, Google revealed the Pixel 6a smartphone during its I/O 2022 conference. Most leaks related to this phone turned out to be true, and impressively, it costs just $450. Pre-orders open on July 21st, though, so prepare to wait a bit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is ApeCoin?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=803581</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/803581/what-is-apecoin/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ApeCoin has recently captured the public’s attention like many other memecoins. However, unlike Dogecoin or Shiba Inu, ApeCoin might actually provide some real utility and be here for the long haul.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>RJ Fulton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unable to downgrade package due to circular dependency]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ungvf0/unable_to_downgrade_package_due_to_circular/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ungvf0/unable_to_downgrade_package_due_to_circular/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T18:45:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm trying to downgrade xorg-server since the latest version is giving me AddScreen/ScreenInit failed for driver errors. However when running sudo pacman -U /var/cache/pacman/pkg/xorg-server-1.20.13-2-x86_64.pkg.tar.zst I get:
 error: failed to commit transaction (conflicting files) xorg-server: /usr/bin/cvt exists in filesystem (owned by libxcvt) xorg-server: /usr/share/man/man1/cvt.1.gz exists in filesystem (owned by libxcvt) Errors occurred, no packages were upgraded. 
 And whenever I try to sudo pacman -Rsn libxcvt I get:
 error: failed to prepare transaction (could not satisfy dependencies) :: removing libxcvt breaks dependency 'libxcvt' required by xorg-server 
 What is the proper way to downgrade xorg-server in this situation?
    submitted by    /u/AndreVallestero  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More AMD RDNA3 / GFX11 Enablement Patches Merged Into LLVM 15.0]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMDGPU-More-LLVM-GFX11</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMDGPU-More-LLVM-GFX11"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T18:35:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AMD's graphics driver engineers continue being very active in volleying new open-source driver patches for GFX11 and other blocks making up their next-generation RDNA3 graphics processors...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft: Windows 10 20H2 has reached end of service]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-windows-10-20h2-has-reached-end-of-service/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-windows-10-20h2-has-reached-end-of-service/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T18:12:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft says multiple editions of Windows 10 20H2 and Windows 10 1909 have reached their end of service (EOS) on this month's Patch Tuesday, on May 10, 2022. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome Will Protect Your Credit Cards With Virtual Numbers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=804341</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/804341/chrome-will-protect-your-credit-cards-with-virtual-numbers/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T18:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers and thieves love credit card numbers, which is why many services have popped up over the years to create alias card numbers for online purchases that protect your real information. Google is now building a similar feature into Chrome and Android.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add and Remove Words in Your Google Docs Personal Dictionary]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=798557</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/798557/google-docs-add-remove-words-to-dictionary/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T18:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not every word you include in a document is in the dictionary. You may write a name of a person or product that you wouldn’t find in Webster’s Dictionary. Luckily, Google Docs offers a personal dictionary for you to use.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can't install, getting "Could not strap in packages: 256" and "pacman -Sy archlinux-keyring" isn't helping, using current image.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/unftcn/cant_install_getting_could_not_strap_in_packages/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/unftcn/cant_install_getting_could_not_strap_in_packages/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T17:57:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey all, just curious if anyone is having issues downloading packages to install Arch? I'm not sure what else to do because that trick is my usual go-to and it's not working this time.
    submitted by    /u/HelpDeskTicket  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Replacement Earbud Tips]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/11280/the-best-replacement-earbud-tips/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/11280/the-best-replacement-earbud-tips/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T17:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The little silicone tips that let your earbuds fit in your ear are easy to lose. Luckily, they’re also easy to replace, with a semi-standard size that will fit about 90% of the earbuds on the market. Here are the best.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Crider</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[YouTube videos won't load when using ANY browser]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/unfa71/youtube_videos_wont_load_when_using_any_browser/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/unfa71/youtube_videos_wont_load_when_using_any_browser/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T17:33:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EDIT: SOLUTION:
 For everyone with the same problem: how u/Santeriabro and u/SystemZ1337 suggested:
 INSTALL pipewire-pulse with sudo pacman -S pipewire-pulse and let it replace PulseAudio:
 After it's done, reboot and it will be fixed! Thanks guys!
 ​
 Hello, so today I've ran into an issue where as the title says, I am not able to get videos on youtube loaded. I'm getting infinite loading circle and after a while text saying "If the video doesn't load shortly, try restarting your device". appears
 I've tried following browsers:
 Firefox (+ private browsing without addons)
 Brave
 Falcon
 LibreWolf
 ​
 This started happening today. Win10 works fine. I've updated my system yesterday. Could that be the cause? Anyone got the same problem? Thanks!
 ​
 EDIT2: Netflix and probably all other similiar websites won't work
    submitted by    /u/DominiCzech  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[make apps startup faster]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/unf7ib/make_apps_startup_faster/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/unf7ib/make_apps_startup_faster/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T17:30:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[i have a pretty much fresh arch install
 when i boot in to arch i try to open a program and it can take 15-20 seconds for it to open (only the first time the second time doesn't even take a second)
 is there a way to make the first launch faster?
 im using i3wm if that changes anything
    submitted by    /u/Kiing_Watermelon  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple May Finally Kill the Lighting Jack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117597/apple-may-finally-kill-the-lighting-jack/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117597/apple-may-finally-kill-the-lighting-jack/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T17:13:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another year, another rumor about the iPhone ditching Lightning for USB-C. But this rumor may be rooted in solid ground. Not just because it comes from a reputable source, but because current circumstance is forcing Apple away from the outdated Lightning standard.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get Apple’s Latest AirPods Pro for $74 Off]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=804570</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/804570/get-apples-latest-airpods-pro-for-74-off/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T17:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some weeks are better than others when it comes to awesome offers, and this one ranks higher up on the list. Today, we’ve uncovered a mound of savings on new Apple AirPods Pro, Google Wi-Fi mesh systems, Xbox Game Pass Ultimate, and more. Let’s get to it!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zach Laidlaw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Install Linux in VirtualBox]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=796988</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/796988/how-to-install-linux-in-virtualbox/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T17:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to try out a Linux distribution, you may want to do it in a virtual machine (VM) before dual-booting or completely overwriting your system. Choose a distribution and let’s run it in a VM using VirtualBox.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mohammed Abubakar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything You Need To Start Building Mechanical Keyboards]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117606/7007-autosave-v1/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117606/7007-autosave-v1/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T16:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Crider</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Programmi di Benchmark del PC Windows su CPU, disco e GPU]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2015/03/programmi-di-benchmark-test-pc-cpu.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2015/03/programmi-di-benchmark-test-pc-cpu.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T16:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I computer di oggi sono davvero molto potenti, eppure capita ancora di vedere computer che rallentano e che vanno in sofferenza dopo aver aperto numerosi programmi o dopo aver avviato un gioco particolarmente pesante. Si può decidere quindi di comprare un nuovo computer, oppure di cambiare soltanto la RAM, la scheda video, il disco o il fornitore di connessione internet per migliorare la...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OTP, cos'è e come funziona il codice usato per l'autenticazione a due fattori]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=OTP-cos-e-e-come-funziona-il-codice-usato-per-l-autenticazione-a-due-fattori_24502</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=OTP-cos-e-e-come-funziona-il-codice-usato-per-l-autenticazione-a-due-fattori_24502"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T16:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Al crescere delle minacce informatiche è diventato sempre più indispensabile adottare strumenti di sicurezza per la protezione dei propri dati. Il nome utente e la password sono dati insufficienti a garantire elevati standard di sicurezza perché sono facili da sottrarre e possono essere utilizzati da soggetti non autorizzati. Ne abbiamo parlato anche in occasione del World Password Day.Molte applicazioni online chiedono oggi agli utenti di aggiungere un ulteriore livello di sicurezza al proprio account e lo fanno abilitando l'autenticazione a due fattori o 2FA (two factor authentication).Abbiamo visto cos'è l'autenticazione a due fattori e sappiamo che esistono vari metodi per implementarla e utilizzarla, alcuni molto più di sicuri di altri. Ad esempio gli SMS sono meno sicuri nell'ambito di un sistema per l'autenticazione a due fattori: la crescita vorticosa del numero di attacchi SIM swap ne è la conferma.
Codici OTP: cosa sono
 Acronimo di One-time password, gli OTP sono codici che vengono generati sul dispositivo dell'utente e che sono validi, in combinazione con altri fattori (ad esempio username e password), per autenticarsi e ottenere l'accesso a un sito Web o un servizio online.Sono anche comunemente utilizzati per apporre la firma digitale remota, utile per sottoscrivere documenti digitali così come se vi si fosse applicata la propria firma autografa.Gli OTP sono anche conosciuti come 'password usa e getta' perché restano validi per breve tempo e in ogni caso solo per una singola sessione di accesso o una specifica transazione.I codici OTP vengono generati da parte di apposite app di autenticazione installabili e avviabili su un dispositivo mobile o su un computer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[* is not in the sudoers file]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/undku2/is_not_in_the_sudoers_file/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/undku2/is_not_in_the_sudoers_file/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T16:18:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, today I stupidly merged a pacnew sudoers file with meld. I have now lost all elevated privileges. I now know that this was not the correct way to handle this but the problem remains. Is there a way to fix this problem I have created? I've searched and tried a few things , but most everything requires some elevated privileges, which I no longer have. 
 Thanks for any help
    submitted by    /u/delusion74  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Home Screen Shortcuts Are the Best Android Feature You’re Not Using]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=803136</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/803136/home-screen-shortcuts-are-the-best-android-feature-youre-not-using/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T16:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Android home screen is known for being highly customizable. There are third-party launchers, icon packs, and tons of widgets to choose from. But you may not know about one of the handiest home screen features: Shortcuts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Should You Store Tomatoes in the Fridge?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lifesavvy.com/128593/should-you-store-tomatoes-in-the-fridge/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lifesavvy.com/128593/should-you-store-tomatoes-in-the-fridge/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T16:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The return of warm weather means the return of warm weather produce and, arguably, one of the most popular selections is the tomato. When it comes to keeping them fresh, though, should you be popping your tomatoes in the fridge?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shea Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HP fixes bug letting attackers overwrite firmware in over 200 models]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hp-fixes-bug-letting-attackers-overwrite-firmware-in-over-200-models/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hp-fixes-bug-letting-attackers-overwrite-firmware-in-over-200-models/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T15:53:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HP has released BIOS updates today to fix two high-severity vulnerabilities affecting a wide range of PC and notebook products, which might allow arbitrary code execution. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The International Scout Could Return as an EV Off-Roader]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117571/the-international-scout-could-return-as-an-ev-off-roader/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117571/the-international-scout-could-return-as-an-ev-off-roader/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T15:44:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The iconic International Scout was ahead of its time as the first SUV, originally manufactured from 1961 to 1980. And while it’s still a hard-to-find classic collector vehicle, Volkswagen wants to revive the off-roader as a new EV for the United States.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Sed in Linux for Basic Shell Tasks]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=470666</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15288442/use-sed-in-linux"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sed is a simple UNIX program. It does not create and edit files. It only modifies the data that passes through its input and presents the modified data on its output. Despite that, sed is considered to be one of the most powerful UNIX utilities that you will encounter in Linux, especially when it is combined with other programs in your system.
    
This article aims to teach the basics of how to use this tiny program. Further, it will also give a brief overview of the UNIX philosophy and how that idea is important in understanding how your computer works.
   

Content

What Is the UNIX Philosophy?
How Does Sed Work?
The Basics of Using Sed
1. Selecting and Trimming Text Streams
2. Removing Text
3. Adding New Text
4. Text Substitution and Stream Manipulation
5. Using Text Substitution with Files
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:5... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramces Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Audio Stopped working seemingly out of nowhere.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/unc2w4/audio_stopped_working_seemingly_out_of_nowhere/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/unc2w4/audio_stopped_working_seemingly_out_of_nowhere/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T15:12:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After powering on the machine this morning all seemed normal, when changing volume settings the normal pop sound effect was heard. Launched a RPGXP game using Wine. The game functioned perfectly yesterday and today I noticed missing music but some sound effects remained working. I did some trouble shooting thinking the files were gone but when I attempted to play them in vlc there was nothing. I now no longer heard the popping from changing volume and all audio was gone. Running soundest on any audio device gave no results. From here I noticed YouTube videos are forever loading and no audio at all out of anything on all outputs tried. Using KDE Plasma as the DE and attempted reinstalling of pulse and Alsa with no success.Still pretty new to Arch and Linux in general so any info that may be needed please let me know and I will post. Thanks for any help!
 ​
 EDIT: Rebooted system again after this post and all is fixed. Not a single clue what went wrong, what broke what. No idea why this reboot worked but the previous 4 did not. If anyone still has insight it is appreciated but the problem is seemingly gone at this time.
 EDIT AGAIN: The problem is back so no real solution has been found. Have not a clue what could be causing it. If there is any ideas out there the help is much appreciated
 ​
    submitted by    /u/CutletSSupreme  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung's Galaxy Z Fold 4 Leak Hints at a Large Cover Display]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117568/samsungs-galaxy-z-fold-4-leak-hints-at-a-large-cover-display/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117568/samsungs-galaxy-z-fold-4-leak-hints-at-a-large-cover-display/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T15:10:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new leak suggests a gorgeous design for Samsung’s upcoming 2022  flagship smartphone, the Galaxy Z Fold 4. The rendered images have revealed a design that’s fairly comparable to the previous-generation Z Fold 3 but a new configuration for the cameras.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzanne Humphries</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch black screen after login then back to login screen]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/unc1a6/arch_black_screen_after_login_then_back_to_login/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/unc1a6/arch_black_screen_after_login_then_back_to_login/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T15:10:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fresh install of arch using archinstall. When I log into my user, it gives a temporary black screen then goes back to login screen as if nothing happened. I have redone the installation 3 times and same issue each time. Any fix?
    submitted by    /u/Yhiz47_  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alexa vs Siri vs Google Assistant: qual è il miglior assistente vocale?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/05/alexa-vs-siri-vs-google-assistant-qual.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/05/alexa-vs-siri-vs-google-assistant-qual.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T15:07:00.006Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gli assistenti vocali più diffusi sono Amazon Alexa, Apple Siri e Google Assistant, presenti su un elevato numero di dispositivi elettronici ed elettrodomestici. Tutti gli assistenti sono buoni ma se volessimo valutare il miglior assistente vocale disponibile, chi vincerebbe la sfida tra i tre? Non è semplice decretare un vincitore, ma possiamo analizzare tutti i pregi e gli inevitabili difetti...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 10 Invoicing & Accounting Tools For Freelancers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/?p=9460</id>
        <link href="https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/accounting-invoicing-services-for-freelance-designers/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T15:01:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Freelancers usually handle many jobs at the same time, and the client is not the only reason who drives freelancers nuts. Being your own boss and manager]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rishabh Agarwal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 Ways to Jump to a Cell or Range in Google Sheets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=802220</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/802220/jump-to-a-cell-or-range-in-google-sheets/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Navigating a large spreadsheet can become increasingly difficult as you add more data. What if you want to quickly go to a particular cell or range in Google Sheets? Here, we’ll show you a few ways to do this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New stealthy Nerbian RAT malware spotted in ongoing attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-stealthy-nerbian-rat-malware-spotted-in-ongoing-attacks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-stealthy-nerbian-rat-malware-spotted-in-ongoing-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T14:49:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new remote access trojan called Nerbian RAT has been discovered that includes a rich set of features, including the ability to evade detection and analysis by researchers. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[App di messaggistica costrette alla scansione dei messaggi: salta la crittografia end-to-end?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=App-di-messaggistica-costrette-alla-scansione-dei-messaggi-salta-la-crittografia-end-to-end_24501</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=App-di-messaggistica-costrette-alla-scansione-dei-messaggi-salta-la-crittografia-end-to-end_24501"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T14:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Forti dubbi si erano sollevati tra gli esperti del settore circa le prescrizioni contenute nel Digital Markets Act (DMA), la nuova normativa europea che dovrebbe entrare in vigore a primavera 2023 salvo modifiche o ulteriori rinvii.Il legislatore ha previsto che piattaforme come WhatsApp, Telegram, iMessage e altre debbano essere rese interoperabili senza però considerare che uno scambio di dati tra app di sviluppatori completamente diversi può avere conseguenze devastanti per la sicurezza e la privacy degli utenti. Quegli stessi soggetti che si cerca di tutelare.Oggi la Commissione Europea ha annunciato un'ulteriore nuova regolamentazione che mira a proteggere i minori dagli abusi.Anche in questo caso le finalità sono nobili ma le conseguenze degli adempimenti di cui si parla potrebbero rivelarsi estremamente invasivi e pericolosissimi sul piano della tutela della privacy.Stando a quanto proposto in sede europea, le applicazioni di messaggistica istantanea, comprese WhatsApp, Facebook Messenger, Telegram, Signal e così via, saranno chiamate ad analizzare selettivamente i messaggi privati degli utenti alla ricerca di materiale pedopornografico e di comportamenti equiparabili ad attività di 'adescamento' di soggetti minorenni.Matthew Green, uno dei più noti e stimati docenti di crittografia, ha condannato senza appello la scelta europea definendo il documento presentato come 'il più terrificante mai visto finora.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA tells federal agencies to fix actively exploited F5 BIG-IP bug]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisa-tells-federal-agencies-to-fix-actively-exploited-f5-big-ip-bug/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisa-tells-federal-agencies-to-fix-actively-exploited-f5-big-ip-bug/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T14:35:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has added a new security vulnerability to its list of actively exploited bugs, the critical severity CVE-2022-1388 affecting BIG-IP network devices. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft's New Adaptive PC Accessories Are Just Incredible]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117422/microsofts-new-adaptive-pc-accessories-are-just-incredible/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117422/microsofts-new-adaptive-pc-accessories-are-just-incredible/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T14:19:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s been four years since Microsoft announced the Xbox Adaptive Controller, a groundbreaking and customizable device that adapts to users’ abilities. And now, Microsoft hopes to make PCs more accessible with a line of incredible Adaptive Accessories—a mouse, a wireless hub, and a big button.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Selling Your Home? Consulting This Type of Expert Could Increase Its Value]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lifesavvy.com/128564/selling-your-home-consulting-this-type-expert-could-increase-its-value/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lifesavvy.com/128564/selling-your-home-consulting-this-type-expert-could-increase-its-value/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T14:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No matter what we’re buying or selling, we all want to get the most bang for our buck. For those who are selling their home, that could mean making a few easy upgrades. Before you do that, though, there’s one step you might be skipping.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shea Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel Announces "Project Amber" For Verifying The Trustworthiness Of Clouds]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-Project-Amber</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-Project-Amber"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following yesterday's Intel Vision 2022 announcements there is a bit more news today. In particular, Intel is announcing Project Amber...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our Medical Devices' Open Source Problem – What Are the Risks?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/our-medical-devices-open-source-problem-what-are-the-risks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/our-medical-devices-open-source-problem-what-are-the-risks/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is no doubt that open source powers our development processes, enabling software developers to build high quality, innovative products faster than ever before. But OSS also comes with its own set of risks that device manufacturers must address while leveraging its many advantages. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sponsored by Cybellum</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Noise Cancelling Headphones of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=794872</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/794872/best-noise-cancelling-headphones/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T14:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking to escape from the world around you and drift away on a cloud of your favorite music? You’ll need a set of noise-cancelling headphones for that, and we’ve got some wonderful options to choose from.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kris Wouk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>