<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-05-04T01:57:05.434Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dockx on a different monitor? Dock is stuck on one monitor!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uhuv14/dockx_on_a_different_monitor_dock_is_stuck_on_one/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uhuv14/dockx_on_a_different_monitor_dock_is_stuck_on_one/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T01:04:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Howdy all, I was trying to obtain Dockx to work but I can't get it to change monitors. It only appears on my primary monitor. EDIT: I have gotten it to move over by setting that monitor as primary, I don't know if this will impact anything else (I'm running xfce) but I'm going to try it out and will update if anything else is broken. My main panel is still in the same place, so we'll see. I have tried dockx --monitor [x] with x being numbers 0 - 5 and 10 and it runs fine but it still shows up on the same monitor. Doing DP-2, for example, will return Warning: Invalid monitor index: DP-2 I have also tried dockx --geometry [locationxlocation] with no success. I cannot get it to change monitors for the life of me, any help is appreciated. This is my xrandr output: Screen 0: minimum 8 x 8, curr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Troubleshoot MiFi Connection Issues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=344147</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/13512143/troubleshoot-mifi-connection-issues"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To connect multiple devices to the Internet, MiFi networks are a great alternative to WLAN routers and mobile hotspots. A pocket-sized MiFi device creates an ad hoc network wherever you go, provided it’s within your carrier coverage area. On rare occasions, your MiFi may fail to connect, even though the hardware isn’t damaged. If you’re facing this issue, follow the steps below to troubleshoot MiFi connection problems and reset your Internet access. 
   

Content

What is a MiFi Device?
Why Is My MiFi Showing No Internet?
1. Check Your Account Status for Any Service Discontinuity
2. Make Sure You've Correctly Configured Your MiFi Device
3. Check Your MiFi Connectivity Status
4. Check MiFi LED Indicator Status
5. Remove and Reinsert the SIM card
6. Do a MiFi Factory Reset
Frequently Asked Questions 

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Troubleshoot the Wi-Fi Hotspot on Your iPhone
  ... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sayak Boral</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD Continues Posting New Patch Series For Next-Gen RDNA3 GPUs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMD-More-RDNA3-Blocks-May</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMD-More-RDNA3-Blocks-May"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T23:48:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In addition to the recent notable Linux patch series enabling GFX11 graphics and VCN4 video encode/decode for next-generation "RDNA3" GPUs, AMD this week has been posting some additional patch series enabling other intellectual property (IP) blocks for their next-generation hardware...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I seem to have installed UEFI and BIOS booting in grub]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uhsqs0/i_seem_to_have_installed_uefi_and_bios_booting_in/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uhsqs0/i_seem_to_have_installed_uefi_and_bios_booting_in/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T23:13:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone, I am not too familiar with bootloaders primarily because of my bad time with them.
 ​
 I seem to have installed the bios since I have a i386-pc and a EFI folder.
 ​
 Its working somehow but causing issues since updating grub doesn't really work and I am scared to play with it more, I feel like it is a house of cards.
 ​
 How can I remove the UEFI and return to standard BIOS
    submitted by    /u/ArchBTW123  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New ransomware strains linked to North Korean govt hackers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-ransomware-strains-linked-to-north-korean-govt-hackers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-ransomware-strains-linked-to-north-korean-govt-hackers/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T22:31:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several ransomware strains have been linked to APT38, a North Korean-sponsored hacking group known for its focus on targeting and stealing funds from financial institutions worldwide. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Verificare la build di Windows installata nel computer]]></title>
        <id>730|20220504000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/windows-10/verificare-build-windows-installata-computer-730"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Per trovare il numero di build di Windows installata nel computer, utile quando dobbiamo capire se Windows 10/11 è aggiornato all’ultima versione disponibile, rilasciata ai Windows Insider https://insider.windows.com/ o “trovata” in rete in qualche modo possiamo accedere alle Impostazioni – Sistema e Informazioni sul sistema.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conti, REvil, LockBit ransomware bugs exploited to block encryption]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/conti-revil-lockbit-ransomware-bugs-exploited-to-block-encryption/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/conti-revil-lockbit-ransomware-bugs-exploited-to-block-encryption/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T21:34:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers commonly exploit vulnerabilities in corporate networks to gain access, but a researcher has turned the table by finding exploits in the most common ransomware and malware being distributed today. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Ilascu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Prevent WhatsApp from Saving Images to Gallery]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=481189</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15271753/prevent-whatsapp-saving-images"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By default, WhatsApp saves received images and videos to your phone. This option can be extremely convenient, allowing you to easily save all the cool memes and group photos for later use. The downside is that your phone’s storage can quickly fill up, especially if you’re quite active on the app. In this article we show you how to disable WhatsApp from automatically saving photos to your phone’s gallery. Whether you own an Android or iOS device, you’ll have a firmer control over your device’s storage with this option turned off.
   

Content

How to Disable WhatsApp from Saving Photos on Android
How to Manually Save Images or Videos on Android
How to Prevent WhatsApp from Saving Photos on iOS
How to Manually Save Images or Videos on iOS
Alternative: Turn on Disappearing Messages for Select Chats
How to Manage Media Storage in WhatsApp for Android and iOS
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexandra Arici</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Remove Viruses and Malware on Your Windows PC]]></title>
        <id>http://www.howtogeek.com/?p=126911</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/126911/what-to-do-if-you-get-a-virus-on-your-computer/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you saw a message saying a virus was detected, or your computer just seems slow and unreliable, you’ll want to scan for malware on your PC and remove any you find. Here’s how to clean your PC of viruses and malware.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lowell Heddings</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I'll have to present something tomorrow on my laptop by connecting it to a video projector. How to make sure it works properly?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uhpcob/ill_have_to_present_something_tomorrow_on_my/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uhpcob/ill_have_to_present_something_tomorrow_on_my/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T20:36:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm using Arch with i3 and I've never tested a video projector. How can I make sure it's going to work properly?
 Is it treated like a monitor? In that case they'll have two different displays and I'm not really confident I can quickly fix it with xrandr without spending time on the wiki.
 Any ideas? It'll be connected through an HDMI cable.
    submitted by    /u/nerooooooo  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How come kuserfeedback is a hard dependency as part of KDE?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uhp3cy/how_come_kuserfeedback_is_a_hard_dependency_as/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uhp3cy/how_come_kuserfeedback_is_a_hard_dependency_as/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T20:25:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While I personally don't mind it, I don't understand why it's compiled as a hard dependency. From what I understand, kuserfeedback can be made an optional dependency through the use of a compile flag (which doesn't seem difficult to implement), so why isn't that the case? There aren't many packages that depend on it, so it should be pretty straight forward. 
 This change would make the affected packages more modular, which would go in the spirit of Arch Linux. 
 To be clear, I'm not trying to be rude to the Arch Linux developers, rather, I'm curious as to what their decision was based on.
    submitted by    /u/shouko_hikari  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using multiple web browsers (and electron apps)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uhowur/using_multiple_web_browsers_and_electron_apps/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uhowur/using_multiple_web_browsers_and_electron_apps/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T20:16:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I use many, many web browsers (and many browser profiles within those browsers).
 I want to associate particular URL's with each browser profile available. E.g. I want to have social media on one browser profile, electron apps should cross-link between one another properly (e.g. a discord link clicked in firefox should open in the discord electron app), and specific websites need to open in specific browser profiles (e.g. if I click a banking link in firefox, I want it to open Profile 2 in chrome).
 How do I get this done?
 xdg-open seems to only be able to handle general protocols, rather than specific URL's. And then each browser has the nasty habit of trying to open websites in itself, rather than letting the system handle how each link is opened.
 What do? How do I solve this for peak workload compartmentalization?
 [NSFW because this idea is potentially indecent and offensive]
    submitted by    /u/810perspectives  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New phishing warns: Your verified Twitter account may be at risk]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-phishing-warns-your-verified-twitter-account-may-be-at-risk/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-phishing-warns-your-verified-twitter-account-may-be-at-risk/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T20:04:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Phishing emails increasingly target verified Twitter accounts with emails designed to steal their account credentials, as shown by numerous ongoing campaigns conducted by threat actors. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Change the Time on Your Amazon Fire TV Stick]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=799205</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/799205/firestick-change-time/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T20:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your Amazon Fire TV device uses the date and time settings from your default time zone. If you ever want to adjust the current date and time on your Firestick, simply change the time zone. Here’s how you can do that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Funded a Right to Repair Study, and the Results Are Encouraging]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/116848/microsoft-funded-a-right-to-repair-study-and-the-results-are-encouraging/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/116848/microsoft-funded-a-right-to-repair-study-and-the-results-are-encouraging/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T19:49:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In October 2021, Microsoft agreed to start making its Surface devices more repairable and promised it would fund an independent study to find how the environment could benefit from the right to repair movement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Office on Android Has a New Way to Sort Your Files]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=802923</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/802923/microsoft-office-on-android-has-a-new-way-to-sort-your-files/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T19:28:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Office has been available on iPhone, iPad, and Android for years, giving you an easy way to quickly view and edit documents on the go. Office on Android is now rolling out a new way to sort through all your files, following similar updates on Apple devices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save $80 on a Nixplay 10.1″ Touch Screen Digital Picture Frame]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=485666</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15271587/nixplay-touch-screen-digital-picture-frame"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just in time for graduations and the wedding season, you can get a Nixplay 10.1″ Touch Screen Digital Picture Frame, constructed with a wood effect and Wi-Fi. You can share your graduation or wedding photos and videos, or any of your cherished media, via email or an app. Plus, you can get it now for $80 off.
    
It doesn’t matter whether your parents or grandparents are on social media or regularly text, as you can gift them with this digital photo frame to share your photos via the Nixplay app, available for both iOS and Android. You can also share photos to the frame through the desktop web app, email, Google Photos, Facebook, and Instagram. The Nixplay cloud storage is on secure, encrypted services in the U.S.
    

    
The Nixplay 10.1″ Touch Screen Digital Picture Frame can be positioned in any orientation, and you can “heart” your favorite photos on the touch screen. The niX-SenseMe smart sensor will wake the frame when you’re in the room and send it to sleep... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC ramps up fight on cryptocurrency fraud by doubling cyber unit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/sec-ramps-up-fight-on-cryptocurrency-fraud-by-doubling-cyber-unit/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/sec-ramps-up-fight-on-cryptocurrency-fraud-by-doubling-cyber-unit/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T19:23:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) announced today that it will almost double the Crypto Assets and Cyber Unit to ramp up the fight against cryptocurrency fraud to protect investors from "cyber-related threats." [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Quest Pro VR Headset: Everything We Know so Far]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/116819/meta-quest-pro/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/116819/meta-quest-pro/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T19:09:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Later this year, Facebook (now Meta) will put its lofty metaverse concept to the test with the Project Cambria headset. Leaks and official statements show that Project Cambria will be a work-focused machine with several stunning features, and Zuckerberg even claims that it could replace your laptop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Change Your AirPods’ Name]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=796862</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/796862/how-to-change-airpod-name/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T19:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By assigning a unique name to your AirPods, you make it easier to find them among other Bluetooth-enabled devices. It’s easy to rename your AirPods, and you can use an Apple device to do that. We’ll show you how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NVIDIA driver problems after upgrade]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uhn3tp/nvidia_driver_problems_after_upgrade/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uhn3tp/nvidia_driver_problems_after_upgrade/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T18:55:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just a friendly heads up for NVIDIA users that might run into this.
 Earlier today I upgraded my NVIDIA driver (which I'm early-loading) from 510.60.02 to 510.68.02. After rebooting, Gnome Shell felt sluggish, and trying to launch a Vulkan game failed. nvidia-smi failed with the message:
 Failed to initialize NVML: Driver/library version mismatch 
 Checking the system log I found these messages from the kernel:
 NVRM: API mismatch: the client has the version 510.68.02, but NVRM: this kernel module has the version 510.60.02. Please NVRM: make sure that this kernel module and all NVIDIA driver NVRM: components have the same version. 
 Solution: updating the initramfs:
 # mkinitcpio -P 
 After that and a reboot, all is back to normal.
 I checked pacman's log and it didn't do any post-upgrade hook to update the initramfs. I had thought this was automatic, but now I think it's just because I probably hadn't ever done an NVIDIA driver update without a kernel upgrade at the same time -- and the latter does trigger that hook.
 Blame's on me for not reading the wiki carefully:
  
If added to the initramfs, do not forget to run mkinitcpio every time there is a nvidia driver update
  
I've now added the extra pacman hook as suggested.
    submitted by    /u/meithan  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux 5.19 Adding Ability To Initiate Firmware Updates Using Sysfs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-FW_UPLOAD-sysfs</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-FW_UPLOAD-sysfs"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T18:38:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In addition to driver-core-next having queued up the long-awaited Zstd compressed firmware support ahead of the Linux 5.19 kernel, another change readied is allowing support for initiating firmware updates for supported drivers via sysfs...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[huge space taken by luks partition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uhm6bf/huge_space_taken_by_luks_partition/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uhm6bf/huge_space_taken_by_luks_partition/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T18:11:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, i've a luks ext4 encrypted partition with 700Gib. It's empty (contains no data).
 When partition is umounted, used space is 1.96GiB https://i.ibb.co/7WbpmrH/1.png
 When partition is mounted, used space is 12.13GiB https://i.ibb.co/mBHVKyj/2.png
 Who takes that space and why it differs in above 2 cases ???
 Images taken in gparted
    submitted by    /u/Spare_Prize1148  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some questions about nvidia-prime and nvidia-smi output]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uhm2mf/some_questions_about_nvidiaprime_and_nvidiasmi/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uhm2mf/some_questions_about_nvidiaprime_and_nvidiasmi/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T18:07:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So I've finally got nvidia-prime working on my laptop. If I do "prime-run steam," steam starts on the nvidia gpu and all subsequent games that I launch. This is apparent from running "nvidia-smi" or "nvidia-settings" where there is clear gpu utilization, so great! 
  
 I am a bit confused as to the output of "nvidia-smi" though:
 +-----------------------------------------------------------------------------+ | NVIDIA-SMI 510.60.02 Driver Version: 510.60.02 CUDA Version: 11.6 | |-------------------------------+----------------------+----------------------+ | GPU Name Persistence-M| Bus-Id Disp.A | Volatile Uncorr. ECC | | Fan Temp Perf Pwr:Usage/Cap| Memory-Usage | GPU-Util Compute M. | | | | MIG M. | |===============================+======================+======================| | 0 NVIDIA…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Could Be the Secret to Grilling the Best Burger]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lifesavvy.com/127428/this-could-be-the-secret-to-grilling-the-best-burger/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lifesavvy.com/127428/this-could-be-the-secret-to-grilling-the-best-burger/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T18:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re a dedicated grill master, you likely already have a secret recipe for making your signature burger. But for those who are open to trying a new technique, you don’t have to look any further than your freezer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shea Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Check the Python Version on Windows, Mac, and Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=796841</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/796841/check-python-version/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T18:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To check what version of Python is installed on your Windows, Mac, or Linux computer, all you have to do is run a single command. We’ll show you how to do that as well as what to do if you have multiple Python versions installed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ampere Adds "Ampere1" CPU Core Support To LLVM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Ampere1-LLVM-Clang-Compiler</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Ampere1-LLVM-Clang-Compiler"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Merged today into mainline LLVM 15.0 for the Clang compiler is Ampere Computing's support for "Ampere1", their next-generation server processor featuring their in-house "Ampere Cores" core design...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PowerShell permette di controllare le modifiche sul registro di Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=PowerShell-permette-di-controllare-le-modifiche-sul-registro-di-Windows_24466</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=PowerShell-permette-di-controllare-le-modifiche-sul-registro-di-Windows_24466"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T17:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quando si installa un programma in Windows la configurazione del sistema operativo viene spesso modificata in profondità.A meno di non usare applicazioni portabili che cioè non applicano variazioni sulla configurazione del file system e del registro di sistema, l'installazione di qualunque programma effettua una serie di modifiche.Nel nostro articolo incentrato sui consigli per disinstallare programmi inutili in Windows rimuovendo tutte le tracce delle applicazioni, abbiamo presentato una serie di programmi che aiutano a monitorare le modifiche su file e registro.In risposta a un tweet in cui si chiedeva se l'Editor del registro di sistema potesse in futuro evidenziare tutte le modifiche che differiscono rispetto alla configurazione standard di Windows, Lee Holmes - Principal Security Arch…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Issues with name resolution?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uhlh1v/issues_with_name_resolution/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uhlh1v/issues_with_name_resolution/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T17:39:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everything worked fine until I powered on the system for the first time today. I did no updates since the last time it worked.
 After powering on, name resolution didn't work, which turned out to be caused by systemd-resolved (which I had been using since I installed the system and I didn't disable it) not running. After enabling it, ping works on some domain names, but doesn't on others. I couldn't get any connection in Firefox or Steam and only managed to load google.com in lynx. I tried using 1.1.1.1 and 8.8.8.8 as DNS.
 Any ideas what could be happening?
    submitted by    /u/Jamesin_theta  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Liteboxer VR Releases the First Free Fitness App for Meta Quest]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/116822/liteboxer-vr-releases-the-first-free-fitness-app-for-meta-quest/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/116822/liteboxer-vr-releases-the-first-free-fitness-app-for-meta-quest/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T17:34:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Liteboxer VR, the popular fitness and boxing platform that lets you step into the virtual ring, will start offering its app completely free. Meta Quest (previously Oculus Quest) owners can enjoy intense sweat sessions without breaking out a debit card.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google: Chinese state hackers keep targeting Russian govt agencies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/google-chinese-state-hackers-keep-targeting-russian-govt-agencies/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/google-chinese-state-hackers-keep-targeting-russian-govt-agencies/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T17:29:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google said today that a Chinese-sponsored hacking group linked to China's People's Liberation Army Strategic Support Force (PLA SSF) is targeting Russian government agencies. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Se la stampante non stampa (HP, Epson e altre), cosa fare]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2017/01/se-la-stampante-non-stampa-hp-epson-e.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2017/01/se-la-stampante-non-stampa-hp-epson-e.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T17:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A volte può capitare che la stampante non risponda al comando di stampa ed anche se tutto sembra acceso e collegato e non è stato toccato nulla, qualcosa si è bloccato e non rende possibile stampare il documento. Questo può dipendere dalla stampante stessa oppure dalla configurazione del PC, che per qualche motivo è cambiata e c'è bisogno di ripristinarla.

 In alcuni casi può esserci un problema...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Turn Off Narrator on Windows 10 and 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=796283</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/796283/how-to-turn-off-narrator/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T17:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows’ Narrator feature reads on-screen text to help you navigate your PC. If you have this feature enabled, but you don’t use it, it’s easy to turn Narrator off on both Windows 10 and 11. We’ll show you two ways to do that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DNS spoofing e poisoning: a rischio dispositivi di 200 produttori]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=DNS-spoofing-e-poisoning-a-rischio-dispositivi-di-200-produttori_24465</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=DNS-spoofing-e-poisoning-a-rischio-dispositivi-di-200-produttori_24465"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T16:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Si torna a parlare di attacchi DNS spoofing e DNS poisoning, entrambi noti per avere come obiettivo quello di reindirizzare la vittima verso server Web che non sono quelli legittimi. Gli attacchi hanno luogo modificando la risposta che viene inviata a una richiesta di risoluzione di un nome a dominio oppure alterando il contenuto della cache DNS.Era il 2008 quando il ricercatore Dan Kaminsky parlò di DNS poisoning e delle modalità con cui si poteva forzare un server DNS ad offrire risposte arbitrarie.Da quel momento iniziò un impegno coordinato per risolvere alla base il problema.L'informatica è però fatta di corsi e ricorsi: come già accaduto di recente, quando si parlò del possibile ritorno degli attacchi DNS poisoning, è adesso venuto a galla l'utilizzo di un'implementazione non sicura …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft PowerShell lets you track Windows Registry changes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-powershell-lets-you-track-windows-registry-changes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-powershell-lets-you-track-windows-registry-changes/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T16:47:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[​A handy tip was shared online this week, showing how you can use PowerShell to monitor changes to the Windows Registry over time. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Security Cameras That Work With Apple Homekit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/115024/the-best-security-cameras-that-work-with-apple-homekit/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/115024/the-best-security-cameras-that-work-with-apple-homekit/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T16:34:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a world where packages can be stolen off your doorstep, investing in a good security system for your home is essential. If your smart home primarily uses Apple HomeKit to integrate everything, finding a compatible security camera is no small feat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Chaney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chiamate indesiderate difficili da bloccare: il numero di telefono non è quello reale]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Chiamate-indesiderate-difficili-da-bloccare-il-numero-di-telefono-non-e-quello-reale_24371</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Chiamate-indesiderate-difficili-da-bloccare-il-numero-di-telefono-non-e-quello-reale_24371"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T16:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[State ricevendo in continuazione chiamate da numeri di cellulare che pubblicizzano questo o quel servizio? Le chiamate indesiderate vi assillano a qualunque ora del giorno e alla risposta si sente sempre una voce preregistrata? Sappiate che non siete i soli: succede anche a noi, così come a buona parte degli italiani.Abbiamo visto com'è possibile bloccare le chiamate indesiderate sia su mobile che sulle numerazioni fisse ma da un po’ di tempo a questa parte gli scocciatori hanno cominciato a usare tattiche fraudolente: chiamano con numeri di utenze mobili sempre diversi. Anche inserendoli nello spam e segnalandoli come tali, le chiamate indesiderate continuano ad arrivare.Se si risponde una voce registrata dice: 'la segreteria di (...) ti dà il benvenuto'. Oppure, ancora, si fa presente che le tariffe di luce, gas, telefonia di casa o dell'ufficio subiranno un aumento. Talvolta si fa riferimento a un fantomatico 'centro di verifica delle tariffe'.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Draft a Gmail Email Directly in Google Docs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=797018</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/797018/draft-a-gmail-email-in-google-docs/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever been working on a document that sparked an email to someone? With a handy feature in Google Docs, you can write your email and then with the click of a button, create the draft in Gmail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thunderbird: arriva l'app per i dispositivi mobili]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Thunderbird-arriva-l-app-per-i-dispositivi-mobili_24464</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Thunderbird-arriva-l-app-per-i-dispositivi-mobili_24464"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T15:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fino ad oggi Thunderbird è da sempre conosciuto come uno dei migliori client di posta elettronica per Windows, Linux e macOS.Chi utilizza Thunderbird su desktop di solito utilizza uno dei tanti client email disponibili per Android e iOS: Gmail e Outlook restano tra i nomi più noti, grazie anche al supporto per l'autenticazione agli account di terze parti mediante protocollo OAuth, ma sono tante le alternative gratuite.Abbiamo già parlato di app email per Android e dell'ottimo FairEmail.Poter installare Thunderbird sui dispositivi mobili potrebbe cambiare radicalmente il modo di lavorare per molti: l'esportazione diretta della configurazione del client di posta dal desktop al telefono sarà una funzione particolarmente apprezzata.Stando alle informazioni emerse in queste ore, la versione mobile di Thunderbird è una priorità per gli sviluppatori che in un primo tempo rilasceranno la release per Android dedicandosi successivamente al mondo iOS.Al momento è stata comunicata una data di lancio di Thunderbird 'mobile' ma è scontato che l'app erediterà buona parte degli strumenti disponibili su desktop facilitando la sincronizzazione dei dati.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[`nproc` limit has to be set, seemingly, too high in order for container to run]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uhj4l6/nproc_limit_has_to_be_set_seemingly_too_high_in/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uhj4l6/nproc_limit_has_to_be_set_seemingly_too_high_in/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T15:51:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/quarksplitter  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[luks on non-empty HDD]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uhixc3/luks_on_nonempty_hdd/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uhixc3/luks_on_nonempty_hdd/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T15:42:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, can I encrypt an HDD with LUKS without losing the data it contains ?
    submitted by    /u/Spare_Prize1148  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LEGO Pays Tribute to The Rolling Stones With Tongue Brick Set]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/116801/lego-pays-tribute-to-the-rolling-stones-with-tongue-brick-set/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/116801/lego-pays-tribute-to-the-rolling-stones-with-tongue-brick-set/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T15:41:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Rolling Stones iconic tongue and lips logo is recognized worldwide, and now you can put it on your wall with the all-new LEGO Art Rolling Stones set.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome 101 Lost Reader Mode, But It’s Coming Back]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=802848</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/802848/chrome-101-lost-reader-mode-but-its-coming-back/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T15:33:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has been testing a Reader Mode in Chrome for a while now, which hides page elements outside the core text. The option mysteriously disappeared in the most recent Chrome 101 update, but it’s coming back.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kindle Will Finally Support EPUB Books, but There's a Catch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/116807/kindle-will-finally-support-epub-books-but-theres-a-catch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/116807/kindle-will-finally-support-epub-books-but-theres-a-catch/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T15:33:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Kindle walled garden is finally falling, sort of. In an unceremonious change to its Documents Service guide, Amazon now says that the Kindle e-reader will support EPUB documents in “late 2022.”    But there’s a somewhat frustrating catch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Guy Behind 'Wordle' Says You Should Try This New Game]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/116798/the-guy-behind-wordle-says-you-should-try-this-new-game/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/116798/the-guy-behind-wordle-says-you-should-try-this-new-game/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T15:31:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s been months now since Wordle debuted and took over the internet. And from it, dozens of clones and creative alternatives have spawned, the latest of which is Knotwords. It blends Wordle‘s mechanics with those of crossword puzzles and word searches and is a fun successor to the original game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzanne Humphries</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why and How to Edit Your Sudoers File in Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=244217</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/9951591/edit-sudoers-file-linux"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Within your Linux system, there is a file called “sudoers”. This is a text file that controls the deepest levels of your permission system. It permits or denies users from gaining super-user access and holds some special preferences for sudo.
   

Content

What is the sudoers file?
When do I Need to Edit the sudoers File?
How can I edit sudoers?
What can Changing The sudoers File Do?
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}    
What is the sudoers file?
    
The sudoers file is a text file that you can find in the “/etc” directory (find out more about Linux directory here). Its main purpose is to control how sudo works on your machine and determine which users and groups have the ability to run with superuser permission.
    
In addition, the sudoers file can also allow a specific user to run commands as another user in the system.
    

    
For example, if you have a web server, you... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramces Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Credit card autofill now enabled in the United Kingdom, France and Germany]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.mozilla.org/?p=68934</id>
        <link href="https://blog.mozilla.org/en/products/firefox/firefox-credit-card-autofill-uk-france-germany/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T15:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the rapid growth of e-commerce in the last few years, more people are expecting their browser to help them out when shopping online. Firefox has supported credit card autofill in the United States and Canada since 2018. Starting today Firefox can remember and fill credit card details additionally in the United Kingdom, France and […]
The post Credit card autofill now enabled in the United Kingdom, France and Germany appeared first on The Mozilla Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>admin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Schermo smartphone si blocca o lampeggia, come risolvere]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/05/schermo-smartphone-si-blocca-o.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/05/schermo-smartphone-si-blocca-o.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T15:16:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Di punto in bianco il display del nostro smartphone ha iniziato a sfarfallare, a lampeggiare (come se si spegnesse e accendesse in pochissimi secondi) o a presentare problemi di varia natura che ne impediscono l'uso corretto, anche per fare una semplice telefonata o inviare un messaggio. Questo tipo di problemi possono capitare sia a telefoni nuovi sia su smartphone con qualche anno sulle spalle...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Flickering LG monitor only on Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uhi2zf/flickering_lg_monitor_only_on_linux/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uhi2zf/flickering_lg_monitor_only_on_linux/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T15:03:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I got myself a LG UltraGear 32GN600.
 For some reasons, it has weird flickering here and there. (and it seems it only gets worse as I use it in a long run) I didn't have such an issue with previous monitor from Dell.
 First, I thought it was a hardware issue. But when I boot into Windows, the issue is gone. I never see a single flickering during 2-hour movie. I get tons of flickering when I watch it on Archlinux.
 I wanted to share how bad it is using video capture, but I don't have a good webcam that is capable of 120hz recording.
 Also I wanted to make it clear that it's quite different from "tearing"
 Things I tried:
  
Tried 2 different DPs, and 1 HDMI cable 
  
-> didn't make any difference
  
Tried using Windows so I can tell if it's a hardware issue 
  
-> turns out it's not
  
Look for drivers for the hardware 
  
-> there were some for windows but not for linux
  
Switched DE and WM (KDE and dwm) & disabled compositors 
  
-> No luck
 Is 120hz display not suitable for Linux at the moment?
 I have no idea how to troubleshoot this problem. Please help me out!
 Specs:
  
Kernel: 5.17.5-arch1-1
  
Thanks.
    submitted by    /u/Teeeeze  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Motion Path Animations in Microsoft PowerPoint]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=798590</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/798590/how-to-use-motion-path-animations-in-microsoft-powerpoint/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft PowerPoint offers many types of animations. You can add effects to text, images, and shapes. But if you want to create your own, you can select a motion path animation to move your object wherever you like.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Kindle Readers Will Soon Support EPUB Books (Kind of)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=802692</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/802692/amazon-kindle-readers-will-soon-support-epub-books-kind-of/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T14:55:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon’s Kindle lineup includes some of the best e-readers around, but no Kindle readers support the industry standard for ebooks: the EPUB format. However, Amazon says that will (partially) change soon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[May's Pixel 6 Update Arrives with Just Three Fixes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/116792/mays-pixel-6-update-arrives-with-just-three-fixes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/116792/mays-pixel-6-update-arrives-with-just-three-fixes/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T14:37:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once again, Google has managed to roll out a Pixel update on time for all supported devices. The May update is now available, though it resolves just three bugs and a handful of security vulnerabilities. Notably, this may be the final update for Google’s Pixel 3a and Pixel 3a XL.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RiotPWR ESL Gaming Controller for iOS Review: Like a Console on the Go]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/113043/riotpwr-esl-gaming-controller-for-ios-review-like-a-console-on-the-go/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/113043/riotpwr-esl-gaming-controller-for-ios-review-like-a-console-on-the-go/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T14:24:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nowadays, our smartphones are capable of running console-quality games—the only problem is dealing with touchscreen inputs. You either get a UI that takes up half of the screen or uncomfortable swipe controls. Enter RiotPWR’s ESL Controller for iOS; a definitive win to that lose-lose situation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcus Mears III</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Antivirus Software of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=794451</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/794451/best-antivirus-software/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T14:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Choosing the right antivirus software to protect your devices has never been more crucial than it is today. Our picks of the best antivirus software for Windows, macOS, and Android will help you make the right choice.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Russ Ware</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is a Data Packet?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=797005</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/797005/what-is-a-data-packet/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T13:30:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like anything else, computer data is easiest to move when it’s divided into smaller portions. In networking, these portions are referred to as “data packets” or simply “packets.” Here’s what you need to know about them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gaurav Shukla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unpatched DNS bug affects millions of routers and IoT devices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/unpatched-dns-bug-affects-millions-of-routers-and-iot-devices/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/unpatched-dns-bug-affects-millions-of-routers-and-iot-devices/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T13:18:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A vulnerability in the domain name system (DNS) component of a popular C standard library that is present in a wide range of IoT products may put millions of devices at DNS poisoning attack risk. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[1Password 8 Arrives for Mac with a Redesign and New Features]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/116737/1password-8-arrives-for-mac-with-a-redesign-and-new-features/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/116737/1password-8-arrives-for-mac-with-a-redesign-and-new-features/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T13:02:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s been nine months since 1Password 8 entered an “early access” beta, but the software has finally arrived for average users. And man, this update was long overdue. The 1Password 8 redesign looks fantastic, and its new features will dramatically improve the experience of using 1Password on a Mac.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s What’s New in Firefox 100]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=802645</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/802645/heres-whats-new-in-firefox-100/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T13:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox might not be as popular as it used to be, but it’s still an excellent alternative web browser, especially if privacy is your number one priority. As of May 3, 2022, Firefox 100 is now rolling out across all platforms with a few new features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celebrating Firefox: How we got to 100]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.mozilla.org/?p=68902</id>
        <link href="https://blog.mozilla.org/en/mozilla/celebrating-firefox-100/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T13:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether it’s celebrating the first 100 days of school or turning 100 years old, reaching a 100th milestone is a big deal worthy of confetti, streamers and cake, and of course, reflection. Today, Firefox is releasing its 100th version to our users and we wanted to take a moment to pause and look back on […]
The post Celebrating Firefox: How we got to 100 appeared first on The Mozilla Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mozilla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forget Microsoft Office: Your Mac Already Has a Free Productivity Suite]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=791954</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/791954/forget-microsoft-office-your-mac-already-has-a-free-productivity-suite/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mac users don’t need Office or Google Docs. If you own a Mac, you already have access to a fully-featured suite of productivity apps for free. It’s called iWork, and it includes Pages, Numbers, and Keynote. Here’s a look at what makes it special.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wyze's Thermostat Gets a Very Smart Room Sensor Accessory]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/116740/wyzes-thermostat-gets-a-very-smart-room-sensor-accessory/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/116740/wyzes-thermostat-gets-a-very-smart-room-sensor-accessory/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T12:59:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Wyze Thermostat is incredibly affordable at just $50. But unlike other offerings on the market, it didn’t have any sensors to check on your whole home. But the company just corrected that shortcoming, and Wyze’s new smart $25 Room Sensor puts the competition to shame.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Hendrickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox’s Picture-in-Picture rolls out subtitles – a Mozilla Connect community requested feature]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.mozilla.org/?p=68888</id>
        <link href="https://blog.mozilla.org/en/products/firefox/firefox-picture-in-picture-rolls-out-subtitles/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T12:43:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are so many different ways that Firefox users count on Picture-in-Picture for their best browsing and content viewing experiences: Toddler duty? Don’t sweat it! Stream your child’s favorite movie to watch on your desktop while you hold down your job and the title of “favorite parent!” Can’t miss the big game? Firefox’s Multiple Picture-in-Picture […]
The post Firefox’s Picture-in-Picture rolls out subtitles – a Mozilla Connect community requested feature appeared first on The Mozilla Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Vasquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Find and Remove Malware With Microsoft Defender Offline]]></title>
        <id>http://www.howtogeek.com/?p=100289</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/100289/how-to-create-a-bootable-offline-version-of-windows-defender/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has long offered a “Microsoft Defender Offline” tool you can use to perform malware scans from outside of Windows. With Windows 10’s Anniversary Update, this tool is included with Windows, and even easier to launch. Here’s how to use it, no matter which version of Windows you’re on.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Installare Play Store sul tablet Amazon Fire per avere tutte le app Google]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2016/01/installare-play-store-sul-tablet-amazon.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2016/01/installare-play-store-sul-tablet-amazon.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T12:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Il tablet Amazon Fire è uno dei tablet più venduti al mondo, non tanto per le sue capacità ma soprattutto per il suo prezzo impareggiabile su Amazon.

 A questo prezzo era inevitabile che diventasse il più venduto, adattissimo soprattutto per i ragazzi e per chi vuole semplicemente uno schermo dove leggere libri, giocare, navigare su internet e vedere film, anche in viaggio e ovunque si vada. Il...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ghacks Deals: The Complete 2022 Linux Certification Training Bundle]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178375</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/05/03/ghacks-deals-the-complete-2022-linux-certification-training-bundle/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T12:10:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Complete 2022 Linux Certification Training Bundle includes 12 online learning courses that teach Linux skills. The bundle is ideal for beginners who want to get started with Linux, but it may […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Ghacks Deals: The Complete 2022 Linux Certification Training Bundle appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wakeup from suspend on a re-connected USB keyboard]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uheirm/wakeup_from_suspend_on_a_reconnected_usb_keyboard/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uheirm/wakeup_from_suspend_on_a_reconnected_usb_keyboard/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T12:02:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've got a udev rule to wake the system from suspend with a key-press on external keyboard. It appears to only work when the keyboard is continuously connected. If I switch the mouse/keyboard to another system on the USB switch, I cannot wake with keyboard upon switching back.
 Is there a setting to handle wake-up with a re-connected USB device?
 EDIT: It appears the same udev rule below applied to the usb root hub will cause the system to wake on any usb disconnect or connect event. Is it possible to set it so it only wakes on connect, but not disconnect? That may be a good solution.
 ACTION=="add", SUBSYSTEM=="usb", DRIVERS=="usb", ATTRS{idVendor}=="1d2b", ATTRS{idProduct}=="0003", ATTR{power/wakeup}="enabled", ATTR{driver/usb2/power/wakeup}="enabled" 
    submitted by    /u/smw5qz  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethernet Splitter vs. Switch: What’s the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=797864</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/797864/ethernet-splitter-vs.-switch-whats-the-difference/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Short on Ethernet ports and looking to connect an extra device or two to your wired network setup? You’re likely to encounter two options: an Ethernet splitter, and an Ethernet switch. Here’s why you should choose the switch every time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla says that some mental health and prayer apps have serious privacy issues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178367</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/05/03/mozilla-research-reveals-shocking-privacy-issues-in-mental-health-and-prayer-apps/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T11:25:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla has released a report after analyzing various mental health apps and prayer apps. The results aren't nice, these apps are spying on users and selling personal data to third parties. The […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Mozilla says that some mental health and prayer apps have serious privacy issues appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD Working to Create A New Yocto Linux Platform For Xilinx SoCs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMD-Hiring-Embedded-Yocto</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMD-Hiring-Embedded-Yocto"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T11:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following AMD completing its Xilinx acquisition back in February, AMD is now preparing to ramp up their investment into embedded Linux. AMD is hiring for the "creation and maintenance" of a Yocto-based Embedded Linux platform for running on Xilinx SoCs...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Internet Explorer ritirato il 15 giugno 2022: cosa implica per gli utenti]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Internet-Explorer-ritirato-il-15-giugno-2022-cosa-implica-per-gli-utenti_24462</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Internet-Explorer-ritirato-il-15-giugno-2022-cosa-implica-per-gli-utenti_24462"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T11:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Era il 16 agosto 1995 quando Microsoft presentò la prima versione di Internet Explorer, browser che mirava a combattere lo strapotere assoluto dello storico Netscape Navigator.Agli albori Internet Explorer veniva distribuito come parte integrante del pacchetto Plus! per Windows 95, che forse alcuni dei nostri lettori si ricorderanno, ed era basato sul motore di rendering Spyglass Mosaic il cui utilizzo era stato ottenuto in licenza da Microsoft.Internet Explorer è praticamente morto a livello consumer da anni ma è ancora usato in diversi ambiti aziendali. Storicamente è conosciuto come un browser lento, non aderente agli standard per il Web e privo delle funzioni più evolute che contraddistinguono i prodotti più moderni.Eppure, strano ma vero, alcuni prodotti continuano ancora oggi ad appoggiarsi a Internet Explorer e a basare il loro funzionamento sugli ActiveX, tecnologia presentata nel 1996 da Microsoft stessa e pensata per ampliare le potenzialità e le funzioni delle applicazioni Web.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Is My Wi-Fi Not as Fast as Advertised?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=798624</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/798624/why-is-my-wi-fi-not-as-fast-as-advertised/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So the marketing for your Wi-Fi router promises a certain speed but your experience with the router doesn’t live up to that speed. What gives? Here’s why you’re not getting the advertised experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Fitzpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alexa Gets New Feature to Alert You of Package Deliveries]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=485474</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15270214/alexa-alert-package-deliveries"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T10:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The pandemic made a few significant changes to the tech world. One of those was an increase in online shopping. Having packages delivered was many times a better option than braving a brick-and-mortar store in a mask. Amazon is holding on to that reliance and has added a feature to Alexa to send notifications when you receive package deliveries.
   
Also read:Ring Doorbell Patents Show Future Uses of Biometric Data
    
Package Delivery Notifications via Alexa
    
Truthfully, Amazon has been tinkering with its package deliveries even before the global health crisis. The company introduced a program where its customers could allow Amazon drivers to enter their homes when they were gone to deliver packages. But that whole idea just never really seemed too appealing.
    
Amazon’s new program seems like it can be used by more people. Instead of letting strangers into your home, Alexa will inform you when a package has been delivered.
 ... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Decade Later, Linux To Better Handle Daisy Chaining Thunderbolt Displays On Apple Hardware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-519-Fix-Thunderbolt-Daisy</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-519-Fix-Thunderbolt-Daisy"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T10:07:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intel's Thunderbolt "Light Ridge" controller was introduced all the way back in 2010 for Apple Macs and the updated Intel Thunderbolt 2 "Falcon Ridge" controller is from 2013. Now in 2022 under Linux the Thunderbolt driver will be better matching the Apple macOS behavior when daisy chaining multiple Thunderbolt displays...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aruba and Avaya network switches are vulnerable to RCE attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/aruba-and-avaya-network-switches-are-vulnerable-to-rce-attacks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/aruba-and-avaya-network-switches-are-vulnerable-to-rce-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T10:07:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security researchers have discovered five vulnerabilities in network equipment from Aruba (owned by HP) and Avaya (owned by ExtremeNetworks), that could allow malicious actors to execute code remotely on the devices. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMTP relay: cos'è e come funziona]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=SMTP-relay-cos-e-e-come-funziona_24461</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=SMTP-relay-cos-e-e-come-funziona_24461"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T10:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tanti utenti utilizzano oggi servizi Web per la gestione della posta elettronica, quelli che un tempo chiamavamo webmail. In un altro articolo abbiamo visto quando usare un client email e quando preferire una webmail.Se si utilizza un client email come Outlook, Thunderbird, MailBird e così via, per ciascun account di posta che si configura va impostato l'indirizzo del server SMTP.Il protocollo SMTP (Simple Mail Transfer Protocol) è uno standard che risale ai primi anni '80 ed è utilizzato per disporre l'invio dei messaggi di posta elettronica. È infatti utilizzato per impostare il server di posta in uscita ed è uno dei parametri che vanno verificati per primi quando le email non partono.SMTP può a sua volta basarsi su meccanismi di cifratura dei dati tanto che oggi è altamente sconsigliato usare server di posta che non supportano il protocollo TLS (Transport Layer Security).I protocolli che accettano email in arrivo si chiamano POP e IMAP: abbiamo visto le differenze tra POP3 e IMAP nella ricezione della posta.
Cos'è SMTP relay
 Con il termine SMTP relay si fa riferimento alla procedura che permette di trasferire un'email dal mittente al destinatario sulla rete Internet.Quando si invia un'email il server SMTP del provider cui ci si appoggia o quello della propria azienda si collega con il server indicato nel record MX (Mail eXchanger) del dominio del destinatario.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Better Support For The Lenovo ThinkPad TrackPoint Keyboard II With Linux 5.19]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=ThinkPad-TrackPoint-II-Linux</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=ThinkPad-TrackPoint-II-Linux"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T09:47:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Lenovo ThinkPad TrackPoint Keyboard II is a standalone keyboard that mimics the traditional ThinkPad notebook's keyboard that comes complete with an integrated TrackPoint. With the Linux 5.19 kernel will be better support for this standalone ThinkPad keyboard...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Random memory leak / system crash on plasma wayland]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uhcg2i/random_memory_leak_system_crash_on_plasma_wayland/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uhcg2i/random_memory_leak_system_crash_on_plasma_wayland/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T09:43:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm having this random memory leak happening for a while now, memory usage keeps going up until the system runs out of swap and crashes (it doesn't really crash, but it becomes completely unusable) this is the first time I was able to notice before it crashes.
 https://i.imgur.com/Y729zCR.png
 https://i.imgur.com/tWBZ1mb.png
 This is happening for like 2 months now and I can't pinpoint any specific cause to it, I was watching htop for a bit and the memory was climbing relatively slowly and it was probably happening for 5 ~ 10 minutes at that point, hard to say what exactly I was doing then, nothing out of the ordinary.
 I would appreciate any insights.
    submitted by    /u/bargu  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Help to get Realtek RTS5129 Card Reader working.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uhcdiv/help_to_get_realtek_rts5129_card_reader_working/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uhcdiv/help_to_get_realtek_rts5129_card_reader_working/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T09:38:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have an Acer laptop and everything works out of the box except my Realtek RTS5129 Card Reader. I have tried using this aur package: rts5139-dkms, which also applys to RTS5129 cards but it still doesn't work.
 Can someone help me to get it to work?
    submitted by    /u/abrattic  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla Firefox 100 Now Available With Various Improvements]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Firefox-100-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Firefox-100-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T09:28:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla has joined Google Chrome in the three digit version world with Firefox 100 being available this morning...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thunderbird mobile application is coming soon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178371</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/05/03/thunderbird-mobile-application-is-coming-soon/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T09:24:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Users of the open source email client Thunderbird may soon install it as an application for use on mobile devices. Thunderbird is a popular desktop email client, but it is not available […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Thunderbird mobile application is coming soon appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux Developers Discuss Improvements To Memory Tiering]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-Better-Memory-Tiering</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-Better-Memory-Tiering"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T09:22:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Already within the Linux kernel there is initial support for tiered memory servers for dealing with platforms like those with Intel Optane DC Persistent Memory for being able to promote/demote pages to slower classes of memory when the speedy system RAM is under pressure. But with more tiered memory servers coming about especially with HBM classes of memory, Google and other vendors are discussing better handling of Linux's tiered memory interface...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Problem with system suspend (sleep)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uhc0rc/problem_with_system_suspend_sleep/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uhc0rc/problem_with_system_suspend_sleep/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T09:11:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm on latest kernel. When I put my system to sleep, a black screen appears with cursor (frozen) and after 45-60 seconds, it unfreezes. Login screen (sddm) comes up, system works perfectly, again I put system to sleep, and it works.
 What is the problem? I don't know troubleshooting steps. I've tried searching the wiki but can't get anything relevant. Please tell me the steps to troubleshoot.
 Edit 1: Once I do the freeze routine, suspend works properly every time after that till I reboot.
 Edit 2: https://pastebin.com/CYu1n8J7. Line 3 and 4 (some task is refusing to freeze). 
    submitted by    /u/heikrana  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Partitionsize for arch to play with]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uhbujl/partitionsize_for_arch_to_play_with/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uhbujl/partitionsize_for_arch_to_play_with/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T08:59:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello:)
 I've been using linux for many years, but I still consider myself a novice.(debian, ubuntu, mint, mx/antix). And i allways used all of my harddrives for linux(last couples of years i havent bothered to make different one for root, boot, home....)
 But i have, do to job and and interest i gaming at the age of 41:D made me to choose windows
 I want to keep my linux "skills" and learn abit more than i have, and chose arch. 
 SO, how much space should i put i my linuxpart of my disk? I just want to install it and make it work and see if i like it. gaming, wotk etc will be done on the windows part
 thanks:)
    submitted by    /u/raakken  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Broke my config]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uhbtnh/i_broke_my_config/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uhbtnh/i_broke_my_config/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T08:57:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I wanted to install a lightdm theme, and at some point I did the wrong thing and now it doesn’t boot, how can I access tty to edit my config file to reset everything to default
 I tried ctrl + alt + F…, but tty… appear then disappear instantly
    submitted by    /u/nobody48sheldor  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox autoscroll setting reset itself]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uhauwj/firefox_autoscroll_setting_reset_itself/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uhauwj/firefox_autoscroll_setting_reset_itself/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T07:41:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Does anyone have issue where Firefox in Arch often reset autoscroll setting? It happen even if Firefox is not being updated. Never encountered this in Ubuntu device.
 Using Gnome Wayland, pacman.
 Edit: Haven't try this, but this might help https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/questions/1038202
    submitted by    /u/luz_booyadude  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SSH Key with VSCode]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uhah8b/ssh_key_with_vscode/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uhah8b/ssh_key_with_vscode/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T07:11:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday I installed vscode (visual-studio-code-bin) and it does its job. The only thing that bothers me is the fact I have en re-enter my password evertime I push something (because of SSH). I installed the x11-ssh-askpass package for this. I was wondering if it was possible to do this automatically so I don't have to enter my passphrase everytime I do some action with git.
    submitted by    /u/DaanKorver  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla releases Firefox 100: here is what is new]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178359</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/05/03/mozilla-releases-firefox-100-here-is-what-is-new/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T05:10:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first three-digit version of Mozilla's Firefox web browser has been released on May 3, 2022. Firefox 100 introduces a whole range of new features and improvements, including captions and subtitle support […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Mozilla releases Firefox 100: here is what is new appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram Premium subscription is reportedly in the works; could offer more stickers and reactions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178355</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/05/03/telegram-premium-subscription-exclusive-stickers-and-reactions/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T04:03:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram Messenger is working on a paid subscription called Telegram Premium. Rumors suggest that it will offer some exclusive stickers and reactions that subscribers may use. The service boasts over 500 million […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Telegram Premium subscription is reportedly in the works; could offer more stickers and reactions appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[error: failed to synchronize all databases (unexpected error)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uh6y1g/error_failed_to_synchronize_all_databases/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uh6y1g/error_failed_to_synchronize_all_databases/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T03:17:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I stopped a running pacman process and since then i have been getting this error along with "error: GPGME error: No data" everytime i perform "sudo pacman -Syu".
 Please help me out.
    submitted by    /u/TheSRPx  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Need help with bluetooth]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uh5a99/need_help_with_bluetooth/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uh5a99/need_help_with_bluetooth/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T01:45:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[i recently installed arch and i can't get bluetooth to work
 it was working fine in gnome session but on i3wm when i run:
 bluetoothctl power on 
 it says "No default controller available"
 bluetoothctl list 
 doesn't print out anything
 bluez is definitely installed
 any idea why this is happening?
 if you need more info just ask
    submitted by    /u/Kiing_Watermelon  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gmail Window scaling issue]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uh4es2/gmail_window_scaling_issue/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uh4es2/gmail_window_scaling_issue/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T00:59:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear all, 
 I have noticed a very annoying behaviour in Gmail on my home machine based on arch, xfce and chromium. (It does not happen at work with Windows/Chrome).
 The gmail main window screen is always somehow using the entire screenwidth even though there are other widgets using the width. Consequently i have to slide the screen left and right to access the reply icon. This is completely stupid!
 https://i.imgur.com/5huKoVy.png
 https://i.imgur.com/3ItA3cW.png
 I understand it may be unrelated to arch - in which case apologies for polluting this thread.
    submitted by    /u/fieldpeter  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Steam On Linux Gaming Usage Grew In April]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Steam-Linux-April-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Steam-Linux-April-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T00:30:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Valve just published the updated Steam Hardware/Software Survey results for April 2022 providing a look at the Linux marketshare for April among other interesting metrics...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fix the Network Cable Unplugged Error in Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=479444</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15268815/fix-network-cable-unplugged-error-windows"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Does your Windows PC or laptop fail to connect to the Internet even though other devices connect on the same network? This usually is preceded by an error message such as “A network cable is unplugged,” “Ethernet not working” or “Ethernet not connected.” Instead of the Internet icon displaying connectivity, you only see the offline “X” symbol which doesn’t go away on its own. 
    
There can be many possible causes for the network cable unplugged error, both software and hardware dependent. We bring you a systematic guide to troubleshoot the problem, and get back online quickly.
   

Content

What Does It Mean When My PC Says Network Cable Unplugged?
Disable and Enable Network Adapter 
Redo the Network Stack
Run an Internet Connection Troubleshooter
Configure BIOS Settings to Allow Internet 
Shut Down and Restart
Reset the Ethernet Authentication Settings
Remove Dust from Cover Panel and Reconnect/Change Network Adapter
Add Another USB Wireless Adapter
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sayak Boral</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[problem with audio interface and pipewire]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uh2u6b/problem_with_audio_interface_and_pipewire/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uh2u6b/problem_with_audio_interface_and_pipewire/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T23:35:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[anyone here could help me with pipewire?
 i have an audio interface, which i used to pipe my usb mic to, so i could adjust its volume/mute it. it worked great with pulseaudio, and it works like this: this interface, generates a sink and a source. i piped my mic to the sink(alsa_output.usb-ZhuHai_JieLi_Technology_JieLi_BR17_20160823-01.analog-stereo) , then, its source (alsa_input.usb-ZhuHai_JieLi_Technology_JieLi_BR17_20160823-01.analog-stereo)to discord. that way, it worked perfectly, it showed the green led when it clipped, i could mute it, change its volume etc. 
 now, with pipewire, it seems that the alsa_input device is not connected to alsa_output device, so it does not work. the device seems to be receiving the audio though, as if i connect my headphones to the interface headphone port, i can hear my mic. i can adjust its volume as well, but the green light does not light up when the audio clips, and the sound does not go to the xxxx_input device.
 that's the interface. i was using the knob on top of the pc symbol to adjust the volume, and the mute under monitor knob to mute it. https://imgur.com/Wu6CN2b
    submitted by    /u/SoxxZ  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[xinit: server error]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uh2krp/xinit_server_error/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uh2krp/xinit_server_error/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T23:21:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Startx not working https://imgur.com/a/L4hBDRw
    submitted by    /u/Dear-Second5353  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mirror list problem on install]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uh1qx8/mirror_list_problem_on_install/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uh1qx8/mirror_list_problem_on_install/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T22:40:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is my first install of arch so this could be an easy fix, but I’ve gone through the setup and have gotten to downloading a mirror list. I go to make a backup of the mirror list with the line “cp /ect/pacman.d/mirrorlist /ect/pacman.d/mirrorlist.bak” I get the error “cp: cannot stat ‘/ect/pacman.d/mirrorlist’ : No such file or directory” Any help would be great!
    submitted by    /u/jipeoples  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese cyber-espionage group Moshen Dragon targets Asian telcos]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/chinese-cyber-espionage-group-moshen-dragon-targets-asian-telcos/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/chinese-cyber-espionage-group-moshen-dragon-targets-asian-telcos/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T22:38:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers have identified a new cluster of malicious cyber activity tracked as Moshen Dragon, targeting telecommunication service providers in Central Asia. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel Tool Aims To Help Developers Move From OpenACC To OpenMP]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-OpenACC-To-OpenMP</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-OpenACC-To-OpenMP"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T22:36:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new open-source tool made public by Intel engineers last month aims to help migrate codebases from using OpenACC to OpenMP. In turn the OpenMP-based offloading is preferred for Intel's XPU offloading strategy...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[Android] Come installare app a pagamento tramite Aurora Store]]></title>
        <id>3563|20220503000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/android-28/android-come-installare-app-pagamento-tramite-aurora-store-3563"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ho già parlato di Aurora Store in un precedente articolo perché è un ausilio fondamentale per poter utilizzare Android senza un account Google configurato sul dispositivo. Vedremo adesso come è possibile installare con questo store app acquistate tramite il classico Play Store!
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sony WH-1000XM5 Headphone Leak Suggests a Sleek New Design]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/116738/sony-wh-1000xm5-headphone-leak-suggests-a-sleek-new-design/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/116738/sony-wh-1000xm5-headphone-leak-suggests-a-sleek-new-design/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T21:25:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While we’ve heard a few reports regarding Sony’s upcoming WH-1000XM5 headphones, we recently received our first big leak revealing plenty of exciting information. Including a sleek new design, substantially longer battery life, enhanced ANC, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Assign a Home Screen on Android]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=361529</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/13840107/assign-a-home-screen-on-android"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you tap the Home button on Android, you’re sent to your home screen. But what if you accidentally changed which screen is home? What if a system update switched your home screen? If you decide you want another screen to be home, you don’t have to move all your icons around. Instead, assign a home screen on Android using any existing screen.
   

Content

Assign a Home Screen on Android
Removing a New Home Screen
Home Screen Changed
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Turn Flashlight On and Off on Android
    
Assign a Home Screen on Android
    
Any screen you create on your Android device can be a home screen. Usually, the first screen is set as your home, but it can easily be the third or fourth if you’d like. Sometimes you may decide to make a... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Crystal Crowder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[no internet, despite connecting to wifi]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uh028d/no_internet_despite_connecting_to_wifi/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uh028d/no_internet_despite_connecting_to_wifi/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T21:21:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This problem came up seemingly out of the blue. I logged out and back in from gnome for applying some changes to gdm and the internet wouldn't work , it connects perfectly to the wifi, but no internet. Therefore I would like some help in troubleshooting it.
 Internet works in other devices, I tried rebooting, reverting the changes to gdm (even if they shouldn't impact the internet) , restarting the router, tried connecting to other networks, logging in as root and even restoring a timeshift btrfs snapshot from the previous day. No luck
 And I am indeed connected to the network, I can access the router config page and my NAS. 
 I would really appreciate some help here, thanks in advance!
 I'm running the lts kernel (also tried booting into the latest one)
    submitted by    /u/Pombinha  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch security for a student]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uh01yk/arch_security_for_a_student/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uh01yk/arch_security_for_a_student/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T21:21:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, I apologize if this is off-topic, but it seems to abide by the rules. I'm a CS student who will use arch since I have an Asus laptop that doesn't play nicely with other distros. I'm not an overly security-conscious person but I'm wondering how my arch installation would compare to more common OS like Windows or Mac. I'm using a non privledged user with sudo and have apparmor and firejail enabled, but only with the default profiles. I'm not quite knowledgeable enough to create my own profiles. I also use ufw with the basic ruleset described in the arch wiki. I did some other steps on the arch wiki security page but I didn't want to go too far down the rabbit hole and do anything I don't understand. I've also heard mixed opinions on both apparmor and firejail. Alongside common sense and an adblocker, is this enough basic security? I realize this is largely opinion-based but it's not like I have extremely valuable information on my laptop.
    submitted by    /u/remdit4me  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Embed Python scripts in HTML with PyScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/embed-python-scripts-in-html-with-pyscript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/embed-python-scripts-in-html-with-pyscript/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T21:17:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The project was announced this weekend at PyCon US 2022 and acts as a wrapper around the Pyodide project, which loads the CPython interpreter as a WebAssembly browser module. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New PyScript project lets you run Python programs in the browser]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/new-pyscript-project-lets-you-run-python-programs-in-the-browser/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/new-pyscript-project-lets-you-run-python-programs-in-the-browser/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T21:17:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The project was announced this weekend at PyCon US 2022 and acts as a wrapper around the Pyodide project, which loads the CPython interpreter as a WebAssembly browser module. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How do I download NetworkManager without Wi-Fi on Arch Linux?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ugzlv2/how_do_i_download_networkmanager_without_wifi_on/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ugzlv2/how_do_i_download_networkmanager_without_wifi_on/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T21:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/Easy_Alps_3095  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does Your Computer Have a Virus? Here’s How to Check]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=441321</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/441321/does-your-computer-have-a-virus-heres-how-to-check/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows computers sometimes do get viruses and other malware, but not every slow or misbehaving PC is infected by malware. Here’s how to check if you actually have a virus—and whether that suspicious process is dangerous or not.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Looking For an Equalizer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ugyofz/looking_for_an_equalizer/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ugyofz/looking_for_an_equalizer/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T20:19:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm a bit of an audiophile, but still shit with coding. Are there any applications in the AUR or other repos with a global or even per-app equalizer? I need more bass in my skull.
    submitted by    /u/xXTheOceanManXx  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Gamers Should Upgrade From a 60Hz Monitor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=794992</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/794992/why-gamers-should-upgrade-from-a-60hz-monitor/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T20:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Playing video games on a 60Hz puts you at a huge disadvantage as a gamer, both competitively and aesthetically. Here’s why you should upgrade to at least a 120Hz monitor to significantly improve your gaming and overall experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Nguyen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can't Sign Up for Hulu From Android Devices Anymore, Here's Why]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/116691/you-cant-sign-up-for-hulu-from-android-devices-anymore-heres-why/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/116691/you-cant-sign-up-for-hulu-from-android-devices-anymore-heres-why/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T19:45:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lately, Google’s made a lot of changes regarding how Android apps handle payments, and those changes are starting to affect people in multiple ways. The latest being users are unable to sign up for Hulu in the Android app or on Android-powered smart TVs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[i cant install arch linux every time the installer is almost done i get a error saying it failed to install the boot loader]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ugxua8/i_cant_install_arch_linux_every_time_the/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ugxua8/i_cant_install_arch_linux_every_time_the/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T19:41:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/ttv_toeasy13  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Cool Things You Can Do with the Samsung Galaxy S22 Ultra]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/116640/7-cool-things-you-can-do-with-the-samsung-galaxy-s22-ultra/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/116640/7-cool-things-you-can-do-with-the-samsung-galaxy-s22-ultra/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T19:31:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your new Galaxy S22 Ultra is more than just a pretty face. Samsung filled the new flagship with tons of unique and useful features—so many, in fact, that some of the Galaxy S22 Ultra’s best features may fly under your radar. So, here are seven cool things you can do with your Galaxy S22 Ultra.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD Posts Linux Driver Patches For New "VCN 4.0" IP Block]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMDGPU-VCN-4.0-Patches</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMDGPU-VCN-4.0-Patches"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T19:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After last week AMD began posting the "GFX11" patches for RDNA3, today AMD published a set of patches enabling the VCN 4.0 IP block for next-generation video encode/decode capabilities...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get a 2021 Apple iPad Mini for Under $400]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=485372</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15267839/2021-apple-ipad-mini"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you can’t decide between an iPhone and iPad, why not get the best of both with an iPad Mini? The 2021 Apple iPad Mini has a Liquid Retina Display, Touch ID, Wi-Fi 6, and works with the 2nd gen Apple Pencil. Get it now for just $399.99.
    
The 6th edition of the iPad Mini has an all-new design with an 8.3″ Liquid Retina display. It’s big enough to see everything on your screen – yet small enough to fit in your hand. The 2nd gen Apple Pencil will attach to the side to charge magnetically. Use Touch ID for secure identification to log in to the iPad and your apps.
    

    
The 2021 Apple iPad Mini includes the new A15 Bionic chip, and an all-day battery allows you to use it for work and leisure activities for up to 10 hours. Make use of the expansive app library on the App Store to do it all. Edit photos and videos, play games, and use the AR capabilities. It includes Wi-Fi 6... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Web Apps Aren’t Going Anywhere]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=802588</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/802588/javascript-web-apps-arent-going-anywhere/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T19:02:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most websites and web applications are written in JavaScript, or at least something that is converted to JavaScript. There have been many attempts over the years to change that, but don’t expect JavaScript to completely go away anytime soon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Find Your iPhone’s IP Address]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=796854</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/796854/iphone-ip-address/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your iPhone’s IP address is a string of numbers identifying your phone on the local network. In some cases, it’s useful to know what it is. We’ll show you a quick and easy way to check your iPhone’s private IP address.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I try to update my Arch Linux but there is an issue with GPG keys it not sure why, I tried all the known ways from the internet and youtube, can anyone help me with this?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ugwuuo/i_try_to_update_my_arch_linux_but_there_is_an/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ugwuuo/i_try_to_update_my_arch_linux_but_there_is_an/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T18:56:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/576096666755792906/970668381990690856/unknown.png
 I tried the following ways but these gave me the error
  
​
 sudo rm -r /etc/pacman.d/gnupg sudo pacman-key --init sudo pacman-key --populate archlinux 
  
updated arch key rings
  
​
 sudo pacman -S archlinux-keyring 
  
Refreshed keys
  
​
 sudo pacman-key --refresh 
 I tried all the ways, I found but not able to the packages this is the error:
 yay error: GPGME error: No data error: GPGME error: No data error: GPGME error: No data :: Synchronizing package databases... core 156.2 KiB 164 KiB/s 00:01 [######################] 100% extra 1699.6 KiB 3.61 MiB/s 00:00 [######################] 100% community 6.6 MiB 2.09 MiB/s 00:03 [########################################################################################] 100% error: GPGME error: No data error: GPGME error: No data error: GPGME error: No data error: failed to synchronize all databases (invalid or corrupted database (PGP signature)) -> error installing repo packages 
 ​
    submitted by    /u/Sridhar02  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Defender for Business stand-alone now generally available]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-defender-for-business-stand-alone-now-generally-available/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-defender-for-business-stand-alone-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T18:34:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft says that its enterprise-grade endpoint security for small to medium-sized businesses is now generally available. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Installing/Running Sonarr/Radarr as user]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ugw011/installingrunning_sonarrradarr_as_user/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ugw011/installingrunning_sonarrradarr_as_user/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T18:18:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm trying to install and/or run Sonarr as my user so that it can read/write to my mounted NAS, but so far I haven't had any luck. I installed Sonarr with Yay and edited the user and group in /usr/lib/systemd/system/sonarr.service as well as chowned the user and group of /var/lib/sonarr. I also tried adding sonarr to the users group and mounting the NAS as that, still no luck. I uninstalled and reinstalled manually, using makepkg. After building I edited sonarr.service, sonarr.sysusers, and sonar.tmpfiles to change the user and group, then installed. Sonarr still installed with the user and group sonarr. Editing sonarr.service once again prevented Sonarr from running. I'm really at a loss as to what to do. I was able to add to my Sonarr library when I mounted my NAS as sonarr:sonarr, but that's not really a solution.
 Any help would be greatly appreciated.
    submitted by    /u/TopherL2014  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Count Characters in a Cell in Google Sheets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=796205</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/796205/character-count-google-sheets/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T18:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unlike Google Docs, Google Sheets doesn’t automatically keep track of character counts for you. If you need to count all or specific characters in a cell, there are a few ways to accomplish this, and we’ll show you how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel Posts Early Linux Enablement Patches For Ponte Vecchio]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-Ponte-Vecchio-i915-Enable</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-Ponte-Vecchio-i915-Enable"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to Intel's "i915" DRM kernel driver much of the work lately by the company's open-source engineers have been focused on DG2/Alchemist for Arc Graphics products. There has been some occasional DRM kernel driver patches mentioning their HPC work and Ponte Vecchio "PVC" preparations while sent out today was the first set of patches actually introducing Ponte Vecchio to this kernel driver...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Pay: bufera sull'impossibilità di accedere al sistema di pagamento da parte di terzi]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Apple-Pay-bufera-sull-impossibilita-di-accedere-al-sistema-di-pagamento-da-parte-di-terzi_24445</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Apple-Pay-bufera-sull-impossibilita-di-accedere-al-sistema-di-pagamento-da-parte-di-terzi_24445"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T17:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Come avevamo anticipato nei giorni scorsi, nuvoloni neri si addensano su Apple Pay, lo strumento di pagamento in mobilità che consente di effettuare transazioni contactless utilizzando un iPhone 6 e successivi o un Apple Watch di qualsiasi generazione presso i negozi fisici grazie al chip NFC integrato.La Commissione Europea ha avviato una verifica formale nei confronti di Apple incentrata proprio sul funzionamento di Pay.La Mela impedisce ai soggetti terzi e ai concorrenti di accedere al suo sistema di pagamento via NFC: tra gli esclusi vi sono ad esempio PayPal e i principali istituti di credito.La tecnologia NFC permette a ciascun utente di pagare avvicinando lo smartphone al terminale di pagamento o POS. Il dispositivo dell'utente è a sua volta collegato con una o più carte di debito o di credito attraverso un portafoglio virtuale.Con il sistema attuale Apple non permette a terzi di elaborare pagamenti attraverso il sistema Pay dicendo che diversamente verrebbero meno la sicurezza e la privacy degli utenti.Al termine dell'indagine preliminare, la Commissione spiega di aver contestato ad Apple la sua decisione di impedire agli sviluppatori di app di accedere all'hardware e al software necessari (utilizzo del chip NFC integrato) a vantaggio della sua soluzione per la gestione dei pagamenti, Apple Pay appunto.'Abbiamo rilevato in via preliminare che Apple potrebbe aver limitato la concorrenza a vantaggio della sua soluzione Apple Pay.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your Roku Device Now Has Apple Music]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=802578</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/802578/your-roku-device-now-has-apple-music/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T17:56:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Music has been around since 2015, but it’s still missing on many popular platforms. Apple Music has been missing from Roku (which sells some of our favorite streaming devices) since the service first launched, but that is finally changing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google SMTP relay service abused for sending phishing emails]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/google-smtp-relay-service-abused-for-sending-phishing-emails/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/google-smtp-relay-service-abused-for-sending-phishing-emails/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T17:51:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Phishing actors abuse Google's SMTP relay service to bypass email security products and successfully deliver malicious emails to targeted users. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VESA AdaptiveSync e MediaSync: cosa sono le due nuove certificazioni]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=VESA-AdaptiveSync-e-MediaSync-cosa-sono-le-due-nuove-certificazioni_24460</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=VESA-AdaptiveSync-e-MediaSync-cosa-sono-le-due-nuove-certificazioni_24460"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T17:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Com'è noto sia AMD che NVidia certificano i monitor compatibile con le rispettive tecnologie FreeSync e G-SYNC: si tratta delle soluzioni che introducono il refresh variabile e permettono di 'sincronizzare' il pannello del display con l'uscita della scheda video. I risultati ai quali pervengono AMD e NVidia sono però spesso diversi a causa delle particolarità che contraddistinguono le due tecnologie: ne abbiamo parlato nell'articolo in cui spieghiamo come scegliere monitor per PC.La certificazione AdaptiveSync di VESA offre una 'copertura' completa prendendo in considerazione sia le valutazioni di AMD che di NVidia sia una serie di aspetti addizionali.

La certificazione VESA è 'aperta' offrendo i risultati di 50 differenti test ai quali sono sottoposti i monitori AdaptiveSync: i vari giudizi includono prove tecniche e visive come flickering, frame drop, jitter, tempi di risposta dei pixel (grey to grey o GaG), ghosting, reverse ghosting e altro ancora.Per essere certificati AdaptiveSync i monitor devono supportare una frequenza di refresh minima pari ad almeno 60 Hz spingendosi fino a 144 Hz.Nel caso della certificazione MediaSync bastano un minimo di 48 Hz e un massimo di almeno 60 Hz: questa 'forbice' è ideale per gestire nella maniera più adeguata la resa di qualunque genere di contenuto multimediale.Anche nel caso di MediaSync lo sfarfallio deve essere assente, sono previsti gli stessi requisiti per evitare il ghosting di AdaptiveSync mentre il jitter deve essere pari a ±0,5 ms per una corretta riproduzione su PC di contenuti multimediali che sono tipicamente registrati a 23,976 Hz (valore che VESA stessa indica come uno 'standard' di fatto per gli studios di Hollywood)..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cyberspies use IP cameras to deploy backdoors, steal Exchange emails]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cyberspies-use-ip-cameras-to-deploy-backdoors-steal-exchange-emails/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cyberspies-use-ip-cameras-to-deploy-backdoors-steal-exchange-emails/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T17:28:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A newly discovered and uncommonly stealthy Advanced Persistent Threat (APT) group is breaching corporate networks to steal Exchange (on-premise and online) emails from employees involved in corporate transactions such as mergers and acquisitions. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[System freezes when hibernating]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uguuud/system_freezes_when_hibernating/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uguuud/system_freezes_when_hibernating/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T17:27:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I often get system freezes during hibernation. I followed that guide https://www.kernel.org/doc/html/latest/power/basic-pm-debugging.html iterating the different test modes for /sys/Power/pm_test. As it seems, hibernation freezes due to a device driver, so I need to disable a half of my drivers? That would even mean I can't boot my system up, I think. Couldn't we narrow the set of possible drivers? I mean, aren't only drivers interesting supporting S4 modes, I don't know. I see a list of devices in /proc/acpi/wakeup, but I can't disable them by writing echo $device > /proc/acpi/wakeup or did I have to disable drivers over rmmod/unloading drivers at boot time? Any suggestions?
    submitted by    /u/sighoya  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yeedi Vac MAX Robot Vacuum Review]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=482308</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15267712/yeedi-vac-max-robot-vacuum"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T17:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When doing your spring cleaning this year, you may have noticed you had to do more than expected on your floors. If you are resolved to do better moving forward, you can start with a yeedi vac MAX Robot Vacuum. Read this review to see how it compares to other robot vacuums.
    
This is a sponsored article and was made possible by Yeedi. The actual contents and opinions are the sole views of the author who maintains editorial independence, even when a post is sponsored.
    
Setting Up the yeedi vac MAX
    
Everything was packed inside the box for the yeedi vac MAX Robot Vacuum as expected. One notable difference from other vacuums is the lack of spare brushes and filters. Every other vacuum I’ve reviewed has had extra brushes and filters.
    

    
Packed inside the box is:
    
Robot vacuum
Side brush
Mopping plate
Cloth mopping Pad
Several Disposable mopping pads
Charger
Electrical cord
Quick Start Guide and Manual
    
It also has a regular charger instead... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arcade1Up's 'NBA Jam SHAQ Edition' Lets You Slam Dunk at Home]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/116658/arcade1ups-nba-jam-shaq-edition-lets-you-slam-dunk-at-home/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/116658/arcade1ups-nba-jam-shaq-edition-lets-you-slam-dunk-at-home/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T17:08:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In January, Arcade1Up announced several new machines coming with upgraded 19-inch screens, and now, the company just confirmed one of its biggest arcade cabinets yet. That being the new Arcade1Up NBA Jam: SHAQ Edition.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Show All Hidden Rows and Columns in Google Sheets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=799255</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/799255/how-to-show-all-hidden-rows-and-columns-in-google-sheets/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T17:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In your large Google Sheets spreadsheets, it’s difficult to find the rows and columns that are hidden. Luckily, you can use a built-in Sheets feature to unhide all your hidden rows and columns at once. We’ll show you how to use this option.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our New Favorite Robot Vacuum Goes on Sale Today]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=801973</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/801973/our-new-favorite-robot-vacuum-goes-on-sale-today/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T16:28:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to robot vacuums, few companies push the boundaries of possibility as effectively as Roborock. Introducing features like advanced navigation with obstacle avoidance, industry-leading suction power, and an automatic bin emptying system, the company continues to redefine what a robot vacuum can do. This year, Roborock has truly outdone themselves by taking all of their fine-tuned innovations and cramming them into the brand new S7 MaxV Ultra, available for purchase starting today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zach Laidlaw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Open Notifications With One Hand on a Google Pixel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=800448</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/800448/how-to-open-notifications-with-one-hand-on-a-google-pixel/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T16:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s no getting around the fact that the majority of Android phones are very large. The Google Pixel series is not exempt from this trend. Thankfully, they have a handy gesture to make opening the notifications easier.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Le 10 Domande su Whatsapp più richieste]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2015/09/le-10-domande-whatsapp-piu-richieste.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2015/09/le-10-domande-whatsapp-piu-richieste.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WhatsApp è una tra le app più usate al mondo ed è normale, vista la sua popolarità, è lecito avere dubbi sul suo funzionamento o su come vengono gestiti i dati personali associati all'app. Non è un caso infatti che la maggior parte delle domande su WhatsApp sono legate alla privacy, al chi può vedere cosa, al come si possa scoprire chi è online o chi legge un messaggio o, viceversa, come...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Nest Hub Gets Even More Integration for Activity Metrics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/116647/google-nest-hub-gets-even-more-integration-for-activity-metrics/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/116647/google-nest-hub-gets-even-more-integration-for-activity-metrics/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T15:51:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Health integrations on Google’s fantastic Nest Hub will become even more robust thanks to a neat new feature. Soon, you will be able to view a bigger variety of activity metrics from Google Fit or Fitbit—like daily calories burned or your steps—directly on the device.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzanne Humphries</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ford F-150 Lightning EV's Most Exciting Feature Is Cheaper Than Expected]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/116642/ford-f-150-lightning-evs-most-exciting-feature-is-cheaper-than-expected/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/116642/ford-f-150-lightning-evs-most-exciting-feature-is-cheaper-than-expected/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T15:48:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most exciting features of the new F-150 Lightning EV is support for bidirectional charging, which owners can use to power their homes in an emergency or power outage. Users will also need Ford’s “Home Integration System,” and it’s more affordable than expected.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Car rental giant Sixt facing disruptions due to a cyberattack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/car-rental-giant-sixt-facing-disruptions-due-to-a-cyberattack/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/car-rental-giant-sixt-facing-disruptions-due-to-a-cyberattack/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T15:44:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[​Car rental giant Sixt was hit by a weekend cyberattack causing business disruptions at customer care centers and select branch [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eseguire programmi Windows 10 e 11 senza far apparire UAC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Eseguire-programmi-Windows-10-e-11-senza-far-apparire-UAC_24458</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Eseguire-programmi-Windows-10-e-11-senza-far-apparire-UAC_24458"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T15:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Per impostazione predefinita, quando un qualunque programma deve poter effettuare modifiche profonde alla configurazione di Windows, vengono richiesti i diritti di amministratore.La richiesta viene gestita con la comparsa della schermata UAC (User Account Control): introdotta ai tempi di Windows Vista essa avvisa l'utente ogni volta che un programma in esecuzione richiede privilegi più elevati rispetto a quelli di base.In un altro articolo abbiamo visto come trovare i programmi che usano i privilegi di amministratore in Windows e come mostrare il pulsante Sì nella finestra UAC se esso fosse sparito.Sia in Windows 10 che in Windows 11 il comportamento della funzione di protezione che impedisce ai programmi in esecuzione di apportare modifiche sostanziali al sistema può essere personalizzato…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Spot a Facebook Phishing Email and Similar Scams]]></title>
        <id>http://maketecheasier.com/?p=27819</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15267419/differentiate-phishing-facebook-mail"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While Facebook (now Meta) is a great place for sharing life moments and staying in contact with friends and family, it is also one of the most common places for scams and fraud on the Internet. A recent report from AI-based cybersecurity firm Vade concluded that in 2021 Facebook once again dominated social media phishing. 
    
With this in mind, it’s now more important than ever to know how to protect yourself from these attacks while using the social network. This article looks at various phishing scenarios and explain what telltale signs to look for. We’ll also walk you through various recommendations that will help you keep your account and personal information safe.
   

Content

What Is Social Media Phishing?
1. Determine Whether the Sender's Email Address Is Legitimate
2. Pay Attention to the Email’s Subject
3. Hover Your Mouse Cursor Over the Link
4. Check if the Email Is Personally Addressed to You
5. Check if the Email Asks for Any Personal Information
Common Facebook Scams to Watch Out For
How to Avoid Phishing Scams on Facebook
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexandra Arici</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch Linux and file names with Korean letters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ugs3ph/arch_linux_and_file_names_with_korean_letters/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ugs3ph/arch_linux_and_file_names_with_korean_letters/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T15:24:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi. I tried to get one Windows game running on arch. Extracting it was a pain as I got errors when trying to extract it. I managed to do that from a VM. After that, the game launches but crashes almost instantly saying that a file was not found (the file contains Korean letters). I tried it on Debian and it works just fine.
 I do have the Korean locale and a font installed. What should I do?
    submitted by    /u/SanttuPOIKA----  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add a Trendline in Microsoft Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=798850</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/798850/how-to-add-a-trendline-in-microsoft-excel/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T15:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adding a trendline to your chart helps your audience better understand the data by way of visualization. Not only can you add a trendline to your already-existing chart in Excel, but you can also format it, too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marshall Gunnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Question: IPv6 on Laptop]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ugr05h/question_ipv6_on_laptop/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ugr05h/question_ipv6_on_laptop/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T14:33:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have breathed new life into my 1st generation Chromebook Pixel by install Arch, Wayland and SWAY. I find it runs better than it ever did with ChromeOS
 I am having problems getting IPv6 working... so a bit of a walkthrough of my set-up
 I have installed iwd, dhcpcd and openresolv for all my networking needs. In general it works great by IPv6 does not seem to work for me, and after browsing the Wiki I can't find any indication.
 My system boots, joins my Wireless Network and then gets an IP and DNS from DHCP. I can browse the internet and access local resources
 My IWD Configuration:
 [Scan] DisablePeriodicScan=true [Network] EnableIPv6=true [General] #EnableNetworkConfiguration=truefe80::14e9:5e75:5d84:b3a dev wlan0 lladdr 90:9c:4a:b7:19:07 STALE fe80::367e:5cff:fef7:1738 dev wlan0 lladd…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Discord randomly freezing all the time]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ugqkzm/discord_randomly_freezing_all_the_time/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ugqkzm/discord_randomly_freezing_all_the_time/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T14:13:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since of today Discord has become unusable for me because it frequently freezes for a few minutes. It seems to be a problem only existing on Arch. On Fedora it worked flawlessly today.
 Is anyone else experiencing this rn? Did try a reinstall of Discord and reboot already, none worked.
    submitted by    /u/Leskodamus  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Pixel 3a Updates End This Month, It's Time to Shop for a New Phone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/116632/google-pixel-3a-updates-end-this-month-its-time-to-shop-for-a-new-phone/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/116632/google-pixel-3a-updates-end-this-month-its-time-to-shop-for-a-new-phone/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T14:12:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Of all the Pixel phones in Google’s backlog, the Pixel 3a is my favorite. It’s the best affordable phone I’ve ever used, and it remains relatively bug-free by Pixel standards. Unfortunately, Google will no longer offer software or security updates for the Pixel 3a or Pixel 3a XL. It’s time to shop for a new phone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Robot Vacuums of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=749819</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/749819/best-robot-vacuum/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robot vacuums are convenient home appliances that keep your floors clean. They pick up dirt, hair, and other debris while navigating around your home. Check out our recommended list of robot vacuums to find one that’s right for your home.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Nguyen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD Ryzen 7 5800X3D Continues Showing Much Potential For 3D V-Cache In Technical Computing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31091</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31091"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a follow-up to last week's AMD Ryzen 7 5800X3D Linux review, here are some additional Linux benchmarks of this first AMD Ryzen CPU with 3D V-Cache.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>