<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-06-08T01:50:37.173Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Help needed with fontconfig]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v7cvuc/help_needed_with_fontconfig/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v7cvuc/help_needed_with_fontconfig/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T01:01:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, I am having problems displaying monospaced fonts in Arch Linux after running sudo pacman -Syu some weeks ago, several packages were upgraded including fontconfig [Imgur Album].
 Problem Description
 Firefox, Chromium, Slack, and other applications are displaying monospaced font as regular, sans-serif fonts (screenshot). To my surprise, monospaced fonts still work on some websites, like archlinux.org (screenshot). Using Web Developer Tools in Firefox it is possible to see that the font resolution is clearly messed up in the left (Github) and not on the right (screenshot).
 Attempted Fixes
  
Tried reinstalling fontconfig and all applications where fonts are not working, didn't work.
 Tried running fc-cache -s, didn't work.
 Tried symlinking all the default fonts again using the comma…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Link Your Android Phone to Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=399714</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/14496622/make-receive-android-phone-calls-windows"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple users who have Macs, iPhones, and iPads enjoy a high level of integration between these devices. Windows users have every reason to envy this, but there’s good news. If you have a Windows computer (running Windows 10 or 11) and an Android phone or tablet, you can link them together and have a little taste of the integrated life.
   

Content

How to Connect Your Android Device to Windows
1. Download the Link to Windows App 
2. Link the Two Devices
Send Text Messages
View Photos From Your Phone
Make Calls
Useful Sidebar Features
Special Features Limited to Select Devices
Phone Link Changes Everything

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Share Files Between Android and Windows on Your Network
    
How to Connect Your Android Device to Windows
    
The process of linking your Windows PC with your... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sydney Butler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram to soon launch its premium plan at $4.99 per month]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/telegram-to-soon-launch-its-premium-plan-at-499-per-month/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/telegram-to-soon-launch-its-premium-plan-at-499-per-month/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T23:58:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In addition to official advertisements in the messaging app, Telegram is also bringing a new premium subscription to the messaging app. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mayank Parmar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US seizes SSNDOB market for selling personal info of 24 million people]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-seizes-ssndob-market-for-selling-personal-info-of-24-million-people/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-seizes-ssndob-market-for-selling-personal-info-of-24-million-people/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T23:47:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SSNDOB, an online marketplace that sold the names, social security numbers, and dates of birth of approximately 24 million US people, has been taken offline following an international law enforcement operation. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US: Chinese govt hackers breached telcos to snoop on network traffic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-chinese-govt-hackers-breached-telcos-to-snoop-on-network-traffic/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-chinese-govt-hackers-breached-telcos-to-snoop-on-network-traffic/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T22:43:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several US federal agencies today revealed that Chinese-backed threat actors have targeted and compromised major telecommunications companies and network service providers to steal credentials and harvest data. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New SVCReady malware loads from Word doc properties]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-svcready-malware-loads-from-word-doc-properties/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-svcready-malware-loads-from-word-doc-properties/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T22:24:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A previously unknown malware loader named SVCReady has been discovered in phishing attacks, featuring an unusual way of loading the malware from Word documents onto compromised machines. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Partition shows up twice in Nemo]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v79l5l/partition_shows_up_twice_in_nemo/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v79l5l/partition_shows_up_twice_in_nemo/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T22:22:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What the title says.
 I run Sway WM, use Nemo as my FM and like the mix of the two. I checked Thunar and it too shows the damn partition twice in my sidebar just like Nemo does. It's very weird. It also allows one to unmount the partition but I suppose that's normal? I've never used Nemo or Thunar until this particular install. Quite a strange issue.
 I do have udev automounting that partition as evidenced by a simple mount |grep data which gives me this:
 ↪ mount|grep data systemd-1 on /data type autofs (rw,relatime,fd=48,pgrp=1,timeout=0,minproto=5,maxproto=5,direct,pipe_ino=17512) /dev/nvme0n1p4 on /data type btrfs (rw,nosuid,nodev,relatime,ssd,discard,space_cache,commit=60,subvolid=5,subvol=/,x-systemd.automount,x-gvfs-show) 
 Could this be the issue? Further information in case it helps:
 ↪ lsblk -l NAME MAJ:MIN RM SIZE RO TYPE MOUNTPOINTS nvme0n1 259:0 0 238.5G 0 disk nvme0n1p1 259:1 0 300M 0 part /boot nvme0n1p2 259:2 0 73.2G 0 part / nvme0n1p3 259:3 0 73.2G 0 part /home nvme0n1p4 259:4 0 81.9G 0 part /data nvme0n1p5 259:5 0 9.8G 0 part [SWAP] 
 My /etc/fstab:
 # /dev/nvme0n1p4 LABEL=data UUID=7ad4926e-5301-4c75-9047-a90b025a985f /data btrfs rw,nosuid,nodev,relatime,ssd,discard,space_cache,subvolid=5,noauto,x-systemd.automount,x-gvfs-show,commit=60,subvol=/ 0 0 
    submitted by    /u/raineling  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qbot malware now uses Windows MSDT zero-day in phishing attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/qbot-malware-now-uses-windows-msdt-zero-day-in-phishing-attacks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/qbot-malware-now-uses-windows-msdt-zero-day-in-phishing-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T22:03:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A critical Windows zero-day vulnerability, known as Follina and still waiting for an official fix from Microsoft, is now being actively exploited in ongoing phishing attacks to infect recipients with Qbot malware. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spotify senza limiti e pubblicità? xManager è il gestore di mod che fa al caso tuo]]></title>
        <id>3583|20220608000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/blocca-pubblicita-block-3390/spotify-senza-limiti-pubblicita-xmanager-gestore-mod-fa-caso-3583"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spotify è un'app che corrisponde ad un servizio musicale che prevede un piano gratuito con delle limitazioni e un piano a pagamento. Grazie al lavoro dei modder, oggi disponiamo di una coppia di app per Android che permettono di aggirare alcuni dei limiti del servizio gratuito.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Google Pay to Track Your Spending and Budget Your Money]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=377673</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/14189712/use-google-pay-track-spending-budgeting"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Google Pay app has a variety of great features to make managing your finances easier. One of the more useful features is the ability to link your debit and credit cards. Doing so will enable you to use Google Pay to track your spending, making balancing your checkbook and budgeting your money super easy.
    
Google Pay is in the middle of another makeover. It has been rebranded, again, as Google Wallet in certain countries. However, Google Pay users in US and Canada can continue to use the app, albeit with a different name, for tracking expenses and budgeting.
   

Content

What Is Google Pay?
How Does Google Pay Help with Budgeting?
Download the Google Pay App
Link Your Bank Account
What Is Plaid?
How to See All of Your Transactions
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:7 of the Best Virtual Credit Card Services
... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Crystal Crowder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xorg-server update broke 2 different arch setups]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v77rpm/xorgserver_update_broke_2_different_arch_setups/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v77rpm/xorgserver_update_broke_2_different_arch_setups/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T21:09:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On my main system (no DM, bspwm), after updating with `pacman -Syu`, several things updated, including xorg-server. Everything was fine until a reboot. Systemd-login would try to start X, but would kick me back to login after "cannot connect to xserver: bad file descriptor". I tried to troubleshoot via other TTY, and read up on the usage of Xorg.wrap if launching X with root is required, but haven't had any luck yet.
 I read https://wiki.archlinux.org/title/xorg#Rootless_Xorg and tried to get it going with that, but no luck.
 I'm pretty sure this has to do with the change of rootles xorg by default. To verify, I booted up my other system, which has lightdm running with bspwm. After updating, it just goes to a black screen with a frozen cursor at the top left.
 I thought I'd see other people mentioning this, but nothing yet.
    submitted by    /u/svjness  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Does “5G UC” Mean on an iPhone or Android Phone?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=758203</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/758203/what-does-5g-uc-mean-on-an-iphone/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you use a modern iPhone or Android phone on T-Mobile’s cellular network, there’s a good chance you’ll see the “5G UC” icon on the status bar instead of “5G.” Here’s what it tells you about your cellular connection.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can't open links from outside of firefox]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v77h2y/cant_open_links_from_outside_of_firefox/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v77h2y/cant_open_links_from_outside_of_firefox/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T20:58:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey y'all,
 I'm running Arch with KDE as an X11 session and Waterfox as my default browser. Whenever I click on links from other applications (e.g. Discord or even the help page links in base programs like my System settings) it opens a new tab with the file index of my home folder. In some cases I can copy the link and paste it in a new tab and that works just fine but it's still a problem for me that I want to have fixed. 
 I looked up some pages but most of them have the same issue but are running a Wayland session, while I am on X11. Anyone else encountered this problem, and if yes, how did you fix it? 
 Thanks!
    submitted by    /u/daveedmee  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chromebooks Have a New Screen Recorder App]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809892</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809892/chromebooks-have-a-new-screen-recorder-app/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T20:54:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s already possible to record your screen on a Chromebook, but the built-in screen recorder is fairly basic. Google has now released an upgraded recorder that you can try out on your Chromebook.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Block websites on wifi hotspot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v774o3/block_websites_on_wifi_hotspot/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v774o3/block_websites_on_wifi_hotspot/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T20:44:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I made a wifi hotspot using this gui tool is there a way to block some websites like youtube on the wifi hotspot created? and only on it, not on my computer internet
    submitted by    /u/ZacS2  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BTRFS RAID root on luks with systemd boot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v76oi9/btrfs_raid_root_on_luks_with_systemd_boot/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v76oi9/btrfs_raid_root_on_luks_with_systemd_boot/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T20:27:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello,
 I was wondering how to make systemd boot ask for the passphrase of more than just one (the root) device, so I could balance the root to a RAID and be sure that all the disks get decrypted at bootup. Sadly I was not able to find any information on this, so I thought I would just ask it in here. 
 Does the bootloader detect the RAID member structure on the sepcified root drive and is it maybe able to trace the remaining member disks of the RAID, so it would automatically ask me to decrypt all?
 Or is there anything I need to specify for example in the boot options for this to work?
 ​
 I am using systemd-boot with an unencrypted vfat efi partition. My root is on a btrfs partition and I am planning to stretch the root fs to make a RAID of three disks. 
 Thanks in advance!
    submitted by    /u/KonKavex  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Does Spotify’s “Enhance” Button Do, and How Do You Use It?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=757632</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/757632/what-does-spotifys-enhance-button-do-and-how-do-you-use-it/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Playlists are an integral part of the Spotify experience, which is why it’s always releasing new features to make them better. If you make your own playlists—and you should be—the “Enhance” button can give you a hand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Started Using the Docker Engine API]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?post_type=devops&amp;p=800754</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/devops/how-to-get-started-using-the-docker-engine-api/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T19:59:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Docker Engine exposes a REST API which you can use to control your containers without the docker CLI. The API exposes equivalent functionality using HTTP network calls. You can script common Docker operations using your favorite programming language or remotely control one of your hosts. The CLI internally relies on the same API to provide its built-in commands.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[total Linux newbie]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v7603k/total_linux_newbie/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v7603k/total_linux_newbie/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T19:58:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello all, I wanted to get into Linux but I was confused about what Linux to start with, I've done some research but It confused me even more, but I kind of liked Arch so I'm here to get opinions about Arch, how hard is it to learn for a total beginner if I am willing to give it some time, do y'all suggest it or not. and if I do install it, will it affect my everyday use of my computer throughout the learning phase?
    submitted by    /u/enormovsdix  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Started Using the Docker Engine API]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?post_type=devops&amp;p=800754</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/devops/how-to-get-started-using-the-docker-engine-api/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T19:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Docker Engine exposes a REST API which you can use to control your containers without the docker CLI. The API exposes equivalent functionality using HTTP network calls. You can script common Docker operations using your favorite programming language or remotely control one of your hosts. The CLI internally relies on the same API to provide its built-in commands.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s Actually Going On With the EU’s Common Charger Rules?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809787</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809787/whats-actually-going-on-with-the-eus-common-charger-rules/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T19:50:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 27 countries in the European Union have been considering a law for years that would force phones, tablets, laptops, and other mobile devices to use a single connector: USB Type-C. Now the EU is one step closer to pulling it off.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Need help. Restore Arch with timeshift after it got stuck booting after a reboot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v75tfy/need_help_restore_arch_with_timeshift_after_it/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v75tfy/need_help_restore_arch_with_timeshift_after_it/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T19:50:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After rebooting my pc it got stuck at booting, I'm using btrfs with subvolumes for home, opt, tmp, .snapshots (which I don't use) and var. And this is everything that happened:
 So I just rebooted my pc and it got stuck with the message Staring version 251.2-1-arch, but I could switch to other TTYs, login on them and the filesystem seemed normal. So I just created a snapshot with timeshift and restored one of 5 days ago, I just got an error saying E: Unable to remove directory at the end but I ignored it.
 Then I rebooted and after the message of Starting version... I got two errors, one saying that it failed to start kernel modules and other saying that failed to mount /boot so I just changed /boot mount options from /etc/fstab file to defaults but just threw me into recovery mode, I also removed the option subvolid in all subvolumes in fstab (because it caused problems with the /home subvolume before) and even tried commenting the line that mounts /boot which leaves me with Failed to start kernel modules but I can switch to other TTYs an all filesystem seems normal.
 After all I just restored to the snapshot created by default before restoring (it has the /boot line commented in /etc/fstab, and it got errors sayng something about failed to mount /dev/nvme0n1p1 (the /boot partition) in /run/timeshift/.../boot) but continued anyway and after rebooting I got an error with Failed to start kernel modules again but the system tried to start a graphical interface in TTY-7 and I was able to switch to TTYs.
 The only things I did on that session were: * Install librewolf with pacaur, but didn't even finished because some package validation failed. * Clone the virtual-display-linux into /opt/virtual-display-linux and tried running it, it said me to reboot. * Download the AppImage of deskreen to /opt/deskreen/Deskreen.AppImage and used it.
 Can someone tell me how to restore any snapshot that works??
    submitted by    /u/javalsai  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Entropy of /dev/random stuck at 256]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v75t5w/entropy_of_devrandom_stuck_at_256/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v75t5w/entropy_of_devrandom_stuck_at_256/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T19:49:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During the last 4 years or so, since I use this computer, the entropy in /dev/random was around 3600 (except right after a reboot). However, since a few days, the entropy is stuck at 256 (it doesn't fluctuate anymore either, which is a different behavior compared to before).
 The command I use to check the entropy level is cat /proc/sys/kernel/random/entropy_avail
 which I know lowers a very tiny bit the entropy, or at least used to, but an entropy stuck at 256 is a first for me. I do update my system almost daily, so maybe a Linux kernel update changed this behavior. I was wondering whether it's normal, what's going, and why it is stuck at that level.
 Thanks.
    submitted by    /u/no_choice99  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save $30 on a Google Nest Thermostat]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=444041</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/14913751/google-nest-thermostat"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the dog days of summer nearly here, you want to be able to get your home cooled down. But why pay to have the air conditioning going when you’re not even home? The Google Nest Thermostat can help you out here. It will also save on energy costs. Add to that a $30 discount, and it’s hard to argue against buying one when the savings will continue on in your energy bill month after month.
    
The smart thermostat is ENERGY STAR-certified to help you save energy while still keeping you comfortable at your desired temperature – meaning no more sweaty, sticky days (and no more chilly ones either). The thermostat will turn itself down or up when you leave so that you won’t be wasting energy – or money – cooling or heating your home when no one is there.
   
 
   
You can also program heating and cooling with a schedule so that it works best with your family’s schedule. The Savings Finder will search for other ways the Google... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can't connect to Wifi via. iwd]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v7529a/cant_connect_to_wifi_via_iwd/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v7529a/cant_connect_to_wifi_via_iwd/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T19:17:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've installed Arch to my Laptop (using USB tethering from my phone) and installed and then installed iwd. I enabled the iwd systemd service and tried to connect to Wifi using iwctl and it seemed to work at first, entering a wrong password would give an error ane entering the right one would give me no error. It doesn't actually connect.
 Using wpa-supplicant works fine and iwd used to work on this laptop, in the past.
 The Wifi chip is a QCA9377.
    submitted by    /u/Deathscyther1HD  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux version of Black Basta ransomware targets VMware ESXi servers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/linux-version-of-black-basta-ransomware-targets-vmware-esxi-servers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/linux-version-of-black-basta-ransomware-targets-vmware-esxi-servers/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T19:06:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Black Basta is the latest ransomware gang to add support for encrypting VMware ESXi virtual machines running on enterprise Linux servers. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Send a Friend Request on Facebook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=805793</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/805793/how-to-send-a-friend-request-on-facebook/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T19:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By adding someone as a friend on Facebook, you get access to more information on their profile page as well as see their posts in your news feed. In this guide, we’ll show you how to send a friend request to someone on Facebook from your desktop and your phone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GNOME's Mutter Variable Rate Refresh Support Closer To Being Merged]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=GNOME-Mutter-VRR-Closer</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=GNOME-Mutter-VRR-Closer"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T19:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Variable rate refresh (VRR / FreeSync / Adaptive-Sync) support for GNOME's Mutter compositor is closer to being merged. The native back-end support for VRR that has been in development the past two years is no longer considered a work-in-progress and it's believed there are no longer any blocking issues that would prevent this code from landing...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Backup an arch linux machine to NAS, using Synology Active Backup for Business?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v74h7l/backup_an_arch_linux_machine_to_nas_using/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v74h7l/backup_an_arch_linux_machine_to_nas_using/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T18:55:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To backup a linux machine using Active Backup for Business, you need to install some sort of agent software on linux.
 Synology provide an rpm, and a deb for download, but not entirely sure whether I should try installing this onto arch (I've heard it's tied to your kernel version anyway). 
 Likewise there's nothing in the AUR, although plenty of other Synology apps there.
 Has anyone got this working?
 I dont want to use Veaam, and I've prefer not to just rsync as I lose file permissions and ownership.
    submitted by    /u/pease_pudding  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[newbie] booting up first time time out error]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v7463t/newbie_booting_up_first_time_time_out_error/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v7463t/newbie_booting_up_first_time_time_out_error/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T18:43:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting version 251.2-1-arch…
 then it just reboots and does it again
 Starting version 251.2-1-arch…
 to which I get Time error
 [ TIME ] Timed out waiting for device /dev/disk/by-uuid/… [DEPEND Dependency failed for File System Check on /dev/disk/by-uuid/… [DEPEND Dependency failed for /boot/efi. [DEPEND Dependency failed for Local File Systems. [DEPEND Dependency failed for /boot. 
 After that. It enters emergency mode to which i enter my password successfully and try to
 pacman -S neofetch 
 type yes to download
 then it errors out and 
 gives error no packages were upgraded
 ​
 How do I go about fixing this? Thanks.
 ​
 ​
 ​
 …
    submitted by    /u/Squareisround  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EU Gives Apple Two Years to Ditch Lightning Cables]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120329/eu-gives-apple-two-years-to-ditch-lightning-cables/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120329/eu-gives-apple-two-years-to-ditch-lightning-cables/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T18:41:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Legislators within the European Union say they’ve reached an agreement on the “common charger” mandate that was proposed last year. By the end of 2024, all battery-powered portable devices sold in the EU must have a USB-C port or rely entirely on wireless charging. And yes, this applies to Apple’s iPhone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to globally listen and consume input events from keyboard / Controller?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v741ge/how_to_globally_listen_and_consume_input_events/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v741ge/how_to_globally_listen_and_consume_input_events/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T18:38:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey all, I know there's all sorts of libraries and packages for this, but its hard to know which will work well, and I am also curious how it works on a lower level. What shared libs does arch use for these functions?
 Basically I am trying to map a steam controller to keyboard events, but I want to add my own logic via python.
 I can either have steam map the controller to keyboard events, then consume those and output new key events, or just have steam output controller events (not sure what protocol this is) and consume those.
 I need the events to be input and output globally, as this is a control layer i want for all apps.
 Any advice is appreciated, thanks!
    submitted by    /u/coffeecofeecoffee  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ghacks Deals: The Ultimate Project & Quality Management Certification Training Bundle]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179029</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/07/ghacks-deals-the-ultimate-project-quality-management-certification-training-bundle/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T18:32:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ultimate Project & Quality Management Certification Training Bundle includes 10 project management courses. Courses teach skills such as Six Sigma and Agile, and even include certification training courses. The following courses […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Ghacks Deals: The Ultimate Project & Quality Management Certification Training Bundle appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A preview of Windows 11 version 22H2 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179025</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/07/a-preview-of-windows-11-version-22h2-is-now-available/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T18:21:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft released a preview of Windows 11 version 22H2, the upcoming feature update of the company's Windows 11 operating system, on June 7, 2022. Windows 11 version 22H2 will be the first […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post A preview of Windows 11 version 22H2 is now available appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DNS lag/timeouts after recent upgrade (using VPN).]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v73ga2/dns_lagtimeouts_after_recent_upgrade_using_vpn/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v73ga2/dns_lagtimeouts_after_recent_upgrade_using_vpn/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T18:16:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I did a pacman -Syu on Sunday and ever since my DNS lookups have been very flaky, sometimes taking about 30 seconds to resolve a domain. I use OpenVPN connected to a VPN service (using the regular OpenVPN daemon) and use NetworkManager to manage my Ethernet connection. I do not use the OpenVPN NetworkManager plugin.
 I can attribute this to DNS as trying to ping a domain name will have ping sometimes wait for about 30 seconds before looking up the domain and pinging OK, however pinging an Internet IP address has no issues. Disconnecting OpenVPN will cease the issues.
 Has anyone else had this issue?
 edit:: downgrading to OpenVPN 2.5.6 seems to have fixed the issue for now.
    submitted by    /u/GeekyGamer01  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RT Patches Updated For Linux 5.19-rc1 - Real-Time Inches Closer To The Finish Line]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-rc1-RT</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-rc1-RT"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T18:15:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The real-time (RT) patch series still hasn't been mainlined but the patch delta is slowly winding down with each new kernel version. Out today is the re-based RT patch series for the recently minted Linux 5.19-rc1 with some of the prior real-time patches having been upstreamed this merge window and other patches re-based to work with the newest kernel code...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is a 240Hz Monitor Worth It?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=797574</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/797574/is-a-240hz-monitor-worth-it/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When shopping for monitors, you’ll see some with high refresh rates—like 120hz, 240Hz, or even higher. So are they even worth the premium price tag usually attached to these monitors? Let’s look at the benefits, limits, and potential drawbacks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Nguyen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 22H2 closer to release, lands in the Release channel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-22h2-closer-to-release-lands-in-the-release-channel/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-22h2-closer-to-release-lands-in-the-release-channel/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T17:59:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has moved Windows 11, version 22H2, to the Windows Insider Release channel, indicating that it is in its final round of testing before it's likely released this fall. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The bat package is out of date and incompatible with the git-delta package]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v72gk0/the_bat_package_is_out_of_date_and_incompatible/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v72gk0/the_bat_package_is_out_of_date_and_incompatible/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T17:39:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It has been for about a month. It's flagged as outdated, but there's no way to track progress on updating it. The issue is delta uses the syntax highlight cache created by bat. bat introduced a breaking change to this cache in v0.21. delta was updated to work with this cache update in v0.13, but it's not backwards compatible with the old cache format. the git-delta package was update to v0.13, but bat is stuck on v0.20. 
 What's the process for getting a community package updated save marking it as outdated? I thought opening a bug would be the correct course of action, but the bug list explicitly says not to do that for outdated packages. I'm happy to update the package myself if the maintainer is busy, I just need to know where to start.
    submitted by    /u/giggly_kisses  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Outlook Keyboard Shortcuts]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=485208</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15355461/outlook-keyboard-shortcuts"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T17:25:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Outlook is one of the most widely used email clients on the market. Many companies use it because of all of the tools and signature customizations it includes, while some people use it for their personal email because you can combine up to 20 email addresses into a single Outlook account and access them all simultaneously. What’s more, Outlook includes many other productivity tools, like a calendar, task manager, and note-taking.
    
While there are definitely benefits to using Outlook, it sometimes takes forever to navigate through the endless menu options to perform simple functions. Luckily, there are keyboard shortcuts to perform nearly every function within Outlook if you learn them. Of course, you don’t have to master them all right away – you can just take advantage of this list of Microsoft Outlook keyboard shortcuts.
   
   
  
Download this Cheatsheet
 Enter your email below to receive this PDF cheatsheet in your Inbox.
    Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Megan Glosson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Google and Sonos Catfight Broke Smart Homes for Pixel Phones]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120282/a-google-and-sonos-catfight-broke-smart-homes-for-pixel-phones/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120282/a-google-and-sonos-catfight-broke-smart-homes-for-pixel-phones/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T17:21:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s been half a year since Sonos won a patent infringement suit against Google, yet the companies are still bickering. In a community blog post, Google says that some Pixel phones are unable to set up new or recently-disconnected smart home devices because of “an interruption caused by Sonos.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PSA: You Might Be Eligible for a Free Copy of Minecraft]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809784</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809784/psa-you-might-be-eligible-for-a-free-copy-of-minecraft/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T17:20:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As of June 7, 2022, Microsoft has combined Minecraft: Java Edition and Bedrock Edition for PC into a single purchase—and if you already own either one, you’re eligible for a free copy of the other.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Fitzpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to See Which Apps Are Using Cellular Data on iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=808021</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/808021/how-to-see-which-apps-are-using-cellular-data-on-iphone/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T17:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If your iPhone’s service bill is high due to cellular data usage, it’s easy to find the culprit in Settings by examining which apps are using the most cellular data. Here’s how to do it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New ‘DogWalk’ Windows zero-day bug gets free unofficial patches]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-dogwalk-windows-zero-day-bug-gets-free-unofficial-patches/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-dogwalk-windows-zero-day-bug-gets-free-unofficial-patches/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T16:59:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Free unofficial patches for a new Windows zero-day vulnerability in the Microsoft Support Diagnostic Tool (MSDT) have been released today through the 0patch platform.  [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[pacman says db locked even tough i have no pacman/yay instances running]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v71cmm/pacman_says_db_locked_even_tough_i_have_no/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v71cmm/pacman_says_db_locked_even_tough_i_have_no/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T16:58:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Σ ~ ❯❯❯ yay -Syu -> /var/lib/pacman/db.lck is present. -> There may be another Pacman instance running. Waiting... 
 Yesterday i was doing a yay -Syu but my pc powered down out of nowhere. For this i have no explanation why other than ill have to replace it as soon a i can.
 I then just ran doas pacman -Syu and same result, idk why this happends. Please help :)
    submitted by    /u/MattioC  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Cheapest Apple Watch Won't Get watchOS 9, and That's a Good Thing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120287/the-cheapest-apple-watch-wont-get-watchos-9-and-thats-a-good-thing/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120287/the-cheapest-apple-watch-wont-get-watchos-9-and-thats-a-good-thing/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T16:44:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week at Apple’s annual WWDC event, the company announced watchOS 9 with several changes and new features. And while Apple didn’t mention the Watch Series 3 specifically, its cheapest watch will not support the next update, meaning it’s reaching the end of its life.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here is a list of devices that support macOS Ventura, and those that won't get the update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179021</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/07/here-is-a-list-of-devices-that-support-macos-ventura-and-those-that-wont-get-the-update/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T16:38:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[macOS Ventura was made official by Apple at WWDC 2022, and there are some interesting new features in the operating system. The company also launched a couple of shiny new MacBooks powered […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Here is a list of devices that support macOS Ventura, and those that won't get the update appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Online gun shops in the US hacked to steal credit cards]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/online-gun-shops-in-the-us-hacked-to-steal-credit-cards/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/online-gun-shops-in-the-us-hacked-to-steal-credit-cards/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T16:27:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rainier Arms and Numrich Gun Parts, two American gun shops that operate e-commerce sites on rainierarms.com and gunpartscorp.com, have disclosed data breach incidents resulting from card skimmer infections on their sites. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PC si spegne da solo: perché e come risolvere]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=PC-si-spegne-da-solo-perche-e-come-risolvere_24611</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=PC-si-spegne-da-solo-perche-e-come-risolvere_24611"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T16:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I motivi per cui un PC si spegne da solo possono essere i più diversi. Di solito, però, la causa può essere hardware, software o esterna (ad esempio uno sbalzo di tensione o un blackout elettrico, più o meno breve).Cosa verificare se si verifica uno spegnimento improvviso del PC? Innanzi tutto è opportuno controllare, con gli strumenti software forniti dal produttore della scheda madre, e con il Visualizzatore eventi di Windows lo stato delle cose.
Spegnimento improvviso del PC o schermata blu
 Quando si presenta un errore critico Windows genera una schermata blu e provvede a riavviare oppure a spegnere il sistema in uso. Per questo motivo spesso non ci si accorge nemmeno della schermata blu che non appare stabilmente a video.Per ovviare a questo problema e avere il tempo materiale, in caso di comparsa di una schermata blu, di leggere e annotare il messaggio d'errore restituito, basta premere Windows+R, digitare sysdm.cpl ,3, cliccare su Impostazioni nel riquadro Avvio e ripristino quindi disattivare la casella Riavvia automaticamente.

In un altro articolo abbiamo visto cosa può provocare una schermata blu o BSOD (Blue-screen-of-Death) e come risalire all'errore restituito da Windows.Nell'articolo abbiamo presentato l'utilità BlueScreenView che estrae dal registro degli eventi di Windows tutti quelli riferibili alla comparsa di una schermata blu.In alternativa si può premere Windows+X quindi scegliere Windows PowerShell (amministratore) in Windows 10 o Terminale Windows (Admin) in Windows 11 quindi impartire il seguente comando:$ErrorActionPreference='SilentlyContinue'; Get-WinEvent -FilterHashtable @{logname='Application';id=1001}Si otterrà la lista delle schermate blu eventualmente comparse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polestar Teases Its First Electric SUV]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120279/polestar-teases-its-first-electric-suv/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120279/polestar-teases-its-first-electric-suv/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T16:16:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Polestar, the premium electric car maker jointly owned by Volvo, has announced it’s ready to manufacture EVs in the United States, starting with the all-new Polestar 3. It will be the first vehicle Polestar builds in the U.S. and the brand’s first “performance SUV.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Orientare la parabola Sky e trovare satelliti tivùsat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2017/10/orientare-la-parabola-sky-e-trovare.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2017/10/orientare-la-parabola-sky-e-trovare.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T16:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[La maggior parte dei problemi di ricezione di Sky vengono causati da piccoli spostamenti della parabola: basta anche un millimetro per far perdere il segnale con il satellite e rendere impossibile la visione dei canali della famosa piattaforma. I problemi sono identici su tivùsat, la piattaforma gratuita destinata al mercato italiano; anche in questo caso basta un millimetro di spostamento della...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DisplayPort vs. HDMI: Which Is Better?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=799781</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/799781/displayport-vs-hdmi-which-is-better/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T16:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you have a monitor or display that’s capable of both DisplayPort and HDMI, which should you choose? Since these ports have different capabilities and purposes, it’s important to understand when to use DisplayPort and when to use HDMI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Georgie Peru</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use the free PowerToys FancyZones in Windows and why you should]]></title>
        <id>4965735e-f466-4ec8-bb55-5112fd0c22ec</id>
        <link href="https://www.zdnet.com/article/how-to-use-the-free-powertoys-fancyzones-in-windows-and-why-you-should/#ftag=RSSbaffb68"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T15:52:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You should really be using FancyZones to supercharge your productivity on your desktop. Here's how to get started.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest topics for ZDNet in Windows</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How come that nvidia-utils doesn't get removed as a nvidia dependency?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v6z4sj/how_come_that_nvidiautils_doesnt_get_removed_as_a/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v6z4sj/how_come_that_nvidiautils_doesnt_get_removed_as_a/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T15:40:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why does pacman-S nvidia pulls nvidia-utils, but pacman -Rs nvidia doesn't remove it?
    submitted by    /u/Zacki_404  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybertruck Sighting Shows off a New Interior and Windshield Wiper]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120271/cybertruck-sighting-shows-off-a-new-interior-and-windshield-wiper/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120271/cybertruck-sighting-shows-off-a-new-interior-and-windshield-wiper/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T15:33:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Love it or hate it, people can’t get enough of Tesla’s upcoming Cybertruck. This week, we received a look at what could be one of the latest Cybertruck prototype designs sporting several “upgrades” to the interior and windshield wiper system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ford Ships Its First F-150 Lightning EVs with a Tesla-Saving Accessory]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120264/ford-ships-its-first-f-150-lightning-evs-with-a-tesla-saving-accessory/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120264/ford-ships-its-first-f-150-lightning-evs-with-a-tesla-saving-accessory/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T15:32:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ford began delivering F-150 Lightning trucks near the end of May, and the first customers are in for a small surprise. As reported by a user on the Lightning Owners forum, F-150 Lightnings come with a free Tesla charging adapter, likely to highlight the truck’s bi-directional charging capabilities (something that Tesla lacks).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Change the Keyboard Layout in Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=post-ideas&amp;p=292364</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/11127830/change-keyboard-layout-linux"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you spend any real length of time working on a computer, you learn that your preferences matter. Having your computer set up exactly as you like can make the difference between getting work done smoothly and dragging through something that’d otherwise be simple. Your keyboard and its layout are a major factor here, whether you’re writing, coding, or just relying on hotkeys.
    
Even though they all have their own ways of handling it, every Linux desktop environment makes it simple to customize your keyboard layout for your language, region, and personal preference.
   

Content

LXDE
GNOME/Budgie
KDE Plasma
XFCE
Cinnamon
MATE
Enlightenment
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:8 of the Best Linux Distros for Windows Users
    
LXDE
    
The Lightweight X11 Desktop Environment (LXDE) is a simple environment for modern Linux-based operating systems. Because it has... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramces Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Machine won’t boot without amdgpu.dpm=0]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v6yfct/machine_wont_boot_without_amdgpudpm0/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v6yfct/machine_wont_boot_without_amdgpudpm0/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T15:14:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey all, I recently got a new work station, and it has an and rx 640 (absolute powerhouse, I know). Everything works great except that I can only get a display if I disable dynamic power mode. Recently my pc has started to completely lock up when I leave the pc alone for more than 10 minutes, requiring a force restart. The only thing that makes sense to me is that these two options are linked and the gpu is causing issues. I have three monitors and when I try to wake the machine, one turns on but the other two remain off and the entire setup freezes. I have scoured the net for this one, setting amdgpu in the mkinitcpio hooks, swapping drivers moving my install to a brand new but identical machine etc. Has anyone else had any luck with overcoming this issue? Thanks.
    submitted by    /u/midnightchips  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weird mouse behavior]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v6ye8j/weird_mouse_behavior/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v6ye8j/weird_mouse_behavior/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T15:13:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, my mouse recently started acting super weird. So every around 2 minutes it just "disconnects". What I mean by that is that I can move it but can't click anything. Then I need to press a key that isn't set to an action in an app (e.g. press an sxhkd shortcut). Then it works again. I already disabled USB Autosuspend.
    submitted by    /u/Radsdteve  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Calculate CAGR in Microsoft Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=806670</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/806670/cagr-formula-excel/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T15:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To keep track of an investment such as a mutual fund, you likely want to calculate the CAGR (compound annual growth rate). You can do so in Microsoft Excel using the RRI function and it’s much easier than you might think.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migliori app PC per disegnare con la tavoletta grafica]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/06/migliori-app-pc-per-disegnare-con-la.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/06/migliori-app-pc-per-disegnare-con-la.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T14:58:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[La tavoletta grafica è uno strumento indispensabile per chi ama disegnare o dipinge per mestiere utilizzando il PC. Con essa possiamo realizzare le bozze dei disegni che andremo a realizzare i seguito ma anche disegnare fumetti, manga o quant'altro direttamente sullo schermo, visto che offrono una resa al tatto molto simile alla penna e alla matita, con un livello di precisione paragonabile al...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shields Health Care Group data breach affects 2 million patients]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/shields-health-care-group-data-breach-affects-2-million-patients/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/shields-health-care-group-data-breach-affects-2-million-patients/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T14:53:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shields Health Care Group (Shields) suffered a data breach that exposed the data of approximately 2,000,000 people in the United States after hackers breached their network and stole data. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your iPhone Soon Won’t Have to Reboot for Security Updates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809692</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809692/your-iphone-soon-wont-have-to-reboot-for-security-updates/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T14:47:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple usually delivers critical security fixes as minor updates for macOS, iOS, iPadOS, and so on, which means a full reboot and a (potentially) long install process. That might change soon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wyze Releases a Third Smart Scale With Small Differences]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120253/wyze-releases-a-third-smart-scale-with-small-differences/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120253/wyze-releases-a-third-smart-scale-with-small-differences/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T14:30:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m noticing a bit of a trend. Last year, Wyze launched the Scale S, a slightly improved (yet slightly worse) version of the original Wyze Scale. And Wyze is now selling the Scale X, another small upgrade with a notable drawback—the new price.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iOttie Velox Wireless Charging Duo Stand Review: Sleek but Slow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119482/iottie-velox-wireless-charging-duo-stand-review-sleek-but-slow/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119482/iottie-velox-wireless-charging-duo-stand-review-sleek-but-slow/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T14:24:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The iOttie Velox Magnetic Wireless Charging Duo Stand is an elegant way to efficiently charge your MagSafe-compatible iPhone and Qi-enabled accessories. But if magnets don’t attract your attention, steer clear and save your money.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chazz Mair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Netflix isn't the Only One Bummed About Password Sharing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/why-netflix-isnt-the-only-one-bummed-about-password-sharing/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/why-netflix-isnt-the-only-one-bummed-about-password-sharing/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Carnegie Mellen found that as much as 28% of end-users willingly share passwords with others, and a Specops study found that of those who share passwords 21% of people don't know who else their password has been shared with. That's a lot of sharing going on. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sponsored by Specops</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best External Solid State Drives of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=764982</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/764982/best-external-solid-state-drive/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[External solid-state drives can provide for the speeds that modern games and software need to run properly and without lag. Couple that with their decreasing cost, and the best SSDs have become a great alternative to external HDDs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Albert Bassili</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New in iOS 16 for iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809638</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809638/whats-new-in-ios-16-for-iphone/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T13:30:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple announced iOS 16 for the iPhone at WWDC 2022. As usual, this update is free and the release is expected in late September (2022). The update is packed with tweaks that will hopefully change the way you use your iPhone for the better.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Android June 2022 updates bring fix for critical RCE vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/android-june-2022-updates-bring-fix-for-critical-rce-vulnerability/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/android-june-2022-updates-bring-fix-for-critical-rce-vulnerability/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T13:14:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has released the June 2022 security updates for Android devices running OS versions 10, 11, and 12, fixing 41 vulnerabilities, five rated critical. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Change Screenshot Folder Location in Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/?p=60028</id>
        <link href="https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/change-screenshot-folder-location-windows-11/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T13:01:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A screenshot is the quickest way to capture and share your screen. There are various ways to take a screenshot in Windows 11, but the two most popular are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hongkiat.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Won’t My Phone Charge? 5 Fixes to Try]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=806507</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/806507/why-wont-my-phone-charge/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T13:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is your iPhone or Android smartphone not charging when you plug it in? Worried it might be the end for your beloved gadget? Run through our checklist of troubleshooting tips to get to the bottom of the issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Much Weight Can an Electric Truck Tow?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119943/how-much-weight-can-an-electric-truck-tow/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119943/how-much-weight-can-an-electric-truck-tow/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T13:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Electric trucks are fast and have insane amounts of torque, which means they have some excellent tow ratings. If you’re interested in any of the exciting electric trucks available or coming soon and plan on doing “truck stuff,” you’ll want to know how much an electric truck can tow and how far.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Enterprise Linux 9.0 Performing Well, Great Benefit To Newer Intel Xeon & AMD EPYC Servers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31189</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31189"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last month RHEL 9.0 reached GA as the newest major update to Red Hat Enterprise Linux. Since then I've been trying out RHEL 9.0 on a few servers. To little surprise, especially for latest-generation Intel Xeon Scalable and AMD EPYC servers, RHEL 9.0 is offering significant uplift compared to the existing RHEL8 series. Here are some Red Hat Enterprise Linux 9.0 benchmarks comparing the performance to RHEL 8.6.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unico caricabatterie USB-C per tutti i dispositivi mobili in Europa]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Unico-caricabatterie-USB-C-per-tutti-i-dispositivi-mobili-in-Europa_23547</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Unico-caricabatterie-USB-C-per-tutti-i-dispositivi-mobili-in-Europa_23547"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T12:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Il Parlamento Europeo ha confermato i piani in tema di caricabatterie unico USB-C per tutti i dispositivi mobili commercializzati e acquistati dagli utenti entro i confini dell'Unione. Le resistenze più vigorose sono state quelle di Apple che storicamente ha preferito utilizzare la sua porta Lightning: ma anche la Mela si sta adeguando alla scelta fatta da altri produttori con cui si guarda appunto al connettore USB-C (o USB Type-C).Obiettivo del legislatore è ridurre i rifiuti elettronici RAEE (11.000 tonnellate ne vengono prodotte ogni anno in Europa) facendo in modo che i caricabatterie siano basati sugli stessi standard e possano essere interoperabili.In un altro articolo ci siamo chiesti e abbiamo visto se i caricabatterie USB-C sono intercambiabili e se quindi possano essere utilizzati da un dispositivo all'altro.Secondo uno studio della Commissione un cittadino europeo possiede oggi almeno tre caricabatterie e ne usa due regolarmente.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Error while booting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v6tw7t/error_while_booting/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v6tw7t/error_while_booting/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T12:14:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, firstly I need to say that I would not create that post if I would find solution for this case of the problem on the internet.
 So I was updating my system with `sudo pacman -Syu` and terminate it with `crtl+c` because my root parition `/` was running out of space, after removing some old packages, `rm- rf /var/cache/*` and `sudo pacman -Rns $(Qtdg)` I run once again `sudo pacman -Syu` and then reboot.
 `/boot/vmlinuz-linix not found` - easy I thought.
  
I plug live usb with arch ios,
 then connect to network,
 mount my root partition to `/mnt` and efi partition to `/mnt/boot`
 `arch-chroot` into `/mnt` ,
 run `pacman -Syu`, (I checked and `vimlinuz-linux` was located in `/mnt/boot`)
 exit, `umount -R /mnt` and reboot
  
Error still remains so I do it all once again but this time I also generate new `mkinitcpio` and `grub-mkconfig`
 Any idea how to fix that problem? I would appreciate it, thanks.
 PS This is my first post as far as I know, if anything is incorrect or needs to be refactored let me know 
 EDIT I fix it by repeating all steps but this time I mount my root partition into /mnt/efi then chroot, check that /boot dir does not have vmlinuz-linux and two *.img files. 
 I exit the chroot enviroment umount /mnt/efi and mount /mnt/boot, copied that 3 files from there to /efi, and lastly regenerate mkinitcpio -P and grub-mkconfig to make sure that everything is fresh
    submitted by    /u/regalwk  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Laptop Fuel Cells Were the Next Big Thing: What Happened?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=797043</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/797043/what-happened-to-laptop-fuel-cells/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T12:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fuel cells were once touted as the ultimate high-tech solution to short laptop battery life, but nearly two decades later we still don’t have them and it seems we never will. What happened to this promising computer power source?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sydney Butler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUSE Linux Enterprise 15 SP4 Released - Switches To NVIDIA's Open Kernel Driver, Adds AMD SEV-ES]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=SUSE-Linux-Enterprise-15-SP4</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=SUSE-Linux-Enterprise-15-SP4"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In kicking off SUSECON, SUSE has announced the release of SUSE Linux Enterprise 15 Service Pack 4. Notable with SLE 15 SP4, SUSE is already switching to using NVIDIA's open-source GPU kernel-mode driver that NVIDIA open-sourced last month and is under active development and has a long road ahead before it's even feasible for upstreaming into the mainline kernel...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TV box Xiaomi Box 4S Max: basato su Android supporta la risoluzione 8K]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=TV-box-Xiaomi-Box-4S-Max-basato-su-Android-supporta-la-risoluzione-8K_24610</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=TV-box-Xiaomi-Box-4S-Max-basato-su-Android-supporta-la-risoluzione-8K_24610"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T11:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Un po’ a sorpresa Xiaomi ha presentato in 'terra d'origine' un versatile e potente TV box che può essere collegato al televisore mediante cavo HDMI e che ottimizza l'esperienza multimediale.Chiamato Xiaomi Box 4S Max, questo smart TV box consente di eseguire applicazioni, trasmettere musica e video, eseguire giochi e molto altro ancora. La novità più importante è il supporto per la risoluzione 8K.

Basato su un SoC Amlogic S905X3 (4 core Cortex-A55 a 1,91 GHz e GPU Mali-G31 MP2), Xiaomi Box 4S Max è equipaggiato con 4 GB di memoria RAM e 64 GB di memoria interna.Propone un'uscita HDMI 2.1 compatibile con la riproduzione di contenuti fino a 8K e 4K a 60 fps con HDR oltre a un jack audio da 3,5 mm e un ingresso USB-A 3.2.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Difetti degli iPhone che fanno preferire Android]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2016/05/motivi-per-preferire-android-iphone.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2016/05/motivi-per-preferire-android-iphone.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T11:41:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sempre in tema di rivalità in ambito mobile, molti utenti non amano affatto gli iPhone e acquistano solo Android, scegliendo se possibile modelli con un elevato rapporto qualità/prezzo (come per esempio i modelli visti nella nostra guida agli smartphone più simili all'iPhone).

 Per chi non è ancora convinto della presunta superiorità di Android rispetto ad iPhone, nella guida che segue vi...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Broadcom]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v6szk5/broadcom/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v6szk5/broadcom/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T11:31:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Guys is there anyway to get the bcm4322 AirPort Extreme card to work on arch I have not got it to work with anything I’ve tried Broadcom-Wl-dkms and Broadcom-wl what should I do
    submitted by    /u/Expensive_Pudding846  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saving screen configuration when hotplugging monitors?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v6stuj/saving_screen_configuration_when_hotplugging/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v6stuj/saving_screen_configuration_when_hotplugging/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T11:22:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So i am trying to get my rather difficult setup working but still having issues with arch. So i have three monitors attached to my computer: One internal laptop screen, one 4k screen and one additional HD side monitor. The side monitor is in portrait mode. However, i also want to be able to unplug the side monitor and hotplug a TV to it, so i can watch series in my bed from my computer. Unfortunately, i am not able to get automatic screen configuration working with this setup. What is the proper way to handle this? 
 What i tried is using the nvidia-settings to configure my initial setup, but when i hotplug the TV, it will also be in portrait mode, basically adapting the side monitors config. Using xrandr i can see that udev recognized my new screen correctly, but is not switching the resolution. I tried autorandr, but this also didn't really change when hotplugging. Back when i used PopOS or Windows, everything worked like a charm, even the sound output changed the way i wanted it to, without any manual configuration. But i just dont seem to get it working on arch. Pls help me. Should i even use the xorg.conf or only rely on autorandr? Should i make a udev rule? Thanks in advance!
    submitted by    /u/maxawake  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple presenta iOS 16, iPadOS 16, watchOS 9, macOS Ventura e Metal 3]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Apple-presenta-iOS-16-iPadOS-16-watchOS-9-macOS-Ventura-e-Metal-3_24609</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Apple-presenta-iOS-16-iPadOS-16-watchOS-9-macOS-Ventura-e-Metal-3_24609"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T11:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sul palco della WWDC 2022 Apple ha portato anche diversi nuovi prodotti software. Le nuove versioni di iOS, iPadOS e macOS, ad esempio, non rappresentano un grande cambiamento rispetto alle release che già oggi utilizziamo sebbene aggiungano alcune migliorie degne di nota per l'utilizzo di ogni giorno.Con iOS 16 viene finalmente introdotta la possibilità di personalizzare la schermata di blocco: il sistema operativo consente adesso di aggiungere immagini, cambiare i colori, i font, attivare l'utilizzo dei widget e passare dall'uno all'altro come se si agisse sul quadrante di uno smartwatch.

La release di iOS appena presentata raccoglie diverse modifiche per quanto riguarda l'app Portfolio, migliora il sistema di dettatura, il rilevamento di oggetti tramite la fotocamera e introduce il ritaglio rapido delle forme per usarle nelle varie applicazioni.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Much Does an Electric Car Battery Replacement Cost?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=805841</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/805841/how-much-does-an-electric-car-battery-replacement-cost/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T11:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern electric vehicles (EVs) will last quite a while on their stock battery pack, but eventually they’ll degrade and need to be replaced. The prospect of a replacement might make you hesitant about buying an EV, so what will a replacement actually run you, and how can you avoid needing one?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Bogna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Chrome not launching]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v6sgjd/google_chrome_not_launching/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v6sgjd/google_chrome_not_launching/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T11:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone
 So I've reinstalled Arch twice in the past weeks (I played around with the archinstall script and then installed my proper system) but in both installs, Google Chrome doesn't launch. Here's one of the errors I got when I tested by launching from the terminal.
 libva error vagetdrivernamebyindex() failed with unknown libva error driver_name = (null)
 This is on 2 different freshly installed systems and in both cases I've tried uninstalling Chrome, deleting all the folders in the home directories like local and cache but this always happens.
 Right now I'm trying out Fedora 36 and I'm writing these lines in Chrome. 
 Maybe there's a package I don't install in my Arch installation script or something but I have no idea what that would be. I've searched for this but no one seems to be having this issue but I also know Chrome isn't the most popular browser with Arch users so maybe that's why.
 Anyhow, does anyone know what I can do to get Chrome working again?
 And please, no answers like "get rid of Chrome" or "Use Firefox" or whatever else. I like Chrome and I know how Google works already and have accepted it ;)
 Thank you!
    submitted by    /u/lalondan  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How do I recover data from an old laptop if I've forgotten the password? [Ask ZDNet]]]></title>
        <id>66df38b2-429a-43fb-b297-f5207c9ee444</id>
        <link href="https://www.zdnet.com/article/how-do-i-recover-data-from-an-old-laptop-if-ive-forgotten-the-password-ask-zdnet/#ftag=RSSbaffb68"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T11:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Got a tech question? Ed Bott and ZDNet's squad of editors and experts probably have the answer. In today's edition: How to recover data from a PC if you've forgotten the password.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest topics for ZDNet in Windows</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WWDC 2022 Brings New iPhone Lock Screen and M2 Chip]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=495431</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15354660/wwdc-2022-iphone-lock-screen-m2-chip"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T10:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first day of WWDC is like Christmas morning for those deeply embedded in the Apple ecosystem. This year provided many changes those same Apple fans have been requesting for years, such as a new iPhone lock screen and multiple windows on iPads. It also provided a few things that were expected, such as the new M2 chip. In other words, there were no surprises but still some excitement.
   
Also read:Everything About Apple Silicon and the M1 Chip That You Need To Know
    
iOS 16/iPadOS 16
    
Proving that Apple is putting a bigger emphasis on mobile, iOS 16 kicked off WWDC 2022, and iPad OS 16 closed it.
    
The iPhone lock screen has been much the same since the launch of the first iPhone, but now it’s receiving radical changes. You’ll be able to move photos around, change the color and typeface, and... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TV arrotolabile OLED R: LG ne mostra il funzionamento al Fuorisalone 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=TV-arrotolabile-OLED-R-LG-ne-mostra-il-funzionamento-al-Fuorisalone-2022_24608</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=TV-arrotolabile-OLED-R-LG-ne-mostra-il-funzionamento-al-Fuorisalone-2022_24608"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T10:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In occasione del Fuorisalone di Milano, la più grande mostra di design al mondo, LG ha fatto 'toccare con mano' il funzionamento di uno dei suoi TV OLED di maggiore impatto.LG SIGNATURE è il marchio di prodotti ultra-premium che da anni è diventata la 'punta di diamante' dell'azienda sudcoreana, la concreta realizzazione di prodotti studiati per estremizzare i concetti di artigianalità, innovazione e autenticità.Così la gamma LG SIGNATURE vuole esaltare il connubio tra arte e tecnologia in una serie di prodotti intelligenti: l''effetto wow' è assicurato.

Il TV OLED R è un televisore con schermo capace di scomparire nella base quando non utilizzato. La 'magia' avviene grazie all'utilizzo di un pannello OLED 8K arrotolabile che permette all'occorrenza di nascondere l'intero TV da 65 pollici in parallelepipedo posto in orizzontale e alto una manciata di centimetri.Il pannello si srotola come un tappeto semplicemente toccando un tasto o usando un comando vocale: la modalità line view consente di far emergere dalla base solamente una piccola porzione dello schermo in modo da utilizzare le funzioni smart.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel Begins Adding Meteor Lake Support To Coreboot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-Meteor-Lake-Coreboot</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-Meteor-Lake-Coreboot"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T10:05:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intel Meteor Lake as the successor to Raptor Lake has begun seeing Coreboot enablement work by Intel engineers...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 Websites and Page Builders to Try]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/?p=43071</id>
        <link href="https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/website-and-page-building-tools/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T10:01:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Finding the "best" of anything is not always an easy task, and when you do, it's only natural to expect to pay a hefty price. This is also true with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Dagli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arm Looking To Make It Easier To Run Docker On AArch64 Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AArch64-defconfig-Docker-Linux</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AArch64-defconfig-Docker-Linux"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T09:54:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While Docker can already run on AArch64 Linux, the mainline Linux kernel's default configuration "defconfig" lacks a few features for allowing it to run out-of-the-box. An Arm engineer is proposing adjusting those defaults to make it more easily/straight-forward to run Docker on 64-bit Arm...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft: Edge's Sleeping Tabs feature saves an average of 39.1 MB of RAM per tab]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179016</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/07/microsoft-edges-sleeping-tabs-feature-saves-an-average-of-39-1-mb-of-ram-per-tab/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T09:44:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Edge's Sleeping Tabs feature saves an average of 39.1 Megabytes of RAM for each tab that it puts to sleep according to Microsoft. Sleeping Tabs was introduced in late 2020 by […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Microsoft: Edge's Sleeping Tabs feature saves an average of 39.1 MB of RAM per tab appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SDL Adds A DirectX 12 Renderer Backend]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=SDL2-Adds-DX12-Backend</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=SDL2-Adds-DX12-Backend"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T09:02:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Somewhat surprisingly, the open-source SDL library that is widely used by games for cross-platform handling and abstracting of various software interfaces has added a Microsoft DirectX 12 renderer...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come ottimizzare SSD in Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Come-ottimizzare-SSD-in-Windows_17484</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Come-ottimizzare-SSD-in-Windows_17484"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T08:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sostituire il vecchio hard disk magnetomeccanico con una nuova 'fiammante' unità SSD è quanto di meglio si possa fare per ridare vita a un PC che comincia a sentire il peso degli anni. Acquistando oggi un nuovo sistema - sia desktop che notebook - bisognerebbe sempre assicurarsi che disponga di un'unità a stato solido come supporto di memorizzazione principale.L'unità SSD deve accogliere almeno il sistema operativo e le applicazioni; se si avesse l'esigenza di gestire grandi quantitativi di dati su PC desktop si può abbinare un capiente hard disk come unità di memorizzazione secondaria.In un altro articolo abbiamo visto le principali caratteristiche e differenze tra hard disk e SSD.
Ottimizzare un SSD in Windows: cosa fare e cosa non fare
 Sul Web si trovano centinaia di guide molto simili che spiegano come ottimizzare gli SSD prodigandosi in consigli che porterebbero ad accrescere le prestazioni e la durata delle unità a stato solido con i sistemi Windows.Diciamo subito che molti di quei consigli sono, secondo noi, inutili e talvolta anche controproducenti.I moderni SSD sono tutt'altro che fragili: come rammentato in altre occasioni, ormai il numero di scritture - tallone d'Achille dei primi modelli di SSD - non è più un problema.I nemici degli SSD, soprattutto per ciò che riguarda l'integrità dei dati in essi memorizzati, sono piuttosto il tempo che passa e le temperature di lavoro.Parlando di durata degli SSD non è quindi certo il numero delle operazioni di scrittura a destare preoccupazione.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple announces macOS Ventura - Here's what's new in it]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178998</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/07/what-is-new-in-macos-ventura/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T08:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple unveiled the next version of macOS at WWDC 2022 today: meet macOS Ventura. What's new in macOS Ventura macOS 13 brings a slew of new features. Here's a brief description of […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Apple announces macOS Ventura - Here's what's new in it appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple presenta il nuovo chip M2 di derivazione ARM oltre ai rinnovati MacBook Pro 13 e MacBook Air]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Apple-presenta-il-nuovo-chip-M2-di-derivazione-ARM-oltre-ai-rinnovati-MacBook-Pro-13-e-MacBook-Air_24607</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Apple-presenta-il-nuovo-chip-M2-di-derivazione-ARM-oltre-ai-rinnovati-MacBook-Pro-13-e-MacBook-Air_24607"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T07:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In occasione dell'evento WWDC 2022 Apple ha annunciato i suoi nuovi SoC, ancora più potenti, basati su architettura ARM. Si tratta degli Apple M2, chip con cui il gigante di Cupertino introduce alcune modifiche degne di nota seppur senza radicali sconvolgimenti.L'aspetto da rimarcare è sicuramente il miglioramento delle prestazioni: i SoC M2 utilizzano il processo costruttivo a 5 nm di TSMC e dispongono di più cache pur mantenendo invariato il numero di core (quattro principali e quattro a maggiore efficienza).Gli Apple M2 utilizzano memoria RAM LPDDR5 a 6500 MHz con la possibilità di sfruttare fino a 100 GB/s di larghezza di banda con un sostanziale balzo in avanti rispetto alla memoria LPDDR4X-4267 del chip M1.

La GPU consta di 8-10 core, usa 1280 shader e trae massimo beneficio dalla larghezza di banda aggiuntiva.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ikey Doherty Returning To Work Full-Time On Serpent OS Linux Distribution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Ikey-Full-Time-Serpent-OS</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Ikey-Full-Time-Serpent-OS"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ikey Doherty started the Solus Linux distribution then disappeared and wrote an open letter on Phoronix about his absence, also was employed by Intel for a year to work on their Clear Linux distribution, had a brief stint starting a game/software development company, and then started the Serpent OS Linux distribution. He's still been working on Serpent OS but then was working full-time elsewhere but now has decided to return full-time to working on his latest Linux distribution...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel Switch Utility]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v6nxbg/kernel_switch_utility/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v6nxbg/kernel_switch_utility/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T05:58:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm coming from Manjaro, and one of the features I miss is the intuitive GUI for switching kernels. 
 Anyone aware of a utility I can install for Arch to do similar?
 Thanks
    submitted by    /u/Sindoreon  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FastForward: skip tracker and intermediary URLs automatically]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178994</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/07/fastforward-skip-tracker-and-intermediary-urls-automatically/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T04:36:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FastForward is a cross-platform browser extension that will skip link shorteners, trackers and intermediary URLs automatically when enabled. It works on sites such as bit.ly, t.co, goo.gl, show.co, or adf.ly, and thousands […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post FastForward: skip tracker and intermediary URLs automatically appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Nearby Sharing to Share Files on Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=483258</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15353540/use-nearby-sharing-windows"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nearby Sharing makes it easy to share files wirelessly from your Windows PC to other nearby Windows devices. You can send documents, photos, links, and other files without the need for cloud services, network file sharing, USB flash drives, or email attachments.
    
This nifty feature uses Wi-Fi, Bluetooth, and Ethernet to transfer files between devices. This guide will show you how to set up, use, and troubleshoot Nearby Sharing.
   

Content

Nearby Sharing Prerequisites
How to Turn on Nearby Sharing
How to Share Files with Nearby Sharing
How to Share Links Using Nearby Sharing 
How to Change Nearby Sharing Download Folder
How to Add Nearby Sharing to Quick Settings for Faster File Sharing
How To Troubleshoot Nearby Sharing
1. Confirm Bluetooth Driver is Installed Correctly
2. Enable Bluetooth Adapter
3. Check Bluetooth Compatibility
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Share... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Kanyoro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for media server options]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v6gr29/looking_for_media_server_options/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v6gr29/looking_for_media_server_options/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T23:28:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wondering if there are any options for media server that also allow it to double as a smart tv interface? 
 I have a projector that I wanna plug mine into and play directly from but I can't find anything but Kodi and experience with that on RPI has soured it for me. Bonus would be if it allows me to use things like netflix of prime video too. 
 Any suggestions welcome, thanks in advance
    submitted by    /u/NGumi  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[macOS 13 Adding Ability To Use Rosetta In ARM Linux VMs For Speedy x86_64 Linux Binaries]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=macOS-13-Rosetta-Linux-Binaries</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=macOS-13-Rosetta-Linux-Binaries"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T22:44:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In addition to announcing the M2 SoC, Apple used its WWDC keynote to also announce macOS 13 "Ventura". One of the interesting technical changes with macOS 13 is the ability to use Apple's Rosetta software for speedy execution of Linux x86_64 binaries running on ARM Linux VMs from Apple Silicon...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Any Arch/btrfs/snapper fans? Just ported httm (my CLI Time Machine-type thing)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v6fp52/any_archbtrfssnapper_fans_just_ported_httm_my_cli/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v6fp52/any_archbtrfssnapper_fans_just_ported_httm_my_cli/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T22:37:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The dream of a CLI Time Machine is still alive with httm
 httm prints the size, date and corresponding locations of available unique versions (deduplicated by modify time and size) of files residing on snapshots, but can also be used interactively to select and restore such files. httm might change the way you use snapshots (because ZFS/btrfs aren't designed for finding for unique file versions) or the Time Machine concept (because httm is very fast!).
 Recently, I ported httm to use btrfs with snapper layouts. A PKGBUILD with btrfs support is available for Arch, and I'm interested to know your thoughts!
    submitted by    /u/small_kimono  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come impostare la modalità Internet Explorer in Microsoft Edge]]></title>
        <id>3590|20220607000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/browser-455/come-impostare-modalita-internet-explorer-microsoft-edge-3590"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Il 15 Giugno 2022 segna una data, in un certo senso, storica, perché Microsoft ritirerà Internet Explorer, il suo browser nato nel 1995. Per quanto a livello di utenti casalinghi sia ormai stato ampiamente superato (e dimenticato) da molto tempo, una piccola fetta di realtà aziendali continuano ad usarlo perché non hanno mai aggiornato le app Web che richiedono appunto tale browser. Vediamo quindi come abilitare Microsoft Edge per simulare, quando necessario, Internet Explorer e poter utilizzare ancora questi siti.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A privacy issue...are the app stores and repositories collecting and sending data to thrid party....]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v6e73t/a_privacy_issueare_the_app_stores_and/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v6e73t/a_privacy_issueare_the_app_stores_and/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T21:29:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey guys....I recently started using linux...and when I went through some blogs and articles I came across this privacy stuff in linux app stores...it seems that there are many third party dependencies that collect so much data from the user without their acknowledgement...should I use app stores to use...or stick with just repositories...or both are same...like this issue in gnome software store a dependency fwupd sends user id,user system name,locale,distro,device ID and so many things to the developer....although the developer has claimed the opposite...it still remains an issue...also in another blog article there was a dependency in arch Linux stating about data being sent to a company when we visit the gnome software store in arch Linux and even if we download from repositories...what should I do...should I stick with terminal and repositories or use software sotre...or just stick with appimages...I know this issue has been addressed in some way a few yaers back...but still I am worried about the privacy....even in arch Linux....
    submitted by    /u/anonymous_persona_  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Access an Android Phone With a Broken Screen]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=306240</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/12480357/access-android-with-broken-screen"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How many times have you dropped your phone, believing that the screen would be cracked when you picked it up? Luckily for us, most phone screens are relatively durable and don’t break easily. But when they do, you’re left scrambling, trying to figure out how to access your Android phone with a broken screen.
    
When your phone breaks and the screen is no longer working, not only can you not use your phone, but now all that information stored on your phone is inaccessible. The good news is it’s possible to recover all the information on your device with a little troubleshooting.
   

Content

Use OTG to Gain Access
USB Debugging
If Your Screen Won't Turn On
How to Prevent These Issues
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Fix the Obtaining IP Address Error on Android
    
Use... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Crystal Crowder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How are you supposed to downgrade nvidia drivers?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v6dyda/how_are_you_supposed_to_downgrade_nvidia_drivers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v6dyda/how_are_you_supposed_to_downgrade_nvidia_drivers/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T21:18:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have used this tool from the AUR called downgrade and I can’t downgrade the “nvidia” package. I don’t know how to easily downgrade it so if someone could leave a comment that would be nice.
 solution: sudo pacman -S linux
    submitted by    /u/VotedDragon_reddit  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QBot now pushes Black Basta ransomware in bot-powered attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/qbot-now-pushes-black-basta-ransomware-in-bot-powered-attacks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/qbot-now-pushes-black-basta-ransomware-in-bot-powered-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T21:01:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Black Basta ransomware gang has partnered with the QBot malware operation to gain spread laterally through hacked corporate environments. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Map a Network Drive on Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=755213</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/755213/how-to-map-a-network-drive-on-windows-11/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you frequently use a networked drive (or “share”) with Windows 11, you can map it to a drive letter in File Explorer to make it appear more like a local drive and quickly access it in the future. Here’s how to do it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple M1 vs. M2: What’s the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809540</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809540/apple-m2-vs-m1-whats-the-difference/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T20:58:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The second generation of Apple Silicon is here. The M2 SOC is Apple’s consumer upgrade to the 2020’s M1 in the Mac lineup and beyond. Here’s a look at how the two chips compare—and what it means for future Macs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Safari on Mac, iPhone, and iPad Will Allow Web Notifications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809573</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809573/safari-on-mac-iphone-and-ipad-will-allow-web-notifications/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T20:37:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple’s Safari web browser has lagged behind some features in recent years, especially with background services. After years of waiting, it seems like Safari will finally support web push notifications on all platforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What to Do If Your PC Can't Upgrade to Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118363/what-to-do-if-your-pc-cant-upgrade-to-windows-11/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118363/what-to-do-if-your-pc-cant-upgrade-to-windows-11/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T20:10:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft’s latest operating system, Windows 11, launched in October 2021, but many PCs lack the hardware required to upgrade. So what can you do if your computer isn’t ready to make the jump? Is upgrading even worth the hassle?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McQuilling</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Change the Page Color in Microsoft Word]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=766538</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/766538/how-to-change-the-page-color-in-microsoft-word/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By default, Microsoft Word uses white as the default page color for all documents. If you’d like to use a custom color for your page, you can change page colors in Word. We’ll show you how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iPad Multitasking Will Be Supercharged With iPadOS 16]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809543</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809543/ipad-multitasking-will-be-supercharged-with-ipados-16/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T19:56:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The iPad has always been in a strange place, with some of the apps commonly found on PCs, but still missing some common desktop features. Apple is attempting to bride that gap with the upcoming iPadOS 16 update.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mandiant: “No evidence” we were hacked by LockBit ransomware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/mandiant-no-evidence-we-were-hacked-by-lockbit-ransomware/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/mandiant-no-evidence-we-were-hacked-by-lockbit-ransomware/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T19:54:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[American cybersecurity firm Mandiant is investigating LockBit ransomware gang's claims that they hacked the company's network and stole data. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia drivers seem to break xorg]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v6c0nc/nvidia_drivers_seem_to_break_xorg/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v6c0nc/nvidia_drivers_seem_to_break_xorg/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T19:52:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have been attempting to install nvidia proprietary drivers on my system for the past couple of days but have run into some major problems. On startup xorg fails every time. From the log I received:
 xinit: giving up
 xinit: unable to connect to X server: Connection refused xinit: server error
 Kind of at a loss for what to do next. For a little more context I’m using lightdm as a display manager. 
 These are the packages I installed:
 nvidia-dkms nvidia-utils lib32-nvidia-utils nvidia-settings vulkan-icd-loader lib32-vulkan-icd-loader
    submitted by    /u/RandomUser6410  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple's Next-Gen CarPlay Is a First Glimpse at the "Apple Car"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120190/apples-next-gen-carplay-is-a-first-glimpse-at-the-apple-car/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120190/apples-next-gen-carplay-is-a-first-glimpse-at-the-apple-car/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T19:46:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we all know, the infotainment systems in cars aren’t all that great, and we don’t see it getting any better with the shift to electric vehicles. Apple wants to transition its popular CarPlay system into an entire vehicle interface as a potential solution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple's iOS 16 Update Is a Mixed Bag of Excitement and Boredom]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120153/apples-ios-16-update-is-a-mixed-bag-of-excitement-and-boredom/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120153/apples-ios-16-update-is-a-mixed-bag-of-excitement-and-boredom/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T19:38:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We finally caught a glimpse at iOS 16 during Apple’s WWDC livestream. And by “a glimpse,” I actually mean “a rapid-fire grocery list of new features with little context.” Yeah, Apple threw everything at the wall this year, and only some of it stuck. But the good stuff is really good.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save $100 on a Pixel 6 Pro, One of Our Favorite Phones]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809465</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809465/save-100-on-a-pixel-6-pro-one-of-our-favorite-phones/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T19:32:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s Pixel 6 Pro has been a hot item for Android enthusiasts — ranking as the fastest selling Pixel phone of all time — and you can get one for its lowest price ever. Drop what you’re doing and pick up a new Pixel 6 Pro for just $799 ($100 off) over at Amazon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zach Laidlaw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save $30 on Bose Sport Wireless Earbuds]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=495277</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15353229/bose-sport-wireless-earbuds"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Music aficionados have known for years that the name Bose is one of the best in the business for headphones and speakers. Take advantage of this deal and get $30 off a set of Bose Sport Wireless Earbuds. They’re rated IPX4 and great for running and working out as well as doing any other activity, even if it’s just relaxing.
    
You’ll feel like your favorite bands and singers are right there running along side you or doing down dogs. The earbuds will make you want to work out longer, which won’t be a problem, as they last up to five hours when you use the charging case. Add two more hours to that after a 15-minute quick charge.
   
 
   
Customize the fit of the Bose Sport Wireless Earbuds with the StayHear Max tips. You’ll get three sizes to be sure they fit well, and they won’t hurt your ears or fall out. They’re also IPX4-rated and wrapped in a material that will keep the moisture out.
    
Along with listening to... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Is Getting Serious About Smart Homes With iOS 16]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809499</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809499/apple-is-getting-serious-about-smart-homes-with-ios-16/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T19:05:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple’s HomeKit and the companion Home app have long felt like a neglected project. With the release of iOS 16, the Home app is getting a facelift and a new lease on life complete with a promise of Matter support.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Fitzpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Debuts Redesigned M2-Powered MacBook Air]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120147/apple-debuts-redesigned-m2-powered-macbook-air/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120147/apple-debuts-redesigned-m2-powered-macbook-air/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T19:04:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve been hearing rumors about a newly redesigned MacBook Air for a while now, and today at its annual WWDC developers event, Apple delivered precisely that. With a design reminiscent of the new 2021 MacBook Pro, the Air now has smaller bezels putting the screen front and center, and more power than ever before.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create and Customize a Drop-Down List in Google Docs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=803342</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/803342/create-a-drop-down-list-in-google-docs/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T19:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Drop-down lists are handy tools for entering data. They give you a choice of input, so there are no misspellings, errors, or unwanted entries. Google Docs offers both preset and custom drop-down lists to fit any type of document.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wifi not working on Arch Live USB]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v6ap7m/wifi_not_working_on_arch_live_usb/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v6ap7m/wifi_not_working_on_arch_live_usb/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T18:53:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I try to connect to wifi on an arch Live USB, using iwd (iwctl), everything seems fine and it looks like it connects to the network I specify. It asks for a password and it seems like it's connecting but it doesn't actually connect to anything. I.e. it has no internet and doesn't appear in my router's list of connected devices.
 Running journalctl -p 3 -b gives me this ouput. The first to thirteenth error are also seen when booting.
    submitted by    /u/Deathscyther1HD  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Weather Is Coming to iPad, Still No Calculator]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809522</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809522/apple-weather-is-coming-to-ipad-still-no-calculator/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T18:43:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple’s iPadOS 16 is getting a big, important new feature. It’s something many iPad users have been begging for for years now. Yes, it’s finally here: The Weather app is now on iPad. It only took 15 years!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[minecraft with prime-run cause exit code 6]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v6agod/minecraft_with_primerun_cause_exit_code_6/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v6agod/minecraft_with_primerun_cause_exit_code_6/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T18:43:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, I wanted to came back to use ArchLinux (cause too good memories) but I have a problem with prime-run and minecraft: when I start minecraft with prime run
 prime-run minecraft-launcher
 the launcher starts but after the game crashes and it reply with Exit Code 6. 
 for the prime-run script: pacman -S nvidia-prime
 my kernel version: 5.18.1-arch1-1
 nvidia video card and drivers: NVIDIA GeForce GTX 1660 Ti with Max-Q Design/ 515.48.07
 do you have any ideas?
    submitted by    /u/matO_oppreal  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[13-Inch MacBook Pro Will Soon Have Apple’s New M2 Chip]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809514</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809514/13-inch-macbook-pro-will-soon-have-apple%e2%80%99s-new-m2-chip/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T18:42:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple updated the 13-inch MacBook Pro with the first M1 chip back in 2020, and now a new model is on the way with an Apple M2 chip.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Announces Its New M2 Processor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Apple-M2</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Apple-M2"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T18:35:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple's WWDC keynote this year was used to announce the M2 processor alongside a slew of other announcements...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft bug banned Rewards accounts when redeeming points]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-bug-banned-rewards-accounts-when-redeeming-points/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-bug-banned-rewards-accounts-when-redeeming-points/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T18:25:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has fixed a bug where the Microsoft Rewards accounts of customers who redeemed points would get suspended without warning. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple’s watchOS 9 Will Track Heart Rate Zones & Running Form]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809495</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809495/apples-watchos-9-will-track-heart-rate-zones-running-form/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T18:25:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Apple Watch is more smartwatch than fitness tracker, but Apple continues to blur that line with watchOS 9. The Workout app is getting the ability to measure your running form, heart rate zones, and new workout types to track.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple’s New M2 MacBook Air Has MagSafe and a Better Webcam]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809500</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809500/apples-new-m2-macbook-air-has-magsafe-and-a-better-webcam/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T18:23:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple announced a new MacBook Air with its new M2 chip at WWDC 2022. The new MacBook Air is even lighter and faster and fixes some of the main complaints about Apple’s line of MacBooks. Here’s what’s new.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple M2 Is Faster and More Power-Efficient Than M1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809496</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809496/apple-m2-is-faster-and-more-power-efficient-than-m1/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T18:18:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple started shipping Mac computers with its M1 chip in 2020, marking the start of Apple’s migration away from Intel chips. Now the company has revealed the aptly-named sequel, the Apple M2.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dual Booting Arch-Linux and Ubuntu]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v69ocj/dual_booting_archlinux_and_ubuntu/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v69ocj/dual_booting_archlinux_and_ubuntu/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T18:07:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi,
 I am thinking of dual-booting my laptop with Arch-Linux which is currently running Ubuntu 20.04. I have installed Arch multiple times on a VM, and also on a usbstick. Now, I feel that I am ready to run it on actual hardware. So, I wanted to know if there was a guide that will guide me through the process of dual-booting Arch-Linux with Ubuntu. Also, if there were some caveats in doing this. I currently have a 512M efi partition, 927G root partition and a 4G swap partition.
 Thanks
    submitted by    /u/Clock_Suspicious  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unable to run integrated graphics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v69mid/unable_to_run_integrated_graphics/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v69mid/unable_to_run_integrated_graphics/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T18:04:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am using propriety nvidia drivers and prime on my laptop. I only use my GPU for some occasional CUDA programing.
 Since the battery life of my laptop is abysmal, I recently did powertop --auto-tune to tune the battery consumption of my laptop. However after running this, it seems like I am unable to switch to integrated graphics anymore. ``` $ glxinfo | grep "OpenGL renderer"
 OpenGL renderer string: NVIDIA GeForce RTX 3070 Laptop GPU/PCIe/SSE2
 $ prime-run glxinfo | grep "OpenGL renderer"
 OpenGL renderer string: NVIDIA GeForce RTX 3070 Laptop GPU/PCIe/SSE2
 $ glxinfo -B
 name of display: :0 display: :0 screen: 0 direct rendering: Yes Memory info (GL_NVX_gpu_memory_info): Dedicated video memory: 8192 MB Total available memory: 8192 MB Currently available dedicated video memory: 7972 MB …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Curve Text in Adobe Photoshop]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=806009</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/806009/how-to-curve-text-in-adobe-photoshop/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T18:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to make your straight text curved without much hassle? If so, Adobe Photoshop has the exact feature you need. You can use it to curve your text in your specified bend level, and we’ll show you how to make use of it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.11 Performance Benchmarks Are Looking Fantastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31183</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31183"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last month Python 3.11 Beta 1 was released as their first preview of this major update to the Python programming language. Besides new language features and other improvements, Python 3.11 performance is looking fantastic with very nice performance uplift over prior Python 3.x releases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open-Source AMDVLK Vulkan Driver Preparing Mesh Shader Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMDVLK-Mesh-Shaders-WIP</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMDVLK-Mesh-Shaders-WIP"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T17:58:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In addition to Mesa's Radeon "RADV" Vulkan driver prepared for mesh shading with an upcoming Vulkan mesh shader extension besides NVIDIA's NV_mesh_shader, it looks like AMD will be punctually supporting the cross-vendor mesh shader extension too...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Messages in iOS 16 Gets Message Editing, Deletion Features]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809473</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809473/messages-in-ios-16-gets-message-editing-deletion-features/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T17:40:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Texting other iPhone users with iMessage has always felt like an instant messaging app. iOS 16 is adding a number of features to the Messages app that makes that even more apparent. Get ready to edit your mistakes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Maps Will Soon Be Better Than Ever]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809480</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809480/apple-maps-will-soon-be-better-than-ever/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T17:39:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Maps started off as a poor substitute for Google Maps, but it has become increasingly better over time. Apple just announced a few major upgrades at WWDC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DocHipo Review: Create Beautiful Documents]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=494463</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15353109/dochipo-review"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T17:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While there are many design apps for every operating system, DocHipo is a web app that specializes in designing documents to showcase your business or events in your personal life. This review takes a look at DocHipo to see if it will be suitable for your design needs.
    
This is a sponsored article and was made possible by DocHipo. The actual contents and opinions are the sole views of the author who maintains editorial independence, even when a post is sponsored.
    
Starting with DocHipo
    
I’ll preface this review by stating that I spent 20 years as a graphic designer, so I can be a little picky. Because DocHipo allows for collaboration, I asked Phil South to collaborate with me, as he, too, spent some of his career in graphic design.
    
To get started, you only need to visit the DocHipo website and sign up for an account.
    

    
You can add your company and multiple users. You can also add multiple companies. I create graphics... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gog Games Summer Sale 2022 with free Sanitarium game and discounts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178986</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/06/gog-games-summer-sale-2022-with-free-sanitarium-game-and-discounts/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T17:19:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Gog Summer Sale 2022 runs from June 6th to June 27th. Gamers from all over the world may buy most of the games that are available on Gog at a discount […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Gog Games Summer Sale 2022 with free Sanitarium game and discounts appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Will Revamp the iPhone Lock Screen for iOS 16]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809472</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809472/apple-revamps-the-iphone-lock-screen-for-ios-16/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T17:19:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple was rumored to be working on a lock screen revamp for iOS 16 on the iPhone, and now that has just been confirmed at WWDC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Laptop slowed down]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v68ll6/laptop_slowed_down/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v68ll6/laptop_slowed_down/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T17:19:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Opening Firefox, Nautilus, Network Manager settings and some others takes 30 seconds or more. This only started last week. Before it was almost instant. Looking for a solution I came across this on the arch wiki - https://wiki.archlinux.org/title/Network_configuration#Local_network_hostname_resolution and changed my hosts file. 
 127.0.0.1 localhost ::1 localhost 127.0.1.1 myhostname
 Could this be the problem?
    submitted by    /u/CyberPolygon  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Stop an iPhone App From Using Cellular Data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=807952</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/807952/how-stop-an-iphone-app-from-using-cellular-data/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T17:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve been using up a lot of cellular data on your iPhone recently, one particular app (such as one that streams video) might be using more than others. Here’s how you can prevent an app from using cellular data at all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[System freezes while playing dota 2. Fresh Arch Kde on laptop]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v684e3/system_freezes_while_playing_dota_2_fresh_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v684e3/system_freezes_while_playing_dota_2_fresh_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T16:58:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey guys! I am experiencing weird system freezes while playing dota. I can hear my friends on discord and move mouse, but cannot open terminal, alt-tab and etc. The only solution is hard shutdown. Have not experienced similar issues in other games. I am running dota natively, via latest zen-kernel and Nvidia proprietary drivers. Not really sure how to collect logs, as I have to reboot every time this happens. So far I have tried: • Gamemode • Both vulkan and openGL • borderless and full-screen modes
    submitted by    /u/mmj0299  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ransomware gangs now give victims time to save their reputation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ransomware-gangs-now-give-victims-time-to-save-their-reputation/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ransomware-gangs-now-give-victims-time-to-save-their-reputation/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T16:56:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat analysts have observed an unusual trend in ransomware group tactics, reporting that initial phases of victim extortion are becoming less open to the public as the actors tend to use hidden or anonymous entries. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux 5.20 + Mesa 22.2 To Allow Conformant Mali G57 OpenGL ES 3.1 Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Mali-G57-Conformant-GLES-3.1</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Mali-G57-Conformant-GLES-3.1"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T16:52:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Panfrost Gallium3D patches landing today into Mesa 22.2 and Panfrost DRM kernel driver support slated to land for the Linux 5.20 cycle later this summer, the Mali G57 GPU has conformant OpenGL ES 3.1 support on this open-source driver and the first Mali GPU of the Valhall generation to have this achievement following the Panfrost driver's successes for the older Bifrost and Midgard architectures...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ford and BMW Will Test Next-Gen EV Batteries Later This Year]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120148/ford-and-bmw-will-test-next-gen-ev-batteries-later-this-year/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120148/ford-and-bmw-will-test-next-gen-ev-batteries-later-this-year/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T16:51:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lithium-ion batteries are much more powerful and efficient than they were just five years ago. And while there’s still plenty of room for improvement, lithium-ion batteries have some physical limitations that are difficult to overcome. That’s why Ford and BMW will test advanced solid-state EV batteries later this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come passare da una finestra all'altra con ALT+TAB e le altre scorciatoie]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Come-passare-da-una-finestra-all-altra-con-ALT+TAB-e-le-altre-scorciatoie_19667</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Come-passare-da-una-finestra-all-altra-con-ALT+TAB-e-le-altre-scorciatoie_19667"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T16:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[La combinazione di tasti ALT+TAB è stata introdotta da Microsoft ai tempi di Windows 3.1 ed è rimasta invariata nel corso di decenni.Premendo ALT+TAB si ottiene la lista delle applicazioni aperte in Windows con un'anteprima del contenuto di ciascuna finestra (almeno nelle versioni più recenti del sistema operativo).Fino all''epoca Windows XP', con la combinazione di tasti ALT+TAB non veniva mostrata l'anteprima delle finestre aperte (non compariva la 'miniatura' del contenuto di ciascuna applicazione): il sistema operativo si limitava a mostrare l'icona del programma aperto e il titolo di ciascuna finestra.Indipendentemente dalla versione di Windows in uso tenendo sempre premuto ALT quindi premendo più volte il tasto TAB si può selezionare una finestra aperta o quelle successive. Rilasciando entrambi i tasti, Windows passerà automaticamente alla visualizzazione della finestra corrispondente alla selezione.Per selezionare le miniature delle app in senso inverso basta premere anche il tasto MAIUSC (MAIUSC+ALT+TAB).Ma non è necessario complicarsi la vita: dopo aver premuto ALT+TAB basta premere le frecce direzionali sulla tastiera (destra/sinistra, su/giù) per spostarsi all'interno della schermata e scegliere la finestra desiderata.

Per aprire la schermata che in Windows 10 e Windows 11 permette di passare da una finestra all'altra senza tenere premuto alcun tasto, si può premere CTRL+ALT+TAB (basta insomma aggiungere la pressione del tasto CTRL): in questo modo le miniature resteranno a video anche rilasciando tutti tre i tasti.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Siti per creare video con foto, musica ed effetti di transizione]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2009/05/presentazione-video-con-foto-e-immagini.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2009/05/presentazione-video-con-foto-e-immagini.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T16:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Su PC sono possiamo usare numerosi programmi per creare video partendo da foto e immagini, a cui possiamo aggiungere musica, immagini di copertina, menu di avvio ed effetti di transizione; molti di questi programmi sono forniti gratuitamente e non hanno nulla da invidiare alle soluzioni a pagamento più famose.

 Il video poi può essere salvato su un DVD e può essere visto come fosse un filmino...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google says Chrome is 20% faster than before on macOS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178980</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/06/google-says-chrome-is-20-faster-than-before-on-macos/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T16:28:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has posted a cryptic message on Twitter that says that Chrome is 20% faster than before on macOS. In March 2022, the Mountain View company did something similar, when it published […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Google says Chrome is 20% faster than before on macOS appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[People Won’t Stop Selling Unreleased Google Pixel Phones]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809426</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809426/people-wont-stop-selling-unreleased-google-pixel-phones/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T16:25:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google showed off the Pixel 6a, Pixel 7, and Pixel 7 Pro for the first time last month at Google I/O. Even though the phones are still months away, people are already selling them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Encrypt disk and hibernation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v6768i/encrypt_disk_and_hibernation/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v6768i/encrypt_disk_and_hibernation/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T16:15:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello. Sorry I speak a little english.
 I install arch via archinstall script. I select crypt my disk and use swap. Also I use nvidia open deivers.
 When I try to wake up my pc, I get a black screen. I think this problem is due to encrypt disk. I have read that I need to use a swap file. But I think something more is needed. Tell me, what else should I know? Thanks
    submitted by    /u/nonamedamage  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows zero-day exploited in US local govt phishing attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/windows-zero-day-exploited-in-us-local-govt-phishing-attacks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/windows-zero-day-exploited-in-us-local-govt-phishing-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T16:09:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[European governments and US local governments were the targets of a phishing campaign using malicious Rich Text Format (RTF) documents designed to exploit a critical Windows zero-day vulnerability known as Follina. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maximum ram usage with no apparent reason]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v66xfb/maximum_ram_usage_with_no_apparent_reason/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v66xfb/maximum_ram_usage_with_no_apparent_reason/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T16:04:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every few days, i notice my computer is being slow, and before i know it, completely unusable. I (barely) open bashtop/htop to see whats going on and i see that (example) 59GB/62.8GB of my memory is being used and i can't see any programs that are using that much memory. Here's a screenshot that i hardly managed to capture
 The programs that i was running before the crash happened
  
Minecraft Fabric 1.18.2 Java edition with Sodium installed, through MultiMC
 ssh
 Brave (brave-nightly-bin)
 Thunar file manager
  
​
 My system specifications
  
Motherboard: B450 AORUS ELITE
 Kernel: 5.18.1-arch1-1
 Window manager: dwm
 Display manager: ly
 Compositor: picom
 CPU: AMD Ryzen 5 2600X (12) @ 3.600GHz
 GPU: NVIDIA GeForce GTX 1080 Ti
 RAM: 2 x TridentZ Neo DDR4 16GB & 2 x HyperX Fury 16GB
  
​
 Sometimes its so bad that I can't even open bashtop/htop to get a screenshot or to look at whats going on, and even if i manage to open one of these 2, the navigation through them is very slow if not impossible. Even through the TTY.
 My current way of fixing this is rebooting my PC.
 I'm not sure how to debug this after rebooting. It's very hard to use the PC without rebooting to fix the issue, I would appreciate it if someone could help me find some logs or something that could be helpful for troubleshooting this issue, or if someone already knows how to fix it
    submitted by    /u/fuckcuff  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another Unreleased Google Pixel Shows Up For Sale]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120129/another-google-pixel-phone-goes-on-sale-before-its-official-release/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120129/another-google-pixel-phone-goes-on-sale-before-its-official-release/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T16:02:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It seems that there’s a leak in Google’s manufacturing process. Just last week, a Pixel 7 prototype appeared on eBay, and another prototype passed off as a “Pixel 6 Pro” in a Facebook Marketplace sale. Now, someone is trying (or was trying) to sell a Pixel 6a on Facebook.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do You Really Need Unlimited Data?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=803657</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/803657/do-you-really-need-unlimited-data/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The holy grail of cellular plans is unlimited data. Everyone wants to be able to stream and download without worrying about going over limits. Do you actually need unlimited data, though? Here are some things to consider.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows does not run anymore on VirtualBox]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v66svu/windows_does_not_run_anymore_on_virtualbox/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v66svu/windows_does_not_run_anymore_on_virtualbox/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T15:59:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have a VirtualBox with Windows 10 x64 which I use from time to time.
 Out of sudden it got broken yesterday - it is BSODing like crazy for many different reasons during boot stage. Sometimes it manages to survive until I can see login prompt but that's the furthest.
 What's worse I cannot even create a fresh virtual machine with windows 10 as booting from windows 10 iso also bsods or fails to copy files on disk. I've downloaded a fresh iso from MS and verified sha and it's ok. Also I have checked this iso on another PC with VB and windows host and it works fine (same VirtualBox version as on my linux machine).
 Currently I have VB 6.1.34 r150636 installed. It runs Windows 7 x86 just fine. Also it boots x64 system rescue cd linux with no visible issues.
 I have tried to roll back to VB 6.1.32 but it didn't helped. I have also tried to turn off all fancy options in cpu and acceleration tabs, but nothing changes.
 Does anyone have similar issue or an idea what else can I test?
    submitted by    /u/Kicer86  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A problem with my 65W laptop battery adapter or battery.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v66qlv/a_problem_with_my_65w_laptop_battery_adapter_or/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v66qlv/a_problem_with_my_65w_laptop_battery_adapter_or/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T15:56:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, let me describe my problem:
 If I run an app, using a rendering engine such as OpenGL, my battery stops charging entirely.
 Now even GLXGears causes this issue.
 I am using default Arch Kernel. I have tried using gamemode, but it doesn’t work.
 Never happened on Windows. I am running a NVIDIA dGPU. With TKG drivers.
    submitted by    /u/amogusdri-  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows Rollback: rimuovere il ripristino di Windows dal menu di avvio]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-Rollback-rimuovere-il-ripristino-di-Windows-dal-menu-di-avvio_24606</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-Rollback-rimuovere-il-ripristino-di-Windows-dal-menu-di-avvio_24606"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T15:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Se avete aggiornato Windows con l'installazione dell'ultimo feature update (sia nel caso di Windows 10 che di Windows 11) è possibile che a ogni successivo avvio della macchina compaia il menu di boot con la voce Windows Rollback. Quest'ultima permette di avviare una procedura di ripristino del sistema attingendo alle informazioni di backup salvate nella cartella Windows.old.Quando si installa un aggiornamento di Windows annuale (i feature update per Windows 10 e Windows 11 vengono rilasciati con questa cadenza), tutte le informazioni sulla precedente configurazione del sistema operativo vengono memorizzate nella cartella Windows.old.Assicurandosi che tutto funziona correttamente dopo l'aggiornamento alla nuova versione di Windows, per rimuovere Windows Rollback dal menu di avvio è possibile tenere in considerazione alcuni aspetti importanti:1) La voce Windows Rollback viene eliminata automaticamente insieme con tutto il contenuto della cartella Windows.old trascorsi 10 giorni dall'applicazione dell'aggiornamento.Se si volesse ottenere qualche giorno in più per controllare che il sistema e le applicazioni installate non presentano problemi, è possibile aumentare il numero di giorni per tornare alla versione precedente di Windows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Revive Your iPod with Rockbox in Linux]]></title>
        <id>http://maketecheasier.com/?p=16922</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15352894/untether-your-ipod-from-itunes-with-rockbox"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you owe an old iPod and are running Linux on your computer, you can use Rockbox to breathe life to your old music player. It enables you to use your iPod without iTunes while also improving on the default sound quality of the iPod. Rockbox is also customizable and really easy to install. Here we will show you how to use Rockbox in Linux.
   

Content

What is Rockbox and Why Install It
Which iPods Are Compatible with Rockbox
How to Obtain Rockbox
How to Install Rockbox in Linux
Detecting Your iPod in the Utility
Setting up the Rockbox Configuration Utility
Install Rockbox to Your iPod
Backing Up and Removing Rockbox
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:The Beginner’s Guide to Using Cron in Linux
    
What is Rockbox and Why Install It
    
Rockbox is an operating system for classic iPods. It is... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramces Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Package Groups, how to use it correctly?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v65rd3/package_groups_how_to_use_it_correctly/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v65rd3/package_groups_how_to_use_it_correctly/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T15:11:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is how I understand it - the only place that pacman saves group affiliation is the groups attribute in an individual packages' PKGBUILD file. And when I install a group, it is equivalent to install the individual packages, meaning the groups concept is more of a syntactic sugar, not much more than that. If that's all true, then I have a problem below:
 In abstract terms, if I install group G, which includes packages a, b, c, the three packages will be installed and marked as explicit by default. Now after some evolution package a dropped out of group G. All good, except that upgrades do not automatically remove a, even if it is not depended by any other installed packages, since it was marked explicit. If I remove group G, a would not be removed either since it is not in that group anymore.
 In reality, I think this was what happened when tracker-miner (the a above) package was removed from group gnome (G above) last week. After I did pacman -Rnsc gnome, package tracker-miner was still there.
 It makes me think package group (such as base-devel, gnome) approach is inferior to a meta-package (such as base). Am I missing something here? Hope someone can point to a better way to understand/use package group. BTW I love the arch distro and enjoy it a ton.
    submitted by    /u/notnullnone  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Translate Formulas in Microsoft Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=806220</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/806220/excel-translate-formula/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T15:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you and your team use versions of Excel in different languages, check out the Functions Translator. This Microsoft add-in can translate entire formulas or help you find the function you want in the language you need.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smartphone-Like App Folders May Come to Windows 11's Desktop]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120115/smartphone-like-app-folders-may-come-to-windows-11s-desktop/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120115/smartphone-like-app-folders-may-come-to-windows-11s-desktop/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T14:44:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Both Microsoft and its customers want more from the Windows 11 Start Menu. That’s why Microsoft is working on tidy little Start Menu app folders, which give you quick access to groups of apps. But oddly enough, this feature could extend to Windows 11’s desktop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dual-GPU setup AMD and NVIDIA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v655c5/dualgpu_setup_amd_and_nvidia/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v655c5/dualgpu_setup_amd_and_nvidia/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T14:44:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OS: Arch Linux btw x86_64
 Host: HP Pavilion Gaming Laptop 15-ec2xxx
 Kernel: 5.18.1-arch1-1
 DE: Plasma 5.24.5
 CPU: AMD Ryzen 5 5600H with Radeon Graphics (12) @ 3.300GHz
 GPU: NVIDIA GeForce RTX 3050 Mobile
 GPU: AMD ATI 05:00.0 Cezanne 
 Hello guys, I hope you all are doing good. I am new to linux and I have a friend who is using arch linux for 2 years but we are unable do dual-GPU setup with amd as iGPU for display and NVIDIA for other stuff like games. I need help with this and is it even possible to keep amd for display and nvidia for other things? 
 also, I had a question. When my friend helped me setup only nvidia gpu for everything from arch-wiki. It was working great for few hours and then suddenly my DE starts to lag alot (stutter). I am having this problem for a long time. I switched to arch a while ago too, I had the same problem. So, I had to switch back to windows 10 for sometime. does anybody know what was the reason of this issue? 
 Thanks in advance guys.
 Have a nice day!
    submitted by    /u/massiar  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some packages installed is newer than the mirrors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v64sm8/some_packages_installed_is_newer_than_the_mirrors/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v64sm8/some_packages_installed_is_newer_than_the_mirrors/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T14:28:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey guys, yesterday I have upgraded my system with pacman -Syyu and some packages as been upgraded and installed. Ok, just normal, but today I run the same command and received this warnings. Yesterday some mirrors is not working, but today they are fine. Is just some bug from mirrors (maybe delayed sync)?
    submitted by    /u/higorslva  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Italian city of Palermo shuts down all systems to fend off cyberattack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/italian-city-of-palermo-shuts-down-all-systems-to-fend-off-cyberattack/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/italian-city-of-palermo-shuts-down-all-systems-to-fend-off-cyberattack/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T14:13:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The municipality of Palermo in Southern Italy suffered a cyberattack on Friday, which appears to have had a massive impact on a broad range of operations and services to both citizens and visiting tourists. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Smart Displays of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=770546</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/770546/best-smart-display/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smart displays offer an elegant solution to all your smart home needs and make it easy to check your calendar, listen to music, or catch up with a video call. Here are the best smart displays you can buy right now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Bitner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come eliminare puntini e simboli P su Word]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/06/come-eliminare-puntini-e-simboli-p-su.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/06/come-eliminare-puntini-e-simboli-p-su.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T13:58:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chi non ha mai visto comparire su Word gli odiati puntini e le P rovesciate all'interno del documento su cui stavamo lavorando? Chi non conosce questi particolari segni andrà subito nel panico, visto che possono essere attivati per sbaglio e non è facile intuire, per chi non è esperto, come rimuoverli dal documento senza danneggiare il testo. 
Questi segni non sono errori, ma è una funzione...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why isn't screensharing working on teams? Only Powerpoint sharing?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v640hn/why_isnt_screensharing_working_on_teams_only/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v640hn/why_isnt_screensharing_working_on_teams_only/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T13:51:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the title says, I cant screenshare, only upload powerpoint files when in meetings. 
 I use Arch with i3 and Xorg, not Wayland. Im using the teams package on the AUR.
    submitted by    /u/copynfrog  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>