<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-04-24T01:42:47.487Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What processors do you all have?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uaivxz/what_processors_do_you_all_have/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uaivxz/what_processors_do_you_all_have/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-24T00:40:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Always wondered about how many of you have powerful processors. I have a dual core i5 that still seems to be fine for everything. 
 *my phone is more powerful btw :/
    submitted by    /u/fuckerydoo2  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Got blue screen, black screen with the white dots while trying to install windows 10 on arch.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uainkp/got_blue_screen_black_screen_with_the_white_dots/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uainkp/got_blue_screen_black_screen_with_the_white_dots/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-24T00:27:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been using arch over 3 months but I got bored because I am design engineer I wanna install cad programs
 however, I download the iso image of w10 and make bootable usb with Ventoy but when I try to boot I got black screen always. Actually at first I tried to install w10 but it said there is no right partition so I shut down my computer during installation and never got in installation again.
 What do you think I got my bios fucked or something? Whst should I do. I change the bootable usb several times.
    submitted by    /u/mechatchronic  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PSA: zlib v1.2.12 is kinda broken... (breaks bunch of stuff including Minecraft)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uaievj/psa_zlib_v1212_is_kinda_broken_breaks_bunch_of/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uaievj/psa_zlib_v1212_is_kinda_broken_breaks_bunch_of/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-24T00:13:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I found this the hard way and took me forever to realize it was breaking Fabric Loader for Minecraft
 If you see error message like:
 java.util.zip.ZipException: invalid entry CRC (expected 0x518510b5 but got 0x5bfe689e) 
 And you're using zlib v1.2.12 then it's zlib fault, downgrading to v1.2.11 works.
 See https://github.com/madler/zlib/issues/613 and https://bugs.archlinux.org/task/74371
    submitted by    /u/davispuh  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can’t boot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uai9fp/cant_boot/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uai9fp/cant_boot/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-24T00:05:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welp… I tried to set up a dual-booting system with Windows 11 and Arch and somehow managed for GRUB to not recognize any operating system at all, only giving me the option to go into EFI, which only shows me GRUB as a bootable “drive”. It was a relatively new machine so I don’t mind having to completely wipe my hard drive, but I hope there’s a way I don’t have to do that. Any help would be appreciated, thanks!
    submitted by    /u/Zeno371  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I'm undecided as to which kernel I'm going to use]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uah9nt/im_undecided_as_to_which_kernel_im_going_to_use/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uah9nt/im_undecided_as_to_which_kernel_im_going_to_use/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T23:10:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm an intermediate linux user, like most, I started with Ubuntu. During my experience with it, I started to notice that its performance was not that different compared to windows (my old system) and performance was always my focus because in that At the time I had a humble 10 year old hd and 2gb of ram. So I tested several other distros and I'm currently running debian, but the stable version of debian has outdated packages as hell, this is so remarkable that I couldn't even run pipewire correctly on bullseye. So not to stray so much from my current debian scenario I thought about using testing or sid, but I saw that arch was more stable than the same. Even though I've used arch before and loved it, I'm confused about the kernel to use (I'll comment on this in a few lines), before formatt…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Locale is messed up, I'm a noob and unsure how to fix it :(]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uagapq/locale_is_messed_up_im_a_noob_and_unsure_how_to/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uagapq/locale_is_messed_up_im_a_noob_and_unsure_how_to/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T22:20:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've followed the wiki, edited /etc/locale.gen, upon running locale-gen I'm getting a few errors. 'm unsure where I have gone wrong?
 Upon writing locale -a I get:
  
locale: Cannot set LC_CTYPE to default locale: No such file or directory 
 locale: Cannot set LC_MESSAGES to default locale: No such file or directory 
 locale: Cannot set LC_COLLATE to default locale: No such file or directory 
 C 
 POSIX 
 en_GB.utf8
  
   submitted by    /u/Sorry-Main-4039  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VAAPI gone till brave and firefox latest versions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uafto6/vaapi_gone_till_brave_and_firefox_latest_versions/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uafto6/vaapi_gone_till_brave_and_firefox_latest_versions/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T21:56:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi does anyone succeeded to get vaapi working on brave or firefox latest versions ??
 Fo brave it doesn't work since 2 months and for firefox it's broken on 99 version release.
    submitted by    /u/Spare_Prize1148  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PulseAudio: avoid-resampling = true issue]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uaevx6/pulseaudio_avoidresampling_true_issue/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uaevx6/pulseaudio_avoidresampling_true_issue/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T21:08:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, having
  avoid-resampling = true resample-method = soxr-vhq ; just for the case when needed? default-sample-format = s32le default-sample-rate = 44100 alternate-sample-rate = 48000 ... 
 in the /etc/pulse/daemon.conf.
 I have two flac files (format told by ffmpeg -i): - Audio: flac, 44100 Hz, stereo, s16 - Audio: flac, 96000 Hz, stereo, s32 (24 bit)
 When I have default-sample-rate = 44100 the first one is played with resample-method = (null) and not the second one (the second one uses the above-mentioned resample method).
 When I have default-sample-rate = 96000 the second one is played with resample-method = (null) and not the first one. Alternate sample rate is ignored.
 (this has been acquired using pacmd list-sink-inputs)
 Question.
 Please, how to config Pulseaudio to allow avoiding resampling for multiple sample rates simultaneously?
 Config. - current stable Arch - not using pipewire-pulse just plain pulseaudio - using external USB DAC capable of 32bit/192kHz - alsa_output.usb-Schiit_Audio_I_m_Fulla_Schiit-00.iec958-stereo/#0: I'm Fulla Schiit Digital Stereo (IEC958)
    submitted by    /u/Original_Two9716  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Default Apps on Android]]></title>
        <id>http://www.howtogeek.com/?p=43135</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/howto/43135/how-to-change-the-default-application-for-android-tasks/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you have multiple apps that do the same thing, Android asks you which one you want to be the “default.” This is one of Android’s best features and you should take advantage of it. We’ll show you how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Google Pixel Watch Trademark Filing Suggests an Imminent Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/115797/a-google-pixel-watch-trademark-filing-suggests-an-imminent-launch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/115797/a-google-pixel-watch-trademark-filing-suggests-an-imminent-launch/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T20:04:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve suspected that Google would release a Pixel Watch, but at best, we had information in the form of rumors. Now, a trademark filing provides near confirmation that the smartwatch is coming, maybe even soon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Hendrickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Antivirus Software Works]]></title>
        <id>http://www.howtogeek.com/?p=125650</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/125650/htg-explains-how-antivirus-software-works/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Antivirus programs are powerful pieces of software that are essential on Windows computers. If you’ve ever wondered how antivirus programs detect viruses, what they’re doing on your computer, and whether you need to perform regular system scans yourself, read on.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Completely Delete and Uninstall Apps on Android]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=post-ideas&amp;p=173665</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/5187194/remove-leftover-files-android"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes, when an app has outlived its usefulness, you’ll want to uninstall it to make way for new ones. Uninstalling apps is easy enough: simply go to the Apps list, find the app, and hit the Uninstall button. But it’s not so easy to completely uninstall apps on Android.
    
Unfortunately, for those who like a clean file system, some apps will leave behind “orphaned files” after uninstallation on Android devices. These files were created by the app so that it can do its job if they weren’t properly deleted after the app was uninstalled. This can get annoying when your device’s system is slowly clogged up by files and folders that aren’t being used. The solution then is to find a way to reliably remove leftover app data.
   

Content

Manual Clean
Deleting Folders
Connect to a Computer
SD Maid
ES File Explorer
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Crystal Crowder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deactivate or Delete a Facebook Account on iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=792555</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/792555/deactivate-or-delete-facebook-account-on-iphone/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T19:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to deactivate or delete your Facebook account? You can do either directly on your iPhone’s Facebook app. We’ll show you how to do that as well as how to uninstall the Facebook app on your iPhone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sharing violation when editing any file through an application running in wine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uac10b/sharing_violation_when_editing_any_file_through/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uac10b/sharing_violation_when_editing_any_file_through/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T18:46:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm having the exact issue that this guy was having here:
  
Hey all, I use musicbee as a music player on windows, and I've found it really convenient to be able to use the exact library files for it on both linux and windows on my dual-booted desktop. The only real problem I'm having (- other than non-latin characters not showing up correctly) is that I'm not able to make any edits to files within musicbee as every time I try to eg, like a song, export a playlist etc, I get the error 'Sharing violation. This file cannot be updated as another application has this file open at the same time'. 
 Checking fuser on the files in question show that they are used by 'MusicBee.exe' and 'wineserver', probably meaning that wineserver is what's causing musicbee to lock up on making these edits. Anyone know of a fix for this?
  
Only, the music is on my Linux Mint, ext4 drive, so I'm not sure what is happening. The comments mention this might be a permissions issue, but I don't have enough linux knowledge to be able to follow the comments or otherwise figure out how to resolve this error.
 Any ideas?
 EDIT: Was able to figure out how to get CJK fonts installed (mostly) using Winetricks, but the sharing violation issue still persists.
    submitted by    /u/revolution_twelve  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to get temperature from Intel NIC through sysfs/hwmon with Intel ixgbe driver]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uabgrn/how_to_get_temperature_from_intel_nic_through/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uabgrn/how_to_get_temperature_from_intel_nic_through/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T18:19:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Through Intel X550 datasheet, the commit and current source for Intel ixgbe driver, I know that X550 chipset has on-die thermal sensor and Intel ixgbe driver already implemented sysfs/hwmon interface for temperature monitoring on Linux.
 But I just could not find the actual interface to the temperature information on the sysfs. Where is it?
    submitted by    /u/hurryman2212  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Function keys are not working. T420]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uab35i/function_keys_are_not_working_t420/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uab35i/function_keys_are_not_working_t420/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T18:01:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The function keys of my T420 are not working for example when trying to change the brightness of my screen. However the function key for the keyboard light does work which makes me think that something might be wrong with my system. Has anyone a solution or experienced this too?
 Thanks in advance
    submitted by    /u/TSRfsm  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sennheiser's Latest Sport Earbuds Will Block Sounds You Never Think About]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/115783/sennheisers-latest-sport-earbuds-will-block-sounds-you-never-think-about/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/115783/sennheisers-latest-sport-earbuds-will-block-sounds-you-never-think-about/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T18:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sennheiser is known for making terrific earbuds with equally great features. It’s no surprise, then, that the company’s latest endeavor—the Sport True Wireless earbuds—have a clever new awareness feature we think anyone can appreciate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzanne Humphries</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Pair a PS4 Controller]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=792747</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/792747/how-to-pair-ps4-controller/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T18:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you want to pair your first or your secondary DualShock 4 controller, Sony’s PlayStation 4 makes the entire pairing process a breeze. We’ll show you how to get your controller synced with your console in this guide.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is there any way to prevent auto-installing some dependencies of meta-packages?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uaahuf/is_there_any_way_to_prevent_autoinstalling_some/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uaahuf/is_there_any_way_to_prevent_autoinstalling_some/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T17:32:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The goal is to remove some of the dependencies of KDE meta-packages (like kde-multimedia-meta and kde-network-meta). For example I don't need kdenlive, falkon, konqueror, konversation..... more....
 I know I can remove the meta-packages (and that's what I started to do) , but I thought that new packages might be added and i would like to learn about them.
 So i can either (1) use some tool to watch and notify me of new dependencies on the meta-packages; or i can (2) keep the metapackages, remove the unneded dependencies and prevent their auto-reinstallation with some tool; or i can (3) remove the metapackages and only keep the ones i want to, using some other tool to monitor for new dependencies on the meta-packages.
 Has anyone used something to do what i want to do?
 EDIT: I've already seen about IgnorePackage and i've red that it only prevents upgrading a package once it's installed, but does not prevent automatic reinstallation of dependency. I have not tried it personally.
 I've also heard about creating a dummy package to lie to the OS, but my gut feeling does not like that.
 EDIT 2: Maybe it'll be best for me to make my own tool to fetch/check for new packages in kde-* groups and possibly use groups.
    submitted by    /u/liubomirwm  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Does “AF” Mean, and How Do You Use It?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=711826</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/711826/what-does-af-mean/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T17:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ve probably seen “AF” on your social media feed at least once. Here’s what this useful internet modifier means and how to use it to spice up your messages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vann Vicente</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla Promises a Robotaxi with No Steering Wheel "In 2024"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/115782/tesla-promises-a-robotaxi-with-no-steering-wheel-in-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/115782/tesla-promises-a-robotaxi-with-no-steering-wheel-in-2024/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T16:34:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we all know by now, Tesla’s CEO Elon Musk is always hinting at exciting new technology or vehicles on the horizon. During Tesla’s latest earnings call this week, the company said its highly efficient Robotaxi will arrive in 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Check Your iPhone’s Storage Capacity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=794902</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/794902/how-to-check-your-iphones-storage-capacity/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T16:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re buying or selling a used iPhone, it’s helpful to identify how much storage capacity it has. Luckily, it’s easy to find out how much data your iPhone can hold in Settings. Here’s how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is there an archive of discontinued AUR projects?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ua82fu/is_there_an_archive_of_discontinued_aur_projects/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ua82fu/is_there_an_archive_of_discontinued_aur_projects/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T15:37:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm looking to install MonoDevelop, specifically, which used to be available on the AUR. I get why no one wants to maintain it on AUR anymore, but I'd like to be able to use the old version anyway.
    submitted by    /u/ReturningTarzan  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add Text With a Formula in Google Sheets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=795106</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/795106/how-to-add-text-in-formula-google-sheets/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T15:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Typing text in a Google Sheets cell is simple. But what if you want to edit that text to include more and apply it to multiple cells? Using a couple of different methods, you can add text using a formula.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Installing Arch with Windows 11 and Ubuntu + GRUB already installed. All on separate drives]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ua62vj/installing_arch_with_windows_11_and_ubuntu_grub/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ua62vj/installing_arch_with_windows_11_and_ubuntu_grub/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T14:01:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have Win11 and Ubuntu installed on 2 different drives already and booting with GRUB. I've been using Ubuntu for a while for school and would like to keep it instead of completely replacing it with Arch. But I'm going to start an internship in a couple months and they use Arch. Any tips on how to install Arch on a 3rd ssd and continue to use GRUB? Anything I should know beforehand that could cause problems? 
 edit: Thanks for the replies. Look's like I was overthinking things and it should be pretty straight-forward. Thanks for the help!
    submitted by    /u/camperryan  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Google Pixel 6 Cases of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=767099</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/767099/best-google-pixel-6-case/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Pixel 6 marks Google’s return to the premium smartphone segment, and like most premium phones, it’s a glass sandwich. So if you want to keep the phone looking fantastic, investing in a case is a good idea. Here are the best cases for the Google Pixel 6.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gaurav Shukla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[how to enable the light on the mute button on my keyboard?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ua5zbu/how_to_enable_the_light_on_the_mute_button_on_my/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ua5zbu/how_to_enable_the_light_on_the_mute_button_on_my/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T13:56:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[i have a 15s-du2004tu, and on the keyboard, there is a mute button, with a light that glows red when muted. the light works perfectly fine in Windows, but, doesn't on Linux. is there any way i can make it work? thanks in advance.
 this is what it looks like: https://imgur.com/9KMw8pF.
    submitted by    /u/sam1090x  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come vedere la Formula 1 su Smart TV, PC, smartphone e tablet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/04/come-vedere-la-formula-1-su-smart-tv-pc.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/04/come-vedere-la-formula-1-su-smart-tv-pc.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T13:31:00.007Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[La Formula 1 coinvolge ogni anno milioni di appassionati in tutto il mondo, che seguono le gesta delle scuderie in giro per il mondo sui circuiti più belli e spettacolari. Se anche noi siamo appassionati di corse e non vediamo l'ora di seguire le gesta della nostra scuderia o del nostro pilota preferito, possiamo utilizzare qualsiasi dispositivo moderno per seguire in diretta streaming le prove...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Are P2E Games? Play-to-Earn NFTs or Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=797623</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/797623/what-are-p2e-games-play-to-earn-nfts-or-crypto/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Few sectors are escaping the crypto craze, but many game developers have really embraced it. Plenty of gaming-related collectibles can now be claimed as NFTs, but some so-called “play-to-earn” games have gone even further and have crypto and NFT as the stakes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fergus O'Sullivan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Discord shows weird boxes in some channels]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ua52b1/discord_shows_weird_boxes_in_some_channels/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ua52b1/discord_shows_weird_boxes_in_some_channels/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T13:07:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have some issues with discord about the font it is using : doesn't show Japanese characters & some special Unicode ones. I've looked into this issue and tried to install new fonts with :
 sudo pacman -Ss noto-fonts-emoji 
 Thing is, discord doesn't seem to recognize the newly installed fonts? Or is there a way to force discord to use these fonts? I'm still a beginner on ARCH and I'm using GNOME if that helps.
    submitted by    /u/LittleBigOwl  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Wi-Fi Calling, and Should You Use It?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=794724</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/794724/what-is-wi-fi-calling/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T13:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If your home or office has spotty cellular coverage, Wi-Fi calling is a nifty little solution that can make your life a lot easier. Here’s everything you need to know about Wi-Fi calling, and how to start using it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gaurav Shukla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Smart Lighting in Your Home Is Worth It]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/113995/why-smart-lighting-in-your-home-is-worth-it/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/113995/why-smart-lighting-in-your-home-is-worth-it/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T13:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smart lights are the perfect introduction to the wonderful world of smart home technology. They’re simple to set up, easy to use, and make your home more productive and more fun at the same time. Plus, they’re not too expensive.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Chaney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Need to run ssh-add -l every time before apps can use gpg-agent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ua4fk3/need_to_run_sshadd_l_every_time_before_apps_can/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ua4fk3/need_to_run_sshadd_l_every_time_before_apps_can/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T12:31:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/sarvasana  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Do My AirPods Keep Pausing?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=798054</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/798054/why-do-my-airpods-keep-pausing/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T12:30:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nothing interrupts your audio bliss quite like your AirPods unceremoniously pausing without notice. There are a few things that may cause this issue, but all of them are simple to diagnose and easy to fix.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kris Wouk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Screen randomly blacking out while playing games?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ua3zu4/screen_randomly_blacking_out_while_playing_games/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ua3zu4/screen_randomly_blacking_out_while_playing_games/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T12:06:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So I do a lot of gaming and sometimes the screen just goes black. I have to move my mouse a bit and then that fixes it. I have no idea what is causing this.
 by the way I'm using a laptop but the battery is taken out so linux just recognizes it as a desktop pc.
 Any ideas as to whats causing this?
 Thanks!
    submitted by    /u/DiamondDanMan12  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 10 Best Action Movies to Stream for Free in 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=793187</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/793187/best-action-movies-to-stream-online-for-free/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s no need to pay for a streaming subscription to get your action-movie fix. Free streaming services have plenty of action-packed movies from a variety of eras and subgenres. Here are the best action movies to stream for free.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Bell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[makechrootpkg: bind directory into build chroot as read-only]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ua3845/makechrootpkg_bind_directory_into_build_chroot_as/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ua3845/makechrootpkg_bind_directory_into_build_chroot_as/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T11:19:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Can anyone help me understand how to bind a local source directory to the chroot and building the package from that source?
 makechrootpkg -D <dir> 
 Where is <dir> bound in the chroot? How is that bind location referenced when prepare() and package() are run?
    submitted by    /u/jimsmith716  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 5 Most Ridiculously Expensive Phones of All Time]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=794742</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/794742/the-5-most-ridiculously-expensive-phones-of-all-time/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T11:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Phones today come at a wide variety of price points. On the upper end, there are devices that push close to $2,000. That may seem steep, but there have been much more expensive phones.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grub not working]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ua2odg/grub_not_working/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ua2odg/grub_not_working/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T10:42:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m having trouble actually trying to boot into my new arch instillation after I set it up. When I reboot I get sent to the installation media and no other bootable drive appears in my bios boot menu. Here’s a list of my commands for my installation
 EDIT: because someone asked me to put the solution here, I had to add ‘—removeable’ to the grub-install command. I’ve also included my entire written installation instructions if people would like to follow along to install Arch. Keep in mind this may not be perfect, as I am a beginner my self, and this was written for UEFI systems using the GPT label. If you’re not using UEFI, you can check out the ArchWiki to see how this installation process differs.
 Arch Install
 ls /sys/firmware/efi/efivars
 (If this command outputs something, then you’r…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ubuntu 22.04 LTS Changes Default For NVIDIA Driver Back To Using X.Org Rather Than Wayland]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Ubuntu-22.04-NVIDIA-XOrg-Back</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Ubuntu-22.04-NVIDIA-XOrg-Back"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T10:33:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While back in March Ubuntu 22.04 "Jammy Jellyfish" changed the default behavior for NVIDIA's driver to use Wayland inline with Intel and Radeon graphics having used the GNOME Wayland session rather than X.Org for the past few releases, this change was reverted at the last-minute. With a launch-day SRU, Ubuntu 22.04 LTS is defaulting to using the GNOME X.Org session rather than Wayland when running the proprietary NVIDIA driver...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Need help to start maintaining an AUR package]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ua27rf/need_help_to_start_maintaining_an_aur_package/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ua27rf/need_help_to_start_maintaining_an_aur_package/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T10:10:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi guys, many years ago I created zaread office/ebook viewer. It was meant initially as a "personal use" script I made mainly because I hated being forced to open LibreOffice (with its RAM usage and bloaty buttons) every time I needed to see the content of a doc file. I uploaded the script on github in case anyone needed a similiar thing, then just forgot about it.
 Then few days ago, checking github after a long time, I discovered that many people adopted it and even made some patches. Also I discovered that a person of good will created and maintained the related AUR package, named zaread-git.
 So, moved by the sense of guilt of my disappearing, I checked the pull requests made in the years, reordered the code, fixed some bugs I discovered and committed on github. Then I reported the updates in its AUR page. The problem is that the creator of zaread-git AUR package is not an Arch user anymore and asks for a new maintainer.
 Now I feel the responsability of maintaining it, my problem is that, despite being a >10 years Arch user... I never did it before. To me AUR packages always have been one of those "magic" things the computer does to simplify your work.I would like to give to it a mandatory dependency (zathura) and some optional dependencies (libreoffice, calibre, md2pdf).
 Does anyone know if there are tutorials that explain how to start from scratch? I know that there is an helper (clean-chroot-manager) but its man page is a bit thin.
 Thanks!
    submitted by    /u/paoloap  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Garmin Upstreams Linux Patch Around Boat Steering Wheels, Marine Navigation Displays]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-Garmin-Marine-Keycodes</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-Garmin-Marine-Keycodes"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T09:43:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Being sent in as a fix for Linux 5.18-rc3 is supporting various marine navigation keycodes with at least Garmin's boat steering wheels and marine navigation displays running Linux...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft starts to phase out NetBIOS and LLMNR to focus on mDNS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178194</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/04/23/microsoft-starts-to-phase-out-netbios-and-llmnr-to-focus-on-mdns/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T09:23:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft's Windows operating system supports several multicast name resolution protocols, including NetBIOS and LLMNR. The state of the art protocol that is widely used today is mDNS, while the protocols NetBIOS and […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Microsoft starts to phase out NetBIOS and LLMNR to focus on mDNS appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More AMD Radeon Graphics Driver Changes Queued Ahead Of Linux 5.19]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMDGPU-Linux-5.19-Batch-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMDGPU-Linux-5.19-Batch-2"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T09:22:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another week, another batch of new AMDGPU and AMDKFD kernel driver feature work ready for queuing in DRM-Next ahead of the next kernel cycle. Feature code continues building up in DRM-Next ahead of the Linux 5.19 cycle...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KDE Plasma Lands More Fixes, Theme Handling Improvements]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=KDE-Theme-Handling-Better</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=KDE-Theme-Handling-Better"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T09:06:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even amid all the April software releases, KDE developers remain very busy working on their open-source desktop stack...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[testdisk hanging in Archlinux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ua1734/testdisk_hanging_in_archlinux/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ua1734/testdisk_hanging_in_archlinux/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T08:55:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am trying to recover some data from an USB disk: it is too large to create a local image before starting.I already successfully used testdisk like that in the past but on a different distro (Ubuntu 20.04).
 I am currently experiencing hangs under Archlinux after I select "Analyse" and then "Quick search". 
 The process stays in "D+" status (uninterruptible sleep (usually IO) in foregound) and there's nothing else I can do besides rebooting. 
 I was expecting the usual "real time" progress information, but it simply freezes.I also tested the "wip" package from AUR, but it doesn't make any difference.Using testdisk on a different drive just works, so I think it's an hardware-related issue.
 Is there a way to fix/workaround this issue and go on?
    submitted by    /u/0BAD-C0DE  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Animated QR codes: how do they work, and how to create your own?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/animated-qr-codes-how-do-they-work-and-how-to-create-your-own/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/animated-qr-codes-how-do-they-work-and-how-to-create-your-own/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T08:14:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is there such a thing as animated QR codes? And could they work? Even those who may not know how exactly QR codes work have pretty much been exposed to them by now. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ax Sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to switch to a different regional Store in the Amazon App]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178183</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/04/23/how-to-switch-to-a-different-regional-store-in-the-amazon-app/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T05:02:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon operates regional stores that customers may buy products from. The Stores are not limited to customers from a specific region, but some products may not be purchasable if a customer comes […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post How to switch to a different regional Store in the Amazon App appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wine 7.7 Continues PE Conversion Work, Allows Theming Control Panel Applets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Wine-7.7-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Wine-7.7-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wine 7.7 is out as the latest bi-weekly release of this open-source software for enjoying Windows games and applications under Linux...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is "cron" the easiest way to run a script as root on boot?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u9was3/is_cron_the_easiest_way_to_run_a_script_as_root/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u9was3/is_cron_the_easiest_way_to_run_a_script_as_root/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T03:31:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/snesgx  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fix the Critical Process Died Error in Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=post-ideas&amp;p=474424</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15239156/fix-critical-process-died-windows"/>
        <updated>2022-04-23T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you facing blue screen of death (BSoD) issues on your Windows computer, accompanied by a “Critical_Process_Died” message? It’s a fatal system error that shows out of nowhere, and freezes or restarts your device. In the worst case, it may prevent you from booting to the desktop.
    
Fortunately, many of the problems that lead to the “critical process died” error are pretty easy to fix. The solutions we cover work for Windows 11 and Windows 10, unless stated otherwise.
   

Content

What Is the "Critical Process Died" Stop Code?
How to Fix the "Critical Process Died" Error
1. Restart in Safe Mode
2. Run Chkdsk on Windows
3. Do a System Restore
4. Find and Fix Bluescreen Problems From Control Panel
5. Update Old Drivers
6. Reset Windows
7. Do a Factory Image Restore
Prevent BSoD Errors With DISM and SFC
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sayak Boral</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dualbooting with Android]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u9qzrg/dualbooting_with_android/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u9qzrg/dualbooting_with_android/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T22:50:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, I'm trying to dualboot Arch and Android x86 and I have troubles getting grub to detect Android partition.
 For now I modified the /etc/grub.d/40_custom to contain
 #!/bin/sh exec tail -n +3 $0 menuentry "Android-x86" { set root='(hd2,7)' linux /android-2021-06-26/kernel quiet root=/dev/ram0 androidboot.hardware=eeepc acpi_sleep=s3_bios,s3_mode SRC=/android-2021-06-26 initrd /android-2021-06-26/initrd.img} 
 I'm not sure if my drive should be hd2,7 since I have one sata drive and two NVME drives in the system.
 I also found out about the android path name by mounting the nvme drive I installed it to and it had a folder named android-2021-06-26 inside… so I guess that's correct.
 After booting this entry grub throws an error:
 ACPI BIOS Error (bug): Failure creating name object [\_SB.PC10.SATO.PRT4._GTF], AE_ALREADY_EXISTS (20200925/dswloadZ-327) ACPI Error: AE_ALREADY_EXISTS, During name lookup/catalog (20200925/psobject-Z21) Detecting Android-x86... found at /dev/nvme0n1p7 
 But after that nothing, screen goes to black and stays like this.Keep in mind that I had to rewrite this error so I might have made some typos.
 Any help is highly appreciated!Also, I'm not entirely sure if this is the best subreddit to post this to, should I post it in a different one?
    submitted by    /u/Granat1  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Questa settimana su TLI (23 aprile 2022)]]></title>
        <id>3556|20220423000001</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/newsletter-turbolab.it-1349/questa-settimana-tli-23-aprile-2022-3556"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T22:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Non hai tempo di leggerci tutti i giorni? nessun problema! ecco a te il riepilogo di quanto proposto da TurboLab.it nel corso della settimana in conclusione.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Set-up an AMD GPU for daily usage (Graphics,Gaming,Compute,etc) in Arch Linux.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u9pto2/setup_an_amd_gpu_for_daily_usage/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u9pto2/setup_an_amd_gpu_for_daily_usage/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T21:55:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone.
 In this post I'm going to show you how to setup an AMD GPU for Arch Linux, while it is much more straight-forward than setting up an nvidia card , new users may still benefit from this guide.
 So first you will need to have at-least functional minimal Arch Linux Installation With Networking.
 And then we will proceed :
 1 - Getting xorg Drivers.
  
Run the following Command to install xorg packages :
  
​
 sudo pacman -S xorg xorg-drivers xf86-video-amdgpu 
 2 - Getting Mesa OpenGL Drivers. (Open-source)
  
Run following Command to install mesa OpenGL packages :
  
​
 sudo pacman -S mesa 
 3 - Getting 32-bit version of Mesa OpenGL Drivers. (Open-source) (Optional)
 To install the proprietary OpenGl Driver (Optional)
  
Enable the Multilib Repository , By un-commenting the fol…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CPU overheats while watching videos]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u9pc0y/cpu_overheats_while_watching_videos/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u9pc0y/cpu_overheats_while_watching_videos/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T21:32:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everytime i watch a video on YouTube or have online live lecture for uni my cpu temps go up. Normally my laptop cpu is around 28-30 C° but when starting videos it goes up to 50 or more sometimes and after 40 C° my fans turn up to really loud (is there a solution for this too?). And im a Computer Science Student ive done many big projects with this laptop and no matter how big the code is and what it does my cpu temps never go higher than 35 C° but for a yt video my fans start rotating.
 Anybody has some suggestions? 
 i use Firefox on a ThinkPad t14s with amd processor (and endeavour is my os but due its based on arch i want to try it in this community)
    submitted by    /u/burek_jesamosamesom  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is a GaN Charger? 5 of the Best GaN Chargers You Can Buy]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=427353</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/14853917/what-is-gan-charger"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you sick of lugging around multiple chargers for all of your devices and hate the fact that the giant batteries inside your phone and laptop seem to take forever to charge? If you answered yes, then you’re in for a treat. 
    
Say goodbye to the heavy, cumbersome charging brick and hello to the svelte, powerful GaN charger. Gallium Nitride chargers are the next step in charging technology. They are more efficient at converting power, which means there is less wasted energy. 
   

Content

What Does GaN Mean?
What's Wrong With Silicon Semiconductors?
How Do GaN Chargers Work?
What Is the Advantage of GaN Chargers? 
Are GaN Chargers Compatible With Multiple Devices?
GaN Charger Recommendations
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:The Best Wireless Chargers and Buying Criteria to Watch For
    
What Does GaN Mean?
 ... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ojash Yadav</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Remove a Google Account From Chrome]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=797946</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/797946/remove-a-google-account-from-chrome/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T21:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Chrome doesn’t require a Google account to function. If you want to remove one or all Google accounts from Chrome, you can do so and still continue to use the browser. We’ll show you how to do that on desktop and mobile.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Help: pacman needs more space on /boot for upgrade. How to expand EFI partition with Windows reserved partition in the way?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u9o8si/help_pacman_needs_more_space_on_boot_for_upgrade/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u9o8si/help_pacman_needs_more_space_on_boot_for_upgrade/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T20:43:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pacman needs to update something on the EFI partition (mount point '/boot') as part of routine upgrade, but there is not enough space on the 190MB EFI partition shared by Windows 11 and GRUB. I can't expand the partition because there is a 128MB "reserved partition" immediately to the right of the EFI partition.
 I have 4.00 GB unallocated to the right of Partition 3 (Windows 11) which I would like to tap into to expand the EFI partition. Any idea how to move around the space safely?
 Partition table from Windows diskpart:
 Partition ### Type Size Offset
 ------------- ---------------- ------- -------
 Partition 1 System 190 MB 1024 KB (EFI)
 Partition 2 Reserved 128 MB 191 MB (reserved)
 Partition 3 Primary 843 GB 319 MB (Windows 11)
 Partition 7 Unknown 14 GB 847 GB (Linux Mint 20.3)
 Partition 8 Unknown 74 GB 861 GB (Arch Linux)
 Partition 4 Recovery 990 MB 936 GB
 Partition 5 Recovery 14 GB 937 GB
 Partition 6 Recovery 1377 MB 952 GB
    submitted by    /u/apple-skunk  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Hack DHS' bug hunters find 122 security flaws in DHS systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hack-dhs-bug-hunters-find-122-security-flaws-in-dhs-systems/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hack-dhs-bug-hunters-find-122-security-flaws-in-dhs-systems/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T20:05:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Department of Homeland Security (DHS) today revealed that bug bounty hunters enrolled in its 'Hack DHS' bug bounty program have found 122 security vulnerabilities in external DHS systems, 27 of them rated critical severity. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Change Safari’s Default Search Engine on Mac]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=797866</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/797866/how-to-change-safaris-default-search-engine-on-mac/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T20:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Safari is a solid browser for most Mac users. It’s fast, energy-efficient, plays nicely with the iPhone and iPad, and more. If you’re not happy with the default search engine, though, changing it takes only a few clicks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save 20% on an Amazon Smart Thermostat]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=482942</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15238845/amazon-smart-thermostat"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To go along with all of Amazon’s smart home devices, the company introduced a new one: the  Amazon Smart Thermostat. To no one’s surprise, it works with Alexa, is ENERGY STAR certified, and is a DIY install. Get it now for under $50.
    
The 20% discount isn’t your only savings. The thermostat is certified for humans and is also ENERGY STAR-certified, which will save you on average $50 a year on our energy bills. Talk to your energy provider about getting rebates for your purchase. There are also energy savings incentives so that you will continue to save throughout the year.
    

    
Alexa will automatically adjust the temperature on the Alexa Smart Thermostat to keep you at your most comfortable. Whether you are at home, out for the day, or sleeping, the thermostat can be set to your desired comfort level. Alexa also allows you to control your heating and air when linked to another Alexa-enabled app.
    
You needn’t worry about installing the thermostat, as step-by-step instructions are included... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gtk theme not working on some apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u9m604/gtk_theme_not_working_on_some_apps/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u9m604/gtk_theme_not_working_on_some_apps/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T19:08:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[on timeshift my gtk theme is not working
    submitted by    /u/h4636oh  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Change Your Home Page in Brave]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=797386</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/797386/how-to-change-home-page-on-brave/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T19:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like with all other web browsers, you can change the Brave browser’s home page to any website of your choice. This lets you open that site in the browser by just clicking the Home button. We’ll show you how to set this up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is there a way to silence kernel/dmesg logs in the TTY?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u9lxk9/is_there_a_way_to_silence_kerneldmesg_logs_in_the/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u9lxk9/is_there_a_way_to_silence_kerneldmesg_logs_in_the/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T18:57:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been getting ACPI errors in the arch Linux live iso tty, and switching between them doesn't help. I've tried looking for a solution but I can only summise that this is due to some OEM firmware bug.
 https://imgur.com/a/OnsgkVs
    submitted by    /u/ChisNullStR  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russian hackers are seeking alternative money-laundering options]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/russian-hackers-are-seeking-alternative-money-laundering-options/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/russian-hackers-are-seeking-alternative-money-laundering-options/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T18:33:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Russian cybercrime community, one of the most active and prolific in the world, is turning to alternative money-laundering methods due to sanctions on Russia and law enforcement actions against dark web markets. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Enable Dark Mode by Tapping the Back of Your iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=793352</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/793352/how-to-enable-dark-mode-by-tapping-the-back-of-your-iphone/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you have an iPhone 8 or later and the latest release of iOS, you can use a feature called Back Tap to switch between dark mode and light mode on your device with just two or three taps. Here’s how to set it up using Shortcuts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mesa's New OpenCL Stack "Rusticl" Nearing Formal Support For OpenCL 3.0]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Mesa-OpenCL-3.0-CTS-Passes</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Mesa-OpenCL-3.0-CTS-Passes"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mesa's Rusticl is a yet-to-be-merged OpenCL implementation for Mesa Gallium3D drivers written in the Rust programming language. The latest code now can pass the Khronos OpenCL 3.0 Conformance Test Suite!..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can Old EV Batteries Be Recycled?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/115750/can-old-ev-batteries-be-recycled/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/115750/can-old-ev-batteries-be-recycled/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T17:40:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In case you haven’t noticed, cars everywhere are going electric. As more EVs hit the road over the next decade or so, what happens to all the old used batteries? While it’s not a big problem yet, it’ll be a huge one soon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung's Galaxy Z Fold 4 Might Be Even More Tablet Sized]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/115771/samsungs-galaxy-z-fold-4-might-be-even-more-tablet-sized/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/115771/samsungs-galaxy-z-fold-4-might-be-even-more-tablet-sized/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T17:36:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we inch closer to the possible announcement date for the Samsung Galaxy Z Fold 4, we also hear more rumors about the foldable smartphone. The latest rumors talk about the battery capacity and Samsung tweaking the size of the phone’s inner display.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzanne Humphries</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mesa or mesa-amber, which to use?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u9k1z5/mesa_or_mesaamber_which_to_use/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u9k1z5/mesa_or_mesaamber_which_to_use/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T17:31:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've got an old X60 Thinkpad and I'm not sure which of these packages I should be using.
 When using mesa, slop gives me this error:
 libGL error: MESA-LOADER: failed to open i915: /usr/lib/dri/i915_dri.so: cannot open shared object file: No such file or directory (search paths /usr/lib/dri, suffix _dri) libGL error: failed to load driver: i915 
 However, it seems to behave just fine.
 When using mesa-amber, it give me the error:
 No matching visuals available.
 and doesn't behave as nicely (no border around the selection, duller colors, etc.)
 For reference, the X60 has a GMA950 gpu.
    submitted by    /u/Human_Techne  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Internet spring cleaning: How to delete Instagram, Facebook and other accounts]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.mozilla.org/?p=68841</id>
        <link href="https://blog.mozilla.org/en/internet-culture/how-to-delete-instagram-facebook-online-accounts/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T17:29:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So you’ve washed your sheets and vacuumed under the couch in the name of spring cleaning. But what about your online clutter? Apps that delight, inform and keep you connected deserve room in your digital space. But if you haven’t used your Facebook account in years, or you’re looking to permanently take back some time […]
The post Internet spring cleaning: How to delete Instagram, Facebook and other accounts appeared first on The Mozilla Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kristina Bravo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to delete your Spotify account]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.mozilla.org/?p=68840</id>
        <link href="https://blog.mozilla.org/en/internet-culture/how-to-delete-spotify/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T17:29:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you want to follow in Neil Young’s footsteps or are already streaming music and podcasts through another service, deleting your stagnant Spotify account is a good idea. If you have a subscription, you’ll need to cancel that first. Once you’re ready, here’s how to delete your Spotify account. In your web browser, go to […]
The post How to delete your Spotify account appeared first on The Mozilla Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kristina Bravo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to delete your Facebook account]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.mozilla.org/?p=68872</id>
        <link href="https://blog.mozilla.org/en/internet-culture/how-to-delete-facebook/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T17:29:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Firefox, you can limit the social media giant tracking your online activities through the Facebook Container extension without deleting your Facebook account. Though, *wildly gestures at news headlines over the past couple of years*, we don’t blame you if you want to stop using the app for good. You may have even deactivated your […]
The post How to delete your Facebook account appeared first on The Mozilla Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kristina Bravo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to delete your Instagram account]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.mozilla.org/?p=68873</id>
        <link href="https://blog.mozilla.org/en/internet-culture/how-to-delete-instagram/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T17:29:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So you’ve decided to shut down your Instagram account. Maybe you want to cleanse your digital space from its parent company, Meta. Perhaps you’re tired of deleting the app only to reinstall it later. Whatever your reason, here’s how to delete your Instagram: Visit https://instagram.com/accounts/remove/request/permanent and log in, if you aren’t already logged in. You’ll […]
The post How to delete your Instagram account appeared first on The Mozilla Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kristina Bravo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to delete your Snapchat account]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.mozilla.org/?p=68874</id>
        <link href="https://blog.mozilla.org/en/internet-culture/how-to-delete-snapchat/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T17:29:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you’ve migrated to another similar social media platform, or have simply outgrown it, you may be tempted to just delete the Snapchat app from your phone and get on with it. But you’ll want to scrub your data, too. Here’s how to delete your Snapchat account from an iOS app: Click on the profile […]
The post How to delete your Snapchat account appeared first on The Mozilla Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kristina Bravo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to delete your Twitter account]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.mozilla.org/?p=68875</id>
        <link href="https://blog.mozilla.org/en/internet-culture/how-to-delete-twitter/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T17:29:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter can be a trove of information. It can also enable endless doomscrolling. If you’d rather get your news and and debate people on the latest hot take elsewhere, here’s how to delete your Twitter account from a browser: Once you’re logged in, click on more on the left-hand side of your Twitter homepage. Click […]
The post How to delete your Twitter account appeared first on The Mozilla Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kristina Bravo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to delete your Google account]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.mozilla.org/?p=68876</id>
        <link href="https://blog.mozilla.org/en/internet-culture/how-to-delete-google/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T17:29:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s share of the global search market stands at about 85%. While the tech giant will likely continue to loom large over our lives, from search to email to our calendars, we can delete inactive or unnecessary Google accounts. Here’s how to do that: Go to https://myaccount.google.com/data-and-privacy and scroll down to your data & privacy […]
The post How to delete your Google account appeared first on The Mozilla Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kristina Bravo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to delete your Amazon account]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.mozilla.org/?p=68877</id>
        <link href="https://blog.mozilla.org/en/internet-culture/how-to-delete-amazon/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T17:29:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon has had its fair share of controversies, particularly about data collection and how the retail giant treats its workers. If you’ve decided that easy access and quick deliveries aren’t worth the price anymore, here’s how to delete your Amazon account: Go to https://www.amazon.com/privacy/data-deletion. Make sure to read which Amazon services you won’t have access […]
The post How to delete your Amazon account appeared first on The Mozilla Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kristina Bravo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to delete your TikTok account]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.mozilla.org/?p=68878</id>
        <link href="https://blog.mozilla.org/en/internet-culture/how-to-delete-tiktok/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T17:29:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TikTok has exploded in popularity, surpassing Twitter and Snapchat’s combined ad revenue in February. If you’ve tried the app and decided it’s not for you, here’s how to delete your TikTok account: In the app, click the profile icon on the bottom right. Click the three-line icon on the top right. Click on settings and […]
The post How to delete your TikTok account appeared first on The Mozilla Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kristina Bravo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to delete your Venmo account]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.mozilla.org/?p=68879</id>
        <link href="https://blog.mozilla.org/en/internet-culture/how-to-delete-your-venmo-account/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T17:29:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Payment app Venmo has made it easier to split bills and pay for things without cash. But if you’ve decided to use other ways to do that, you’ll want to delete your account along with your bank information with it. You’ll first have to transfer any funds in your Venmo account to your bank account. […]
The post How to delete your Venmo account appeared first on The Mozilla Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kristina Bravo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Staking in Crypto?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=796608</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/796608/what-is-staking-in-crypto/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Proof-of-stake blockchains offer cryptocurrency investors another way to earn some extra cash. However, staking isn’t a risk-free investment: There are some things to keep in mind. Here’s how it works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>RJ Fulton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a "Super Raspberry Pi" With Framework's Mainboard]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/115745/build-a-super-raspberry-pi-with-frameworks-mainboard/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/115745/build-a-super-raspberry-pi-with-frameworks-mainboard/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T16:55:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Framework has quickly made a name for itself by creating a genuinely repairable Laptop for nearly anyone. Now the company is expanding that offering a little by pulling back. Instead of buying the whole kit, you can now purchase just the Mainboard and make a powerful “Raspberry Pi.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Hendrickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything You Need to Know About NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/111674/everything-you-need-to-know-about-nfts/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/111674/everything-you-need-to-know-about-nfts/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T16:34:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve reached a point where NFTs are unavoidable. They line the bowels of social media, turn franchises like Star Trek into “investments,” and hog advertising space during football games. Still, despite the over-saturation of NFTs, you probably have zero experience with the technology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US govt grants academics $12M to develop cyberattack defense tools]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-govt-grants-academics-12m-to-develop-cyberattack-defense-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-govt-grants-academics-12m-to-develop-cyberattack-defense-tools/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T16:33:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US Department of Energy (DOE) has announced that it will provide $12 million in funding to six university teams to develop defense and mitigation tools to protect US energy delivery systems from cyberattacks. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[how to hide the ESC character]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u9iohk/how_to_hide_the_esc_character/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u9iohk/how_to_hide_the_esc_character/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T16:29:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[how to stop showing these ESC characters.
 i am using nnn which has a in-built plugin called preview-tui
 https://i.imgur.com/DgDdr8w.png
    submitted by    /u/h4636oh  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Are The Best 'Star Wars' Day LEGO Deals for 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/115741/here-are-the-best-star-wars-day-lego-deals-for-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/115741/here-are-the-best-star-wars-day-lego-deals-for-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T16:10:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every serious Star Wars fan is looking forward to the upcoming holiday. No, not Memorial Day, silly, Star Wars Day! That’s right, May 4 is just around the corner, and with it comes a slew of deals for the movie franchise, like these cool deals from LEGO.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzanne Humphries</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[i3blocks isn't working]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u9i4a5/i3blocks_isnt_working/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u9i4a5/i3blocks_isnt_working/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T16:04:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have [brightness] and [battery] in my i3blocks.conf but it isn't appearing, only the [time] and [documentation] blocks are appearing.
 I have "status_command i3blocks" in my i3.conf
 And I have downlaoded the vivien collection of scripts
 ​
 Any help would be great, I'm ready to move to Linux just need my bar fixed up
    submitted by    /u/thinlycuta4paper  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Mute Calls By Flipping Your Android Phone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=798418</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/798418/how-to-mute-calls-by-flipping-your-android-phone/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T16:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smartphones have ended the days of slamming your phone down to end a call. If you have an Android phone, you can flip your phone to do the same thing. It’s not quite as satisfying—but still convenient.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Add This to Your Grilled Cheese for Instant Charcuterie]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lifesavvy.com/125912/add-this-to-your-grilled-cheese-for-instant-charcuterie/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lifesavvy.com/125912/add-this-to-your-grilled-cheese-for-instant-charcuterie/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T16:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are a lot of food combinations you might find strange. For example, I enjoy ranch dressing on a baked potato. Lately, though, lots of people have been adding a questionable spread to perfectly fine grilled cheese sandwiches, and to say it sounds odd is an understatement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shea Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mesa 22.1-rc1 AMD Radeon Linux Gaming Performance vs. NVIDIA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31071</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31071"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Mesa 22.1 having been branched and working its way towards release in early to mid May, it's a good time to deliver some fresh Linux gaming benchmarks on the latest GPU drivers. In this article are some reference benchmark results of various AMD Radeon graphics cards on Mesa 22.1-rc1 as of branching paired with Linux 5.17 and then benchmarked against NVIDIA's latest driver and various GeForce RTX GPUs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[App di Chat privata con crittografia e messaggi protetti e cifrati]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2015/01/app-per-comunicare-in-modo-sicuro-dal.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2015/01/app-per-comunicare-in-modo-sicuro-dal.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T15:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Se desideriamo scambiare dei messaggi sicuri sul cellulare a prova di intercettazione e di spionaggio dovremmo dimenticare la grande maggioranza delle applicazioni normali che usiamo sul telefono, incluse Facebook, Messenger e WhatsApp.
Anche se la maggior parte di queste app ha fornito una crittografia end-to-end, molti dati viaggiano su server non accessibili e non sappiamo se essi possono...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I do not recognize the scanner at the first time]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u9ht9z/i_do_not_recognize_the_scanner_at_the_first_time/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u9ht9z/i_do_not_recognize_the_scanner_at_the_first_time/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T15:51:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone. I have connected an HP ENVY 4500 multifunction device that works without problems both for printing and scanning.
 If I want to print something it does it the first time and without any problems. If I want to scan something, it always asks me for a password (and I don't care, since I'm the only one using this PC) and it never recognizes the device the first time. I need to turn my HP ENVY off and on and then yes, it recognizes it right away, and I can scan without any problems.
 I have cups.service and cups.socket enabled, as well as added my user to the sys group, apart from the wheel, but I don't really know why it doesn't recognize the computer at first and asks me for a password, something that doesn't happen with other distro: Manjaro, Endeavouros or openSUSE Tumbleweed.
 Any help to solve this problem will be very welcome, thanks. Regards, Juan.
    submitted by    /u/jbellas  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The U.K. Will Let You Watch TV While the Car Drives (With Limitations)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/115740/the-u-k-will-let-you-watch-tv-while-the-car-drives-with-limitations/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/115740/the-u-k-will-let-you-watch-tv-while-the-car-drives-with-limitations/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T15:30:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine being able to watch TV behind the wheel of a vehicle without breaking the law. It sounds dangerous, but with the rise in electric and autonomous cars, that’s exactly what’s possible, thanks to a new law passed in the U.K. by the country’s Department for Transportation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Troubleshoot OneDrive Sync Issues]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=472791</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15238667/troubleshoot-onedrive-sync-issues"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the great things about OneDrive is being able to sync your files for easy access wherever you need them on a wide variety of devices. While most of the time, you can set it and forget it, this doesn’t always work as smoothly as you’d hope. If you discover your files aren’t syncing properly, you’ll need to troubleshoot OneDrive sync issues to discover the root cause before syncing can go back to normal. 
   

Content

Signs of OneDrive Sync Issues
1. Check for Error Codes
2. Verify Your Storage
3. Close and Reopen
4. Ensure Your Account is Linked
5. Update Windows and OneDrive
6. Move a File or Folder
7. Ensure Files Meet OneDrive Requirements
8. Verify Account Access
9. Prevent Network Bandwidth Restrictions
10. Temporarily Turn Off Antivirus and Firewalls
11. Whitelist OneDrive
12. Repair OneDrive
13. Reset OneDrive
14. Uninstall OneDrive
How to Stop OneDrive Syncing Permanently
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Crystal Crowder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[App Android Windows 11: come installarle e utilizzarle]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=App-Android-Windows-11-come-installarle-e-utilizzarle_24429</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=App-Android-Windows-11-come-installarle-e-utilizzarle_24429"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T15:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Come abbiamo messo in evidenza in tanti nostri articoli finalmente Windows 11 introduce la possibilità di installare ed eseguire 'nativamente' le app Android.L'aggettivo 'nativo' va un po’ preso con le dovute cautele: Windows 11 supporta un componente software chiamato Windows Subsystem for Android (WSA) che come WSL, usato per eseguire Linux in Windows, si appoggia alla virtualizzazione di Microsoft Hyper-V. È la virtualizzazione a essere 'nativa' nel senso che le applicazioni Android verranno eseguite direttamente sull'hardware del sistema ospitante (host).
App Android Windows 11: il modo più veloce per installare WSA
 Al momento in cui scriviamo questo articolo WSA non è stato ancora aggiunto nella versione stabile di Windows 11.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[T-Mobile confirms Lapsus$ hackers breached internal systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/t-mobile-confirms-lapsus-hackers-breached-internal-systems/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/t-mobile-confirms-lapsus-hackers-breached-internal-systems/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T15:19:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[T-Mobile has confirmed that the Lapsus$ extortion gang breached its network "several weeks ago" using stolen credentials and gained access to internal systems. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add Section and Slide Zooms in Microsoft PowerPoint]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=794843</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/794843/how-to-add-section-and-slide-zooms-in-microsoft-powerpoint/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T15:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to move to a different slide or section in your presentation, you can easily add a link on your slide. But by using a Section or Slide Zoom in PowerPoint, you can make that move look professional.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia GPU set up.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u9gm5y/nvidia_gpu_set_up/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u9gm5y/nvidia_gpu_set_up/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T14:57:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi. 
 I usually use proprietary nvidia drivers at the moment it is (510.60.02). I use rtx 2080ti
 To install I use DKMS:
 sudo pacman -S nvidia-dkms nvidia-utils lib32-nvidia-utils nvidia-settings vulkan-icd-loader lib32-vulkan-icd-loader lib32-opencl-nvidia opencl-nvidia libxnvctrl
 Then:
 sudo mkinitcpio -P
 What is the problem:
 I noticed that when watching videos (for example, YouTube), my GPU is not loaded at all, but the processor is loaded.
 In this case, the browser itself starts to work more slowly when the video is running.
 This can be seen in scrolling or animations. (Like 30fps, lmao)
 With the video running, it is also noticeable how the system itself becomes slower, dragging windows and resizing them occurs as in 30fps.
 As soon as I put the video on pause - the problem does not appear.
 ​
 Please help me with this problem. Do I need to install some packages for the system to work correctly?
 ​
 pc configuration:
 AMD Ryzen 7 2700X (16) @ 4.075GHz
 NVIDIA GeForce RTX 2080 Ti
 RAM 32GB
    submitted by    /u/neoHand  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese hackers behind most zero-day exploits during 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/chinese-hackers-behind-most-zero-day-exploits-during-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/chinese-hackers-behind-most-zero-day-exploits-during-2021/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T14:34:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat analysts report that zero-day vulnerability exploitation is on the rise with Chinese hackers using most of them in attacks last year. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[tty stuck on starting version screen: wifi-menu]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u9g2ba/tty_stuck_on_starting_version_screen_wifimenu/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u9g2ba/tty_stuck_on_starting_version_screen_wifimenu/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T14:32:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Output message:
 \[FAILED\] Failed to Start Automatic?enerated profile by wifi-menu 
 When I look into netctl wifi-menu in other tty, it says I'm connected to the wifi. Not sure what is going wrong here.
    submitted by    /u/Baz_Morty  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come collegare disco di rete al FRITZ!Box]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/04/come-collegare-disco-di-rete-al-fritzbox.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/04/come-collegare-disco-di-rete-al-fritzbox.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T14:25:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I modem FRITZ!Box sono a tutti gli effetti i migliori modem che possiamo utilizzare per le connessioni Internet, visto l'elevato numero di funzioni avanzate che si portano dietro e agli aggiornamenti costanti a cui vengono sottoposti per mantenerli sempre efficienti. Tra le funzioni più interessanti del FRITZ!Box troviamo sicuramente la condivisione del disco in rete, che permette di trasformare...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Atlassian fixes critical Jira authentication bypass vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/atlassian-fixes-critical-jira-authentication-bypass-vulnerability/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/atlassian-fixes-critical-jira-authentication-bypass-vulnerability/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T14:05:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Atlassian has published a security advisory to alert that its Jira and Jira Service Management products are affected by a critical authentication bypass vulnerability in Seraph, the company's web application security framework. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Tripods of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=790697</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/790697/the-best-tripods-of-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T14:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A tripod is one of the single best investments in gear a photographer can make. But how do you find the best tripod for you? Check out these picks for some solid places to start.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Bogna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Upper third of screen lagging on Tuxedo Infinitybook Pro 14]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u9f4g8/upper_third_of_screen_lagging_on_tuxedo/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u9f4g8/upper_third_of_screen_lagging_on_tuxedo/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T13:48:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I just recieved my first Tuxedo laptop and of course instantly flattened the drive and installed arch. During the install process, it already became aparent that the upper third of the screen wasn't refreshing properly.
 After setting up KDE with sddm, the issue became much more visible (because you can simply see it easier in the gui).
 I never had issues of that kind. On my other system, I'm running on NVidia with a weird uwqhd resolution and everything works fine. The Infinitybook has an Intel Iris Xe and 2880x1800 display. I've tried the fallback to the modesetting driver as stated on the Intel page in the wiki but didn't get X to launch without the xf86-video-intel package installed.
 Has anyone had similar issues? It's the first time I'm tinkering with Intel APU stuff so I don't even know what I'm really dealing with. Also, the point that the issue is also visible in the tty confuses me.
 Edit: I was able to get the issue fixed now! Thank you so much to /u/w0330 for pointing the solution out. Everything works like a charm now, in tty and KDE.
 i915.enable_psr=0 as kernel parameter was the correct solution but somehow it didn't work in the beginning, I guess because I messed something up.
 If you encounter the same issue using Intel Iris Xe graphics, try setting the given parameter, don't use xf86-video-intel and don't provide any additional launch information for xorg.
    submitted by    /u/ViaRegia95  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>