<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-05-31T01:58:43.921Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Which package owns /boot/vmlinuz-linux?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v1egwh/which_package_owns_bootvmlinuzlinux/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v1egwh/which_package_owns_bootvmlinuzlinux/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T01:03:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[pacman -Qo found no packages that claim it. There does not seem to be an install script for package linux either. So who copies the /usr/lib/modules/version/vmlinuz to /boot?
    submitted by    /u/notnullnone  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[f2fs_gc occupies 100 per cent of a core with the 5.18 kernel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v1e66x/f2fs_gc_occupies_100_per_cent_of_a_core_with_the/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v1e66x/f2fs_gc_occupies_100_per_cent_of_a_core_with_the/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T00:47:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[if you have the same problem please give your contribution here:
 ​
 https://bugs.archlinux.org/task/74906
 ​
 and here:
 ​
 https://bugzilla.kernel.org/show_bug.cgi?id=216050
 ​
 thanks!
    submitted by    /u/guiodic76  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ping takes a long time, slow first connection to pages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v1dted/ping_takes_a_long_time_slow_first_connection_to/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v1dted/ping_takes_a_long_time_slow_first_connection_to/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T00:27:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After I booted up my internet is behaving very weirdly, my first connection to any website takes a long time to load and if I try to `ping google.com` on my terminal it takes at least 15s to get any response.
 After I connect to a page, my internet seems to be back to normal for that webpage. I did a speed test and my internet seems to be normal (300mb/s). 
 Also booted into an old HD with windows and connections is normal with it, so I guess it has nothing to do with anything physical.
 I'm trying to do a system update to see if it can sort the problem out but I'm getting timeout when trying to run `pacman -Syu`, I really don't know what to do
    submitted by    /u/papoti_  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dual Boot Menu Not Showing in Windows? Here’s How to Fix It]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=483178</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15338536/fix-windows-dual-boot-menu-not-showing"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is the dual boot menu missing when you boot up Windows? You’re likely dealing with an incorrectly configured boot manager. Luckily, this is a common problem with newly created dual boots and is easy to fix.
    
We bring you a detailed guide to help sort out this problem by tweaking a few Windows settings.
   

Content

Why Dual Boot Menu Isn’t Showing
1. Use Command Prompt to Enable Boot Menu
2. Use EasyBCD to Configure Boot Menu
3. Make the Boot Disk Partition Active
4. Use Startup and Recovery to Configure the Default OS
5. Disable Windows Fast Start
6. Restore Boot Menu with the System Configuration Tool 
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}       
Why Dual Boot Menu Isn’t Showing
    
After you install a second OS on your Windows PC, you should be able to switch seamlessly between the two using the boot menu. Unfortunately, the boot menu may not show for one of the following reasons:
    
Fast startup is enabled, so the PC boots directly into the default... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Kanyoro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weird Audit Messages and NVMe Errors after the latest kernel update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v1d2l8/weird_audit_messages_and_nvme_errors_after_the/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v1d2l8/weird_audit_messages_and_nvme_errors_after_the/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T23:46:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is anyone having audit messages painted at their screen and some NVMe or PCIe bus error messages painted over their screens after the latest kernel update?
 I have two laptops running arch, one was using the kernel version 5.17.9 and the other laptop which I was installing Arch fresh today with the latest kernel 5.18.1. 
 For the new laptop, I saw some weird audit messages and PCIe bus errors printing on the screen every few seconds. I thought it was my laptop's motherboard problem. 
 Now that I upgraded my old laptop to the latest kernel, I started to see same effects taking place. I had to downgrade to get rid of them.
 Is anyone having the same experience with the latest kernel?
    submitted by    /u/tyson_the_13th  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accidentally removed ca-certificates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v1bpay/accidentally_removed_cacertificates/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v1bpay/accidentally_removed_cacertificates/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T22:33:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi eveyone. I wanted to post that because I felt very dumb for doing this but I’m proud to solve this by myself.
 I recently noticed there is an update for ca-certificates-mozilla. I thought it is a package installed because I installed and uninstalled firefox before. I tried to delete it and pacman said ca-certificates package requires that. I blindly removed both. And my network connection lost as it should be.
 I searched forums on my phone but I couldn’t get any solution worked for my case. Luckily i had an arch iso and i flashed it. I boot arch install image and mounted my root device to /mnt directory. I copied ca-certificates files to my drive and rebooted to my system. Then I was able to upgrade system. After that I installed ca-certificates-mozilla package. Finally my internet connection works well again.
 I wanted to share my experience about it so maybe this would be helpful some fools like me.
    submitted by    /u/Elagoht  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux 5.19 Allows Using TRIM To Zero-Out Sectors On Supported eMMC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-MMC</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-MMC"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T22:30:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week the (e)MMC storage new feature code landed into the Linux 5.19 merge window...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[only one account, security issues?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v1bkmu/only_one_account_security_issues/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v1bkmu/only_one_account_security_issues/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T22:27:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm a noob I'm using arch for a month or so and this is the third time that i reinstalling arch. First time i sucked at setting up and installing all sorts of packages. Second time i did follow the main arch tutorials for the install did go much and much better and the experience was way slicker, but i updated plasma and accidentally reinstalling linux-utils because I thought you needed it for the swapon functions but that was already preinstalled. Did a swap off and swapon to test the functions and the next boot it wouldn't start anymore. The boot hangs on unable to start modules or failed to start modules, tried for a hour chrooting inside of arch to fix it but i wasn't able to fix the system or at least installing a package from chroot :$ or use systemctl. 
 So this is the third time reinstalling arch I'm on the verge to add a user and following the tutorial of kde-plasma but this is what I don't understand:
 I read a lot of tutorials about "it's a bad idea to run for example kde as root user. Steps that need to be done according to the tutorials. 1. Create a user with home dir or not 2. install sudo 3. Add user to the sudoers file. 
 But all the users inside of the sudoers file have the same privilege as the root user, only a different password. That seems unsafe for me. 
 Also yay needs to be installed on the second user account, and can install packages stand alone. 
 Isn't there a better way to all of this?
 To make it that the second user only can acces all the necessary stuff but can't use fdisk, pacman, yay, etc.
 But kde needs to have some acces to adjust themes and so on. 
 Thanks for helping and reading my post :)
    submitted by    /u/Pure_Pasifist  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Attento, c'è un virus in quel contratto di lavoro! Storia di come stavo per essere hackerato con un .zip .doc .scr (video)]]></title>
        <id>3582|20220531000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/youtube-42/attento-c-virus-quel-contratto-lavoro-storia-come-stavo-essere-hackerato-.zip-.doc-.scr-video-3582"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[La settimana scorsa sono stato contatto per una apparente opportunità lavorativa, per iniziale la quale avrei dovuto firmare un contratto. Ma mi sono reso conto di cosa stesse realmente accadendo appena in tempo: il file che avrei dovuto firmare conteneva un malware, che avrebbe consentito al criminale di ottenere pieno controllo del mio PC, accesso a tutti i file, alla mail e agli account web. In questo video-articolo racconto la mia storia, nella speranza che possa essere utile ad altri e prevenire raggiri simili
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Best Spotify Alternatives for Music Streaming]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=post-ideas&amp;p=188770</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/5841231/best-spotify-alternatives"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spotify is often seen as the best music streaming service, but it’s facing some serious competition. There are a variety of music apps like Spotify to give you an endless supply of music. If you’re ready to try something new, check out some of the best Spotify alternatives to see which one fits your needs the best.
   

Content

1. Qobuz
2. YouTube Music
3. Apple Music
4. Pandora Radio
5. Deezer
6. Tidal
7. Amazon Music Unlimited
Honorable Mentions
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Change Your Username on Snapchat, Spotify, Fortnite, and More
    
1. Qobuz
    
Qobuz is relatively new in comparison to the other Spotify alternatives on this list, but it already boasts over 80 million tracks, with most in hi-res audio. You can even buy digital downloads and physical CDs directly... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Crystal Crowder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best options for obfuscated ssh on Arch?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v19zej/best_options_for_obfuscated_ssh_on_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v19zej/best_options_for_obfuscated_ssh_on_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T21:09:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I think I'm looking for something like this:
 GitHub - zinglau/obfuscated-openssh-patches: Patches for adding handshake obfuscation to OpenSSH
 Any suggestions? Ideally something in the Arch repos (including AUR) that has a maintainer.
 I use an OpenSSH reverse tunnel (to my own VPS) and Firefox's socks5 proxy configuration to browse the Internet. My goal is to obfuscate the fact that I'm using a proxy or ssh tunnel. I'm not sure what the best approach would be, but since I already use an SSH reverse tunnel, I thought I would look into obfuscated-openssh. I don't find anything about it on the Arch website. I guess there must be some other more popular way to do this.
 I don't use a VPN because I need application-specific proxying.
    submitted by    /u/cowsface  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NixOS 22.05 Released With New Graphical Installer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=NixOS-22.05-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=NixOS-22.05-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T21:05:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NixOS as the Linux distribution built around the unique Nix package manager is out with its first release of the year...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Oil-Cooled PCs Aren’t Popular Anymore]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=769887</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/769887/why-oil-cooled-pcs-arent-popular-anymore/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At one point, PC performance enthusiasts had the idea to cool a computer by immersing its components in mineral oil—and it worked! Yet today no one’s doing it anymore, so what happened to these awesome submerged “fish tank” PCs?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sydney Butler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vodafone plans carrier-level user tracking for targeted ads]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/vodafone-plans-carrier-level-user-tracking-for-targeted-ads/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/vodafone-plans-carrier-level-user-tracking-for-targeted-ads/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T20:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vodafone is piloting a new advertising ID system called TrustPid, which will work as a persistent user tracker at the mobile Internet Service Provider (ISP) level. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[11 Things to Check When Buying a Used iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=774408</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/774408/what-to-check-when-buying-a-used-iphone/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Used iPhones are always in hot demand, and they’re a good option if you’re looking to save some money on an Apple smartphone. Like any second-hand purchase, there are some things you should check before you hand over your money.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Laptop struggling to restart after a weird shut down.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v17rhh/laptop_struggling_to_restart_after_a_weird_shut/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v17rhh/laptop_struggling_to_restart_after_a_weird_shut/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T19:25:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting my laptop runs a black console with a long lists of errors, it doesn’t stop and I can’t find a way to reset everything.
    submitted by    /u/douhan_wicht  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save $30 on a JBL Clip 4 Portable Bluetooth Speaker]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=493793</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15338200/jbl-clip-4-portable-bluetooth-speaker"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you enjoying a Memorial Day outing right now but wish you could have brought your tunes with you? The perfect choice would be a JBL Clip 4 Portable Bluetooth Speaker: it’s small, waterproof, and clips onto anything. But the best part of this Bluetooth speaker is that you can get it now for $30 off.
    
Although this is a small, portable speaker, you’ll still get rich audio and a hitting base – even though it fits in your hand. You can wirelessly stream your favorite music from Bluetooth-enabled devices, including your phone or tablet.
    

    
The construction of the JBL Clip 4 Portable Bluetooth Speaker includes a redesigned carabiner clip that attaches to nearly everything for the ultimate in portability. It clips onto a belt, strap, or buckle, providing extra protection. It ships with a USB-C cable, quick start guide, warranty card, and safety sheet.
    
Bring your speaker with you to the beach or pool, a picnic, on a hike, or a bike ride, as it’s waterproof... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Laptop struggling to restart after a weird shut down.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v17ijq/laptop_struggling_to_restart_after_a_weird_shut/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v17ijq/laptop_struggling_to_restart_after_a_weird_shut/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T19:13:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/douhan_wicht  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Third Cutest 'Star Wars' Droid Will Come to LEGO]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119402/the-third-cutest-star-wars-droid-will-come-to-lego/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119402/the-third-cutest-star-wars-droid-will-come-to-lego/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T19:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the world of cute Star Wars droids, the order goes R2D2, BB8, and then BD-1. C3PO is awesome but not cute. And if you agree with that list, you’ll be happy to hear that it looks like LEGO will release a BD-1 set.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Hendrickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Delete Folders in Gmail]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=805803</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/805803/how-to-delete-folders-in-gmail/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gmail’s folders (also known as labels) let you put relevant emails together. If you don’t need one or more of these folders, it’s easy to delete them from Gmail’s web, iPhone, and iPad versions. We’ll show you how to do just that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Italy warns organizations to brace for incoming DDoS attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/italy-warns-organizations-to-brace-for-incoming-ddos-attacks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/italy-warns-organizations-to-brace-for-incoming-ddos-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T18:10:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Computer Security Incident Response Team in Italy issued an urgent alert yesterday to raise awareness about the high risk of cyberattacks against national bodies and organizations on Monday. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is an Airdrop in Crypto?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=802954</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/802954/what-is-an-airdrop-in-crypto/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T18:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchains and cryptocurrencies continue to challenge traditional ideas around finance. Project developers have leveraged these innovations by introducing new ways to market and advertise. Airdrops are one of these recent developments that help promote cryptocurrencies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>RJ Fulton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FlexiSpot BackSupport Office Chair BS10 Review]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=492174</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15338103/flexispot-backsupport-office-chair-bs10"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T17:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well-known for their standard office chairs, FlexiSpot also makes a range of more specialized business and home office furniture. Many office workers prize back support, as when you spend much of the day sitting quietly in a chair, it can play havoc with your back and spine health. It only gets worse as you age. This review takes a look at the FlexiSpot BackSupport Office Chair BS10 to see how it helps with such a problem.
    
Pain in the Neck
    
The FlexiSpot BackSupport Office Chair BS10 is an office chair meant for long periods of sitting. All office chairs are rated depending on the supposed average durations they will be used, so casual chairs for people in reception areas are obviously not designed for long durations. Standard office worker chairs are designed for quite a few hours – but not all day. Executive chairs are designed for entire days of sitting. This is all very logical and as you would expect.
    

    
The FlexiSpot BS10 is definitely in the latter category, with specialized back support... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phil South</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wyze Air Purifier Review: Powerful with Great Filter Options]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118980/wyze-air-purifier-review-powerful-with-great-filter-options/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118980/wyze-air-purifier-review-powerful-with-great-filter-options/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T17:13:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Between allergens, pollution, and wildfires, there’s just no good reason not to own an air purifier at this point. And if you’re looking for one with a powerful array of filters and a lightweight design, Wyze’s impressive new Air Purifier is pretty hard to beat!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzanne Humphries</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[keyboard and mouse not working]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v14r3g/keyboard_and_mouse_not_working/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v14r3g/keyboard_and_mouse_not_working/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T17:05:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I setup an LUKS fs as the root... When I boot the system, the keyboard works on the grub and bios but when arch starts I can't even use the keyboard to type the encryption password to decrypt the LUKS fs. 
 I was doing a vanilla arch install and in the process by mistake deleted the '/etc/default/grub' idk if this has anything to do with the issue tho...
 Can someone please help me on how to fix this... And could you also send a copy of your /etc/default/grub if you can?
 Thanks so much in advance!
    submitted by    /u/nicholas_tesla_rocks  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Update Microsoft Outlook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=806546</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/806546/how-to-update-microsoft-outlook/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T17:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To receive the latest features and patch existing bugs, update your Microsoft Outlook app to the latest version. You can do this for free on all of the compatible platforms, including desktop, Android, iPhone, and iPad. We’ll show you how to do that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SuperH4 GCC toolchain]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v13t9u/superh4_gcc_toolchain/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v13t9u/superh4_gcc_toolchain/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T16:20:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Where I can obtain GCC SuperH4 toolchain? And what's target name for SH4 in GCC config? I didn't figured it out
    submitted by    /u/nikolaytihonov  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fare la foto scansione ai biglietti da visita (App Android e iPhone)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2014/07/fare-la-foto-scansione-ai-biglietti-da.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2014/07/fare-la-foto-scansione-ai-biglietti-da.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T16:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quando si possiede un iPhone o un qualsiasi smartphone Android moderno, non c'è alcuna necessità di conservare tutti i biglietti da visita cartacei in un cassetto o in un porta documenti. Grazie ad alcune semplici applicazioni possiamo scansionare ogni biglietto da visita in modo tale da poter conservare tutte le informazioni in esso scritte in modo ordinato e facile da ritrovare.

 Nella guida...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google quietly bans deepfake training projects on Colab]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/google-quietly-bans-deepfake-training-projects-on-colab/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/google-quietly-bans-deepfake-training-projects-on-colab/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T16:13:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has quietly banned deepfake projects on its Colaboratory (Colab) service, putting an end to the large-scale utilization of the platform's resources for this purpose. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Crop Videos on Android]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=807767</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/807767/how-to-crop-videos-on-android/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T16:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We typically think of cropping as a tool for photo editing, but it can be used on videos, too. Sometimes the original aspect ratio doesn’t fit what you want. Thankfully, it’s pretty easy to crop videos on Android.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SSD PCIe 5.0: controller Phison permette di arrivare fino a 12 GB/s]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=SSD-PCIe-50-controller-Phison-permette-di-arrivare-fino-a-12-GB-s_24582</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=SSD-PCIe-50-controller-Phison-permette-di-arrivare-fino-a-12-GB-s_24582"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T15:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Già dallo scorso anno Phison ha iniziato a parlare del suo nuovo controller per le unità SSD PCIe 5.0 ad alte prestazioni PS5026-E26.L'azienda ha anche rivelato che le unità a stato solido più performanti potranno richiedere un sistema di dissipazione attivo.La società, che fornisce i controller utilizzati in molti modelli di unità SSD dei vari produttori (tra cui Samsung e Western Digital), ha mostrato i risultati dei test condotti con CrystalDiskMark spiegando che le unità PCIe 5.0 possono raggiungere i 12/10 GB/s in lettura/scrittura sequenziali. Curiosamente i valori indicati da Phison risultano inferiori a quanto mostrato in precedenza dall'azienda al CES 2022 anche se adesso i risultati si riferiscono a una vera e propria unità.

Nel caso delle operazioni di lettura/scrittura random 4K i valori ottenuti sono un po’ più bassi (fino a 5,4-4,8 GB/s) perché si fa riferimento ai due casi estremi ovvero alla situazione in cui si sfrutta tutto il parallelismo o a quella in cui c'è solo un processo attivo.Come curiosità va detto che l'unità usata da Phison per i test ha un formato M.2 2580: ciò significa che è 3 mm più larga della solita versione M.2 2280.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cannot delete partition in arch install environment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v12vou/cannot_delete_partition_in_arch_install/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v12vou/cannot_delete_partition_in_arch_install/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T15:36:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After formatting my hdd, if I run 'lsblk -f' it outputs 'sda2 lvm2' which i think was the swap space for my old system, how do I remove it, I searched around on the wiki but couldn't find any entry about it.
    submitted by    /u/Megareaper85  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Windows 11 for ARM and Who Is It For?]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=490202</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15337875/windows11-for-arm"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ARM computers are now more popular than ever. So it’s no surprise that you can get Windows 11 for ARM as an alternative to the traditional version most people use. Both of these versions of Windows 11 look and feel the same. However, there are major differences under the hood that bring major advantages and compromises to the table.
   

Content

ARM Vs. x86 Computers
Windows 11 for ARM in a Nutshell
How Do Non-ARM Windows Apps Run
You Can't Buy Windows 11 for ARM (Yet)
Who Should Use Windows 11 for ARM
Not Ready for Primetime

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Install Windows 11 on a Raspberry Pi 4
    
ARM Vs. x86 Computers
    
Windows 11 for ARM can only run on ARM computers. In contrast regular Windows 11 can only run on x86 (specifically x86-64) computers.
  ... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sydney Butler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You May Need to Replace Your Old Kindle Soon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118964/you-may-need-to-replace-your-old-kindle-soon/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118964/you-may-need-to-replace-your-old-kindle-soon/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T15:23:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re still holding on to an old Kindle, you may want to replace it soon. Amazon is now emailing customers to warn that select Kindles, specifically five very old models, will lose access to the Amazon eBook store on August 17th of 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Problems mounting ZFS root pool on boot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v12d9j/problems_mounting_zfs_root_pool_on_boot/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v12d9j/problems_mounting_zfs_root_pool_on_boot/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T15:12:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, I followed this tutorial for a ZFS boot pool (on a LUKS) and a ZFS root pool with native encryption. https://openzfs.github.io/openzfs-docs/Getting%20Started/Arch%20Linux/index.html The tutorial itself worked out fine and my arch is running properly. The only thing is, whenever I reboot, I'm dropped into an emergency shell because it could not mount the root dataset automatically. The exact message is: filesystem 'ZFS=rpool/ROOT/default' cannot be mounted, unable to open dataset.When I execute the following commands in the emergency shell it still finishes to boot and I can use my system as usual:
  zpool import -R /new_root rpool zfs load-key rpool zfs mount rpool/ROOT/default zfs mount -a exit 
 After trying multiple suspected solutions, it still doesn't work. The fixes I've tried so far are:
  
do not use root=ZFS=rpool/ROOT/default but root:ZFS=rpool/ROOT/default suggested here 
 The result was, that the error changed and it complained about missing NFS in the emergency shell even though I don't use an NFS mounts
 
 do not use root=ZFS=rpool/ROOT/default but zfs=rpool/ROOT/default in the linxu in grub 
 I'm still dropped into the emergency shell, but the error messaged changed to zfs_mount_at(): encryption key not loaded. I can export/import rpool and even manually load it's key and mount it, but the boot process does not recover after manually mounting the dataset
 
  
I'm no ZFS or Grub expert and now I don't know how to continue. Any ideas?
 thanks
    submitted by    /u/Prestigious_Yam_1642  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Nigerians arrested for malware-assisted financial crimes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/three-nigerians-arrested-for-malware-assisted-financial-crimes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/three-nigerians-arrested-for-malware-assisted-financial-crimes/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T15:07:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Interpol has announced the arrest of three Nigerian men in Lagos, who are suspected of using remote access trojans (RATs) to reroute financial transactions and steal account credentials. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NetworkManager: Ipv6 errors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v128kg/networkmanager_ipv6_errors/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v128kg/networkmanager_ipv6_errors/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T15:06:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[```
 sudo journctl -u NetworkManager
 ...
 May 30 09:51:59 1337 NetworkManager[499]: <warn> [1653918719.7647] platform-linux: do-add-ip6-address[4: fe80::c2b0:7b0b:4420:320a]: failure 13 (Permission denied)
 May 30 09:53:29 1337 NetworkManager[499]: <warn> [1653918809.8212] ipv6ll[06195b9399eef6b4,ifindex=4]: changed: no IPv6 link local address to retry after Duplicate Address Detection failures (back off) ```
 Today, I started using NetworkManager to replace iwd. I've been getting these errors and I have no idea where to start to get rid of them.
 I'm able to connect to wifi just fine though.
    submitted by    /u/dominic_l  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IINA video player for macOS now supports OpenSubtitles, HDR, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178850</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/05/30/whats-new-in-the-iina-1-3-0-update/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T15:03:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The IINA video player for macOS has been updated to version 1.3.0. This is the first update for the popular app in over a year. What's new in IINA 1.3.0 Last year, […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post IINA video player for macOS now supports OpenSubtitles, HDR, and more appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create an Interactive Story in Google Slides]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=804872</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/804872/interactive-story-google-slides/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T15:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Interactive stories are popular for both kids and adults these days. Whether a game or a book, you determine the journey and the outcome with the choices you make. With Google Slides, you can make your own interactive story.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SD-WAN: cos'è e perché è sempre più utile in azienda]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=SD-WAN-cos-e-e-perche-e-sempre-piu-utile-in-azienda_24581</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=SD-WAN-cos-e-e-perche-e-sempre-piu-utile-in-azienda_24581"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Con le aziende che ricorrono sempre più spesso allo smart working o comunque a schemi di lavoro ibrido, la commistione tra le risorse disponibili in locale e quelle fornite in cloud è cosa all'ordine del giorno.Fare in modo che le risorse dell'azienda siano accessibili sia tramite l'infrastruttura locale (on-premise) che da remoto pone sfide importanti in termini di gestione degli utenti e sicurezza. Questi problematiche diventano ancora più delicate quando l'azienda condivide i suoi dati e i suoi asset in tutto o in parte sul cloud permettendo il collegamento di dipendenti, collaboratori, partner, fornitori da più sedi fisicamente separate l'una dall'altra.La tecnologia SD-WAN (Software-defined WAN) aiuta a stabilire connessioni remote sicure con la rete dell'impresa, indipendentemente dalla sua struttura e se essa si serva o meno di risorse cloud.Lo schema tradizionale basato sull'utilizzo di router si limita semplicemente a consentire l'instradamento del traffico in base agli indirizzi TCP/IP e alle ACL (access control list).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Le migliori alternative ad Office da usare su Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/05/le-migliori-alternative-ad-office-da.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/05/le-migliori-alternative-ad-office-da.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T14:33:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I programmi più utilizzati sui computer sono senza ombra di dubbio quelli inclusi nella suite Microsoft Office: Word, Excel e PowerPoint. Questi programmi sono disponibili a pagamento e girano solo su Windows e su Mac: nonostante gli appelli fatti negli anni passati dalla comunità di appassionati Microsoft non ha mai voluto fornire supporto ufficiale alle distribuzioni GNU/Linux, limitandone in...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Microsoft Office zero-day used in attacks to execute PowerShell]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-microsoft-office-zero-day-used-in-attacks-to-execute-powershell/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-microsoft-office-zero-day-used-in-attacks-to-execute-powershell/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T14:23:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security researchers have discovered a new Microsoft Office zero-day vulnerability that is being used in attacks to execute malicious PowerShell commands via Microsoft Diagnostic Tool (MSDT) simply by opening a Word document. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Ilascu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Fitness Trackers of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=800000</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/800000/best-fitness-tracker/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T14:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A fitness tracker can help you get in shape by providing data about your physical activities, heart health, recovery, and more. But the number of choices can make it confusing to select one. We’ve handpicked the best fitness trackers to help.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gaurav Shukla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[L'ideatore di Cydia fa causa ad Apple per presunte pratiche anticoncorrenziali]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=L-ideatore-di-Cydia-fa-causa-ad-Apple-per-presunte-pratiche-anticoncorrenziali_22266</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=L-ideatore-di-Cydia-fa-causa-ad-Apple-per-presunte-pratiche-anticoncorrenziali_22266"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T13:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tutti coloro che da anni utilizzano gli Apple iPhone si ricorderanno certamente di Cydia, uno store online alternativo a quello della Mela accessibile da coloro che effettuavano il jailbreaking dei loro dispositivi.La società guidata da Tim Cook ha da sempre strenuamente osteggiato la pratica del jailbreaking presentandola come pericolosa dal punto di vista della sicurezza. In tutte le versioni di iOS sono quindi state applicate contromisure per prevenire il jailbreaking.Seppur il jailbreaking dei dispositivi iOS sia tornato di maggiore attualità rispetto al passato, le crescenti difficoltà incontrate nel corso del tempo al fine di rimuovere le restrizioni software imposte da Apple ha di fatto portato alla fine progetti 'alternativi'.Cydia esiste ancora oggi ma non è neppure lontanamente paragonabile a ciò che era alcuni anni fa al massimo del suo 'splendore': secondo alcune stime tra il 2011 e il 2012 Cydia avrebbe raccolto qualcosa come 10 milioni di dollari, business che in forza delle politiche applicate da Apple non è più possibile.A dicembre 2020 l'ideatore di Cydia, Jay 'Saurik' Freeman, ha quindi deciso di fare causa ad Apple per presunte pratiche anticoncorrenziali.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protecting Your Gadgets From Solar Flares]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/113863/protecting-your-gadgets-from-solar-flares/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/113863/protecting-your-gadgets-from-solar-flares/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T13:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A large solar flare frying all of Earth’s electronic devices and sending us back to the stone age sounds like the plot of a bad science fiction movie—but it could happen. Luckily, protecting your electronics from solar flares and electromagnetic pulses (EMPs) is quite simple.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McQuilling</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is a PVM, and Why Do Retro Gamers Want Them?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=801908</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/801908/what-is-a-pvm-professional-video-monitor/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T13:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CRT (Cathode Ray Tube) displays have several major advantages over modern flat-panel screens, making them popular among certain gamers. Within the hallowed halls of CRT fandom, the PVM (Professional Video Monitor) is the holy grail of retro image quality.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sydney Butler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can someone help me understand network bridges (pref. using systemd-networkd)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0zkmn/can_someone_help_me_understand_network_bridges/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0zkmn/can_someone_help_me_understand_network_bridges/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T12:54:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've never been a network guy. I can't seem to figure out how to work this in order to accomplish my goals. I've read through several tutorials, including Arch Wiki, but still manage to screw it up. Here's what I'm after:
  
Create bridge with static IP to use with Home Assistant.
 Configure networking to make Barrier work.
 Be able to use Internet with proper DHCP.
 Be able to use SMB for fast file sharing.
  
So far I started out using dhcpcd to handle domain resolving and got SMB working quite well (connecting with netbios name). I then was able to stop using dhcpcd in favor of systemd-resolved. Then I tried bridging... 1st attempt ended in my ethernet device (eno1) being enslaved by bridge (br0) but unable to use internet (DNS issue). I managed to fix that, kind of, and maybe had a static IP? (hard to tell.. think DHCP for eno1 was above static IP config for br0 but it kind of worked.. static IP was visible, no gateway showing in Windows VM for bridge, internet worked sort of -- hit or miss DNS resolution. Previous SMB mapping failed but assuming same problem). br0 seems to always say "configuring" when I run networkctl. eno1 sometimes enslaved, sometimes routable (sometimes configured, sometimes configuring). 
 I really don't understand this stuff. I just want all 4 list items above to work properly :/
    submitted by    /u/profile_this  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome non risponde, è lento o è bloccato: cosa fare]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Chrome-non-risponde-e-lento-o-e-bloccato-cosa-fare_24580</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Chrome-non-risponde-e-lento-o-e-bloccato-cosa-fare_24580"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T12:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Il sistema sembra faticare come non mai, i siti Web non si aprono o le pagine vengono caricate nel browser con grande difficoltà. È uno scenario piuttosto comune quando si usa Chrome e si tengono tante schede contemporaneamente aperte.Il browser di Google utilizza un sistema chiamato Tab freeze che si occupa di sospendere il caricamento in memoria delle schede aperte che non si usano da qualche tempo. Come abbiamo visto nell'articolo sui migliori browser per la gestione della memoria con tante schede aperte, provate a digitare chrome://discards/ nella barra degli indirizzi: vedrete quali schede sono state rimosse dalla memoria RAM (unloaded) per lasciare posto ad altri dati caricati dal browser, dalle altre applicazioni e dal sistema operativo.Quando Chrome non risponde, è lento o è bloccato significa che qualche pagina Web caricata in una o più schede sta utilizzando in modo anomalo le risorse disponibili, ad esempio per caricare contenuti (spesso video o rich applications) pesanti o mal realizzati dal punto di vista del codice di programmazione.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here's Everything Coming to Netflix the Week of May 30, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lifesavvy.com/130997/heres-everything-coming-to-netflix-the-week-of-may-30-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lifesavvy.com/130997/heres-everything-coming-to-netflix-the-week-of-may-30-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T12:30:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ve likely already marathon-watched all of Stranger Things, but the good news is that Netflix is swooping in with more content. Plus, this week marks the beginning of June, which means a plethora of new content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shea Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Link Rot, and How Does It Threaten the Web?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=786227</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/786227/what-is-link-rot-and-how-does-it-threaten-the-web/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve been browsing the web and hit a 404 error page or an unexpected redirection, you’ve seen link rot in action. Over time, the links that hold the web together break, threatening our shared cultural history. Here’s a look at why that happens.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dove sta Internet Explorer in Windows 10 e Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2016/06/dove-sta-internet-explorer-in-windows-10.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2016/06/dove-sta-internet-explorer-in-windows-10.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T11:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gli utenti che hanno utilizzato Windows 8.1 o Windows 7 e sono passati a Windows 11 o Windows 10 di recente avranno notato sicuramente la "scomparsa" di Internet Explorer. Sui nuovi sistemi operativi esso non è più il browser di riferimento, visto che al suo posto è presente Microsoft Edge. Questo importante cambiamento dovrebbe far capire che lo sviluppo di Internet Explorer non è più nei piani...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenJPH 0.9 Released For Further Speeding Up Open-Source High-Throughput JPEG 2000]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=OpenJPH-0.9</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=OpenJPH-0.9"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T11:36:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While JPEG XL is regarded as the next-generation JPEG standard and JPEG 2000 never quite took off to supersede the original JPEG standard, there are open-source projects continuing to work on this image compression standard. OpenJPH 0.9 was released last week as the open-source high-throughput JPEG 2000 implementation and with this new version comes even more performance gains...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Raspberry Pi Sense HAT Joystick Driver Lands In Linux 5.19]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Raspberry-Pi-HAT-Joystick-Lands</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Raspberry-Pi-HAT-Joystick-Lands"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T11:02:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This weekend Linus Torvalds landed the Raspberry Pi Sense HT Joystick driver into the Linux 5.19 kernel as part of the input subsystem updates...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USB Flash Drive vs. External Hard Drive: Which Is Better?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=798817</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/798817/usb-flash-drive-vs.-external-hard-drive-which-is-better/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T11:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re looking to expand your portable storage, you’re likely considering either an external hard drive (HDD) or a smaller portable flash drive. So what are the differences, is one always better than the other, and are there other options?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PSA. If you run kernel 5.18 with NVIDIA, pass `ibt=off` to your kernel cmd line if your NVIDIA driver refuses to load.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0x3c4/psa_if_you_run_kernel_518_with_nvidia_pass_ibtoff/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0x3c4/psa_if_you_run_kernel_518_with_nvidia_pass_ibtoff/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T10:19:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I reported this bug here as I first noticed it in the open source kernel modules, but this indeed also seems to affect the closed source NVIDIA drivers too.
 It only seems to affect Arch though so I may open a bug report with Arch Linux about this as it might be something to do with how the modules are built for Arch specifically.
    submitted by    /u/UKSFM99  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supercomputer: AMD batte tutti i record con processori EPYC e acceleratori Instinct]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Supercomputer-AMD-batte-tutti-i-record-con-processori-EPYC-e-acceleratori-Instinct_24579</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Supercomputer-AMD-batte-tutti-i-record-con-processori-EPYC-e-acceleratori-Instinct_24579"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T10:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AMD ha comunicato di aver raggiunto e superato un importante traguardo: i processori EPYC e gli acceleratori Instinct alimentano il primo supercomputer al mondo ad aver superato la barriera dell'exascale.Cosa significa? Con il termine exascale computing si fa riferimento ai sistemi informatici in grado di elaborare almeno 1018 operazioni in virgola mobile al secondo.

Il sistema Frontier dell'Oak Ridge National Laboratory (Tennessee, Stati Uniti) basato sulla tecnologia AMD si è classificato al 1° posto sia nella Top500 che nella Green500 facendo segnare 1,102 exaflop di performance e 62,68 gigaflops/watt di efficienza energetica.Frontier diventa così il supercomputer più veloce e più efficiente al mondo balzando subito al primo posto anche nella classifica HPL-AI con 6,86 exaflop.HPL-AI è un benchmark che combina un'attenta valutazione per i carichi di lavoro di calcolo ad alte prestazioni (HPC) con le elaborazioni di intelligenza artificiale (AI).

Tra gli altri sistemi alimentati da AMD EPYC e AMD Instinct MI200, il supercomputer LUMI di CSC (Center for Science, Finlandia) si è classificato al terzo posto sia nella Top500 che nella Green500 con 152 petaflop di prestazioni e 51,63 gigaflops/watt di efficienza energetica.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Beginner’s Guide to Creating an Online Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/?p=59962</id>
        <link href="https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/creating-online-course/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T10:01:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you a skilled trade professional or knowledgeable about effective time management? No matter what field you're in, your expertise has value, and it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helen Colman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Outdated llvm packages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0wtfk/outdated_llvm_packages/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0wtfk/outdated_llvm_packages/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T10:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi! Could you tell me how is it possible to help to update packages in Extra repository? 
 LLVM-related packages are flagged out-of-date for about 2 month and even Ubuntu 22.04 has newer versions.
 https://archlinux.org/packages/?sort=&q=llvm&maintainer=foutrelis&flagged=Flagged
 I understand that maintainer may not have time to update it. Is there any procedure to change maintainer or to become a maintainer of some packages?
 I would like to contribute to Arch by maintaining some packages.
    submitted by    /u/Kuznetsss  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OverlayFS Adding Support For IDMAPPED Layers For Various Benefits]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=OverlayFS-IDMAPPED-Layers</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=OverlayFS-IDMAPPED-Layers"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T09:46:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sent in this morning for the Linux 5.19 merge window were the OverlayFS updates of which the main feature addition this cycle is support for IDMAPPED layers...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[System is going to shutdown NOW!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0wlzg/system_is_going_to_shutdown_now/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0wlzg/system_is_going_to_shutdown_now/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T09:45:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I try to shut down the computer, it says "The system going to shut down NOW!" and makes a loud noise, which is even louder when you run grub. At the same time, if you type wall Hello in the console, this sound appears again. Help me to fix it, my ears will soon die from this and I have to take a sedative because this sound scares me even more.
    submitted by    /u/Reged1tFox  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can't seem to add an AUR SSH key]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0wdus/cant_seem_to_add_an_aur_ssh_key/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0wdus/cant_seem_to_add_an_aur_ssh_key/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T09:29:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've created a new key using ssh-keygen -f ~/.ssh/aur from the wiki and tried adding the public key but every time I get the following error:
 The PGP key fingerprint is invalid. 
 I've tried copying it with the mouse and pasting it as well as running cat ~/.ssh/aur.pub | xclip -i -selection clipboard but it still give me the error. I've checked it and there aren't any newlines in it, it's all on one line. I've also tried random other public keys in different formats I have on my machine and none of them work.
 Does anyone know where I'm going wrong?
    submitted by    /u/itmecho  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LoongArch CPU Port Might Still Land For Linux 5.19]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=LoongArch-Maybe-For-5.19</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=LoongArch-Maybe-For-5.19"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T09:27:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the open questions this merge window is whether the MIPS64-based LoongArch CPU architecture port of the kernel will manage to land for the Linux 5.19 cycle. There has been a discussion this holiday weekend by upstream kernel developers and looks like it may still land, but possibly without necessary hardware drivers included...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smart TV da 55 pollici a 419 euro: possibile con i nuovi modelli Xiaomi F2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Smart-TV-da-55-pollici-a-419-euro-possibile-con-i-nuovi-modelli-Xiaomi-F2_24578</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Smart-TV-da-55-pollici-a-419-euro-possibile-con-i-nuovi-modelli-Xiaomi-F2_24578"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T09:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Xiaomi ha annunciato oggi la disponibilità in Italia di una nuova linea di smart TV evolute. Si tratta della serie Xiaomi TV F2 basata sul sistema operativo di Amazon di derivazione Android: Fire OS.Xiaomi TV F2 è la prima gamma di televisori del produttori a integrare la piattaforma Amazon Fire TV: il vantaggio è la flessibilità di uno strumento ormai largamente conosciuto ed apprezzato che consente l'utilizzo e il controllo del TV con l'assistente digitale Alexa.Tre i modelli disponibili di Xiaomi TV F2: da 43, 50 e 55 pollici. Rispetto ai prezzi di listino è possibile acquistare per alcuni giorni le tre varianti con una promozione davvero interessante su Amazon Italia beneficiando, ove attivato, di tutti i vantaggi dell'abbonamento Prime tra cui anche la consegna veloce:- Xiaomi TV F2 43 pollici: 339,99 euro- Xiaomi TV F2 50 pollici: 379,99 euro- Xiaomi TV F2 55 pollici: 419,99 euro

Con un'elegante struttura in metallo a doppio supporto, la serie Xiaomi TV F2 con Fire TV presenta un design con cornici sottili.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grub does not recognize other distributions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0w2qo/grub_does_not_recognize_other_distributions/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0w2qo/grub_does_not_recognize_other_distributions/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T09:06:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello people. I am writing here after not finding a way to solve this problem.
 I had Arch installed on my SSD without any other distribution, nor windows either, although with a free partition in case I wanted to do some test. I install Fedora without problems, and in the grub menu I get Arch, but it does not let me access it.
 Through the Arch ISO I do a chroot and reinstall the Arch grub and now if I can enter Arch normally.
 The problem is that Fedora does not appear anywhere, but it is still there.
 How can I recover the Fedora entry in the Arch grub? In case of having other distributions installed, is it indifferent which grub you have installed?
 Thank you very much in advance. Regards, Juan.
    submitted by    /u/jbellas  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox Translations: Firefox's offline translate feature is making progress]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178846</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/05/30/firefox-translations-firefoxs-offline-translate-feature-is-making-progress/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T09:04:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox Translations, Firefox's privacy friendly built-in translate feature, has reached a new milestone with the release of a new add-on version. Translate functionality that is built-into the web browser was introduced by […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Firefox Translations: Firefox's offline translate feature is making progress appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rete unica più vicina: Open Fiber e TIM firmano un primo importante accordo]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Rete-unica-piu-vicina-Open-Fiber-e-TIM-firmano-un-primo-importante-accordo_24577</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Rete-unica-piu-vicina-Open-Fiber-e-TIM-firmano-un-primo-importante-accordo_24577"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T08:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Non è ancora un contratto vero e proprio ma il memorandum d'intesa che Open Fiber e TIM, di concerto con CDP Equity, KKR, Macquarie (rispettivamente soci in Open Fiber e Fibercop), hanno siglato rappresenta un deciso balzo in avanti verso la rete di telecomunicazioni unica in Italia.L'obiettivo del documento sottoscritto nelle scorse ore è quello di avviare un processo volto alla creazione di un solo operatore per la gestione delle reti di telecomunicazioni. Il nuovo soggetto sarebbe non verticalmente integrato, controllato da Cassa Depositi e Prestiti e partecipato da Macquarie e KKR.La newco che andrebbe a costituirsi (in passato si era parlato della possibile denominazione AccessCo) si occuperebbe di accelerare la diffusione della fibra ottica e delle infrastrutture VHCN (Very High Capacity Network) sull'intero territorio nazionale permettendo così l'accesso ai servizi più innovativi ed efficienti offerti dal mercato alla generalità della popolazione, agli enti pubblici e alle imprese.Le parti protagoniste dell'importante intesa si sono accordate sul fatto che l'operazione possa articolarsi mediante la separazione delle attività infrastrutturali di rete fissa da quelle commerciali di TIM.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migliori antivirus 2022: quali acquistare al prezzo più basso di sempre]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Migliori-antivirus-2022-quali-acquistare-al-prezzo-piu-basso-di-sempre_24560</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Migliori-antivirus-2022-quali-acquistare-al-prezzo-piu-basso-di-sempre_24560"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T08:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows integra già un buon antimalware: si chiama Microsoft Defender e risulta attivato per impostazione predefinita. Rispetto al passato il software Microsoft è maturato molto, tanto che oggi può essere inserito senza difficoltà nell'élite dei migliori antivirus disponibili.L'antivirus migliore è infatti certamente quello che riesce a riconoscere e bloccare qualunque tentativo di infezione, i malware che utilizzano tecniche di offuscamento ed espedienti di vario genere nel tentativo di non essere rilevati e le cosiddette minacce zero-day, appena comparse in rete e non ancora catalogate dai principali produttori di soluzioni per la sicurezza informatica.Senza lasciare da parte l'efficacia, quindi, Microsoft Defender è certamente un antivirus economico: essendo integrato in Windows non richiede l'attivazione di alcun abbonamento né l'esborso di alcun costo di licenza (in aggiunta rispetto alla licenza del sistema operativo: licenze di Windows 10 e 11 si possono acquistare a prezzo scontato).La sua interfaccia di gestione integrata con la finestra Sicurezza di Windows espone un numero limitato di funzionalità: per ottimizzare Microsoft Defender si può usare un semplice espediente ed esporre l'accesso a tutte le caratteristiche avanzate.Perché allora scegliere antivirus professionali se Windows già integra un software gratuito come Microsoft Defender? In un altro articolo abbiamo messo in evidenza le differenze tra i migliori antivirus a pagamento e gratuiti: ecco quando e perché preferire un antivirus più completo rispetto a quello offerto da Windows.Di seguito presentiamo alcuni consigli per selezionare il miglior antivirus per PC: i prodotti proposti sono ordinati partendo da quello più consigliato.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD-Powered Frontier Supercomputer Tops Top500 At 1.1 Exaflops, Tops Green500 Too]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Top500-Green500-Frontier</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Top500-Green500-Frontier"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As part of ISC 2022 happening this week in Hamburg, Germany, the new Top500 supercomputer and Green500 energy efficiency lists have been published...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Giveaway: WinX HD Video Converter Delux è gratis per un periodo di tempo limitato]]></title>
        <id>3589|20220530065711</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/giveaway-755/giveaway-winx-hd-video-converter-delux-gratis-periodo-tempo-limitato-3589"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T04:57:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hai la necessità di tagliare video lunghi in piccole clip per condividerle più velocemente sui social? Vuoi tagliare parti di video indesiderate e ridurre il tuo filmato all'essenziale? Devi ridimensionare un video di grandi dimensioni senza perdere qualità visiva?
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bionic Reading: promises better, faster and more focused reading]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178842</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/05/30/bionic-reading-promises-better-faster-and-more-focused-reading/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T04:49:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bionic Reading is a reading system that is designed to improve reading through the use of typographic highlights. The system highlights parts of words in texts to guide the human eye and […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Bionic Reading: promises better, faster and more focused reading appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[is my encrypted disk just screwed now?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0rnle/is_my_encrypted_disk_just_screwed_now/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0rnle/is_my_encrypted_disk_just_screwed_now/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T03:59:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[First what I did was I setup a new systed-cryptsetup key using my fido2 Yubikey, then I luksRemoved the last password on the drive, thinking I could just add a new password using my USB key, it wasnt until I read the docs that they said  it's generally recommended to combine TPM2, FIDO2, PKCS#11 key enrollment with enrolling a regular passphrase or recovery key.  Is there absolutely nothing I can do,? Am I just forever locked into using my FIDO2 key to unlock my system ?
    submitted by    /u/StratusFearMe21  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Just installed arch - installation and first impressions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0mlqr/just_installed_arch_installation_and_first/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0mlqr/just_installed_arch_installation_and_first/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T23:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been a Debian user for a long time, and just tried arch for the first time. I'm still happy with Debian but I got gifted an old laptop and wanted to try something different on it. Also I had trouble getting android studio and flutter to work on Debian (although others seem to have no problem) and I thought it would be nice to have a Linux system that could run newer programs and systems without issue. 
 I've been loyal to Debian because I love the stability, being able to sit down to a system that just always works and not having to do too much maintenance. Which is probably not good for switching Arch, but I figured why not, since so many seem to enjoy it. Some people say Arch breaks and needs maintenance, others say it's very stable and they only update it once every few weeks. I'm …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel Media Driver Adding Vulkan Video Acceleration Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-Media-Driver-Vulkan</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-Media-Driver-Vulkan"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T22:55:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While Intel has long supported GPU-based video decode acceleration on Linux using the Video Acceleration API (VA-API) and more recently via oneVPL under their oneAPI umbrella, with their Intel Media Driver stack they have begun offering support for video decoding using the cross-platform video acceleration extensions to the Vulkan API...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apparently I don't have space on a 1TB drive despite having done nothing...]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0loeq/apparently_i_dont_have_space_on_a_1tb_drive/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0loeq/apparently_i_dont_have_space_on_a_1tb_drive/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T22:10:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just installed arch, and now my main partition is apparently full, sans 400mb. This makes no goddamn sense.The closest thing ive got is that when I was partitioning this SSD, the logs for the size of what was going to be swap (didnt keep the swap) stayed when I made /dev/sda2 the root partition (which gnome disks lists as its actual size). Can't install or do shit with the system reading stuff like this.Any ideas on how to fix this? 
 SOLVED: Ran [ resize2fs -f /dev/sda2 ] as root, it resized the ext4 filesystem on sda2 to fill the partition.
    submitted by    /u/CrazyIronMyth  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come togliere gli elementi in evidenza dalla barra di ricerca di Windows 10]]></title>
        <id>3588|20220530000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/windows-10/come-togliere-elementi-evidenza-barra-ricerca-windows-10-3588"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chi utilizza le versioni più aggiornate di Windows 10, potrebbe aver visto comparire nella sua barra di ricerca delle strane icone e cliccandoci sopra ci sono delle informazioni aggiuntive, che cambiano sempre, e usano Bing per essere visualizzate.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PC suddenly reboots during VM configuration in KVM/QEMU]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0lfyb/pc_suddenly_reboots_during_vm_configuration_in/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0lfyb/pc_suddenly_reboots_during_vm_configuration_in/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T21:58:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm following this guide to passthrough my GPU to VM, but when I get to the part where I pass the SSD, my host system freezes for a second and reboots. For reference, I'm running the zen-kernel on Gnome.
 Specs: i7-8700, 2x16GB RAM, 512GB SATA, 1TB NVMe.
    submitted by    /u/AlpinDale  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethernet doesnt work after done installing and dhcpcd command doesnt work]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0l6bu/ethernet_doesnt_work_after_done_installing_and/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0l6bu/ethernet_doesnt_work_after_done_installing_and/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T21:45:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My ethernet isnt working, i just finished installing and i already took the installation usb off, tried the dhcpcd things and it didnt work because it results in not found.
    submitted by    /u/allmynamesweretaken1  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Encrypted system doesn't boot up when remotely unlocking]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0l2bn/encrypted_system_doesnt_boot_up_when_remotely/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0l2bn/encrypted_system_doesnt_boot_up_when_remotely/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T21:39:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently updated my system after a few weeks of not updating and rebooted. I get this message when I enter the decryption key into tinyssh.
  ~ > ssh root@10.0.10.3 Enter passphrase for /dev/sda1: cryptsetup(209): Function not implemented cryptsetup: no process found Connection to 10.0.10.3 closed. 
 I can still ping the server, but then I end up not being able to SSH into the system and it seemingly hangs endlessly.
 Whereas usually I encounter on a successful bootup:
  ~ > ssh root@10.0.10.3 Enter passphrase for /dev/sda1: Connection to 10.0.10.3 closed. 
 I can still manually decrypt the LUKS container, mount the LVM volume, and interact with files if I boot into a microSD card instead of trying a remote unlock. I'm using the LVM on LUKS setup described on the Arch Wiki. fsck reports clean drives as well. What could be going on?
    submitted by    /u/nasdack  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add Dark Mode to Google Chrome]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=330529</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15336440/add-dark-mode-google-chrome"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Chrome is by far the world’s most popular web browser. But with that, users have grown to have certain expectations. One of those is a dark mode. The idea of dark mode is that it makes the screen easier on your eyes in a low- or no-light setting. Of course, there are still some questions about the extent to which dark themes are really better for your eyes, but it’s certainly useful in certain circumstances.
    
There are a few different ways to enable dark mode in Chrome, though weirdly it’s not quite as simple and obvious as it should be. Here’s how to do it.
   

Content

Enable Chrome Dark Mode in Desktop
Enable Chrome Dark Mode in Flags
Enable Chrome Dark Mode on iOS
Enable Chrome Dark Mode on Android
Use Third-Party Dark Mode Extension

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}    
Enable Chrome Dark Mode in Desktop
    
Whether you’re using Windows or macOS, the simplest – though not most effective – way of enabling dark mode in Google Chrome is to do it through your desktop.... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Zak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is the Best VPN Protocol? OpenVPN vs. WireGuard vs. SSTP and More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=770807</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/770807/what-is-the-best-vpn-protocol-openvpn-vs-wireguard-vs-sstp-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are multiple VPN protocols, and which protocol a VPN uses has a big influence on how it functions. Some protocols are a lot better than others. Thankfully, finding the best VPN protocol is easy as there are only a few candidates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fergus O'Sullivan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[i8kutils is broken]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0jmy0/i8kutils_is_broken/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0jmy0/i8kutils_is_broken/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T20:26:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I noticed my fan wasn't running at the right speed after updating the kernel. i8kfan was giving can't open /proc/i8k: No such file or directory. According to the kernel documentation, for /proc/i8k to exist, the kernel must be compiled with the CONFIG_I8K. And, here's the diff for the 5.18 kernel. CONFIG_IK8 has gone. Why? Is there a fix? Is i8kutils just dead?
    submitted by    /u/-LeopardShark-  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Barnes & Noble Releases an eReader with Actual Freaking Buttons]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119393/barnes-and-noble-releases-an-ereader-with-actual-freaking-buttons/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119393/barnes-and-noble-releases-an-ereader-with-actual-freaking-buttons/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T20:04:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bookseller giant Barnes & Noble just released its newest Nook eReader, the Nook GlowLight 4e, and it’s looking to be an excellent competitor for Amazon’s Kindle eReaders. It’s an exciting entry into the often slow-moving world of eReaders, and packs some highly-desired features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzanne Humphries</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to See Your Android Phone’s Processor and Speed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=773050</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/773050/how-to-see-your-android-phones-processor-and-speed/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some people like to know what’s powering the device in their pocket, others simply forgot the specs. Whatever the case may be, we’ll show you how to see the processor in your Android phone—and how fast it is.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cross compiling Gentoo from Arch for Raspberry Pi.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0iokh/cross_compiling_gentoo_from_arch_for_raspberry_pi/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0iokh/cross_compiling_gentoo_from_arch_for_raspberry_pi/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T19:39:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been trying to get a Gentoo system up, and running; but, have been running into issues getting it to boot properly. Previously, I installed Raspbian on the Pi, created a partition for Gentoo, and tried to build and bootstrap from there. For some reason the kernel is not able to load the Gentoo root partition.
 So, I think it would be faster and easier to just build a kernel from my Arch machine for the Pi. My Gentoo machine won't be up for a couple of weeks, and I'd like to get this working sooner. So, how can I compile the Raspberry Pi kernel from Arch? How should I go about configuring QEMU?
    submitted by    /u/Zara629  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best cheap laptops for running archlinux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0i9km/best_cheap_laptops_for_running_archlinux/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0i9km/best_cheap_laptops_for_running_archlinux/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T19:19:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, I'm a guy from Argentina and computers here are expensive af, could you guys suggest good laptops for running arch as main OS? 
 EDIT: I use DWM and no other heavy programs
 Thank you in advance
    submitted by    /u/Outzide_  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Restart a MacBook Pro]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=807426</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/807426/how-to-restart-a-macbook-pro/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T19:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re troubleshooting minor issues with a MacBook Pro, it can help to restart (reboot) your computer. This will reload macOS and give you a fresh start without affecting any of your documents or data. Here’s how to do it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wifi driver does not work after 5.18 update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0guah/wifi_driver_does_not_work_after_518_update/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0guah/wifi_driver_does_not_work_after_518_update/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T18:08:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[rtw88_8821ce does not work well at all so i had to install rtl8821ce-dkms-git from aur repository. but the dkms fails to build in the new update and i'm stuck with rtw88_8821ce. 
 i reverted back to linux-5.17.7 and rtl8821ce is working fine. Just wondering if anyone else bumped into the same issue.
    submitted by    /u/Ashik80  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How You Can Get Banned as a Twitch Viewer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=803608</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/803608/how-you-can-get-banned-as-a-twitch-viewer/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T18:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Love watching and chatting with your favorite streamers on Twitch? Well, if you’re not careful, you may receive a temporary or permanent ban from a streamer’s channel. Here’s what it takes to get banned as a viewer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Nguyen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla's Latest App Update Now Shows Recalls for Your Vehicle]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119396/teslas-latest-app-update-now-shows-recalls-for-your-vehicle/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119396/teslas-latest-app-update-now-shows-recalls-for-your-vehicle/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla is continuously updating its vehicles with changes or new features, and the same applies to the mobile app. The company recently updated its mobile app (Android/iOS) to version 4.9, and it now shows all recalls for the connected vehicle.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[PKGBUILD] How do I make Pacman stop asking for providers and instead just use the one specified in the PKGBUILD]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0gnop/pkgbuild_how_do_i_make_pacman_stop_asking_for/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0gnop/pkgbuild_how_do_i_make_pacman_stop_asking_for/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T17:59:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OK, so I've just created a gaming meta-package. One of its dependencies is lib32-pipewire-jack, because my system will use Pipewire. However, when I try and install it Pacman still asks me:
 :: There are 2 providers available for lib32-jack: :: Repository multilib 1) lib32-jack2 2) lib32-pipewire-jack Enter a number (default=1): 
 It's a problem, because one can easily hit enter by accident and install lib32-jack2 instead. (Well actually you can't because Pacman throws an error saying lib32-jack2 and lib32-pipewire-jack are in conflict). How can I force my package to install lib32-pipewire-jack instead of asking for a lib32-jack provider?
    submitted by    /u/dankcuddlybear-v2-0  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can I Use an arch .config to Compile a Xubuntu 22.04 Kernel?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0fjm0/can_i_use_an_arch_config_to_compile_a_xubuntu/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0fjm0/can_i_use_an_arch_config_to_compile_a_xubuntu/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T17:04:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have a Pocket 3 N6000, which has no sound in any linux unless patched by this:
 https://github.com/thesofproject/linux/issues/3393
 My various attempts at compiling have failed for fewer and fewer reasons that I can grasp, and I don't know arch at all.
 But this arch .config: https://aur.archlinux.org/cgit/aur.git/tree/config?h=linux-p3-patch
 apparently works. Can I use that .config in xubuntu?
 Many thanks for any help, Jake
    submitted by    /u/jakfish  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fix “Page Fault in Nonpaged Area” on Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=807269</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/807269/how-to-fix-page-fault-in-nonpaged-area-on-windows/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some Blue Screens of Death (BSODs) are difficult or impossible to diagnose and fix, whereas others are pretty straightforward. Luckily, a Page Fault BSOD is often fixable. Here are some things you can try.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Lewis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EnemyBot malware adds exploits for critical VMware, F5 BIG-IP flaws]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/enemybot-malware-adds-exploits-for-critical-vmware-f5-big-ip-flaws/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/enemybot-malware-adds-exploits-for-critical-vmware-f5-big-ip-flaws/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T16:39:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EnemyBot, a botnet based on code from multiple malware pieces, is expanding its reach by quickly adding exploits for recently disclosed critical vulnerabilities in web servers, content management systems, IoT, and Android devices. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch Linux's Archinstall 2.5 Released With FIDO2 Support, Other Improvements]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Arch-Linux-Archinstall-2.5</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Arch-Linux-Archinstall-2.5"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T16:10:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just in time for Arch Linux's June 2022 monthly ISO refresh, Archinstall 2.5 was released today as the newest version of this text-based Arch Linux installer...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Manage Notification Grouping on iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=805354</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/805354/how-to-manage-notification-grouping-on-iphone/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T16:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[iPhone notifications can be a bit overwhelming at times. Notification Grouping is a feature that aims to help you clean things up. We’ll show you how to use it to bring some more organization to your iPhone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[11 Strategies to Find Great Deals and Save Money]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=442945</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/14960580/deal-strategy-save-money"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deal, sale, special offer, buy now, all of these phrases are words that are meant to grab our attention and click the “Buy” button. Between Amazon, Walmart+ and retail shops all around us, it’s easy to impulse buy as soon as you think something is a good deal. The reality is quite different after a few minutes of research. This article will help you out and tell you if something really is a great deal. Read on to learn whether you should jump on a low price or keep waiting.
   

Content

1. Integrate Cashback into Your Browser
2. Never Pay Full Price
3. Use a Price Comparison Tool
4. Look for Coupons First
5. Save Money with Discounted Gift Cards
6. Add Items to Your Shopping Cart and Wait
7. Follow Discount Sites/Deal-Hunters
8. Wait for Specific Times to Buy
9. Check for Veteran, Education, and Other Discounts
10. Search a Deal Website First
11. Using the Right Credit Cards
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Tee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Volkswagen's ID. Buzz Meets the 'Obi-Wan' Cast In a New Promo Video]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118969/volkswagens-id-buzz-meets-the-obi-wan-cast-in-a-new-promo-video/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118969/volkswagens-id-buzz-meets-the-obi-wan-cast-in-a-new-promo-video/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T15:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Volkswagen is joining the force with the first advertisement for its ID. Buzz EV. The short video features characters from Obi-Wan Kenobi, a new Star Wars prequel series from Disney+. Oh, and Ewan McGregor is now the brand ambassador for Volkswagen, so there’ll probably be more tie-in ads in the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mobile trojan detections rise as malware distribution level declines]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/mobile-trojan-detections-rise-as-malware-distribution-level-declines/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/mobile-trojan-detections-rise-as-malware-distribution-level-declines/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T15:15:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kaspersky's quarterly report on mobile malware distribution records a downward trend that started at the end of 2020, detecting one-third of the malicious installations reported in Q1 2021, and about 85% of those counted in Q4 2021. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Does “LTE” Mean on a Phone?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=805712</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/805712/what-does-lte-mean-on-my-phone/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T15:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Curious about the LTE symbol on your smartphone? It’s one of the many wireless standards that allow you to communicate on the go. But what does LTE mean, and how is it different from 5G?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gaurav Shukla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Confronto VPN: qual è la più veloce e la più sicura?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/05/confronto-vpn-qual-e-la-piu-veloce-e-la.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/05/confronto-vpn-qual-e-la-piu-veloce-e-la.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T14:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scegliere una VPN al giorno d'oggi è davvero molto difficile: ci sono così tanti servizi in commercio e spesso troviamo scritte e valori che non comprendiamo appieno, affidandoci quindi solo al prezzo di vendita e a pochi altri dettagli. Una VPN va scelta invece con molta cura, visto che su di essa passeranno le informazioni sulla nostra connessione e su quello che facciamo sul PC quando...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Yorker imprisoned for role in carding group behind $568M damages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-yorker-imprisoned-for-role-in-carding-group-behind-568m-damages/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-yorker-imprisoned-for-role-in-carding-group-behind-568m-damages/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Telusma, a 37-year-old man from New York, was sentenced to four years in prison for selling and using stolen and compromised credit cards on the Infraud carding portal operated by the transnational cybercrime organization with the same name. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Mice of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=732167</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/732167/the-best-mice-for-gaming-productivity-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smooth browsing, productivity shortcuts right at your fingertips, and the accuracy needed to land the perfect shot. An average computer mouse can’t do these things, but with our recommendations, your new mouse can do all of that and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Henges</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>