<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-06-07T01:50:46.897Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Nearby Sharing to Share Files on Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=483258</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15353540/use-nearby-sharing-windows"/>
        <updated>2022-06-07T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nearby Sharing makes it easy to share files wirelessly from your Windows PC to other nearby Windows devices. You can send documents, photos, links, and other files without the need for cloud services, network file sharing, USB flash drives, or email attachments.
    
This nifty feature uses Wi-Fi, Bluetooth, and Ethernet to transfer files between devices. This guide will show you how to set up, use, and troubleshoot Nearby Sharing.
   

Content

Nearby Sharing Prerequisites
How to Turn on Nearby Sharing
How to Share Files with Nearby Sharing
How to Share Links Using Nearby Sharing 
How to Change Nearby Sharing Download Folder
How to Add Nearby Sharing to Quick Settings for Faster File Sharing
How To Troubleshoot Nearby Sharing
1. Confirm Bluetooth Driver is Installed Correctly
2. Enable Bluetooth Adapter
3. Check Bluetooth Compatibility
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Share... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Kanyoro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for media server options]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v6gr29/looking_for_media_server_options/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v6gr29/looking_for_media_server_options/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T23:28:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wondering if there are any options for media server that also allow it to double as a smart tv interface? 
 I have a projector that I wanna plug mine into and play directly from but I can't find anything but Kodi and experience with that on RPI has soured it for me. Bonus would be if it allows me to use things like netflix of prime video too. 
 Any suggestions welcome, thanks in advance
    submitted by    /u/NGumi  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[macOS 13 Adding Ability To Use Rosetta In ARM Linux VMs For Speedy x86_64 Linux Binaries]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=macOS-13-Rosetta-Linux-Binaries</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=macOS-13-Rosetta-Linux-Binaries"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T22:44:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In addition to announcing the M2 SoC, Apple used its WWDC keynote to also announce macOS 13 "Ventura". One of the interesting technical changes with macOS 13 is the ability to use Apple's Rosetta software for speedy execution of Linux x86_64 binaries running on ARM Linux VMs from Apple Silicon...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Any Arch/btrfs/snapper fans? Just ported httm (my CLI Time Machine-type thing)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v6fp52/any_archbtrfssnapper_fans_just_ported_httm_my_cli/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v6fp52/any_archbtrfssnapper_fans_just_ported_httm_my_cli/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T22:37:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The dream of a CLI Time Machine is still alive with httm
 httm prints the size, date and corresponding locations of available unique versions (deduplicated by modify time and size) of files residing on snapshots, but can also be used interactively to select and restore such files. httm might change the way you use snapshots (because ZFS/btrfs aren't designed for finding for unique file versions) or the Time Machine concept (because httm is very fast!).
 Recently, I ported httm to use btrfs with snapper layouts. A PKGBUILD with btrfs support is available for Arch, and I'm interested to know your thoughts!
    submitted by    /u/small_kimono  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come impostare la modalità Internet Explorer in Microsoft Edge]]></title>
        <id>3590|20220607000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/browser-455/come-impostare-modalita-internet-explorer-microsoft-edge-3590"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Il 15 Giugno 2022 segna una data, in un certo senso, storica, perché Microsoft ritirerà Internet Explorer, il suo browser nato nel 1995. Per quanto a livello di utenti casalinghi sia ormai stato ampiamente superato (e dimenticato) da molto tempo, una piccola fetta di realtà aziendali continuano ad usarlo perché non hanno mai aggiornato le app Web che richiedono appunto tale browser. Vediamo quindi come abilitare Microsoft Edge per simulare, quando necessario, Internet Explorer e poter utilizzare ancora questi siti.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A privacy issue...are the app stores and repositories collecting and sending data to thrid party....]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v6e73t/a_privacy_issueare_the_app_stores_and/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v6e73t/a_privacy_issueare_the_app_stores_and/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T21:29:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey guys....I recently started using linux...and when I went through some blogs and articles I came across this privacy stuff in linux app stores...it seems that there are many third party dependencies that collect so much data from the user without their acknowledgement...should I use app stores to use...or stick with just repositories...or both are same...like this issue in gnome software store a dependency fwupd sends user id,user system name,locale,distro,device ID and so many things to the developer....although the developer has claimed the opposite...it still remains an issue...also in another blog article there was a dependency in arch Linux stating about data being sent to a company when we visit the gnome software store in arch Linux and even if we download from repositories...what should I do...should I stick with terminal and repositories or use software sotre...or just stick with appimages...I know this issue has been addressed in some way a few yaers back...but still I am worried about the privacy....even in arch Linux....
    submitted by    /u/anonymous_persona_  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Access an Android Phone With a Broken Screen]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=306240</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/12480357/access-android-with-broken-screen"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How many times have you dropped your phone, believing that the screen would be cracked when you picked it up? Luckily for us, most phone screens are relatively durable and don’t break easily. But when they do, you’re left scrambling, trying to figure out how to access your Android phone with a broken screen.
    
When your phone breaks and the screen is no longer working, not only can you not use your phone, but now all that information stored on your phone is inaccessible. The good news is it’s possible to recover all the information on your device with a little troubleshooting.
   

Content

Use OTG to Gain Access
USB Debugging
If Your Screen Won't Turn On
How to Prevent These Issues
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Fix the Obtaining IP Address Error on Android
    
Use... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Crystal Crowder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How are you supposed to downgrade nvidia drivers?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v6dyda/how_are_you_supposed_to_downgrade_nvidia_drivers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v6dyda/how_are_you_supposed_to_downgrade_nvidia_drivers/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T21:18:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have used this tool from the AUR called downgrade and I can’t downgrade the “nvidia” package. I don’t know how to easily downgrade it so if someone could leave a comment that would be nice.
 solution: sudo pacman -S linux
    submitted by    /u/VotedDragon_reddit  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QBot now pushes Black Basta ransomware in bot-powered attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/qbot-now-pushes-black-basta-ransomware-in-bot-powered-attacks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/qbot-now-pushes-black-basta-ransomware-in-bot-powered-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T21:01:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Black Basta ransomware gang has partnered with the QBot malware operation to gain spread laterally through hacked corporate environments. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Map a Network Drive on Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=755213</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/755213/how-to-map-a-network-drive-on-windows-11/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you frequently use a networked drive (or “share”) with Windows 11, you can map it to a drive letter in File Explorer to make it appear more like a local drive and quickly access it in the future. Here’s how to do it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple M1 vs. M2: What’s the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809540</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809540/apple-m2-vs-m1-whats-the-difference/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T20:58:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The second generation of Apple Silicon is here. The M2 SOC is Apple’s consumer upgrade to the 2020’s M1 in the Mac lineup and beyond. Here’s a look at how the two chips compare—and what it means for future Macs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Safari on Mac, iPhone, and iPad Will Allow Web Notifications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809573</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809573/safari-on-mac-iphone-and-ipad-will-allow-web-notifications/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T20:37:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple’s Safari web browser has lagged behind some features in recent years, especially with background services. After years of waiting, it seems like Safari will finally support web push notifications on all platforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What to Do If Your PC Can't Upgrade to Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118363/what-to-do-if-your-pc-cant-upgrade-to-windows-11/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118363/what-to-do-if-your-pc-cant-upgrade-to-windows-11/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T20:10:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft’s latest operating system, Windows 11, launched in October 2021, but many PCs lack the hardware required to upgrade. So what can you do if your computer isn’t ready to make the jump? Is upgrading even worth the hassle?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McQuilling</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Change the Page Color in Microsoft Word]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=766538</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/766538/how-to-change-the-page-color-in-microsoft-word/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By default, Microsoft Word uses white as the default page color for all documents. If you’d like to use a custom color for your page, you can change page colors in Word. We’ll show you how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iPad Multitasking Will Be Supercharged With iPadOS 16]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809543</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809543/ipad-multitasking-will-be-supercharged-with-ipados-16/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T19:56:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The iPad has always been in a strange place, with some of the apps commonly found on PCs, but still missing some common desktop features. Apple is attempting to bride that gap with the upcoming iPadOS 16 update.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mandiant: “No evidence” we were hacked by LockBit ransomware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/mandiant-no-evidence-we-were-hacked-by-lockbit-ransomware/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/mandiant-no-evidence-we-were-hacked-by-lockbit-ransomware/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T19:54:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[American cybersecurity firm Mandiant is investigating LockBit ransomware gang's claims that they hacked the company's network and stole data. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia drivers seem to break xorg]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v6c0nc/nvidia_drivers_seem_to_break_xorg/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v6c0nc/nvidia_drivers_seem_to_break_xorg/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T19:52:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have been attempting to install nvidia proprietary drivers on my system for the past couple of days but have run into some major problems. On startup xorg fails every time. From the log I received:
 xinit: giving up
 xinit: unable to connect to X server: Connection refused xinit: server error
 Kind of at a loss for what to do next. For a little more context I’m using lightdm as a display manager. 
 These are the packages I installed:
 nvidia-dkms nvidia-utils lib32-nvidia-utils nvidia-settings vulkan-icd-loader lib32-vulkan-icd-loader
    submitted by    /u/RandomUser6410  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple's Next-Gen CarPlay Is a First Glimpse at the "Apple Car"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120190/apples-next-gen-carplay-is-a-first-glimpse-at-the-apple-car/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120190/apples-next-gen-carplay-is-a-first-glimpse-at-the-apple-car/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T19:46:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we all know, the infotainment systems in cars aren’t all that great, and we don’t see it getting any better with the shift to electric vehicles. Apple wants to transition its popular CarPlay system into an entire vehicle interface as a potential solution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple's iOS 16 Update Is a Mixed Bag of Excitement and Boredom]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120153/apples-ios-16-update-is-a-mixed-bag-of-excitement-and-boredom/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120153/apples-ios-16-update-is-a-mixed-bag-of-excitement-and-boredom/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T19:38:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We finally caught a glimpse at iOS 16 during Apple’s WWDC livestream. And by “a glimpse,” I actually mean “a rapid-fire grocery list of new features with little context.” Yeah, Apple threw everything at the wall this year, and only some of it stuck. But the good stuff is really good.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save $100 on a Pixel 6 Pro, One of Our Favorite Phones]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809465</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809465/save-100-on-a-pixel-6-pro-one-of-our-favorite-phones/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T19:32:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s Pixel 6 Pro has been a hot item for Android enthusiasts — ranking as the fastest selling Pixel phone of all time — and you can get one for its lowest price ever. Drop what you’re doing and pick up a new Pixel 6 Pro for just $799 ($100 off) over at Amazon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zach Laidlaw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save $30 on Bose Sport Wireless Earbuds]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=495277</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15353229/bose-sport-wireless-earbuds"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Music aficionados have known for years that the name Bose is one of the best in the business for headphones and speakers. Take advantage of this deal and get $30 off a set of Bose Sport Wireless Earbuds. They’re rated IPX4 and great for running and working out as well as doing any other activity, even if it’s just relaxing.
    
You’ll feel like your favorite bands and singers are right there running along side you or doing down dogs. The earbuds will make you want to work out longer, which won’t be a problem, as they last up to five hours when you use the charging case. Add two more hours to that after a 15-minute quick charge.
   
 
   
Customize the fit of the Bose Sport Wireless Earbuds with the StayHear Max tips. You’ll get three sizes to be sure they fit well, and they won’t hurt your ears or fall out. They’re also IPX4-rated and wrapped in a material that will keep the moisture out.
    
Along with listening to... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Is Getting Serious About Smart Homes With iOS 16]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809499</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809499/apple-is-getting-serious-about-smart-homes-with-ios-16/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T19:05:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple’s HomeKit and the companion Home app have long felt like a neglected project. With the release of iOS 16, the Home app is getting a facelift and a new lease on life complete with a promise of Matter support.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Fitzpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Debuts Redesigned M2-Powered MacBook Air]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120147/apple-debuts-redesigned-m2-powered-macbook-air/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120147/apple-debuts-redesigned-m2-powered-macbook-air/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T19:04:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve been hearing rumors about a newly redesigned MacBook Air for a while now, and today at its annual WWDC developers event, Apple delivered precisely that. With a design reminiscent of the new 2021 MacBook Pro, the Air now has smaller bezels putting the screen front and center, and more power than ever before.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create and Customize a Drop-Down List in Google Docs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=803342</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/803342/create-a-drop-down-list-in-google-docs/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T19:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Drop-down lists are handy tools for entering data. They give you a choice of input, so there are no misspellings, errors, or unwanted entries. Google Docs offers both preset and custom drop-down lists to fit any type of document.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wifi not working on Arch Live USB]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v6ap7m/wifi_not_working_on_arch_live_usb/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v6ap7m/wifi_not_working_on_arch_live_usb/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T18:53:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I try to connect to wifi on an arch Live USB, using iwd (iwctl), everything seems fine and it looks like it connects to the network I specify. It asks for a password and it seems like it's connecting but it doesn't actually connect to anything. I.e. it has no internet and doesn't appear in my router's list of connected devices.
 Running journalctl -p 3 -b gives me this ouput. The first to thirteenth error are also seen when booting.
    submitted by    /u/Deathscyther1HD  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Weather Is Coming to iPad, Still No Calculator]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809522</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809522/apple-weather-is-coming-to-ipad-still-no-calculator/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T18:43:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple’s iPadOS 16 is getting a big, important new feature. It’s something many iPad users have been begging for for years now. Yes, it’s finally here: The Weather app is now on iPad. It only took 15 years!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[minecraft with prime-run cause exit code 6]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v6agod/minecraft_with_primerun_cause_exit_code_6/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v6agod/minecraft_with_primerun_cause_exit_code_6/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T18:43:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, I wanted to came back to use ArchLinux (cause too good memories) but I have a problem with prime-run and minecraft: when I start minecraft with prime run
 prime-run minecraft-launcher
 the launcher starts but after the game crashes and it reply with Exit Code 6. 
 for the prime-run script: pacman -S nvidia-prime
 my kernel version: 5.18.1-arch1-1
 nvidia video card and drivers: NVIDIA GeForce GTX 1660 Ti with Max-Q Design/ 515.48.07
 do you have any ideas?
    submitted by    /u/matO_oppreal  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[13-Inch MacBook Pro Will Soon Have Apple’s New M2 Chip]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809514</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809514/13-inch-macbook-pro-will-soon-have-apple%e2%80%99s-new-m2-chip/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T18:42:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple updated the 13-inch MacBook Pro with the first M1 chip back in 2020, and now a new model is on the way with an Apple M2 chip.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Announces Its New M2 Processor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Apple-M2</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Apple-M2"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T18:35:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple's WWDC keynote this year was used to announce the M2 processor alongside a slew of other announcements...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft bug banned Rewards accounts when redeeming points]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-bug-banned-rewards-accounts-when-redeeming-points/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-bug-banned-rewards-accounts-when-redeeming-points/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T18:25:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has fixed a bug where the Microsoft Rewards accounts of customers who redeemed points would get suspended without warning. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple’s watchOS 9 Will Track Heart Rate Zones & Running Form]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809495</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809495/apples-watchos-9-will-track-heart-rate-zones-running-form/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T18:25:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Apple Watch is more smartwatch than fitness tracker, but Apple continues to blur that line with watchOS 9. The Workout app is getting the ability to measure your running form, heart rate zones, and new workout types to track.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple’s New M2 MacBook Air Has MagSafe and a Better Webcam]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809500</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809500/apples-new-m2-macbook-air-has-magsafe-and-a-better-webcam/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T18:23:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple announced a new MacBook Air with its new M2 chip at WWDC 2022. The new MacBook Air is even lighter and faster and fixes some of the main complaints about Apple’s line of MacBooks. Here’s what’s new.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple M2 Is Faster and More Power-Efficient Than M1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809496</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809496/apple-m2-is-faster-and-more-power-efficient-than-m1/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T18:18:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple started shipping Mac computers with its M1 chip in 2020, marking the start of Apple’s migration away from Intel chips. Now the company has revealed the aptly-named sequel, the Apple M2.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dual Booting Arch-Linux and Ubuntu]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v69ocj/dual_booting_archlinux_and_ubuntu/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v69ocj/dual_booting_archlinux_and_ubuntu/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T18:07:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi,
 I am thinking of dual-booting my laptop with Arch-Linux which is currently running Ubuntu 20.04. I have installed Arch multiple times on a VM, and also on a usbstick. Now, I feel that I am ready to run it on actual hardware. So, I wanted to know if there was a guide that will guide me through the process of dual-booting Arch-Linux with Ubuntu. Also, if there were some caveats in doing this. I currently have a 512M efi partition, 927G root partition and a 4G swap partition.
 Thanks
    submitted by    /u/Clock_Suspicious  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unable to run integrated graphics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v69mid/unable_to_run_integrated_graphics/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v69mid/unable_to_run_integrated_graphics/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T18:04:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am using propriety nvidia drivers and prime on my laptop. I only use my GPU for some occasional CUDA programing.
 Since the battery life of my laptop is abysmal, I recently did powertop --auto-tune to tune the battery consumption of my laptop. However after running this, it seems like I am unable to switch to integrated graphics anymore. ``` $ glxinfo | grep "OpenGL renderer"
 OpenGL renderer string: NVIDIA GeForce RTX 3070 Laptop GPU/PCIe/SSE2
 $ prime-run glxinfo | grep "OpenGL renderer"
 OpenGL renderer string: NVIDIA GeForce RTX 3070 Laptop GPU/PCIe/SSE2
 $ glxinfo -B
 name of display: :0 display: :0 screen: 0 direct rendering: Yes Memory info (GL_NVX_gpu_memory_info): Dedicated video memory: 8192 MB Total available memory: 8192 MB Currently available dedicated video memory: 7972 MB …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Curve Text in Adobe Photoshop]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=806009</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/806009/how-to-curve-text-in-adobe-photoshop/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T18:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to make your straight text curved without much hassle? If so, Adobe Photoshop has the exact feature you need. You can use it to curve your text in your specified bend level, and we’ll show you how to make use of it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.11 Performance Benchmarks Are Looking Fantastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31183</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31183"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last month Python 3.11 Beta 1 was released as their first preview of this major update to the Python programming language. Besides new language features and other improvements, Python 3.11 performance is looking fantastic with very nice performance uplift over prior Python 3.x releases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open-Source AMDVLK Vulkan Driver Preparing Mesh Shader Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMDVLK-Mesh-Shaders-WIP</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMDVLK-Mesh-Shaders-WIP"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T17:58:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In addition to Mesa's Radeon "RADV" Vulkan driver prepared for mesh shading with an upcoming Vulkan mesh shader extension besides NVIDIA's NV_mesh_shader, it looks like AMD will be punctually supporting the cross-vendor mesh shader extension too...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Messages in iOS 16 Gets Message Editing, Deletion Features]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809473</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809473/messages-in-ios-16-gets-message-editing-deletion-features/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T17:40:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Texting other iPhone users with iMessage has always felt like an instant messaging app. iOS 16 is adding a number of features to the Messages app that makes that even more apparent. Get ready to edit your mistakes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Maps Will Soon Be Better Than Ever]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809480</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809480/apple-maps-will-soon-be-better-than-ever/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T17:39:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Maps started off as a poor substitute for Google Maps, but it has become increasingly better over time. Apple just announced a few major upgrades at WWDC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DocHipo Review: Create Beautiful Documents]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=494463</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15353109/dochipo-review"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T17:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While there are many design apps for every operating system, DocHipo is a web app that specializes in designing documents to showcase your business or events in your personal life. This review takes a look at DocHipo to see if it will be suitable for your design needs.
    
This is a sponsored article and was made possible by DocHipo. The actual contents and opinions are the sole views of the author who maintains editorial independence, even when a post is sponsored.
    
Starting with DocHipo
    
I’ll preface this review by stating that I spent 20 years as a graphic designer, so I can be a little picky. Because DocHipo allows for collaboration, I asked Phil South to collaborate with me, as he, too, spent some of his career in graphic design.
    
To get started, you only need to visit the DocHipo website and sign up for an account.
    

    
You can add your company and multiple users. You can also add multiple companies. I create graphics... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gog Games Summer Sale 2022 with free Sanitarium game and discounts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178986</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/06/gog-games-summer-sale-2022-with-free-sanitarium-game-and-discounts/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T17:19:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Gog Summer Sale 2022 runs from June 6th to June 27th. Gamers from all over the world may buy most of the games that are available on Gog at a discount […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Gog Games Summer Sale 2022 with free Sanitarium game and discounts appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Will Revamp the iPhone Lock Screen for iOS 16]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809472</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809472/apple-revamps-the-iphone-lock-screen-for-ios-16/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T17:19:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple was rumored to be working on a lock screen revamp for iOS 16 on the iPhone, and now that has just been confirmed at WWDC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Laptop slowed down]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v68ll6/laptop_slowed_down/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v68ll6/laptop_slowed_down/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T17:19:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Opening Firefox, Nautilus, Network Manager settings and some others takes 30 seconds or more. This only started last week. Before it was almost instant. Looking for a solution I came across this on the arch wiki - https://wiki.archlinux.org/title/Network_configuration#Local_network_hostname_resolution and changed my hosts file. 
 127.0.0.1 localhost ::1 localhost 127.0.1.1 myhostname
 Could this be the problem?
    submitted by    /u/CyberPolygon  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Stop an iPhone App From Using Cellular Data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=807952</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/807952/how-stop-an-iphone-app-from-using-cellular-data/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T17:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve been using up a lot of cellular data on your iPhone recently, one particular app (such as one that streams video) might be using more than others. Here’s how you can prevent an app from using cellular data at all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[System freezes while playing dota 2. Fresh Arch Kde on laptop]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v684e3/system_freezes_while_playing_dota_2_fresh_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v684e3/system_freezes_while_playing_dota_2_fresh_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T16:58:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey guys! I am experiencing weird system freezes while playing dota. I can hear my friends on discord and move mouse, but cannot open terminal, alt-tab and etc. The only solution is hard shutdown. Have not experienced similar issues in other games. I am running dota natively, via latest zen-kernel and Nvidia proprietary drivers. Not really sure how to collect logs, as I have to reboot every time this happens. So far I have tried: • Gamemode • Both vulkan and openGL • borderless and full-screen modes
    submitted by    /u/mmj0299  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ransomware gangs now give victims time to save their reputation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ransomware-gangs-now-give-victims-time-to-save-their-reputation/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ransomware-gangs-now-give-victims-time-to-save-their-reputation/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T16:56:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat analysts have observed an unusual trend in ransomware group tactics, reporting that initial phases of victim extortion are becoming less open to the public as the actors tend to use hidden or anonymous entries. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux 5.20 + Mesa 22.2 To Allow Conformant Mali G57 OpenGL ES 3.1 Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Mali-G57-Conformant-GLES-3.1</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Mali-G57-Conformant-GLES-3.1"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T16:52:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Panfrost Gallium3D patches landing today into Mesa 22.2 and Panfrost DRM kernel driver support slated to land for the Linux 5.20 cycle later this summer, the Mali G57 GPU has conformant OpenGL ES 3.1 support on this open-source driver and the first Mali GPU of the Valhall generation to have this achievement following the Panfrost driver's successes for the older Bifrost and Midgard architectures...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ford and BMW Will Test Next-Gen EV Batteries Later This Year]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120148/ford-and-bmw-will-test-next-gen-ev-batteries-later-this-year/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120148/ford-and-bmw-will-test-next-gen-ev-batteries-later-this-year/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T16:51:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lithium-ion batteries are much more powerful and efficient than they were just five years ago. And while there’s still plenty of room for improvement, lithium-ion batteries have some physical limitations that are difficult to overcome. That’s why Ford and BMW will test advanced solid-state EV batteries later this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come passare da una finestra all'altra con ALT+TAB e le altre scorciatoie]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Come-passare-da-una-finestra-all-altra-con-ALT+TAB-e-le-altre-scorciatoie_19667</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Come-passare-da-una-finestra-all-altra-con-ALT+TAB-e-le-altre-scorciatoie_19667"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T16:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[La combinazione di tasti ALT+TAB è stata introdotta da Microsoft ai tempi di Windows 3.1 ed è rimasta invariata nel corso di decenni.Premendo ALT+TAB si ottiene la lista delle applicazioni aperte in Windows con un'anteprima del contenuto di ciascuna finestra (almeno nelle versioni più recenti del sistema operativo).Fino all''epoca Windows XP', con la combinazione di tasti ALT+TAB non veniva mostrata l'anteprima delle finestre aperte (non compariva la 'miniatura' del contenuto di ciascuna applicazione): il sistema operativo si limitava a mostrare l'icona del programma aperto e il titolo di ciascuna finestra.Indipendentemente dalla versione di Windows in uso tenendo sempre premuto ALT quindi premendo più volte il tasto TAB si può selezionare una finestra aperta o quelle successive. Rilasciando entrambi i tasti, Windows passerà automaticamente alla visualizzazione della finestra corrispondente alla selezione.Per selezionare le miniature delle app in senso inverso basta premere anche il tasto MAIUSC (MAIUSC+ALT+TAB).Ma non è necessario complicarsi la vita: dopo aver premuto ALT+TAB basta premere le frecce direzionali sulla tastiera (destra/sinistra, su/giù) per spostarsi all'interno della schermata e scegliere la finestra desiderata.

Per aprire la schermata che in Windows 10 e Windows 11 permette di passare da una finestra all'altra senza tenere premuto alcun tasto, si può premere CTRL+ALT+TAB (basta insomma aggiungere la pressione del tasto CTRL): in questo modo le miniature resteranno a video anche rilasciando tutti tre i tasti.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Siti per creare video con foto, musica ed effetti di transizione]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2009/05/presentazione-video-con-foto-e-immagini.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2009/05/presentazione-video-con-foto-e-immagini.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T16:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Su PC sono possiamo usare numerosi programmi per creare video partendo da foto e immagini, a cui possiamo aggiungere musica, immagini di copertina, menu di avvio ed effetti di transizione; molti di questi programmi sono forniti gratuitamente e non hanno nulla da invidiare alle soluzioni a pagamento più famose.

 Il video poi può essere salvato su un DVD e può essere visto come fosse un filmino...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google says Chrome is 20% faster than before on macOS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178980</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/06/google-says-chrome-is-20-faster-than-before-on-macos/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T16:28:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has posted a cryptic message on Twitter that says that Chrome is 20% faster than before on macOS. In March 2022, the Mountain View company did something similar, when it published […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Google says Chrome is 20% faster than before on macOS appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[People Won’t Stop Selling Unreleased Google Pixel Phones]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809426</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809426/people-wont-stop-selling-unreleased-google-pixel-phones/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T16:25:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google showed off the Pixel 6a, Pixel 7, and Pixel 7 Pro for the first time last month at Google I/O. Even though the phones are still months away, people are already selling them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Encrypt disk and hibernation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v6768i/encrypt_disk_and_hibernation/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v6768i/encrypt_disk_and_hibernation/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T16:15:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello. Sorry I speak a little english.
 I install arch via archinstall script. I select crypt my disk and use swap. Also I use nvidia open deivers.
 When I try to wake up my pc, I get a black screen. I think this problem is due to encrypt disk. I have read that I need to use a swap file. But I think something more is needed. Tell me, what else should I know? Thanks
    submitted by    /u/nonamedamage  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows zero-day exploited in US local govt phishing attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/windows-zero-day-exploited-in-us-local-govt-phishing-attacks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/windows-zero-day-exploited-in-us-local-govt-phishing-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T16:09:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[European governments and US local governments were the targets of a phishing campaign using malicious Rich Text Format (RTF) documents designed to exploit a critical Windows zero-day vulnerability known as Follina. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maximum ram usage with no apparent reason]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v66xfb/maximum_ram_usage_with_no_apparent_reason/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v66xfb/maximum_ram_usage_with_no_apparent_reason/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T16:04:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every few days, i notice my computer is being slow, and before i know it, completely unusable. I (barely) open bashtop/htop to see whats going on and i see that (example) 59GB/62.8GB of my memory is being used and i can't see any programs that are using that much memory. Here's a screenshot that i hardly managed to capture
 The programs that i was running before the crash happened
  
Minecraft Fabric 1.18.2 Java edition with Sodium installed, through MultiMC
 ssh
 Brave (brave-nightly-bin)
 Thunar file manager
  
​
 My system specifications
  
Motherboard: B450 AORUS ELITE
 Kernel: 5.18.1-arch1-1
 Window manager: dwm
 Display manager: ly
 Compositor: picom
 CPU: AMD Ryzen 5 2600X (12) @ 3.600GHz
 GPU: NVIDIA GeForce GTX 1080 Ti
 RAM: 2 x TridentZ Neo DDR4 16GB & 2 x HyperX Fury 16GB
  
​
 Sometimes its so bad that I can't even open bashtop/htop to get a screenshot or to look at whats going on, and even if i manage to open one of these 2, the navigation through them is very slow if not impossible. Even through the TTY.
 My current way of fixing this is rebooting my PC.
 I'm not sure how to debug this after rebooting. It's very hard to use the PC without rebooting to fix the issue, I would appreciate it if someone could help me find some logs or something that could be helpful for troubleshooting this issue, or if someone already knows how to fix it
    submitted by    /u/fuckcuff  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another Unreleased Google Pixel Shows Up For Sale]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120129/another-google-pixel-phone-goes-on-sale-before-its-official-release/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120129/another-google-pixel-phone-goes-on-sale-before-its-official-release/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T16:02:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It seems that there’s a leak in Google’s manufacturing process. Just last week, a Pixel 7 prototype appeared on eBay, and another prototype passed off as a “Pixel 6 Pro” in a Facebook Marketplace sale. Now, someone is trying (or was trying) to sell a Pixel 6a on Facebook.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do You Really Need Unlimited Data?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=803657</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/803657/do-you-really-need-unlimited-data/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The holy grail of cellular plans is unlimited data. Everyone wants to be able to stream and download without worrying about going over limits. Do you actually need unlimited data, though? Here are some things to consider.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows does not run anymore on VirtualBox]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v66svu/windows_does_not_run_anymore_on_virtualbox/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v66svu/windows_does_not_run_anymore_on_virtualbox/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T15:59:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have a VirtualBox with Windows 10 x64 which I use from time to time.
 Out of sudden it got broken yesterday - it is BSODing like crazy for many different reasons during boot stage. Sometimes it manages to survive until I can see login prompt but that's the furthest.
 What's worse I cannot even create a fresh virtual machine with windows 10 as booting from windows 10 iso also bsods or fails to copy files on disk. I've downloaded a fresh iso from MS and verified sha and it's ok. Also I have checked this iso on another PC with VB and windows host and it works fine (same VirtualBox version as on my linux machine).
 Currently I have VB 6.1.34 r150636 installed. It runs Windows 7 x86 just fine. Also it boots x64 system rescue cd linux with no visible issues.
 I have tried to roll back to VB 6.1.32 but it didn't helped. I have also tried to turn off all fancy options in cpu and acceleration tabs, but nothing changes.
 Does anyone have similar issue or an idea what else can I test?
    submitted by    /u/Kicer86  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A problem with my 65W laptop battery adapter or battery.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v66qlv/a_problem_with_my_65w_laptop_battery_adapter_or/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v66qlv/a_problem_with_my_65w_laptop_battery_adapter_or/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T15:56:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, let me describe my problem:
 If I run an app, using a rendering engine such as OpenGL, my battery stops charging entirely.
 Now even GLXGears causes this issue.
 I am using default Arch Kernel. I have tried using gamemode, but it doesn’t work.
 Never happened on Windows. I am running a NVIDIA dGPU. With TKG drivers.
    submitted by    /u/amogusdri-  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows Rollback: rimuovere il ripristino di Windows dal menu di avvio]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-Rollback-rimuovere-il-ripristino-di-Windows-dal-menu-di-avvio_24606</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-Rollback-rimuovere-il-ripristino-di-Windows-dal-menu-di-avvio_24606"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T15:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Se avete aggiornato Windows con l'installazione dell'ultimo feature update (sia nel caso di Windows 10 che di Windows 11) è possibile che a ogni successivo avvio della macchina compaia il menu di boot con la voce Windows Rollback. Quest'ultima permette di avviare una procedura di ripristino del sistema attingendo alle informazioni di backup salvate nella cartella Windows.old.Quando si installa un aggiornamento di Windows annuale (i feature update per Windows 10 e Windows 11 vengono rilasciati con questa cadenza), tutte le informazioni sulla precedente configurazione del sistema operativo vengono memorizzate nella cartella Windows.old.Assicurandosi che tutto funziona correttamente dopo l'aggiornamento alla nuova versione di Windows, per rimuovere Windows Rollback dal menu di avvio è possibile tenere in considerazione alcuni aspetti importanti:1) La voce Windows Rollback viene eliminata automaticamente insieme con tutto il contenuto della cartella Windows.old trascorsi 10 giorni dall'applicazione dell'aggiornamento.Se si volesse ottenere qualche giorno in più per controllare che il sistema e le applicazioni installate non presentano problemi, è possibile aumentare il numero di giorni per tornare alla versione precedente di Windows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Revive Your iPod with Rockbox in Linux]]></title>
        <id>http://maketecheasier.com/?p=16922</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15352894/untether-your-ipod-from-itunes-with-rockbox"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you owe an old iPod and are running Linux on your computer, you can use Rockbox to breathe life to your old music player. It enables you to use your iPod without iTunes while also improving on the default sound quality of the iPod. Rockbox is also customizable and really easy to install. Here we will show you how to use Rockbox in Linux.
   

Content

What is Rockbox and Why Install It
Which iPods Are Compatible with Rockbox
How to Obtain Rockbox
How to Install Rockbox in Linux
Detecting Your iPod in the Utility
Setting up the Rockbox Configuration Utility
Install Rockbox to Your iPod
Backing Up and Removing Rockbox
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:The Beginner’s Guide to Using Cron in Linux
    
What is Rockbox and Why Install It
    
Rockbox is an operating system for classic iPods. It is... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramces Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Package Groups, how to use it correctly?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v65rd3/package_groups_how_to_use_it_correctly/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v65rd3/package_groups_how_to_use_it_correctly/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T15:11:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is how I understand it - the only place that pacman saves group affiliation is the groups attribute in an individual packages' PKGBUILD file. And when I install a group, it is equivalent to install the individual packages, meaning the groups concept is more of a syntactic sugar, not much more than that. If that's all true, then I have a problem below:
 In abstract terms, if I install group G, which includes packages a, b, c, the three packages will be installed and marked as explicit by default. Now after some evolution package a dropped out of group G. All good, except that upgrades do not automatically remove a, even if it is not depended by any other installed packages, since it was marked explicit. If I remove group G, a would not be removed either since it is not in that group anymore.
 In reality, I think this was what happened when tracker-miner (the a above) package was removed from group gnome (G above) last week. After I did pacman -Rnsc gnome, package tracker-miner was still there.
 It makes me think package group (such as base-devel, gnome) approach is inferior to a meta-package (such as base). Am I missing something here? Hope someone can point to a better way to understand/use package group. BTW I love the arch distro and enjoy it a ton.
    submitted by    /u/notnullnone  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Translate Formulas in Microsoft Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=806220</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/806220/excel-translate-formula/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T15:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you and your team use versions of Excel in different languages, check out the Functions Translator. This Microsoft add-in can translate entire formulas or help you find the function you want in the language you need.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smartphone-Like App Folders May Come to Windows 11's Desktop]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120115/smartphone-like-app-folders-may-come-to-windows-11s-desktop/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120115/smartphone-like-app-folders-may-come-to-windows-11s-desktop/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T14:44:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Both Microsoft and its customers want more from the Windows 11 Start Menu. That’s why Microsoft is working on tidy little Start Menu app folders, which give you quick access to groups of apps. But oddly enough, this feature could extend to Windows 11’s desktop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dual-GPU setup AMD and NVIDIA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v655c5/dualgpu_setup_amd_and_nvidia/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v655c5/dualgpu_setup_amd_and_nvidia/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T14:44:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OS: Arch Linux btw x86_64
 Host: HP Pavilion Gaming Laptop 15-ec2xxx
 Kernel: 5.18.1-arch1-1
 DE: Plasma 5.24.5
 CPU: AMD Ryzen 5 5600H with Radeon Graphics (12) @ 3.300GHz
 GPU: NVIDIA GeForce RTX 3050 Mobile
 GPU: AMD ATI 05:00.0 Cezanne 
 Hello guys, I hope you all are doing good. I am new to linux and I have a friend who is using arch linux for 2 years but we are unable do dual-GPU setup with amd as iGPU for display and NVIDIA for other stuff like games. I need help with this and is it even possible to keep amd for display and nvidia for other things? 
 also, I had a question. When my friend helped me setup only nvidia gpu for everything from arch-wiki. It was working great for few hours and then suddenly my DE starts to lag alot (stutter). I am having this problem for a long time. I switched to arch a while ago too, I had the same problem. So, I had to switch back to windows 10 for sometime. does anybody know what was the reason of this issue? 
 Thanks in advance guys.
 Have a nice day!
    submitted by    /u/massiar  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some packages installed is newer than the mirrors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v64sm8/some_packages_installed_is_newer_than_the_mirrors/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v64sm8/some_packages_installed_is_newer_than_the_mirrors/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T14:28:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey guys, yesterday I have upgraded my system with pacman -Syyu and some packages as been upgraded and installed. Ok, just normal, but today I run the same command and received this warnings. Yesterday some mirrors is not working, but today they are fine. Is just some bug from mirrors (maybe delayed sync)?
    submitted by    /u/higorslva  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Italian city of Palermo shuts down all systems to fend off cyberattack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/italian-city-of-palermo-shuts-down-all-systems-to-fend-off-cyberattack/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/italian-city-of-palermo-shuts-down-all-systems-to-fend-off-cyberattack/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T14:13:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The municipality of Palermo in Southern Italy suffered a cyberattack on Friday, which appears to have had a massive impact on a broad range of operations and services to both citizens and visiting tourists. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Smart Displays of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=770546</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/770546/best-smart-display/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smart displays offer an elegant solution to all your smart home needs and make it easy to check your calendar, listen to music, or catch up with a video call. Here are the best smart displays you can buy right now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Bitner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come eliminare puntini e simboli P su Word]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/06/come-eliminare-puntini-e-simboli-p-su.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/06/come-eliminare-puntini-e-simboli-p-su.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T13:58:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chi non ha mai visto comparire su Word gli odiati puntini e le P rovesciate all'interno del documento su cui stavamo lavorando? Chi non conosce questi particolari segni andrà subito nel panico, visto che possono essere attivati per sbaglio e non è facile intuire, per chi non è esperto, come rimuoverli dal documento senza danneggiare il testo. 
Questi segni non sono errori, ma è una funzione...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why isn't screensharing working on teams? Only Powerpoint sharing?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v640hn/why_isnt_screensharing_working_on_teams_only/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v640hn/why_isnt_screensharing_working_on_teams_only/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T13:51:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the title says, I cant screenshare, only upload powerpoint files when in meetings. 
 I use Arch with i3 and Xorg, not Wayland. Im using the teams package on the AUR.
    submitted by    /u/copynfrog  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple WWDC 2022: How to Watch and What to Expect]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=808733</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/808733/apple-wwdc-2022-how-to-watch-and-what-to-expect/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple holds a Worldwide Developers Conference (WWDC) every year, and WWDC 2022 is quickly approaching. Here’s how to watch it, and what Apple might reveal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Documenti: cos'è il formato Senza pagine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Google-Documenti-cos-e-il-formato-Senza-pagine_24605</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Google-Documenti-cos-e-il-formato-Senza-pagine_24605"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T13:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google ha da poco integrato un'interessante novità nella sua suite per l'ufficio online. Google Documenti si arricchisce infatti del formato Senza pagine. Ma cos'è e a che cosa serve?Ormai siamo sempre più abituati a lavorare su documenti digitali che non vengono mai stampati. Google Documenti porta all'estremo il concetto di collaborazione: per creare documenti, fogli elettronici, presentazioni e altro ancora non è necessario installare nulla in locale; basta semplicemente servirsi di un qualunque dispositivo dotato di browser e connessione alla rete Internet. Anzi, attivando la modalità offline è possibile modificare i documenti senza neppure essere connessi: per procedere in tal senso basta accedere alla home page di Google Documenti, cliccare sul menu in alto a sinistra quindi sceglier…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix’s Movies Secret Codes You Probably Don’t Know]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/?p=60025</id>
        <link href="https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/netflix-special-codes/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T13:01:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What makes Netflix one of the most popular streaming services in the world? Well, there are dozens of reasons for that, but one of the top reasons is that]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hongkiat.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What You Need to Know About Speaker Wiring Cables]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=802075</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/802075/what-you-need-to-know-about-speaker-wiring-cables/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T13:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to speakers, the wires or cables you use are important. They may not affect the sound quality overall, but if you want everything to work properly, make sure you’re using the right tool for the job.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kris Wouk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SteelSeries Aerox 5 Mouse Review: Lightweight and Customizable]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117854/steelseries-aerox-5-mouse-review-lightweight-and-customizable/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117854/steelseries-aerox-5-mouse-review-lightweight-and-customizable/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T13:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A great mouse is an underrated addition to your desk setup, regardless of whether you typically game or work at your desk. A regular old desk mouse isn’t customizable or attractive and often makes your wrist uncomfortable. The SteelSeries Aerox 5 mouse solves all the problems standard mice present, and I thoroughly enjoyed my experience with it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Chaney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DaVinci Resolve has a window bigger than my screen]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v62rgo/davinci_resolve_has_a_window_bigger_than_my_screen/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v62rgo/davinci_resolve_has_a_window_bigger_than_my_screen/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T12:48:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The DaVinci Resolve installed throught the AUR don't fit my screen and I can't shrink he's window, using the official installation method results in the same thing. I am using Gnome on X.Org.
 https://imgur.com/a/cNksqSv
    submitted by    /u/nashira_deer  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here's Everything Coming to Netflix the Week of June 6, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lifesavvy.com/131625/heres-everything-coming-to-netflix-the-week-of-june-6-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lifesavvy.com/131625/heres-everything-coming-to-netflix-the-week-of-june-6-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T12:30:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week is a good one for Netflix fans. Not only dos a hit series return for another season, but an anticipated adaptation also hits streaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shea Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Correggere errori disco con Chkdsk (Scan Disk) su Windows 10 e 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2007/07/controllo-errori-sul-disco-con-scandisk.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2007/07/controllo-errori-sul-disco-con-scandisk.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T12:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Se durante l'utilizzo del PC per lavoro o per studio si verificano errori di caricamento dei programmi, se improvvisamente Windows non risponde più a nessun comando da tastiera o dal mouse o vediamo comparire la schermata blu dell'errore fatale in molti casi il problema è generato da un errore del disco interno. Questo errore può essere sia di origine hardware (e quindi siamo a rischio di rottura...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux 5.19 Features: AMD SEV-SNP + Zen 4 Prep, Intel TDX + IFS, LoongArch, Big TCP, Apple M1 NVMe]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31179</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31179"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T10:30:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the Linux 5.19 merge window complete, here is my usual look at all of the interesting changes I've been watching for this next version of the Linux kernel. Linux 5.19 is quite a big summer time upgrade to this open-source kernel with many new and improved features coming for this kernel that will debut as stable in late July.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers May Make Switch from Ransomware to BEC]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=495230</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15352292/hackers-ransomware-to-bec"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T10:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We often report here on new malware attacks and mention that it’s a constant back-and-forth action, with hackers and law enforcement changing their methods to combat the other better. With the law pushing back more on ransomware, hackers may turn more toward business email compromise (BEC).
   
Also read:iPhones Vulnerable to Malware Even When Powered Down
    
What Is BEC?
    
Before we can compare business email compromise and ransomware, we need to learn what BEC is. In this hacking method, cybercriminals break through corporate email accounts to issue fake invoices or contracts. The goal is for these emails to look legitimate enough to trick businesses into sending money, thinking it’s just another bill they’re required to pay.
   
 Image source: Unsplash
   
Many BEC attacks originate in Nigeria, West Africa. The methods are based more on the effort of trickery... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Giveaway: TurboLab.it regala Uranium Backup Gold]]></title>
        <id>3544|20220606121319</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/giveaway-755/giveaway-turbolab.it-regala-uranium-backup-gold-3544"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T10:13:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Uranium Backup è un software per la gestione delle copie di sicurezza che, nella prova pubblicata qualche tempo fa, ci ha convinti completamente grazie ad un enorme numero di funzionalità e opzioni che lo rendono altamente personalizzabile in base alle specifiche necessità dell'utente, persino di quelle dello smanettone più esigente. Uranium Backup è disponibile anche in edizione "free", ma oggi, grazie ad una collaborazione fra TurboLab.it e lo sviluppatore Nanosystems, abbiamo a disposizione alcune licenze omaggio della completissima versione "Gold". Gli interessati devono però sbrigarsi e richiederla subito
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to run Thunderbird Beta next to the Stable email client]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178974</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/06/how-to-run-thunderbird-beta-next-to-the-stable-email-client/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T09:45:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The email client Thunderbird is available in several editions. Most users use the stable version of the email client, but some may be interested in running the beta and nightly editions of […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post How to run Thunderbird Beta next to the Stable email client appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux 5.19 Frowns On x86/x86_64 Late Microcode Loading - "It's Just Lottery & Broken"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-Late-ucode-Loading</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-Late-ucode-Loading"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T09:28:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A last minute change sent in on Sunday and merged prior to Linux 5.19-rc1 disables late microcode loading by default for x86/x86_64 processors over its sad state of affairs...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More Old GLSL Code Is Gutted From Mesa 22.2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Mesa-GLSL-Unrolling-Delete</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Mesa-GLSL-Unrolling-Delete"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T09:18:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's not only the Linux kernel that's been seeing some spring cleaning but Mesa developers have also been quite busy on working to remove some old, poorly maintained code from their open-source 3D driver components...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[AUR] User "BioArchLinuxBot" just added over 2000 new packages - 2,71% of the repository]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v5yocj/aur_user_bioarchlinuxbot_just_added_over_2000_new/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v5yocj/aur_user_bioarchlinuxbot_just_added_over_2000_new/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T09:12:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The packages are probably all libraries for R. At the moment, he has 2089 packages out of 76961 packages that exist in total in the AUR. That makes 2,71%. He created the first package yesterday. You can find all his packages here.
    submitted by    /u/Spixmaster  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to force Xorg to use integrated graphics instead of NVIDIA GPU]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v5ymfu/how_to_force_xorg_to_use_integrated_graphics/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v5ymfu/how_to_force_xorg_to_use_integrated_graphics/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T09:09:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My laptop (Acer Predator Helios 300) has an Intel CPU which has graphics support built into it. My laptop also has a dedicated GPU (NVIDIA GeForce RTX 3070 Mobile). I know that battery life on Linux is not that great but on my laptop I can barely get 2 hours of battery life tops. Therefore I am looking at ways to increase my battery life.
 Since I only use my GPU for some CUDA programing, I was planning to turn it off when I am not using it. For this I am using PRIME. I modified /etc/udev/rules.d/80-nvidia-pm.rules and /etc/modprobe.d/nvidia-pm.conf as per the instructions on archwiki. However, even after this, I am unable to get better battery life. I am also running auto-cpufreq improve the battery life further. While I was investigating this issue, I decided to check if my GPU was really off or not.
 Here the screenshot of nvidia-smi and here is the screenshot of nvtop. I think these screenshots indicate that Xorg is running on the NVIDIA GPU and not on integrated graphics.
 Also I am using i3blocks's GPU block to view the usage. Could this be the reason why my GPU is always active?
 So, can anybody tell me how can I force Xorg to use the integrated graphics instead of the dedicated GPU so that I may be able to increase my battery life.
 Thanks
    submitted by    /u/pr0_Disappointment  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Look at Titan Linux -- Customized Debian Stable]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178968</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/06/titan-linux-review/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T09:01:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was talking with a friend of mine about Linux distributions, and he asked me if I had ever heard of Titan Linux, to which I replied I had not. He told […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post A Look at Titan Linux -- Customized Debian Stable appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Turcotte-McCusker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Comprare Windows 11 su chiavetta USB: la nuova iniziativa Microsoft]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Comprare-Windows-11-su-chiavetta-USB-la-nuova-iniziativa-Microsoft_24492</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Comprare-Windows-11-su-chiavetta-USB-la-nuova-iniziativa-Microsoft_24492"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T08:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I supporti DVD sono ormai obsoleti tanto che nessun PC in commercio dispone più un lettore di dischi ottici. Così Microsoft si aggiorna e nel caso di Windows 11, sistema operativo pubblicato in versione finale il 5 ottobre 2021, ha iniziato a proporre chiavette USB per l'installazione del sistema operativo.Ricordiamo che gli utenti di Windows 10 e delle precedenti versioni di Windows possono aggiornare gratis a Windows 11 utilizzando un Product Key o una licenza digitale riferibili alla medesima edizione del sistema operativo.Ad esempio, Windows 10 Pro può essere aggiornato a Windows 11 Pro ma non è possibile passare direttamente da Windows 10 Home a Windows 11 Pro.Iniziando dagli Stati Uniti (la stessa iniziativa sarà presumibilmente estesa presto anche all'Europa), Microsoft ha cominciato a commercializzare Windows 11 su chiavetta USB: si tratta di una classica versione 'in scatola' che permette l'installazione del più recente sistema operativo in versione Retail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripristino app di Windows 11: utile ma supporta soltanto il Microsoft Store]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Ripristino-app-di-Windows-11-utile-ma-supporta-soltanto-il-Microsoft-Store_24604</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Ripristino-app-di-Windows-11-utile-ma-supporta-soltanto-il-Microsoft-Store_24604"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T08:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quanto sarebbe comodo se Windows permettesse di ripristinare i programmi che si utilizzano abitualmente al momento della configurazione di un nuovo PC?L'azienda guidata da Satya Nadella sta finalmente guardando a questa possibilità che però resta limitata al solo Microsoft Store: ciò significa che su un nuovo dispositivo Windows 11, dopo aver effettuato il login con il proprio account utente, è possibile chiedere il ripristino di tutte le app. Il Microsoft Store richiede se si vogliano davvero caricare le app utilizzate sul vecchio PC installandole sul sistema in uso.

Cliccando sull'icona Raccolta del Microsoft Store, la nuova funzionalità presto restituirà l'elenco completo delle app associate con l'account utente. Sarà quindi possibile ripristinare tutte le app 'in un colpo solo' oppure selezionarne soltanto alcune.Il sistema può funzionare perché utilizza una piattaforma comune, il Microsoft Store appunto, e poggia sulle informazioni conservate sul cloud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Edge Drop: per inviare file a tutti i propri dispositivi]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Edge-Drop-per-inviare-file-a-tutti-i-propri-dispositivi_24603</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Edge-Drop-per-inviare-file-a-tutti-i-propri-dispositivi_24603"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T07:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nella versione Canary di Edge i tecnici di Microsoft hanno aggiunto una nuova caratteristica che sarà prossimamente inserita anche nella release stabile del browser.La novità si chiama Edge Drop: si tratta di uno strumento che consente di trasferire testi, note e file da un'istanza del browser all'altra.Si supponga di utilizzare più sistemi sui quali si è effettuato il login con il medesimo account utente Microsoft: con Edge Drop gli utenti possono condividere file e altre risorse tra tutti i dispositivi sotto il proprio diretto controllo.Edge Drop utilizza OneDrive (viene creata una cartella dedicata) come supporto per il trasferimento dei dati: quando l'utente decide di 'mettere a fattor comune' una risorsa questa viene caricata sul cloud di Microsoft e condivisa esclusivamente con i dispositivi che usano lo stesso account.La nuova funzione appare sotto forma di icona a destra della barra degli indirizzi del browser Microsoft (è attivabile anche dalla sezione Aspetto delle impostazioni: edge://settings/appearance).Cliccando sull'icona di Edge Drop appare una barra laterale attraverso la quale è possibile selezionare i file che devono essere oggetto di condivisione.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows Autopatch: cos'è. Gli aggiornamenti si installano da soli]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-Autopatch-cos-e-Gli-aggiornamenti-si-installano-da-soli_24602</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-Autopatch-cos-e-Gli-aggiornamenti-si-installano-da-soli_24602"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T07:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft ha pubblicato l'anteprima pubblica di Windows Autopatch, un nuovo meccanismo per l'aggiornamento dei sistemi aziendali, che prevede la gestione e l'applicazione automatica delle patch disponibili.Con Windows Autopatch gli aggiornamenti non vengono più scaricati e installati con Windows Update perché tutto il processo è elaborato sul cloud da parte di Microsoft. Vengono comunque utilizzati alcuni dei componenti software alla base del funzionamento di Windows Update for Business per gestire gli aggiornamenti.Windows Autopatch non può essere utilizzato nell'ambito di domini locali Active Directory ma solo ed esclusivamente con Azure AD, anche in configurazione ibrida. Si rivolge quindi agli utenti in possesso di una licenza Windows 10/11 Enterprise E3 o superiore ed è gratuito.In un video pubblicato su YouTube Microsoft illustra i passaggi necessari per attivare Windows Autopatch: è necessario effettuare il login su Endpoint Manager come amministratore globale quindi cercare Windows Autopatch nel menu principale.Dopo aver configurato un tenant in Azure AD, Windows Autopatch suddivide automaticamente i dispositivi usati in azienda in quattro gruppi indicati da Microsoft come 'rings', 'anelli' in italiano.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Edge Drop: transfer files between all Edge instances on all devices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178963</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/06/microsoft-edge-drop-transfer-files-between-all-edge-instances-on-all-devices/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T05:04:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft is testing a new feature called Drop in the Canary version of the company's Edge web browser. Drop allows Edge users to transfer files and notes between all Edge instances on […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Microsoft Edge Drop: transfer files between all Edge instances on all devices appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some days I like nvidia for all their cool hardware, other days I hate them for the crappy drivers; this week has been a lot of the latter.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v5sif6/some_days_i_like_nvidia_for_all_their_cool/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v5sif6/some_days_i_like_nvidia_for_all_their_cool/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T02:20:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I updated my laptop to kernel 5.18 and bam! Kernel panic ensues because of nvidia drivers messing stuff up.
 For context, I had just started an internship this week and finished setting up my laptop with all the software/services I'd need. I restart my laptop to get everything in working order. I restart and it would just die on me after boot (it would be on but no io).
 Luckily I had a spare desktop, and after setting that up I could get to some work over the weekend, but that still put me through a lot of stress.
 I spent half my weekend diagnosing the issue and it was Nvidia's fault:
 https://github.com/NVIDIA/open-gpu-kernel-modules/issues/256
 I switched to nouveau and things are usable now.
 Sorry and thanks for listening to my rant.
  
Yes, once I found the issue I was also able to find the PSA on Reddit for this exact thing. Thanks for it, I wasn't able to make best use of it but hopefully someone else would.
    submitted by    /u/frustrated-nerd  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I almost gave up on Arch today]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v5rs9d/i_almost_gave_up_on_arch_today/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v5rs9d/i_almost_gave_up_on_arch_today/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T01:39:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I almost gave up on Arch today when I manually edited /etc/pacman.d/mirrorlists and messed it all up. Then I RTFM and fixed it... lesson learned so it's all good...
    submitted by    /u/blue_y59  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can't use PrtScr key for shortcuts (Budgie DE)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v5rfis/cant_use_prtscr_key_for_shortcuts_budgie_de/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v5rfis/cant_use_prtscr_key_for_shortcuts_budgie_de/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T01:19:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone! I'm trying to set up my Arch installation so that pressing the PrtScr key will open an interactive screenshot prompt to allow me to select a portion of the screen. I'm using the Budgie desktop environment with gnome-screenshot.
 On the surface, this sounds easy—according to the keyboard shortcuts, I just press the PrtScr key (image)!
 But pressing the PrtScr key takes a full-screen screenshot (with a white border flash and saving to Pictures). And disabling that shortcut doesn't change anything—it still takes a full-screen screenshot and saves it to Pictures. 
 If I uninstall gnome-screenshot, it stops taking screenshots when I press PrtScr. But when I assign the PrtScr button to any other shortcuts (for example, to launch Flameshot, another screenshot utility), nothing happens when I press it.
 So my problem is that: 
  
When gnome-screenshot is installed, I can only use PrtScr to take a full-screen screenshot.
 When gnome-screenshot is uninstalled, I can't use PrtScr for any other shortcuts.
  
Does anybody know what's going on here?
    submitted by    /u/TheKingElessar  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lenovo z50-70 with 4th gen i7 is unusually slow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v5qx5t/lenovo_z5070_with_4th_gen_i7_is_unusually_slow/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v5qx5t/lenovo_z5070_with_4th_gen_i7_is_unusually_slow/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T00:51:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/IllMakeItIn  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux 5.19-rc1 Released With Intel TDX, AMD SEV-SNP, LoongArch, Big TCP & A Lot More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-rc1</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-rc1"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T00:47:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following a rather eventful Linux 5.19 merge window the past two weeks, Linus Torvalds just released Linux 5.19-rc1. It's a great way coincidentally to mark the end of the Phoronix 18th birthday...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ambilight per PC: le luci ambientali fai-da-te con Firefly Luciferin]]></title>
        <id>3592|20220606000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/giochi-videogiochi-passatempi-1088/ambilight-pc-luci-ambientali-fai-te-firefly-luciferin-3592"/>
        <updated>2022-06-05T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Il 'Bias lighting' è un tipo di luce che si installa nel retro di uno schermo con lo scopo di rendere più gradevole l'ambiente visivo. Grazie ad un progetto italiano fai-da-te puoi applicare questa tecnica allo schermo del PC con una spesa contenuta e dal risultato incredibile.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fix ‘No SIM Card Detected’ Error on Android and iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=256766</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/9158225/fix-no-sim-card-detected-android"/>
        <updated>2022-06-05T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are various reasons why your Android or iOS device won’t read the SIM card. Some possible causes could be that you didn’t insert the SIM card correctly or your device is experiencing a software issue. Whatever the reason, a solution needs to be found quickly when your phone says: “No SIM card detected.”
    
Here are some fixes for those times when your phone can’t detect the SIM card. 
    
Note: Depending on the brand and model of your phone, some of the settings may not be available in the same locations as discussed below. For example, for certain settings, you may have to navigate to “Network & Internet -> Mobile Networks” instead of “SIM cards & Mobile Networks” on some phones.
   

Content

1. Reboot or Shut Down Your Phone
2. Switch Your SIM Card On
3. Change the Network Mode to Auto
4. Choose the Correct Network Operator
5. Enter Your Network APN Settings Manually
6. Remove the SIM Card and Battery
7. Try Using Your Phone in Safe Mode
8. Airplane Mode Solution
9. Fix the SIM Card Error by Clearing the Cache
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ojash Yadav</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Change the Alarm Volume on iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=749875</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/749875/how-to-change-the-alarm-volume-on-iphone/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-05T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is your iPhone’s alarm volume too quiet or too loud for you? Whether you’re getting up at sunrise or just need a reminder, you can finetune the alarm so that you’ll never miss an alarm and also won’t be totally jarred by it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[System rebooting while asleep?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v5m1ab/system_rebooting_while_asleep/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v5m1ab/system_rebooting_while_asleep/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-05T20:37:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi All,
 I've been having a very weird issue with my system for a while. Whenever my laptop's been in sleep mode (lid closed) for a while (it seems to be only when it's been closed for a few hours), I'll open it up only to be presented with the luks prompt, meaning that it's rebooted itself while in sleep mode.
 I used to not have any swap, but I recently set up a swap file (12G for my 8G RAM) for hibernation. I've confirmed that hibernation works flawlessly, but for some reason, this issue persists. The output from journalctl doesn't seem to provide any useful info, I'll paste it here.
 Jun 05 15:33:22 sputnik kernel: sd 2:0:0:0: [sda] Synchronizing SCSI cache
 Jun 05 15:33:22 sputnik kernel: sd 2:0:0:0: [sda] Stopping disk
 Jun 05 15:33:28 sputnik kernel: ata3: SATA link up 6.0 Gbps (SSt…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ancestry's Latest Tool Allows You to Colorize Old Family Photos]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120041/ancestrys-latest-tool-allows-you-to-colorize-old-family-photos/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120041/ancestrys-latest-tool-allows-you-to-colorize-old-family-photos/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-05T20:04:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Investigating your family’s origins can be fun and rewarding. But go back very far, and you’ll run into an issue with history: color photography. In the grand scheme of things, color photos haven’t been around very long. Now Ancestry.com has a fun new tool to help automatically colorize old photos.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Hendrickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can You Delete an Amazon Order from Your History?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=751673</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/751673/can-i-delete-an-amazon-order-from-my-history/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-05T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve bought something on Amazon.com that you don’t want to show up in your order history, you can’t delete it, but you can hide it using an “archive” feature. We’ll show you how to do it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is there an alternative to windows' chkdsk?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v5kxd5/is_there_an_alternative_to_windows_chkdsk/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v5kxd5/is_there_an_alternative_to_windows_chkdsk/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-05T19:42:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I must admit that the chkdsk command on windows is extremely useful for fixing almost every drive issue. Is there any linux alternative with the same efficiency?
    submitted by    /u/AlpinDale  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No CUDA device in software that requires it (Blender and OBS)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v5kh91/no_cuda_device_in_software_that_requires_it/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v5kh91/no_cuda_device_in_software_that_requires_it/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-05T19:20:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm running a GTX 750 Ti (compute capability 5.0) and I've been trying to fix this issue on several distros (OpenSuse, Void and Arch) with no effects. Not only the software like Blender and OBS can't seem to find the CUDA device, but it's also a system-wide thing (seen in deviceQuery logs). Installing CUDA manually on Void didn't help either. Alas, running Arch on my second HDD and installing CUDA through pacman also did nothing. It's driving me nuts because when I tried using Blender on the same machine with Windows 10 it worked like a charm and I'm not planning to switch back any time soon. Searching online gave me pretty bad results, either the forum posts were dead and inactive or people managed to fix it by rebooting their PC (which is amusing as I've had this issue for about a year n…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can somebody help? i messed up pretty badly.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v5k7u2/can_somebody_help_i_messed_up_pretty_badly/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v5k7u2/can_somebody_help_i_messed_up_pretty_badly/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-05T19:08:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greetings fellow Arch users.
 I'v been on Arch for about 4 months. It worked flawlessly until today when i decided to switch the UI language to German. I have the Cinnamon DE and the original install was made in English, but the keyboard was set to German since day 1. 
 As i couldn't find the language settings in Cinnamon, I followed this guide : 
 https://arcolinux.com/how-to-change-the-language-of-your-desktop-on-arcolinux-or-arch-linux-any-desktop/
 After reboot, i could not launch the terminal anymore but the GUI worked and it was in German.
 I began freaking out and went frantically to revert the changes i made using a GUI. I was succesful in reverting both the locale.gen and locale.conf using a text editor and a hex editor, respectivelly.
 After reboot the UI reverted back to English but i still cannot launch the terminal. And my system is now pretty useless. I cannot live without the terminal lol.
    submitted by    /u/Tiny-Refrigerator-98  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Change Your Phone Number on Amazon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=807034</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/807034/how-to-change-phone-number-on-amazon/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-05T19:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you’ve changed your phone number or you’d like to use a different number in your account, Amazon makes changing phone numbers in your account as easy as changing your password. We’ll show you how to do this from your desktop and your mobile phone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wiping the Main Disk]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v5jnhu/wiping_the_main_disk/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v5jnhu/wiping_the_main_disk/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-05T18:40:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I want to wipe my current main ssd which has arch (Installed from a rep) , to reinstall it again manually
    submitted by    /u/Titan_D  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AT&T's "Flying COWs" Bring Internet to the Boonies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120047/atts-flying-cows-bring-internet-to-the-boonies/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120047/atts-flying-cows-bring-internet-to-the-boonies/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-05T18:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Those who live in rural areas could gain 5G access thanks to an experimental new drone. The AT&T 5G Flying COW broadcasts a strong 5G signal within a range of about 10 miles. It’s a stunning and strange achievement, partially aided by tethering the drone for power.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Remove Shortcuts From the Google Chrome New Tab Page]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=803684</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/803684/remove-shortcuts-from-chrome-new-tab-page/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-05T18:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Chrome keeps shortcuts to your most visited sites on its home page. If you don’t find this list useful, you can either individually remove these shortcuts or hide all the shortcuts at once. We’ll show you how to do that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Phoronix Turns 18 Years Old For Covering Linux Hardware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Phoronix-18</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Phoronix-18"/>
        <updated>2022-06-05T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was eighteen years ago today that I started Phoronix.com to focus on Linux hardware reviews. Back then it was difficult getting peripherals working under Linux from 56k modems to printers and other components today where Linux support can just be assumed. Open-source graphics drivers back then were also in their infancy and lacking vendor support while NVIDIA was well regarded then for their proprietary driver being at least featureful and performant. It's been quite a journey...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hardware Timestamping Engine Subsystem Merged For Linux 5.19]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-HTE</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-HTE"/>
        <updated>2022-06-05T17:34:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While just a day prior Linus Torvalds was questioning the proposed "HTE" subsystem, today on this final day of the Linux 5.19 merge window he decided to land this new subsystem...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hard vs. Soft Mouse Pad: Which Is Better?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=803517</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/803517/hard-vs.-soft-mouse-pad-which-is-better/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-05T17:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hard mouse pads provide a smooth, level surface for your mouse to glide across quickly. Soft pads can do the same thing, so which is better? Let’s discuss the differences to see which you might prefer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Nguyen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploit released for Atlassian Confluence RCE bug, patch now]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/exploit-released-for-atlassian-confluence-rce-bug-patch-now/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/exploit-released-for-atlassian-confluence-rce-bug-patch-now/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-05T16:41:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Proof-of-concept exploits for the actively exploited critical CVE-2022-26134 vulnerability impacting Atlassian Confluence and Data Center servers have been widely released this weekend. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Plasma auto-hide floating panels]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v5h446/plasma_autohide_floating_panels/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v5h446/plasma_autohide_floating_panels/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-05T16:36:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Has anyone tried having a floating panel with auto hide? Running on X11 with nvidia GPU and it shows the animation of it disappearing but statys visible underneath. Full size panels auto hide with no problem.
    submitted by    /u/MCManiac52  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The LEGO Ferrari Daytona SP3 Set Gets a Sweet Designer Video]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120051/the-lego-ferrari-daytona-sp3-set-gets-a-sweet-designer-video/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120051/the-lego-ferrari-daytona-sp3-set-gets-a-sweet-designer-video/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-05T16:34:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re a fan of LEGO and are considering the epic new LEGO Ferrari Daytona SP3 Edition that came out on June 1st, we have a treat for you. After nearly six months without a new Designer Video, LEGO just released a new one, giving us a look under that cherry red Ferrari hood.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Old nvidia drivers issue?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v5guv6/old_nvidia_drivers_issue/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v5guv6/old_nvidia_drivers_issue/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-05T16:24:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone, arch newbie here. 
 I am trying to finish the installation but obviously I do not have the proper drivers for my machine. I am using NX8600GT card and all I can run is the command prompt. Any ideas about how should I proceed please? Pretty much everything is set up - the system is installed, the accounts are set, the system is upgraded, I have installed the fonts and SDDM + KDE Plasma but no luck so far! The wiki articles are big help but some of them are just too advanced since I am a newbie and this is my first Arch installation. 
 Thanks in advance for all the help!
    submitted by    /u/AardvarkDeep  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anything Chromium randomly freezes when doing anything]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v5ge44/anything_chromium_randomly_freezes_when_doing/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v5ge44/anything_chromium_randomly_freezes_when_doing/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-05T16:02:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have this weird issue lately where anything that uses chromium engine (Brave, Electron apps, Steam, etc.) just randomly freezes when I'm doing something like clicking on a link, typing on a text box, or loading a video. It won't response to my clicks or my keyboard input. It happens for few second before the program becomes responsive again. 
 The frequency is unpredictable. Sometimes Brave never freeze on one session, sometimes it freezes many times under an hour of use.
 Has this happened to anyone? I have Lenovo Yoga Slim 7 with Ryzen 5 4600U (no discrete GPU) and running on LTS kernel 5.15 and xorg server (dwm).
 Edit: Intellij IDEA is not an electron app and I may misremember it being frozen along with Brave.
    submitted by    /u/Rilukian  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can You Plug a Surge Protector Into a Surge Protector?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=804157</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/804157/can-you-plug-a-surge-protector-into-a-surge-protector/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-05T16:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many people wonder whether it’s a good idea to connect two surge protectors, either to provide additional protection or to gain access to more power outlets. The simple answer is no, and for good reason.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Recover Deleted Text Messages on Android]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=post-ideas&amp;p=309020</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/12698100/recover-deleted-text-messages-android"/>
        <updated>2022-06-05T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you accidentally deleted an important text message from your Android phone, you’re probably wondering how you can get it back. In all honesty, your chances of recovering it are not stellar, especially if you deleted the text a long time ago. Yet, there is some hope on the horizon for those who constantly back up their data. This tutorial shows you how to recover deleted text messages on Android.
   

Content

What Does It Mean to Delete Text Messages from Your Android Phone?
Use Google Drive Backup to Restore Texts on Android
Check Your Carrier App (If Available)
Reach Out to the Sender/Recipient
Back Up and Restore Messages Using a Third-Party SMS App
Other Third-Party Software
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Lock Photos and Text Messages on Android
    
What Does It Mean to Delete Text Messages from Your Android Phone?
... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexandra Arici</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evasive phishing mixes reverse tunnels and URL shortening services]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/evasive-phishing-mixes-reverse-tunnels-and-url-shortening-services/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/evasive-phishing-mixes-reverse-tunnels-and-url-shortening-services/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-05T15:06:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security researchers are seeing an uptick in the use of reverse tunnel services along with URL shorteners​​​​​​​ for large-scale phishing campaigns, making the malicious activity more difficult to stop. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Pageless Format in Google Docs, and How Do You Use It?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=803944</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/803944/pageless-format-google-docs/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-05T15:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you want to insert a wide table or large image in your document that doesn’t shrink? Do you have no plans to print your document? Check out Pageless format in Google Docs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft: Windows Autopatch now available for public preview]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-windows-autopatch-now-available-for-public-preview/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-windows-autopatch-now-available-for-public-preview/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-05T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has announced this week that Windows Autopatch, a service to automatically keep Windows and Microsoft 365 software up to date in enterprise environments, has now reached public preview. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Monitors for Mac of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=792273</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/792273/best-monitor-for-mac/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-05T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you are upgrading your existing setup or looking to add some extra screen real estate to your MacBook, a good monitor is a wise investment. Here are our picks for the best monitors for Mac.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gaurav Shukla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>