<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-04-27T01:59:56.940Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 Tools to Track Your Steam Stats, Deals, Spending and Play Time]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=309881</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/12732007/tools-see-steam-spending-play-time-achievement-stats"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Player stats are a staple metric in video games, so why aren’t they front and center on your Steam profile? Moreover, you’re probably looking for the best deals on the titles you want to play. Luckily, there are free third-party tools and websites to see how much you’re spending money- and time-wise on Steam and find the best prices on games. To do this, you need to find your Steam ID and set your profile to public.
   

Content

How to Find Your Steam ID
Set Your Steam Profile to Public
1. IsThereAnyDeal
2. Steam Gauge
3. Completionist.me
4. HowLongToBeat
5. Steamtime
6. SteamCalculator
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}    
How to Find Your Steam ID
    
Your Steam ID is a a 17-digit identifier by default or any custom ID you set that’s tied to your account. It’s not the username you use to log in to your account, and you can find it just by logging in to your Steam account through the Steam client or website.
    
In the Steam client:
   ... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Natalie dela Vega</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Errors when trying to replace mariadb with mysql]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ucpdl4/errors_when_trying_to_replace_mariadb_with_mysql/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ucpdl4/errors_when_trying_to_replace_mariadb_with_mysql/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T23:09:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the error I get. It wont let me remove mariadb either because akonadi depends on it, and I can't remove akonadi because kdepim-runtime depends on it.
 ​
 error: failed to commit transaction (conflicting files)
 mysql: /usr/bin/mysql_upgrade exists in filesystem (owned by mariadb-clients)
 mysql: /usr/bin/mysqlbinlog exists in filesystem (owned by mariadb-clients)
 mysql: /usr/bin/mysqltest exists in filesystem (owned by mariadb-clients)
 mysql: /usr/share/man/man1/mysql_upgrade.1.gz exists in filesystem (owned by mariadb-clients)
 mysql: /usr/share/man/man1/mysqlbinlog.1.gz exists in filesystem (owned by mariadb-clients)
 Errors occurred, no packages were upgraded.
 -> exit status 1
    submitted by    /u/SeaworthinessNo293  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s on your arch install?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ucohzl/whats_on_your_arch_install/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ucohzl/whats_on_your_arch_install/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T22:27:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In other words, what are the go-to packages you install right away on a new system?
    submitted by    /u/Upbeat_Asparagus_351  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome 101 Released With Priority Hints, Federated Credential Management API]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Chrome-101-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Chrome-101-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T22:14:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome 101 is out today as stable for the newest feature update to Google's cross-platform web browser...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come installare l'emulatore di Android, senza Android Studio [Linux][MacOS][Windows]]]></title>
        <id>3558|20220427000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/android-28/come-installare-emulatore-android-senza-android-studio-linuxmacoswindows-3558"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[L'emulatore di Android messo a disposizione da Google è sicuramente il migliore che possiamo trovare dato che quasi ogni app rilasciata sul PlayStore è stata molto probabilmente testata proprio su questo programma. Di solito fa parte della suite Android Studio che contiene tutti i componenti e i programmi necessari per creare app per Android ma se vogliamo solo l'emulatore e poco altro è possibile averlo senza per forza installare tutta la suite. Dato che sarà un installazione minimale, dovremo utilizzare la linea di comando per configurare e avviare l'emulatore, il che non è affatto un male perché questo metodo di interazione con il computer è uno dei più efficienti che ci sia!
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Installed it on a spare laptop. After doing reboot I’m stuck in the boot menu and I don’t know how to get out.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ucnr8i/installed_it_on_a_spare_laptop_after_doing_reboot/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ucnr8i/installed_it_on_a_spare_laptop_after_doing_reboot/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T21:52:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This on a spare laptop with uefi and I follows distrotube’s guide.
    submitted by    /u/username2J  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel 5.17.4 seems to have broken my scripts which use /sys/bus/pci - help?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ucni1p/kernel_5174_seems_to_have_broken_my_scripts_which/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ucni1p/kernel_5174_seems_to_have_broken_my_scripts_which/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T21:40:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, I updated my system recently - my kernel version is now 5.17.4-arch1-1. I have some scripts which reset a GPU which I passthrough to a VM which seem to have stopped working. I get either "permission denied" even with sudo, or the shell locks up and doesn't even respond properly to Ctrl+C. When I shut down the machine it also hangs indefinitely waiting for a virtualisation demon stop job to complete. Anyone seen this or have any ideas?
 echo "1" > /sys/bus/pci/devices/0000\:4d\:00.0//remove echo "1" > /sys/bus/pci/devices/0000\:4d\:00.1//remove echo "1" > /sys/bus/pci/devices/0000\:4d\:00.2//remove echo "1" > /sys/bus/pci/devices/0000\:4d\:00.3//remove echo "1" > /sys/bus/pci/rescan 
    submitted by    /u/kieranvs  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Invalid PGP Signature]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ucncb0/invalid_pgp_signature/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ucncb0/invalid_pgp_signature/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T21:33:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I tried updating my system earlier and I got this:
 error: libinih: signature from "Maxime Gauduin <[alucryd@gmail.com](mailto:alucryd@gmail.com)>" is marginal trust
 :: File /var/cache/pacman/pkg/libinih-55-2-x86_64.pkg.tar.zst is corrupted (invalid or corrupted package (PGP signature)).
 Do you want to delete it? [Y/n]
 error: failed to commit transaction (invalid or corrupted package)
 Errors occurred, no packages were upgraded.
 ​
 ​
 Not sure whether I shouldn't delete that signature. Would it be safe to not delete it?
    submitted by    /u/Prizefighter-Mercury  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Disable Computer Notifications on Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=post-ideas&amp;p=473515</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15251219/disable-computer-notifications"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows devices have a variety of system and app notifications (sometimes incorrectly called program pop-ups) that alert you about events happening in real time. Be it incoming VoIP calls, Outlook calendar reminders, or frequent prompts for a Windows version update, they might all seem equally urgent.
    
However that’s not always the case; and even if it were, any user action required from you can easily wait a bit longer. Notifications can be especially annoying when you’re hard at work or enjoying your favorite game or TV show.
    
To stop these alerts from being intrusive, we recommend disabling them, hiding them temporarily, or enabling only the important ones. We’ll show you how to do disable computer notifications on Windows.
   

Content

How to Permanently Disable Notifications 
How to Dismiss Notifications
How to Disable Specific App Notifications
How to Temporarily Hide Notifications With Focus Assist
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sayak Boral</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US offers $10 million reward for tips on Russian Sandworm hackers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-offers-10-million-reward-for-tips-on-russian-sandworm-hackers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-offers-10-million-reward-for-tips-on-russian-sandworm-hackers/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T21:20:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. is offering up to $10 million to identify or locate six Russian GRU hackers who are part of the notorious Sandworm hacking group. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emotet malware now installs via PowerShell in Windows shortcut files]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/emotet-malware-now-installs-via-powershell-in-windows-shortcut-files/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/emotet-malware-now-installs-via-powershell-in-windows-shortcut-files/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T21:17:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Emotet botnet is now using Windows shortcut files (.LNK) containing PowerShell commands to infect victims computers, moving away from Microsoft Office macros that are now disabled by default. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Ilascu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Cancel Your Netflix Subscription]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=662944</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/662944/how-to-cancel-your-netflix-subscription/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re looking to save some money, don’t enjoy the price hikes, or no longer enjoy the shows and movies offered by the streaming service, it’s time to cancel your Netflix subscription. Thankfully, it’s easy to do, even if you subscribe through T-Mobile.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kennedy Maring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Help with mopidy + ncmpcpp pipewire setup]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ucltcl/help_with_mopidy_ncmpcpp_pipewire_setup/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ucltcl/help_with_mopidy_ncmpcpp_pipewire_setup/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T20:23:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the title says, I'm trying to setup mopidy with ncmpcpp but I cannot get it to work. I have installed mopidy and mopidy-mpd and configured it as the docs says but when I start ncmpcpp it says 'connection refused', but then, if I start ncpmcpp as sudo or with the flag -h 127.0.0.1 (Host which ncmpcpp should supposedly already connect because I have it like that in the config files) it connects, but the sound has a lot of latency, like one to two seconds (which I suspect it has to do with pipewire but idk), for example when I try to lower the volume it lags and two secones later it lowers the volume... I would really appreciate your help as I would like to set up mopidy-spotify later down the line. Thanks for reading!!
    submitted by    /u/NoUnderstanding99  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are Wired or Wireless Headsets Better for Gaming?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=794924</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/794924/wired-vs-wireless-gaming-headsets/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T20:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Although wireless headsets offer you more freedom than wired ones, they’re not as easy to manage as you might think. Let’s talk about the key differences between the two and discuss which is better for gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Nguyen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save $70 on a Blink Outdoor 2 Cam and Echo Show 5 Bundle –]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=442396</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/14887299/blink-outdoor-2-cam-echo-show-5-bundle"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Warmer weather is a great excuse for everyone to spend more time outdoors, so you’ll want to keep an eye on the outside of our house. If you get the Blink Outdoor 2 Cam and Echo Show 5 Bundle, you can keep watch of everything in the backyard and front yard and can do it from the convenience of your Echo Show 5, while also saving $70.
    
The wireless security cameras are battery powered and will keep watch on your home at all times – even after dark with infrared night vision. Built to withstand the elements, they will protect your home in all weather conditions. With two cameras, you can cover two separate areas of your home, such as the front and back, the front and side yard, etc. Best of all, you can set them up yourself in just minutes, as they don’t require wiring or a professional installation.
    

    
The Blink Outdoor cameras will provide motion detection alerts and allow you to customize motion zones in the Blink Home... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Install the Android 13 Beta on Your Phone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=800305</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/800305/how-to-install-the-android-13-beta-on-your-phone/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T19:13:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Android 13 is the latest version of Google’s operating system and it’s scheduled for an official release in late 2022. Until then, you can try it out with the Android 13 Beta program. We’ll show you how easy it is.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is WaaSMedic Agent.exe? (& How to Fix High Disk Usage)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=799392</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/799392/what-is-waasmedic-agent-exe-how-to-fix-high-disk-usage/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T19:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WaaSMedicAgent is responsible for repairing Windows Update when it breaks. Unfortunately, the Medic Agent itself can cause problems by having high RAM, high CPU, and high disk usage. Luckily, the WaaS MedicAgent can be disabled completely.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Lewis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KMSAN Patches For The Linux Kernel Updated For Catching Uninitialized Memory Problems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=KernelMemorySanitizer-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=KernelMemorySanitizer-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T18:45:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the Linux patch series that has been in the works for years in conjunction with Clang compiler side changes and already being responsible for exposing hundreds of kernel bugs is the KernelMemorySanitizer (KMSAN). Sent out today was the latest patch series working on the kernel infrastructure for catching uninitialized memory issues...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[American Dental Association hit by new Black Basta ransomware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/american-dental-association-hit-by-new-black-basta-ransomware/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/american-dental-association-hit-by-new-black-basta-ransomware/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T18:42:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The American Dental Association (ADA) was hit by a weekend cyberattack, causing them to shut down portions of their network while investigating the attack. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coca-Cola investigates hackers' claims of breach and data theft]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/coca-cola-investigates-hackers-claims-of-breach-and-data-theft/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/coca-cola-investigates-hackers-claims-of-breach-and-data-theft/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T18:20:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coca-Cola, the world's largest soft drinks maker, has confirmed in a statement to BleepingComputer that it is aware of the reports about a cyberattack on its network and is currently investigating the claims. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are Electric Trucks Heavier and More Dangerous Than Traditional Pickups?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/116061/are-electric-trucks-heavier-and-more-dangerous-than-traditional-pickups/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/116061/are-electric-trucks-heavier-and-more-dangerous-than-traditional-pickups/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T18:17:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The auto industry is going green by building electric vehicles, but many fear that the switch to EVs will make roads more dangerous than ever before. Electric trucks are heavy, and they could be more dangerous than traditional trucks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Calculate Percentage in Google Sheets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=795701</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/795701/google-sheets-percentage-formula/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T18:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Calculating percentage is one of those things that make many people cringe. But if showing a percent in your spreadsheet is beneficial, we’ll show you a few easy ways to calculate a percentage and format it in Google Sheets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fusione Tiscali Linkem: cosa significa per il mercato delle telecomunicazioni]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Fusione-Tiscali-Linkem-cosa-significa-per-il-mercato-delle-telecomunicazioni_23974</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Fusione-Tiscali-Linkem-cosa-significa-per-il-mercato-delle-telecomunicazioni_23974"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T17:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A fine 2021 Tiscali e Linkem hanno congiuntamente annunciato l'intenzione di fondere le due società per formare quello che è destinato a diventare quinto operatore italiano nel mercato per l'accesso a Internet da postazione fissa e il primo nel segmento degli accessi ultrabroadband in tecnologia FWA e FTTH, quindi Fixed Wireless Access e Fiber-to-the-Home (cavo fibra fino al router dell'utente finale abbonato al servizio).In un altro articolo abbiamo visto le differenze tra le varie tecnologie FTTx.Stando ai dati AGCOM la quota di mercato complessiva appannaggio del soggetto che si formerà dall'unione di Tiscali e Linkem sarà pari al 19,4%.L'operazione, spiegano le due aziende, interessa da un lato Tiscali e dall'altro Linkem Retail, ramo d'azienda relativo interamente posseduto da Linkem S.p.A.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ghacks Deals: The 2022 CompTIA & AWS, Cisco Certification Paths Bundle: Lifetime Access]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178249</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/04/26/ghacks-deals-the-2022-comptia-aws-cisco-certification-paths-bundle-lifetime-access/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T17:54:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2022 CompTIA & AWS, Cisco Certification Paths Bundle includes lifetime access to exam preparation courses for 13 different certification exams. Here is the list of included certification exams that you may […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Ghacks Deals: The 2022 CompTIA & AWS, Cisco Certification Paths Bundle: Lifetime Access appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Android 13 Beta 1 Released - Continues Focus On Privacy & Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Android-13-Beta-1</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Android-13-Beta-1"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T17:50:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google today announced the first public beta of Android 13...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Perché Microsoft Defender è un antivirus meno abile nella scansione offline]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Perche-Microsoft-Defender-e-un-antivirus-meno-abile-nella-scansione-offline_24435</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Perche-Microsoft-Defender-e-un-antivirus-meno-abile-nella-scansione-offline_24435"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T17:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[È di questi giorni la pubblicazione di un report firmato AV-Comparatives che getta un'ombra su molti prodotti antimalware ritenuti ormai poco adeguati per effettuare scansioni offline.Nel caso di Microsoft Defender abbiamo visto cos'è e come funziona la scansione offline spiegando anche come essa può essere richiamata al bisogno.Nel caso della scansione offline non solo Microsoft Defender ma anche gli altri prodotti concorrenti lavorano utilizzando un approccio più tradizionale basato sulle firme virali e sull'analisi comportamentale. Alcuni comportamenti posti in essere dai file e dai processi in esecuzione sul sistema, cioè, possono essere la spia di un'attività malevola.Nei test di AV-Comparatives Defender ha ottenuto una valutazione bassa per quanto riguarda il riconoscimento delle minacce usano esclusivamente la scansione online.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I have just purchased a Brother HL-1112 printer. I see there is an aur packaged but it hasn't been updated for 5 years. Should I use that or build a new one?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uchul5/i_have_just_purchased_a_brother_hl1112_printer_i/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uchul5/i_have_just_purchased_a_brother_hl1112_printer_i/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T17:26:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Link. The maintainer is still active on other packages, having updated them even up to this month this year. This make me wonder if there has been no need for them to update that package since.
 Or maybe they got a new printer so don't care about it any more. Often you will see a note on the aur comments if a maintainer is abandoning a package though.
 Any other clues as to whether I should try this one or repackage myself?
    submitted by    /u/usera8787782  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Icons missing for Adwaita XFCE. Using a different icon set is the only solution?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uchhho/icons_missing_for_adwaita_xfce_using_a_different/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uchhho/icons_missing_for_adwaita_xfce_using_a_different/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T17:10:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Installing XFCE with archinstall, I can see only two icon sets present: Adwaita and HighContrast. I think Adwaita icons look good enough, but the problem is that it lacks a lot of icons for WhiskerMenu or the default image viewer tool bar. If I set the icon set to "HighContrast", all those missing icons are displayed, but the high contrast icons look ugly. I have tested it with EndeavourOS and its default icon set was Qogir. If I change it to Adwaita, I can see missing icons there, too.
 I think I could find some different icon sets from the Internet, but I think the default Adwaita looks good enough. Can I keep Adwaita and add missing icons? Or using another icon set is the sane solution?
    submitted by    /u/evolution2015  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The First Android 13 Beta Arrives, Here's How to Install It]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/116049/the-first-android-13-beta-arrives-heres-how-to-install-it/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/116049/the-first-android-13-beta-arrives-heres-how-to-install-it/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T17:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just as Google promised, the first Android 13 Beta is now available for anyone with the patience to install it. This Beta release doesn’t pack as many new features as last month’s Developer Preview, but it’s the first version of Android 13 that’s stable enough for the average geek to test.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is an Internet Fandom?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=795217</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/795217/what-is-an-internet-fandom/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T17:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you seen people on the internet discussing the “fandoms” they’re a part of? Fandoms are some of the most powerful forces on the internet. Here’s what these devoted fanbases are and how they bring people together.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vann Vicente</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Convertire audio in testo su PC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2016/05/trascrivere-un-file-audio-o-video-come.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2016/05/trascrivere-un-file-audio-o-video-come.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T16:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Una delle funzioni meno utilizzate sul PC è la trascrizione, ossa la conversione di un audio di qualsiasi tipo in un testo leggibile e condivisibile. Per trascrivere un audio in un testo è possibile utilizzare alcuni programmi o software online gratuiti e sicuri, in grado di generare testo da qualsiasi tipo di audio riprodotto dal PC (anche acquisito dal microfono).

 Vediamo insieme i migliori...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Panfrost Lands Valhall Driver Code For Mesa 22.2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Panfrost-More-Valhall-Mesa-22.2</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Panfrost-More-Valhall-Mesa-22.2"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T16:09:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Panfrost open-source, reverse-engineered Arm Mali driver stack so far has been focused on Midgard and Bifrost architectures but the newer Valhall graphics support is beginning to materialize. Since last year the developers involved have been working heavy on reverse engineering and bringing up Valhall. More of that Valhall driver support landed today...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Find the Freshest Frozen Fish at the Grocery Store]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lifesavvy.com/126308/how-to-find-the-freshest-frozen-fish-at-the-grocery-store/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lifesavvy.com/126308/how-to-find-the-freshest-frozen-fish-at-the-grocery-store/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T16:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most of us are on a mission to get the most bang for our buck at the grocery store. Sometimes, this means opting for frozen rather than fresh, which often includes meat. If you enjoy fish, there’s one way you can make sure the frozen stuff is as fresh as possible.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shea Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Merge Duplicate Contacts on Android]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=799740</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/799740/how-to-merge-duplicate-contacts-on-android/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T16:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The “Contacts” app is probably one of the most neglected apps on your Android phone. Email, SMS, and phone apps use your contacts, so it’s important to routinely clean them up. We’ll show you how to combine duplicates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rivian Will Speed Up R1T Production by Delaying More Complicated Orders]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/116062/rivian-will-speed-up-r1t-production-by-delaying-more-complicated-orders/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/116062/rivian-will-speed-up-r1t-production-by-delaying-more-complicated-orders/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T15:56:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rivian kicked off R1T electric pickup production at an incredibly slow rate—it made just two vehicles per day. And while the company is slowly inching toward a more reasonable production volume, its latest revelation may disappoint some customers. Basically, complicated vehicle customizations take more time to manufacture, so they’re getting delayed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SD Card vs. SSD: What Is Really the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=215484</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/6798373/sd-card-vs-ssd"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The solid state drive has given us a leap forward in the ability to open applications and read files quickly. Its storage mechanism operates under the same principles that other flash storage mediums use, namely non-volatile memory, which prevents memory from disappearing due to loss of power like it does in RAM. Since both SD cards and SSDs use solid-state storage and have no moving parts, is there any notable difference between the two types of memory? Shouldn’t a massive-capacity SD card be just about the same thing as a small SSD?
   
Also read:SSD vs. HDD vs. USB Flash Drive: Everything You Need to Know
    
Explaining NAND Flash
    
Almost all the memory you use stored on a chip other than the RAM on your computer uses a technology known as NAND flash.
    
NAND flash memory depends on other hardware installed on the... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miguel Leiva-Gomez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Markdown in Google Docs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=797345</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/797345/google-docs-markdown/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T15:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re a fan of using Markdown to format your documents, you’ll be glad to know you can use it in Google Docs. By turning on a simple setting, Docs recognizes Markdown so you can type, format, and keep going.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Play Store now forces apps to disclose what data is collected]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/google-play-store-now-forces-apps-to-disclose-what-data-is-collected/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/google-play-store-now-forces-apps-to-disclose-what-data-is-collected/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google is rolling out a new Data Safety section on the Play Store, Android's official app repository, where developers must declare what data their software collects from users of their apps. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public interest in Log4Shell fades but attack surface remains]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/public-interest-in-log4shell-fades-but-attack-surface-remains/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/public-interest-in-log4shell-fades-but-attack-surface-remains/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T14:59:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's been four months since Log4Shell, a critical zero-day vulnerability in the ubiquitous Apache Log4j library, was discovered, and threat analysts warn that the application of the available fixes is still way behind. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[mkinitcpio -L doesn't show "bluetooth" as an available HOOK, which I need to use BT keyboard to open a LUKS container.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uce7ah/mkinitcpio_l_doesnt_show_bluetooth_as_an/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uce7ah/mkinitcpio_l_doesnt_show_bluetooth_as_an/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T14:45:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hence mkinitcpio -P fails with ERROR: Hook 'bluetooth' cannot be found.
 Both BT mouse and keyboard work just fine once I'm in the system.
    submitted by    /u/barraba  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come usare copia e incolla speciale su Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/04/come-usare-copia-e-incolla-speciale-su.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/04/come-usare-copia-e-incolla-speciale-su.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T14:31:00.005Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[La procedura di copia delle celle su Excel è davvero molto semplice: nella maggior parte dei casi è sufficiente selezionare le celle che vogliamo copiare, premere CTRL+C sulla tastiera, portarci su un altro foglio di calcolo ed utilizzare CTRL+V per incollare i valori riportati. Non sempre però è tutto così immediato e gli scenari in cui è necessario utilizzare la funzione incolla speciale sono...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tovala Smart Oven and Meal Plan Review: Scan a Bar Code, Press Start, and Eat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/105196/tovala-smart-oven-and-meal-plan-scan-a-bar-code-press-start-and-eat/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/105196/tovala-smart-oven-and-meal-plan-scan-a-bar-code-press-start-and-eat/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T14:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m not a particularly good cook, but one look at me and you know I like to eat. The Tovala smart oven and its associated meal plan make it easy for me to get great tasty meals at the press of a button.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ted Needleman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These Bus Tours Take the Hassle Out of Traveling Through Europe]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lifesavvy.com/125915/these-bus-tours-take-the-hassle-out-of-traveling-through-europe/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lifesavvy.com/125915/these-bus-tours-take-the-hassle-out-of-traveling-through-europe/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T14:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When taking a trip to Europe, some travelers prefer to find their own way, while others would much rather hire a tour company to plan an itinerary, so they don’t miss anything. A popular way to enjoy a guided tour is via bus, and these are some of the best companies to check out if you’re planning a European vacation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anne Taylor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung T7 Shield Review: The Best Portable SSD, Now Rugged]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=798789</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/798789/samsung-portable-ssd-t7-shield-review/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T14:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung introduced the T7 at CES 2020, and it has been one of our favorite portable SSDs ever since. Its greatest weakness is the lack of a water or dust resistance rating. The latest addition to Samsung’s SSD lineup, the T7 Shield, fixes that with IP65 protection and greater drop resistance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Justin Duino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung Debuts Its Most Durable Portable SSD to Date]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/115979/samsung-debuts-its-most-durable-portable-ssd-to-date/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/115979/samsung-debuts-its-most-durable-portable-ssd-to-date/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T14:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung’s best and fastest portable SSD is now available in an ultra-rugged form factor. Available now for $160, the Samsung T7 Shield is a durable beast, with a proper IPX rating, improved drop protection, and a durable rubberized finish.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[David Colombo on Tesla Hacks and Growing into Hacking]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/david-colombo-on-tesla-hacks-and-growing-into-hacking/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/david-colombo-on-tesla-hacks-and-growing-into-hacking/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybellum interviewed David Colombo, the cyber boy wonder of Germany, and founder of Colombo Technologies for our podcast, Left to Our Own Devices. Not yet 20 years old, the prolific cyber researcher already has to his credit the exposure of numerous critical vulnerabilities, including the honor of hacking his way into Tesla vehicles. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sponsored by Cybellum</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 ARM su Apple Silicon: si può ma il sistema operativo non è supportato]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-11-ARM-su-Apple-Silicon-si-puo-ma-il-sistema-operativo-non-e-supportato_24434</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-11-ARM-su-Apple-Silicon-si-puo-ma-il-sistema-operativo-non-e-supportato_24434"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T13:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Soluzioni per la virtualizzazione come Parallels Desktop e VMware Fusion consentono di eseguire la versione ARM64 di Windows 11 sui sistemi Mac basati su Apple Silicon.Con il termine Apple Silicon si fa riferimento ai SoC (System-on-a-Chip) con architettura di derivazione ARM che la Mela ha sviluppato per i suoi dispositivi mobili prima e in tempi più recenti anche per i Mac andando di fatto ad abbandonare la piattaforma Intel x86.Per chi volesse usare Windows 11 sui Mac basati su Apple Silicon di fatto non esistono immagini ISO o file in formato WIM disponibili pubblicamente. Soltanto gli iscritti al programma Volume Licensing Service Center di Microsoft sembrano poter accedere alle immagini ufficiali di Windows 11 ARM64.L'azienda di Redmond offre comunque l'immagine di un'installazione d…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AirPods Pro Problems? Apple Might Replace Them for Free]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=799975</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/799975/airpods-pro-problems-apple-might-replace-them-for-free/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple is offering free replacement AirPods Pro earbuds for users affected by specific issues. The program is only available for a limited time, so here’s how to check if your own pair is eligible for replacement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NVIDIA 510.68.02 Released As A Minor Bug Fix Update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=NVIDIA-510.68.02-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=NVIDIA-510.68.02-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NVIDIA released the 510.68.02 Linux driver today as a very minor bug-fix release...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome 101 ships with controversial advertising system trials]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178244</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/04/26/chrome-101-ships-with-controversial-advertising-system-trials/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T13:13:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google plans to release a new stable version of the company's Chrome web browser later today. Chrome 101 is released four weeks after the last version of Chrome was released, which was […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Chrome 101 ships with controversial advertising system trials appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Maximize Your Crypto Earnings on Crypto.com]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/?p=59533</id>
        <link href="https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/maximize-crypto-earnings/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T13:01:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto.com has been making its rounds not just in the United States, but also all over the globe with their robust list of services and most importantly,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hongkiat Lim</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dell's New Laptop Will Help You Avoid The Awkward Zoom Hang Up]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/115986/dells-new-laptop-will-help-you-avoid-the-awkward-zoom-hang-up/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/115986/dells-new-laptop-will-help-you-avoid-the-awkward-zoom-hang-up/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T13:01:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week Dell announced a trio of new laptops, all with varying screen sizes up to 17-inches. In addition, the release includes one with the world’s first collaboration touchpad built with shortcuts to make meetings easier than ever.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can Any Electric Car Use Any EV Charger?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=794923</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/794923/can-any-electric-car-use-any-ev-charger/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before you invest in an electric vehicle (EV), there are a few things you should research. One of the most important factors, though, is what kind of charging connector an EV uses. Here’s how they’re different, and where you can actually use them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Bogna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GraalVM CE 22.1 Released With Performance Improvements, Apple Silicon Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=GraalVM-22.1-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=GraalVM-22.1-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oracle this morning published the GraalVM Community Edition 22.1 feature release for this high-performance Java/JDK distribution that also provides runtimes for JavaScript, Python, and other languages...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers exploit critical VMware RCE flaw to install backdoors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-exploit-critical-vmware-rce-flaw-to-install-backdoors/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-exploit-critical-vmware-rce-flaw-to-install-backdoors/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T12:51:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced hackers are actively exploiting a critical remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability, CVE-2022-22954, that affects in VMware Workspace ONE Access (formerly called VMware Identity Manager). [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Disinstallare programmi inutili in Windows: alcuni suggerimenti]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Disinstallare-programmi-inutili-in-Windows-alcuni-suggerimenti_19742</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Disinstallare-programmi-inutili-in-Windows-alcuni-suggerimenti_19742"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T12:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quando si installano nuove applicazioni in Windows queste non soltanto vanno a occupare spazio a livello di filesystem ma contribuiscono ad appesantire le varie aree del sistema operativo, in particolare il registro, e a rallentare l'avvio.Con Windows 10 Microsoft ha provato a mettere in campo qualche strategia per ridurre i tempi di avvio precaricando alcune applicazioni e servizi in esecuzione durante la precedente sessione di lavoro: ecco perché spegnere Windows 10 non equivale a un riavvio del sistema.Lo stesso approccio è stato conservato con l'introduzione di Windows 11.Il boot di una macchina completamente spenta, però, richiede del tempo e - soprattutto con i sistemi dotati di una configurazione hardware economica che non usano un'unità SSD - l'attesa prima della comparsa del deskt…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New in Fedora 36]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=797884</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/797884/whats-new-in-fedora-36/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s no time to waste in the world of Linux distributions. Fedora 35 dropped in November 2021, and Fedora 36 is set to arrive a few short months later in April 2022. Here’s what’s new in Red Hat’s open-source Linux distribution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Paul</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Dogecoin?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=799037</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/799037/what-is-dogecoin/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The original memecoin, Dogecoin, brought cryptocurrency into the mainstream media spotlight. Its rise in popularity is nothing short of historic. Here’s where it came from and why everyone can’t stop talking about it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>RJ Fulton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Collegamento OTG USB su smartphone e tablet (Android e iPhone)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2014/12/usare-una-penna-usb-su-android-come.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2014/12/usare-una-penna-usb-su-android-come.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T11:49:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gli smartphone di nuova generazione possono essere collegati a svariate periferiche USB utilizzando uno speciale adattatore noto come OTG USB. Quando serve, per esempio durante un viaggio in treno, possiamo collegare al nostro smartphone (ma anche al tablet) una penna USB tablet con tutti i film dentro, scegliendo quindi quale vedere senza intaccare la memoria interna. Oltre alle chiavette USB...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Second external monitor not working]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ucag1z/second_external_monitor_not_working/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ucag1z/second_external_monitor_not_working/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T11:34:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I already posted this in the Arch forum, but didn't receive an answer, so I'll try again here. What follows is a copy and paste of that post:
 I use a USB-C hub with two HDMI slots, and the second monitor won't turn on. Or, If I explicitely try to enable it via wdisplay, it will only work with a resolution of 720x400. I run wayland and sway. My laptop has an Intel gpu and a dedicated nvidia GPU for which I use nouveau. But I'm pretty sure, that the nvidia GPU is not involved with the external monitors.
 I'm not sure if this is a problem with Sway, Wayland, the intel driver, or my system configuration which is why I ask for help here.
 In the sway log, there is this regarding the issue:
  00:00:03.894 [DEBUG] [sway/desktop/output.c:857] New output 0x556dc7c04a80: DP-5 (non-desktop: 0) 00:00…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 e 10: quanto spazio occupano le app preinstallate e quelle caricate dal Microsoft Store]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-11-e-10-quanto-spazio-occupano-le-app-preinstallate-e-quelle-caricate-dal-Microsoft-Store_24433</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-11-e-10-quanto-spazio-occupano-le-app-preinstallate-e-quelle-caricate-dal-Microsoft-Store_24433"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T11:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Le applicazioni preinstallate in Windows 11 e in Windows 10 possono facilmente occupare più di 1,5 GB di spazio. Lo conferma un test pubblicato su Out of Office Hours basato sull'utilizzo di un semplice script PowerShell e che tutti possono replicare.Sia Windows 11 che Windows 10 installano automaticamente un gran numero di applicazioni. Via via che si utilizza il sistema operativo, inoltre, anche nelle edizioni Pro, Windows ha la brutta abitudine di scaricare e installare applicazioni aggiuntive che appaiono nella finestra accessibile digitando App e funzionalità nella casella di ricerca.Abbiamo presentato un comodo file batch velocizzare Windows 11 e ottimizzare il sistema mentre a suo tempo abbiamo descritto il funzionamento di uno script per ottimizzare e velocizzare Windows 10.
Quanto spazio occupano le app del Microsoft Store in Windows 10 e 11
 Premendo la combinazione di tasti Windows+X quindi scegliendo Terminale Windows in Windows 11 oppure Windows PowerShell in Windows 10, si può digitare un semplice comando che permette di raccogliere le informazioni sulle app Microsoft Store installate:Get-AppxProvisionedPackage -online | Out-GridViewIl problema è che le applicazioni Microsoft Store tipicamente usano diverse cartelle, non dichiarate non file manifest in formato XML.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux 5.19 Looks Like It Will Be The Base Requirement For Intel Arc Graphics / Alchemist]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-IDs-DG2-Alchemist</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-IDs-DG2-Alchemist"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T11:13:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While Intel launched the Arc A-Series Mobile Graphics at the end of Q1, so far at least in major US markets no laptops with these graphics are currently available. As such it's hard to assess the current Linux driver support level and with no clear communication from Intel on the matter. Intel has been working on their upstream DG2/Alchemist support for a while but it looks like with the Linux 5.19 kernel this summer is what will likely be their base version requirement for the DG2/Alchemist-based Intel GPUs...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New in Chrome 101, Available Now]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=800007</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/800007/whats-new-in-chrome-101/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome hit the big 100 in March 2022, but the celebration is over now. We’re back already with another release on April 26, 2022. Chrome 101 includes more improvements to the new download UI, saving Tab Groups, and the password manager. Let’s take a look.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Concerns Raised Over The "New" NTFS Linux Driver That Merged Last Year]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=NTFS3-Linux-Driver-2022-Sad</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=NTFS3-Linux-Driver-2022-Sad"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T10:25:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in 2020 file-system driver provider Paragon Software announced they wanted to upstream their NTFS driver into the Linux kernel. This driver was previously a proprietary, commercial offering from the company but given the state of NTFS these days they wanted to upstream this driver with full read/write support and other features not found within the existing NTFS driver. Finally last year after going through many rounds of review, the new driver was merged into Linux 5.15. Sadly, less than one year later, concerns have been raised that the driver is already effectively orphaned and not being maintained...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[After Musk’s Twitter Deal, Users Rush to Mastodon]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=483462</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15249836/musks-twitter-deal-users-mastodon"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T10:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unless you’ve stayed away from social media and the news the past few days, you’ve undoubtedly heard that Elon Musk bought Twitter. Frankly, if you haven’t heard, you probably don’t care. Many that do care seem to be taking part in a mass exodus. After the Twitter deal was finalized, the servers at competitor Mastodon hit a traffic surge, and Twitter employees started asking questions.
   
Also read:Do We Have Elon Musk to Thank for a Twitter Edit Button?
    
Twitter Users Appear to Jump Ship for Mastodon
    
Elon Musk just made an epic business move – and it has nothing to do with Tesla or SpaceX. The Twitter board announced on Monday, April 25, that a deal was reached for Musk to buy the social network for close to $44 billion.
    
This was immediately upsetting to many Twitter users. Musk’s views about Twitter are well-known. He doesn’t believe... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LXDE keeps turning off after suspension]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uc94i4/lxde_keeps_turning_off_after_suspension/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uc94i4/lxde_keeps_turning_off_after_suspension/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T10:08:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whenever I boot up my arch linux and log in to LXDE, it always boots up and works properly. Whenever I put it into suspension (by closing the lid) it goes into suspension like expected. However, whenever I open the lid back up and start using it again, it starts like normal but then just randomly goes into suspension at random moments and the only fix so far is to reboot but i don’t want to have to keep doing that. I also like lxde. How do i fix this?
 Hardware:
 •Razor Blade 15
 •Nvidia Gpu
 I’ve tried:
 •Reading the troubleshooting manual (nothing seen)
 •booting without quiet (nothing unusual)
 •Looking through the configs
 •Updating the system
 NOTE: When installing lxde, I installed it as/is with nothing additional. Also I had this issue from as early as the first time closing the lid.
    submitted by    /u/regimain  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the Top Command in Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/?p=59116</id>
        <link href="https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/linux-command-top/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T10:01:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The "top" command reveals the process running in the operating system. It shows the process id or PID for short, the user running the process, the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hongkiat.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Apple AirTag Accessories of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=724536</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/724536/best-apple-airtag-accessories/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Apple AirTag offers an affordable way for iPhone users to track nearly anything, but there’s a catch. By itself, the AirTag can really only be thrown into a bag. To make it more versatile, you’ll need some accessories.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arm Scalable Matrix Extension Readied Ahead Of Linux 5.19]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Arm-Scalable-Matrix-Linux-5.19</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Arm-Scalable-Matrix-Linux-5.19"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T09:52:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It looks like Linux 5.19 will have all the base preparations in place for Arm Scalable Matrix Extension (SME) support...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[/dev/random + /dev/urandom Unification May Be Revisited In The Future, Blocker Addressed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Random-Unification-Future</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Random-Unification-Future"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T09:30:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Originally attempted with Linux 5.18 were patches so /dev/urandom and /dev/random would behave exactly the same. That was dropped though due to not enough randomness at boot for some platforms like Arm 32-bit, Motorola m68k, Microblaze, Xtensa, and others. But then the change went in to opportunistically initialize /dev/random as a best-effort approach where it at least works nicely on x86/x86_64. The good news is that original unification effort may be re-visited in the future now that the original blocker issue has been addressed...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VMware Lands SVGAv3 In Mesa 22.2 For Their Virtual Graphics Device]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=VMware-SVGAv3-Mesa-22.2</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=VMware-SVGAv3-Mesa-22.2"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T09:09:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VMware has merged support for SVGAv3 into Mesa 22.2. SVGAv3 is the latest update to their virtual graphics device for allowing 3D guest virtual machine acceleration with VMware's virtualization products...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GRUB won’t recognize Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uc854i/grub_wont_recognize_windows_11/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uc854i/grub_wont_recognize_windows_11/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T08:58:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’d like to preface this by saying that this is my first real experience with any Linux installation, and I just followed the wiki to the best of my ability to get to where I’m at.
 I want a dual booting system with Windows 11 and Arch Linux. I followed the Arch Linux installation guide very closely. I mounted Windows’ EFI partition to /boot, and the “Microsoft basic data” to /mnt/win11 to have access to those files while in Arch. Ran grub-mkconfig with os-prober, and rebooted, to be greeted with GRUB showing me only Arch Linux, not Windows.
 On booting Arch, I get: Starting version 250.4-2-arch /dev/nvme0n1p6: clean, 40974/3972672 files, 729772/15859712 blocks [FAILED] Failed to mount /win11. [DEFEND] Dependency failed for Local File Systems. You are in emergency mode. After logging in, type “journalctl -xb” to view system logs, “systemctl reboot” to reboot, “systemctl default” or “exit” to boot into default mode.
 I tried looking it up but all I could find were problems regarding Arch, not a dual boot system. Any suggestions on how to get Windows booting? Thanks as always
    submitted by    /u/Zeno371  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cavi audio Hi-Fi Premium Manhattan: quali sono le caratteristiche]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Cavi-audio-Hi-Fi-Premium-Manhattan-quali-sono-le-caratteristiche_24430</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Cavi-audio-Hi-Fi-Premium-Manhattan-quali-sono-le-caratteristiche_24430"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T08:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Per collegare apparecchi audio come cuffie, microfoni, e altoparlanti a dispositivi come tablet, laptop e molto altro è importante usare cavi audio di alta qualità. Manhattan, leader nello sviluppo di tecnologie smart e dispositivi capaci di assicurare elevate prestazioni, presenta un'ampia selezione di nuovi cavi audio Hi-Fi Premium per il trasporto di flussi audio senza la minima perdita di qualità.Dai cavi adattatori jack stereo da 3,5 mm per collegare cuffie e microfoni ai cavi ottici digitali TOSLINK per ricevitori AV, soundbar, TV, PC, DAC, Playstation e Xbox, sino ai cavi audio stereo Hi-Fi Premium per altoparlanti, casse, tablet e laptop.Tutti i prodotti sono realizzati con una guaina altamente flessibile, resistente e con contatti placcati in oro 24K per un'ottima resa sonora e una lunga durata nel tempo.Indispensabili per il collegamento di cuffie, microfono e altoparlanti a dispositivi come smartphone, laptop e tablet, PlayStation, Xbox e altri device sono i nuovi cavi adattatori con splitter audio e stereo AUX da 3,5 mm.In particolare, il modello ICOC 35H-1F2M-015 è dotato di un connettore femmina a due maschi stereo da 3,5 mm e consente di 'splittare' una connessione audio singola permettendo per esempio di collegare una cuffia con singolo plug da 3,5 mm ad un laptop o un PC dotato di porta separata per microfono e speaker.

Il modello ICOC 35H-1M2F-020 è invece dotato di un connettore maschio e due femmina stereo da 3,5 mm.Esso permette la connessione a smartphone, laptop, tablet, iPad, iPod e lettori MP3 con un singolo jack stereo ottenendo in uscita due jack per cuffia e microfono.

Il modello ICOC 35H-1M2F-015 è anch'esso dotato di un connettore jack maschio e di due connettori femmina da 3,5 mm per il collegamento di due cuffie o auricolari sfruttando una singola porta di uscita audio.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Perché Elon Musk ha acquisito Twitter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Perche-Elon-Musk-ha-acquisito-Twitter_24432</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Perche-Elon-Musk-ha-acquisito-Twitter_24432"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T08:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apprezzato e utilizzato in tutto il mondo Twitter non è esattamente una delle realtà che si mettono più in evidenza se si parla di introiti.Eppure Elon Musk ha espresso il suo vivo interesse nell'acquisire il social network o meglio il servizio di microblogging lanciato da Jack Dorsey nel marzo 2006.Musk, imprenditore noto per essere CEO della casa automobilistica Tesla, CEO e CTO della compagnia aerospaziale SpaceX, cofondatore e CEO di Neuralink, presidente di SolarCity, ideatore del sistema di trasporto ultraveloce Hyperloop, fondatore di The Boring Company e cofondatore di PayPal e OpenAI, avrebbe però 'grandi piani' per Twitter intendendo monetizzarne al massimo le attività.Classe 1971, l'imprenditore sudafricano con cittadinanza canadese naturalizzato statunitense, aveva acquistato circa il 9% di Twitter lo scorso mese con l'obiettivo di entrare nel consiglio di amministrazione.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WinfrGUI: easy to use Windows file recovery application]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178237</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/04/26/winfrgui-easy-to-use-windows-file-recovery-application/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T08:28:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WinfrGUI is a free program to recover files on Windows PCs. The program is easy to use and runs under Windows 10 and 11 only at the time of writing. The file […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post WinfrGUI: easy to use Windows file recovery application appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eye of GNOME (image viewer) not launching after GNOME 42 update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uc7hye/eye_of_gnome_image_viewer_not_launching_after/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uc7hye/eye_of_gnome_image_viewer_not_launching_after/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T08:07:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever since the big update to GNOME 42 eog is not launching anymore. I can’t view any pictures. Have to use mpv or GIMP. I get this error.
 Failed to register: Timeout was reached
 What changed? Any help is appreciated. My system is up to date as of now.
 My setup:
  
linux-hardened 5.16.20.hardened1-1
 eog 42.1-1
 gnome-shell 1:42.0-1
 Wayland
  
   submitted by    /u/87b4de70-cd66-4bd8  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel mobile iGPU GMA4500MHD]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uc7e04/intel_mobile_igpu_gma4500mhd/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uc7e04/intel_mobile_igpu_gma4500mhd/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T07:59:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OK, OK, The Wiki already mention this, but I think this would / could help someone more! 😉 When installing Arch on a laptop with the integrated Intel GMA 4500MHD GPU, please remember:
  
modesetting is OK, no need to install xf86-video-intel (unless you're facing some HW acceleration issues)
 there's no need to create a configuration file in /etc/X11/xorg.conf.d/
 also add intel_agp inside MODULES=(... intel_agp i915 ...)
 my laptop's screen died, so I'm outputting the video via the VGA port only... Then this option comes in handy: video=LVDS-1:d in the kernel command line parameter in the bootloader.
  
SOURCE: https://wiki.archlinux.org/title/Intel_graphics
    submitted by    /u/Bombini_Bombus  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Videocamera con gimbal stabilizzatore: Feiyu Pocket 2 in offerta]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Videocamera-con-gimbal-stabilizzatore-Feiyu-Pocket-2-in-offerta_24431</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Videocamera-con-gimbal-stabilizzatore-Feiyu-Pocket-2-in-offerta_24431"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T07:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Se realizzate spesso video in esterna e in movimento sapete quanto, utilizzando i normali smartphone, i risultati lascino spesso a desiderare.La videocamera Feiyu Pocket 2 con gimbal è in offerta speciale per un breve periodo di tempo. Si tratta di un dispositivo di dimensioni compatte che integra una videocamera grandangolare (130°) con risoluzione 4K a 60 fps montata su uno stabilizzatore a giunto cardanico a tre assi.I gimbal o giunti cardanici aiutano ad acquisire video di qualità senza tremolii: per questo sono entrati da tempo a far parte del corredo di accessori dei videomaker.

Un prodotto come Feiyu Pocket 2 si rivela quindi essenziale per acquisire video professionali anche con soggetti in movimento.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitwarden Password Manager can now generate unique usernames]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178229</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/04/26/how-to-generate-unique-usernames-in-bitwarden-password-manager/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T07:56:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While many people use password managers for the convenience of remembering a single login, the master password, the primary advantage that such programs offer, is that they provide an easy way to […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Bitwarden Password Manager can now generate unique usernames appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sostieni i tuoi siti preferiti disattivando selettivamente l'adblock]]></title>
        <id>3557|20220426081000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/blocca-pubblicita-block-3390/sostieni-siti-preferiti-disattivando-selettivamente-adblock-3557"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T06:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Si dice che la pubblicità sia l’anima del commercio, però quando è troppa, spesso, disturba, ma permette a molti siti Web di coprire, almeno in parte, le spese di gestione (perché non tutto è gratis sul Web, pensate solo a quanto costa noleggiare un server che ospita un sito come il nostro). Sono nate così una serie di estensioni, dette AdBlocker, per i principali browser che hanno lo scopo di bloccare queste pubblicità e molte altre cose.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to mount partitions as read and write?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uc3xg8/how_to_mount_partitions_as_read_and_write/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uc3xg8/how_to_mount_partitions_as_read_and_write/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T04:03:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey, I dual booted my laptop from windows and I want to able to use those drives in linux as well. I am able to read and open those partitions but I am not able to make any changes in the folders whatsoever. I some yt video about doing sudo mount -o remount /dev/sda1 /mnt/sda1 and I was able to convert the partition as 'rw' when I enter sudo mount in the terminal but I am still not able to make any changes there. Also when I rebooted the laptop, it just went back to 'ro' and I tried doing it again but it didn't work.
 ​
 What to do ?
    submitted by    /u/GuyKage8  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why is rofi not finding my bitmap font?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uc2sx6/why_is_rofi_not_finding_my_bitmap_font/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uc2sx6/why_is_rofi_not_finding_my_bitmap_font/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T03:01:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I want to use the font UW Ttyp0 in rofi, but for whatever reason, it can't find it. I've tried putting font: "UW Ttyp0 9" inside the config.rasi file, but it always falls back to the default font. Alacritty seems to find the font just fine. Can anyone help?
    submitted by    /u/JoshuaTheProgrammer  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuteBrowser: Fatal Error Pyqt5.Qtcore | libicui18,.so67 cannot open share object file]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uc2c7o/qutebrowser_fatal_error_pyqt5qtcore_libicui18so67/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uc2c7o/qutebrowser_fatal_error_pyqt5qtcore_libicui18so67/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T02:37:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm relatively new to Arch Linux, but am looking for help on how to fix this issue.
 When i try to open Qutebrowser I receive the following:
 Fatal error: PyQt5.QtCore is required to run qutebrowser but could not be imported! Maybe it's not installed?
 ​
 The error encountered was:
 libicui18n.so.67: cannot open shared object file: No such file or directory
 ​
 Please search for the python3 version of PyQt5.QtCore in your distributions packages, or see https://github.com/qutebrowser/qutebrowser/blob/master/doc/install.asciidoc
 ​
 If you installed a qutebrowser package for your distribution, please report this as a bug.
 ​
 What I've tried so far:
 Installing qutebrowser from the official & the git option
 reinstalling python, pyqt5, icu 
 Running a debug from https://github.com/qutebrowser/qutebrowser/blob/master/doc/stacktrace.asciidoc#archlinux
 ​
 Any help or insight would be great.
    submitted by    /u/HammerSmashedFacedd  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lenovo Ideapad Sleep Drivers?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uc1kbu/lenovo_ideapad_sleep_drivers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uc1kbu/lenovo_ideapad_sleep_drivers/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T01:57:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So I've had this trouble with my Lenovo IdeaPad 5 14ARE05 (AMD) for it has to be at least half a year. When I leave/close my laptop it goes to sleep and everything stays running, but when I attempt to wake up the screen (like with the use of a click of a mouse or key) nothing happens. The only time I've been able to solve this is by upgrading my system to a newer version, but this doesn't last for very long. I was thinking it could maybe be something to do with the drivers, but all of them are for windows.
 Link to drivers
 PC specs:
 Kernel: 5.17.4-archl-l
 Shell: bash 5.1.16
 DE: GNOME 42.0
 WM: Mutter
 All help is appreciated :)
    submitted by    /u/mrjohndoe42069  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 10 KB5011831 update released with 26 bug fixes, improvements]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-10-kb5011831-update-released-with-26-bug-fixes-improvements/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-10-kb5011831-update-released-with-26-bug-fixes-improvements/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T01:37:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has released the optional KB5011831 Preview cumulative update for Windows 10 20H2, Windows 10 21H1, and Windows 10 21H2 that fixes 26 bugs. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Touchpad Trouble - Asus Vivobook X513UA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uc0yih/touchpad_trouble_asus_vivobook_x513ua/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uc0yih/touchpad_trouble_asus_vivobook_x513ua/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T01:26:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've got a new install of an arch spin (endeavour) on my asus vivobook (x513ua), and the touchpad (which xinput informs me is an ELAN1300) intermittently freezes/stops inputting, and then resumes working. This occurs more frequently when the laptop is heating up, and exactly how long and how frequently it freezes for varies.
 I've looked online for answers, but nothing I found seems to work. Any ideas?
    submitted by    /u/Hate9  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Activate Parental Controls on TikTok]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=479539</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15248514/activate-parental-controls-tiktok"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Video-sharing social media app TikTok is extremely popular with the younger crowd including teens and pre-teens. If you’re a parent who is worried about your child spending an ever-increasing amount of time on the social app, then you should know that TikTok includes a host of parental controls, as well as privacy settings meant to enable young users to use TikTok safely. In this article we’ll show you how you can set up parental controls for your child’s TikTok account.
   

Content

Does TikTok Have an Age Limit?
How to Set Up Family Pairing in TikTok
Parental Control Options in TikTok
How to Turn on Digital Wellbeing Features in TikTok
Frequently Asked Question

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Add Two or More Songs to Your TikToks
    
Does TikTok Have an Age Limit?
    
TikTok will automatically adjust its settings based... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexandra Arici</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA adds 7 vulnerabilities to list of bugs exploited in attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisa-adds-7-vulnerabilities-to-list-of-bugs-exploited-in-attacks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisa-adds-7-vulnerabilities-to-list-of-bugs-exploited-in-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T00:03:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has added seven vulnerabilities to its list of actively exploited security issues, including those from Microsoft, Linux, and Jenkins. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RADV Exploring "A Driver On The GPU" In Moving More Vulkan Tasks To The GPU]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=RADV-Exploring-Indirect-Draw</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=RADV-Exploring-Indirect-Draw"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T23:32:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In order to fully support Direct3D Indirect Drawing for allowing more rendering tasks to be moved from the CPU to the GPU, the open-source RADV Radeon Vulkan driver is working on experimental code for effectively hosting "a driver on the GPU."..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setting NVIDIA fan speed without logging in graphically]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ubwslt/setting_nvidia_fan_speed_without_logging_in/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ubwslt/setting_nvidia_fan_speed_without_logging_in/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T22:03:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi,
 I'm try to set my fans to 30% speed when my machine boots
 I've been using nvidia-settings to do it via CLI and even set up a small script to do a fan profile for me every changing every ~5C (before I discovered GreenWithEnvy )
 I'm using SDDM with Plasma. I tried adding the below to my /usr/share/sddm/scripts/Xsession
 nvidia-settings -a "[gpu:0]/GPUFanControlState=1" -a "[fan:0]/GPUTargetFanSpeed=30" -a "[fan:1]/GPUTargetFanSpeed=30" 
 It doesn't seem to activate when SDDM starts. It seems like nvidia-settings doesn't run at all unless a user is logged in graphically. To confirm this, I logged in to tty2 after SDDM started and was sitting at the user login screen. I ran nvidia-settings and it failed, however after adding DISPLAY=:0, it failes with a different error about MIT-MAGIC-COOKIE missing.
 Both of those are kind of beside the problem though. If this was a headless server that wasn't running X, how would I go about using nvidia-settings to set the fanspeed?
    submitted by    /u/bitwaba  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your PC Can’t Run Windows 11? Try Changing These Settings]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=472736</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15248271/windows-wont-upgrade-change-settings"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tried upgrading to Windows 11 only to discover Microsoft’s latest OS version can’t run on your PC? Before you run out and buy a whole new computer, there are a few things you can try first. Here’s what to do.
   

Content

Windows 11 Hardware Requirements
Run PC Health Check
How to Find Out if Your PC Has a TPM
How to Enable TPM on Your PC
How to Enable Secure Boot
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Safely Bypass the TPM 2.0 Requirement in Windows 11
    
Windows 11 Hardware Requirements
    
Before you do anything, you’ll want to make sure that your PC has the following minimum hardware requirements necessary to run Windows 11. Unfortunately, if your PC doesn’t meet these requirements, you won’t be able to run Windows 11. 
    
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Lynch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Posture for Long-Term PC Productivity and Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=794979</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/794979/the-best-posture-for-long-term-pc-productivity-and-gaming/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T21:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Having bad posture can lead to several health problems down the road, including back and neck pain. You can prevent these by using an ergonomic chair or actively paying attention to your posture until it becomes natural.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Nguyen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why You Should Downgrade to a "Dumb" Phone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/115887/why-you-should-downgrade-to-a-dumb-phone/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/115887/why-you-should-downgrade-to-a-dumb-phone/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T20:46:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smartphones have become more than just a minor distraction. Swiping through social media all day is mentally and physically exhausting, yet it’s almost unavoidable, as we’re all addicted to our phones. And while certain apps can help you curb your phone usage, it may be time to just ditch the smartphone and use an old-fashioned “dumb” phone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is this a packaging bug?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ubutzp/is_this_a_packaging_bug/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ubutzp/is_this_a_packaging_bug/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T20:36:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[kwi 25 22:33:11 host-censored systemd[1]: Starting PostgreSQL database server... kwi 25 22:33:11 host-censored postgres[131814]: 2022-04-25 22:33:11.230 CEST [131814] FATAL: incompatible library "/usr/lib/postgresql/timescaledb.so": version mismatch kwi 25 22:33:11 host-censored postgres[131814]: 2022-04-25 22:33:11.230 CEST [131814] DETAIL: Server is version 14, library is version 13. kwi 25 22:33:11 host-censored postgres[131814]: 2022-04-25 22:33:11.230 CEST [131814] LOG: database system is shut down 
 System is up to date, installed from extra/postgresql and community/timescaledb
    submitted by    /u/jaskij  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[xautolock killer not working]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ubussg/xautolock_killer_not_working/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ubussg/xautolock_killer_not_working/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T20:35:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[what's wrong with this line? it gives me no error but the suspend part doesn't work, it only turns the monitor off after 5 min
 xautolock -time 5 -locker "xset dpms force off" -killtime 10 -killer "systemctl suspend" -detectsleep
 if i run systemctl suspend it works
    submitted by    /u/Difri1984  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter Gets a New Crypto Bro CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/115960/twitter-gets-a-new-crypto-bro-ceo/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/115960/twitter-gets-a-new-crypto-bro-ceo/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T20:33:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One crypto bro steps down; another comes to take his place. Just a few weeks after announcing his bid for Twitter, Elon Musk has entered a “definitive agreement” to purchase full ownership of the company. The deal is valued at around $44 billion, and upon its completion, Twitter will exit the stock market and become a private company.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Delete Your Twitter Account]]></title>
        <id>http://www.howtogeek.com/?p=280483</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/280483/how-to-delete-your-twitter-account/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to leave Twitter behind? You can permanently delete your account, erasing all your tweets, followers, favorites, and other data. It will vanish from Twitter almost immediately, and will be fully wiped from Twitter’s servers in 30 days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emotet malware infects users again after fixing broken installer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/emotet-malware-infects-users-again-after-fixing-broken-installer/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/emotet-malware-infects-users-again-after-fixing-broken-installer/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T20:28:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Emotet malware phishing campaign is up and running again after the threat actors fixed a bug preventing people from becoming infected when they opened malicious email attachments. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bash-completion with Zsh for pacman/paru]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ubulez/bashcompletion_with_zsh_for_pacmanparu/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ubulez/bashcompletion_with_zsh_for_pacmanparu/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T20:26:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have switched to using zsh on my arch machine, I'm used to bash and find bash-completion really useful, specially when using pacman. I have installed zsh-completions but it does not give completions for pacman. Is it possible to get them with zsh?
 ​
 Edit: Or even better, complete commands like Fish does. 
    submitted by    /u/PenaflorPhi  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up a PDF Preset in Adobe InDesign]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=793884</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/793884/how-to-set-up-a-pdf-preset-in-adobe-indesign/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T20:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adobe InDesign lets you export your InDesign file as a PDF. Depending on what kind of document you created, you may want to use different PDF presets. You can choose one of InDesign’s PDF presets, or just create your own.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marshall Gunnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SDL 2.0.22 Released With New APIs, Continued Wayland Work]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=SDL-2.0.22-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=SDL-2.0.22-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T19:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SDL 2.0.22 is now officially out as the newest version of this widely-used library by multi-platform games and other software for abstracting various input, graphics, and other system details...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save $100 on an iRobot Roomba i3 EVO Robot Vacuum]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=483186</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15248272/irobot-roomba-i3-evo-robot-vacuum"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are many brands of robot vacuums currently, but if you want to get the job done, why not get the brand that started it all? You can get an iRobot Roomba i3 EVO Robot Vacuum that includes updated features, such as smart mapping, while also saving $100.
    
This vacuum features a premium three-stage cleaning system that delivers 10 times the power-lifting suction compared to the Roomba 600 series. It also includes the Imprint smart mapping system to allow you to clean wherever you need it most. Set schedules so that you can clean whenever you need it as well.
    

    
Your floors will be cleaned in straight lines by the iRobot Roomba i3 EVO Robot Vacuum as it intelligently navigates around obstacles, such as your furniture or pets. Sensors will determine where the vacuum fits to avoid getting stuck anywhere.
    
Pet hair will not be an obstacle, as dual multi-surface rubber brushes flex to adjust to different flooring types to avoid tangles of pet hair. The patented... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add Numbers in Google Sheets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=793168</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/793168/how-to-add-numbers-in-google-sheets/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T19:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can perform many different mathematical operations in Google Sheets, including the addition of numbers. You can add numbers across columns or rows, or even numbers in different cells. Here’s how it’s done.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marshall Gunnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does disabling SWAP save SSD lifetime?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ubs4n8/does_disabling_swap_save_ssd_lifetime/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ubs4n8/does_disabling_swap_save_ssd_lifetime/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T18:40:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Saw this post https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ubeiki/deleted_my_swap_partition_and_computer_feels/ and got curious if I hypothetically didn't have swap, would my SSD last longer.
    submitted by    /u/slohobo  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Animated QR Codes Go Viral, Here's How to Make One]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/115927/animated-qr-codes-go-viral-heres-how-to-make-one/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/115927/animated-qr-codes-go-viral-heres-how-to-make-one/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T18:33:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quick Response (QR) codes are everywhere these days. You’ll find these two-dimensional barcodes in restaurants for the menu, and everyone probably remembers that Coinbase QR code Super Bowl commercial. Most people have used a QR code at some point, but have you ever seen an animated QR code?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Having trouble with internet sharing as explained in the wiki]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ubrynj/having_trouble_with_internet_sharing_as_explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ubrynj/having_trouble_with_internet_sharing_as_explained/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T18:32:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm trying to share over wifi my ethernet connection, and have followed the "Software access point" tutorial on the wiki.
 I've created the wifi link layer without any issues, and managed to connect to it with my phone.
 I set up the NAT with iptables, copying pasting the commands from the wiki without understanding them very well. I substituted the interface names where necessary.
 The manual IP assignment is a bit mysterious on the wiki, so here is how I interpreted it:
 sudo ip address add 192.168.123.105/24 broadcast + dev wlo1 
 Where 192.168.123.105 is the IP address I wish for my phone to connect with.
 On my phone, I connected with the static IP setting, and chose this address and configured the DNS to 1.1.1.1.
 However, my phone says "No internet access" once it has connected to the access point. What did I do wrong and how can I troubleshoot it? Thanks in advance!
    submitted by    /u/7dare  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can I have two Nvidia drivers installed at the same time?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ubrwvz/can_i_have_two_nvidia_drivers_installed_at_the/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ubrwvz/can_i_have_two_nvidia_drivers_installed_at_the/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T18:30:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have two kernels install: the stable kernel and the LTS kernel. However, I cannot boot with the LTS kernel, since I only installed nvidia and not install nvidia-lts as well. Is it possible to have both drivers installed at the same time or will that mess up my installation?
    submitted by    /u/Kronborg11  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Count Unique Values in Google Sheets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=795235</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/795235/how-to-count-unique-values-in-google-sheets/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T18:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Counting the number of distinct values in a spreadsheet is valuable in many situations. Whether it’s customer names, product numbers, or dates, one simple function can help you count unique values in Google Sheets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean hackers targeting journalists with novel malware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/north-korean-hackers-targeting-journalists-with-novel-malware/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/north-korean-hackers-targeting-journalists-with-novel-malware/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T17:51:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean state-sponsored hackers known as APT37 have been discovered targeting journalists specializing in the DPRK with a novel malware strain. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wine Experimenting With GitLab For Improving Development]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Wine-GitLab-Experiment</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Wine-GitLab-Experiment"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T17:30:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wine project leader Alexandre Julliard shared they have setup a GitLab instance for Wine development -- currently as an experiment but they hope it will lead to boosting their workflow for working on this open-source software moving forward...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EKSA E900 Pro Gaming Headset Review]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=478787</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15243325/eksa-e900-pro-gaming-headset"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T17:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gaming headphones are an essential bit of kit if you crave full immersion and comms with other players in MPGs. The only downside for me has always been the permanent mic stalk, as any gaming headset looks silly on the train or at times they’re used for your phone or other device. The EKSA E900 Pro Gaming Headset gets around this limitation in a couple of interesting ways and produces a set of headphones that are very decent in quality while being versatile as well. They score well in other areas too.
    
This is a sponsored article and was made possible by EKSA. The actual contents and opinions are the sole views of the author who maintains editorial independence, even when a post is sponsored.
    
Nice Pro Features
    
Unboxing the EKSA E900 Pro headphones, you will find a nice chunky pair of gaming headphones with LEDs embedded on the outside of the earpieces, so you look super-cool in Zoom chats, but they also have some nice pro features. The mic is detachable, and although the headset is designed primarily to work via USB, you also have an additional cable... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phil South</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is MoUSO Core Worker Process? (mousocoreworker.exe)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=799180</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/799180/what-is-mouso-core-worker-process-mousocoreworker.exe/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T17:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A mysterious executable that is causing high disk usage, high RAM consumption, and using your CPU can be alarming. But don’t worry — mousocoreworker.exe is a normal part of Windows 10 and Windows 11. Here’s what you need to know.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Lewis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[importing pgp key error?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ubpq8i/importing_pgp_key_error/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ubpq8i/importing_pgp_key_error/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T16:54:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[doing a fresh arch install. The iso I am using is the latest release. Getting an error when trying to install git on a live usb. Any help? 
 Error: 
 Import PGP key 51E8B148A9999C34, "Euangelos Foutras foutrelis@archlinux.org"? [Y/n] y 
 error: key "Evangelos Foutras Kevangelos@foutrelis.com>" could not be imported 
 error: required key missing from keyring error: failed to commit transaction (unexpected error) 
 Errors occurred, no packages were upgraded.
    submitted by    /u/QuackAttack206  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Raspberry Pi 4 (40 Euro) da usare come PC, console, tablet, NAS o server]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2015/03/il-raspberry-pi-2-da-40-euro-puo.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2015/03/il-raspberry-pi-2-da-40-euro-puo.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T16:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Il Raspberry Pi è un vero e proprio computer tascabile, pensato per gli esperti informatici che vogliono smanettare con il codice e creare piccoli computer per la domotica, piccoli PC desktop, server dati e server multimediali da collegare alla TV o alla rete casalinga. Questo non significa che gli utenti meno esperti non possano provare il Raspberry PI 4: a volte basta solo il case giusto e...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[System76 Releases Pop!_OS 22.04]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Pop-OS-22.04</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Pop-OS-22.04"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T16:19:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[System76 has released Pop!_OS 22.04 as the newest version of their Linux distribution downstream based on Ubuntu 22.04 LTS...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deal Alert: Samsung's Galaxy S22 Ultra Hits Its Lowest Price Yet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/115885/deal-alert-samsungs-galaxy-s22-ultra-hits-its-lowest-price-yet/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/115885/deal-alert-samsungs-galaxy-s22-ultra-hits-its-lowest-price-yet/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T16:02:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung’s latest Galaxy S22 line has a lot to offer, including the top-of-the-line Galaxy S22 Ultra with its S-Pen stylus. Unfortunately, it’s also pretty expensive, but Samsung’s flagship phone just hit its lowest price yet on Amazon this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Expands Its Accessories Lineup With ... Smart Water Bottles?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/115884/apple-expands-its-accessories-lineup-with-smart-water-bottles/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/115884/apple-expands-its-accessories-lineup-with-smart-water-bottles/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T16:02:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple’s array of accessories are almost as exciting as its terrific smartphones and laptops. The two latest additions to the company’s line of accessories are smart water bottles, and they sport some super cool functionality to help you get (and stay) hydrated.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzanne Humphries</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Restart a Phone Without the Power Button]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=799575</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/799575/how-to-restart-a-phone-without-the-power-button/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T16:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes the physical power buttons on Android phones and iPhones stop working. The longer you use a device, the more likely that moving parts will fail. Can you restart a phone without the power button? There are options.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Rid of Photoshop's "Save to Creative Cloud" Popup]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/115869/how-to-get-rid-of-photoshops-save-to-creative-cloud-popup/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/115869/how-to-get-rid-of-photoshops-save-to-creative-cloud-popup/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T15:45:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s hard to use Photoshop without running into some annoyance or inconvenience. But the file exporting process is an especially big pain point, and it’s only gotten worse with Adobe’s new “Save to Creative Cloud” popup. Thankfully, you can disable this popup to save a step in the exporting process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I updated my system yesterday and now several packages are borked. What should I do when pacman acts up?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ubo52v/i_updated_my_system_yesterday_and_now_several/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ubo52v/i_updated_my_system_yesterday_and_now_several/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T15:45:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several of my packages would get the error where their not installed correctly because they exist while also not existing.
 Zsh required me to manually remove all zsh files from /usr to even reinstall zsh.
 For vtk I had able to use a pacman --overwrite.
 I needed those two packages for work which I can start about almost 5 hours later than expected now. Im assuming many other packages are screwed as well.
 Running pacman -Qkk gives me hundreds of warnings. And used to give an error for vtk.
 How did something like this even happen. Now that it has happened how can I fix it wthout creating a long delay again.
    submitted by    /u/NoCSForYou  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weird problem adding user to group]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ubnztb/weird_problem_adding_user_to_group/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ubnztb/weird_problem_adding_user_to_group/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T15:39:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm trying to add myself to the uucp group to access serial devices, but I'm experiencing strangeness. Apparently my user isn't added to the group until I do a redundant su:
 [bb@bbc ~]$ groups sys network power lxd lp wheel bb [bb@bbc ~]$ whoami bb [bb@bbc ~]$ su bb Password: [bb@bbc ~]$ groups sys network power lxd uucp lp wheel bb 
 I've tried logging out completely, but the issue remains. The new group config apparently just isn't loaded for the user until I su. It also gets unloaded afterwards:
 [bb@bbc ~]$ groups sys network power lxd uucp lp wheel bb [bb@bbc ~]$ exit exit [bb@bbc ~]$ groups sys network power lxd lp wheel bb [bb@bbc ~]$ groups bb wheel lp uucp sys network power lxd bb 
 Did I miss a step to make Linux parse the config after usermod -a -G?
    submitted by    /u/ReturningTarzan  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Tricks to Speed Up Compile Times in Gentoo Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=470660</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15243050/speed-up-compile-times-gentoo"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gentoo is a powerful and flexible Linux distribution. With its innovative package manager – Portage – it allows you to sculpt your computer system down to its most basic parts.
    
This is because Gentoo, by default, requires you to compile all the packages that you want to install. That approach allows you to change compile-time settings. This includes settings for various technologies which would not have been possible in a binary-based distribution.
   

Content

What is Source Package Management?
1. Optimize MAKEOPTS
2. Take Advantage of CCache
3. Try DistCC
4. Use BuildPKG
5. Optimize your Compiler in Gentoo
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Fix Broken Packages in Linux
    
What is Source Package Management?
    
Source-based package management is the original way of distributing third-party programs in Linux. This is a system where a maintainer has a list of... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramces Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch as a first distro?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ubno3p/arch_as_a_first_distro/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ubno3p/arch_as_a_first_distro/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T15:24:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ok. What the hell. Ive gone through 5 installation attempts and didnt sleep for 2 days because I liked the neofetch icon. I know. Then I configured Realtek adapter to work so I feel like there`s nothing I cant fix now. Ive been running the system for a few days now and did a lot of customization. But when I told my experienced friend about it he said Arch is an unnecessarily complex system and I should just switch to Ubuntu because its kernel has more lines or something and so it is better. Thoguhts?
    submitted by    /u/Expert-Independent-6  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unable to recover from suspend.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ubnlhf/unable_to_recover_from_suspend/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ubnlhf/unable_to_recover_from_suspend/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T15:21:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have a Dell XPS 15 9500, with an nvidia graphcis card. I've had an issue for a while where my laptop isn't able to recover from suspend (either triggered directly via systemctl suspend, or by closing the laptop lid). After suspend, no input given to the laptop will cause the display to turn back on. The only thing I'm able to do is press the power button to turn the laptop off.
 Update: initially my kernel modules in /etc/mkinitcpio.conf were
 MODULES=(intel_agp i915 nvidia nvidia_modeset nvidia_uvm nvidia_drm) 
 I haven't tried every combination of these, but using
 MODULES=() 
 allows for recovering from suspend, although this seems like a bad idea
    submitted by    /u/ss7m  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Pixel Watch May Have Larger Bezels Than We Expected]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/115851/the-pixel-watch-may-have-larger-bezels-than-we-expected/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/115851/the-pixel-watch-may-have-larger-bezels-than-we-expected/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T15:07:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It seems that a Google employee left their Pixel Watch prototype in a Chicago restaurant. Photos of the purported prototype were published by Android Police, and these images seem to verify previous leaks about the smartwatch’s design. Unfortunately, the new pictures also reveal the Pixel Watch’s thick bezels.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Mine ArQmA Coin (ARQ) With Your PC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/?p=59561</id>
        <link href="https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/mine-arqma-coin-cpu/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T15:01:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ArQmA is a decentralized open-source public blockchain project. It is a cryptocurrency based on the Monero source code and is constantly being improved]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikita</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Copy Values From the Status Bar in Microsoft Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=795249</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/795249/how-to-copy-values-from-the-status-bar-in-microsoft-excel/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T15:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Status Bar in Microsoft Excel allows you to quickly see the average, sum, or count of selected cells. But what’s better than viewing those values is being able to use them. Here’s how copy directly from the Status Bar.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[French hospital group disconnects Internet after hackers steal data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/french-hospital-group-disconnects-internet-after-hackers-steal-data/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/french-hospital-group-disconnects-internet-after-hackers-steal-data/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T14:48:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The GHT Coeur Grand Est. Hospitals and Health Care group comprising nine establishments with 3,370 beds across Northeast France has disclosed a cyberattack that resulted in the theft of sensitive administrative and patient data. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GM Confirms a Hybrid Electric Corvette Is Coming Next Year]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/115857/gm-confirms-a-hybrid-electric-corvette-is-coming-next-year/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/115857/gm-confirms-a-hybrid-electric-corvette-is-coming-next-year/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T14:47:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following years of rumors and speculation, today, General Motors finally confirmed an “electrified” Chevy Corvette is coming next year. This is big news for the automotive world, but that’s not all the company had to say.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Install Arch on Windows 10 laptop]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ubmji6/install_arch_on_windows_10_laptop/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ubmji6/install_arch_on_windows_10_laptop/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T14:33:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I would like to use the entire disk of my HP Elitebook (Intel i5-7300U @ 2.60GHz) to install Arch. Currently it contains Windows 10. I've read the install guide. It recommended to use the existing EFI partition ("If the disk from which you want to boot already has an EFI system partition, do not create another one, but use the existing partition instead.") 
 A few lines further down, in the example layout, the suggested minimum size for this partition is 300 Mb. I'm confused, because my existing partition is 99 Mb (see below). I would much rather start with a clean slate.
 So my question is twofold: can I ignore this advice about the existing EFI partition and what is the best way to start with an empty disk? And as an aside: do I need EFI at all?
 fdisk -l Disk /dev/nvme0n1: 238.47 GiB, 2…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 App per guadagnare soldi veri con lo smartphone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2016/01/6-app-per-guadagnare-soldi-veri-con-lo.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2016/01/6-app-per-guadagnare-soldi-veri-con-lo.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T14:21:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Da sempre internet ha fornito mezzi e possibilità per guadagnare soldi da casa, generalmente inserendo pubblicità sul proprio sito web o blog oppure caricando video su YouTube. Per guadagnare qualcosa sono disponibili anche delle applicazioni, per smartphone Android e iPhone, che permettono di intascare soldi veri in vari modi. Non si tratta certamente di applicazioni che ci faranno diventare...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What You Need to Know About the Insignia Air Fryer Recall]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lifesavvy.com/126154/what-you-need-to-know-about-the-insignia-air-fryer-recall/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lifesavvy.com/126154/what-you-need-to-know-about-the-insignia-air-fryer-recall/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T14:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We all love our air fryers, but you might want to double-check your model number—it might be part of the recall recently issued by Best Buy in conjunction with the Consumer Product Safety Commission.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shea Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Laptop Bags of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=768978</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/768978/the-best-laptop-bags-of-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T14:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Laptops are expensive and fragile objects, so it’s important to take care of them in transit. The right bag can keep your laptop safe, whether you’re commuting to work on a train or bicycling in the rain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>