<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-04-10T01:42:47.661Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Archlinux and imposter syndrome - A thread for Noobs.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u05bsf/archlinux_and_imposter_syndrome_a_thread_for_noobs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u05bsf/archlinux_and_imposter_syndrome_a_thread_for_noobs/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T23:43:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I installed Archlinux last year, and it was a disaster from the start because I was struggling to understand some of the basic concepts. I took time to finally read about the things that were causing me trouble, such as Grub, Sudo, networking and some other random issue.
 FF today, and I was feeling like an imposter on Arch. I began asking myself if I could swim. So I decided, hey; let's try installing to a VM without diving into man or info files except maybe for a reference, and stick with only the Arch User Install guide. Granted, I still need to do some system maintenance.
 I cautiously booted the April Installer in VirtualBox via UEFI mode, and got nervous that maybe it wouldn't work because of vbox issues in the past. I had to choose the EFI image, and then to test, I attempted the archinstall script. This failed when installing packages. I felt defeated for a brief moment, and then remembered that was only to see how it would work. No big deal.
 I then began to follow the Install Guide,which I myself, and many in the Arch community recommend. The time was set, the partitions were made, the system was pacstrapped and it all seemed to go much easier than I recall. Could this work from the first go, I questioned myself? Something must have been done incorrectly, this is not going to work. Having installed LXQt, I ran systemctl enable sddm and hoped for the best.
 Aha, I was greeted with the login screen, and no user listed. I had forgotten a simple useradd So, I switched to tty2 and made the user and rebooted. I then proceeded to boot into my freshly installed Archlinux vm and was presented with the LXQt desktop Environment. There are still many things to do for house cleaning, but this felt like success.
 Don't give up.
 edited for spelling.
    submitted by    /u/RandomXUsr  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gnome update broke my themes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u054yg/gnome_update_broke_my_themes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u054yg/gnome_update_broke_my_themes/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T23:32:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I had like 5 or 6 themes before updating, the after i updated i saw, that my adwaita-dark theme (that i used) is gone, tweaks thinks that there is only one theme, while in the folder (/usr/share/themes). Any way to recover my theme settings?
    submitted by    /u/ZmEYkA_3310  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best way to install on 2 equally sized hard drives]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u048v5/best_way_to_install_on_2_equally_sized_hard_drives/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u048v5/best_way_to_install_on_2_equally_sized_hard_drives/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T22:45:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have two 1 TB SSD's on my computer. I have been searching through google for a while now in order to figure out best course of action to utilize this space. Most of the posts I have encountered center around installing on a system with one small root SSD and one bigger home one which does not apply to me. The second SSD can be easily formatted and mounted to be used as a storage space for files but then the package manager does not install packages there when home partition gets full.
 What I planned to do was that one SSD would have boot, swap, root ,home as usual while the other SSD also being included in /home so that it is utilized by the package manager. I don't exactly know if this is possible. In any case, can anyone point me into the right direction to look at to figure it out?
 TL;DR my main goal is that I want my OS to use both drives to install packages, both home partition of the 1st drive and the whole of 2nd drive, kinda like treating it as one.
    submitted by    /u/LopsidedExperience30  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cinnamon doesn't load: "Could not locate g_main_context_new_with_flags"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u03mqp/cinnamon_doesnt_load_could_not_locate_g_main/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u03mqp/cinnamon_doesnt_load_could_not_locate_g_main/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T22:12:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just installed Arch, but I have some old config directories I copied over. I'm open to removing the cinnamon-specific directories and starting from scratch, though I removed .config/cinnamon-session and it doesn't seem to have helped.
 Here's the full error text: ``` Cinnamon warning: Failed to load theme "Adwaita": Failed to find a valid file for theme Adwaita
 Cinnamon warning: Failed to load theme "Adwaita": Failed to find a valid file for theme Adwaita
 Cinnamon warning: Could not find theme Adwaita. Falling back to default theme.Cinnamon warning: Could not find theme Adwaita. Falling back to default theme.Clutter-Message: 18:04:13.748: Sync method: PRESENTATION TIME Clutter-Message: 18:04:13.748: Sync method: PRESENTATION TIME Cjs-Message: 18:04:13.939: JS LOG: About to start Cinnamon…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NTFS partition keeps failing to mount?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u02dgy/ntfs_partition_keeps_failing_to_mount/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u02dgy/ntfs_partition_keeps_failing_to_mount/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T21:09:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have a windows 11 + Arch dualboot, and a third NTFS partition for data shared between the OS' so I don't have to mount the real windows partition.
 In Windows, Hybrid sleep/Fast startup is turned off.
 I've tried `sudo ntfsfix /dev/nvme0n1p1 && sudo mount /dev/nvme0n1p1 /shared, and that works for that running instance, but if I reboot, it doesn't stay working, it fails to mount on boot again. I don't even need to do the ntfsfix either, mount on its own works fine.
 I have not yet tried going back to the ntfs-3g driver, cause I'd like to avoid doing that if possible. I had some issue a while back with some program not supporting FUSE drivers, while ntfs3 isn't FUSE. I can't remember what program it was, but I don't want to have to find a workaround for that. I just want my partition work…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make Sure a File Is Safe Before Downloading It]]></title>
        <id>http://www.howtogeek.com/?p=30508</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/howto/30508/make-sure-downloads-are-safe-before-downloading-them/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re concerned a file might be malicious, you don’t need to download it and rely on your antivirus. You can scan the file for malware with over 90 antivirus engines before you download it—all with one single tool.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Didn't Believe This Irish Spring Gamer Shower Was Real, but It Is]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/114538/we-didnt-believe-this-irish-spring-gamer-shower-was-real-but-it-is/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/114538/we-didnt-believe-this-irish-spring-gamer-shower-was-real-but-it-is/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T20:04:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Irish Spring announced the “Gamer Shower” on April 1st, we assumed that it was a joke. Everybody knows that gamers don’t bathe, and all that. But it turns out that the 2-in-1 body wash company actually made an elaborate shower for gamers, complete with a gaming massage chair, giant TVs, and thankfully, soap.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Having a bad time attempting to use a prebuilt Linux VM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u011pq/having_a_bad_time_attempting_to_use_a_prebuilt/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u011pq/having_a_bad_time_attempting_to_use_a_prebuilt/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T20:01:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello :-)
 I wanted to try Arch Linux out & am struggling to get to the GUI I was hoping it'd just boot into it.
 It's not :-(
 Here's where I got the VM from: https://www.linuxvmimages.com/images/archlinux/#download-links
 I tried to login with the supplied credentials & am taken to a terminal so I tried start & startx neither boots up a GUI.
 I admittedly don't know very much about Linux & was going to use this to see what I thought of it since I've heard it's 1 of the common distros becoming pretty popular similar to Manjaro, Linux Mint, Ubunuto/Kubunutu/Lubunutu etc
 Would appreciate it very much if anyone could tell me what to do to get to a GUI based mode.
    submitted by    /u/Jaladhjin  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Default Printer Paper Size on Mac]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=790969</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/790969/how-to-set-default-printer-paper-size-on-mac/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T20:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you print frequently with different paper sizes on a Mac, you might get frustrated if the system is stuck on the wrong paper size that you don’t want to use. Luckily, it’s easy to set the default paper size for all printers on your Mac. Here’s how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Remove Bloatware from Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=330184</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/14560083/remove-bloatware-from-windows10"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t you hate it when you get a shiny new computer, and you find it to be full of programs you don’t want or need (or what we call bloatware)? The manufacturer added these programs to your computer to promote their apps or the apps of their partners. They waste space on your hard drive, appear on your Start menu, and sometimes they can run in the background and slow down your PC.
    
You can remove bloatware from Windows 10 or Windows 11 and free up space. Be aware, though, that major Windows updates tend to reinstall them anyway, so you may find yourself battling against that. 
    
Luckily, we’ve put together a list of different ways to get rid of bloatware and unwanted applications. Here they are!
   

Content

O&O ShutUp10++
Remove Suggestions and Ads
Traditional Uninstall
Remove Bloatware with PowerShell
Delete Bloatware Using DISM
Windows 10 Debloater App (also works in Windows 11)

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Zak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dealing with an issue. that often happens after the computer is logged into KDE for extended period of time, It will suddenly no longer be able to open apps, or even show the KDE lockscreen this is the error that appears when attempting to run an app from the terminal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u0095w/dealing_with_an_issue_that_often_happens_after/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u0095w/dealing_with_an_issue_that_often_happens_after/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T19:21:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maximum number of clients reachedFailed to open display
 Maximum number of clients reachedqt.qpa.xcb: could not connect to display :0
 qt.qpa.plugin: Could not load the Qt platform plugin "xcb" in "" even though it was found.
 This application failed to start because no Qt platform plugin could be initialized. Reinstalling the application m
 ay fix this problem. 
 Available platform plugins are: eglfs, linuxfb, minimal, minimalegl, offscreen, vnc, wayland-egl, wayland, wayland-
 xcomposite-egl, wayland-xcomposite-glx, xcb.
 This happens with apps like LibreOffice, Chromuim and more
    submitted by    /u/skymtf  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mistakenly reinstalled dbus, can't boot anymore]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tzzyeb/mistakenly_reinstalled_dbus_cant_boot_anymore/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tzzyeb/mistakenly_reinstalled_dbus_cant_boot_anymore/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T19:06:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, I didn't know dbus was part of the system and did pacman -S dbus Now I can't execute any command (it says "Failed to connect to bus") which is ironic because every solution on Google seems to be running systemctl commands. Any idea? Thanks
    submitted by    /u/MathWellan  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Delete a YouTube Playlist]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=791449</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/791449/delete-youtube-playlist/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T19:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[YouTube playlists aren’t meant to be kept forever. If you’ve finished watching all contents of a playlist, you can delete the playlist so your list is not cluttered. Here’s how to do just that on YouTube from your desktop or mobile phone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Borked telegram-desktop 3.6.1-2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tzzrjn/borked_telegramdesktop_3612/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tzzrjn/borked_telegramdesktop_3612/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T18:57:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm facing huge CPU usage by telegram-desktop 3.6.1-2 after opening a chat, anyone facing the same issue?
    submitted by    /u/joseph20_  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Locale-gen error during installation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tzzg8x/localegen_error_during_installation/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tzzg8x/localegen_error_during_installation/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T18:41:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So i uncommented en_us.utf-8 utf-8 in locale.gen but when i did locale-gen it said character map file ‘utf-8’ not found: no such file or directory.
    submitted by    /u/Intrepidtelephone2  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers use Conti's leaked ransomware to attack Russian companies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-use-contis-leaked-ransomware-to-attack-russian-companies/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-use-contis-leaked-ransomware-to-attack-russian-companies/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T18:30:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A hacking group used the Conti's leaked ransomware source code to create their own ransomware to use in cyberattacks against Russian organizations. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Installing zfs breaks dependency]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tzysyg/installing_zfs_breaks_dependency/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tzysyg/installing_zfs_breaks_dependency/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T18:08:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently installed zfs-dkms and zfs-utils from the AUR to get zfs support, and this is the first time I'm upgrading my system since then. I saw these upgrades available in yay.
 aur/zfs-dkms 2.1.3-1 -> 2.1.4-1 aur/zfs-utils 2.1.3-1 -> 2.1.4-1 
 When I ran the upgrade command it spent a long time upgrading various packages including some of these zfs related things then failed with this error.
 :: installing zfs-utils (2.1.4-1) breaks dependency 'zfs-utils=2.1.3' required by zfs-dkms 
 I had to uninstall zfs-dkms and zfs-utils then reinstall them for it to work. But why did this happen? How can I prevent it from happening on future upgrades?
    submitted by    /u/Status-Floor3119  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Check Out This Creator's Custom 3D-Printed Film Movie Camera]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/114509/check-out-this-creators-custom-3d-printed-film-movie-camera/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/114509/check-out-this-creators-custom-3d-printed-film-movie-camera/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T18:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anybody can film something digitally on a cheap smartphone, but you’ll need some serious (and seriously expensive) equipment to film a big-budget movie on, well, film. One filmmaker is looking to make film cameras more expensive, and just made one with a 3D printer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzanne Humphries</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Screen Record on iPhone 13]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=796671</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/796671/how-to-screen-record-on-iphone-13/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T18:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you need to capture what’s happening on your iPhone 13’s screen in motion, don’t take a screenshot—grab a screen recording video instead. Luckily, your iPhone 13 (regular, Mini, Pro, or Pro Max) makes it easy with a Control Center shortcut. Here’s how to use it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Question about creation of a swap file]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tzy2fg/question_about_creation_of_a_swap_file/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tzy2fg/question_about_creation_of_a_swap_file/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T17:32:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey everybody, I've been on arch for a week or two now (as a first time user), and I've finally gotten around to trying to create a swap file for my laptop with 8GiB of RAM. 
 The issue I'm facing is that while i do know how to create a swap file on an ext4 system, I'm not quite sure how to do so on a btrfs system with auto snapshot-ting also set up. Simply creating a swap file leads to timeshift not being able to create snapshots, so I have to apparently set up a swap file in a separate sub volume. I frankly don't know how to do this, so any and all help with creating swap like this would be appreciated. 
 Going on a tangent, what do you guys think i should be using? Zram or swap? As i said I have a machine with 8gigs of RAM and occasionally this leads to complete freezes after which i have to force reboot. 
 Thanks for all the replies.
    submitted by    /u/NakamericaIsANoob  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Automatically Change Wallpaper on a Chromebook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=795729</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/795729/how-to-automatically-change-wallpaper-on-a-chromebook/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Changing the wallpaper on your desktop is an easy way to personalize your Chromebook. It’s what you see any time you’re not using an app. We’ll show you how to automatically see a new desktop background every day.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Good News, LG Just Confirmed at Least Three Phones Will Get Android 12]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/114512/good-news-lg-just-confirmed-at-least-three-phones-will-get-android-12/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/114512/good-news-lg-just-confirmed-at-least-three-phones-will-get-android-12/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T16:34:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After years of battling the competition, LG closed its mobile division in early 2021 to put its time and effort into other things. Almost exactly one year later, LG has confirmed that several phones will be getting the Android 12 update soon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JPG vs. JPEG: Are They the Same Thing?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=796389</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/796389/jpg-vs.-jpeg-are-they-the-same-thing/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T16:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve used a computer, digital camera, or smartphone long enough, you’ve likely seen files with either JPG or JPEG extensions in them. But are they the same thing? What’s the difference? We’ll explain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best way to create a live USB, with a writable partition ?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tzvrhx/best_way_to_create_a_live_usb_with_a_writable/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tzvrhx/best_way_to_create_a_live_usb_with_a_writable/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T15:40:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To lead workshops, I would like to provide a usb flash drives which boots an archlinux on any hardware (I mean x86_64 hardwares... but that can boot on UEFI and Bios).
 But here is the tricky thing :
 I would to have a common OS part which does the boot and hold the different packages, and a choice of the workshop to load (either at boot, either later.
 These workshop configurations would only concern the home directory, and the software launched at boot. By the way, I would also like to forbid the user any modification on neither the flash drive, neither the host machine.
 But I would like to myself be able to change these workshop configurations later on without burning again the full drive. 
 How would you do it ?
 ​
 Here are my ideas :
 1 partition for the system, that would remain read-only.
 1 partition for the mods for each workshop.
 The workshop could be changed by logging to a specific user account, and to avoid modification on the drive, a ram disk would be mounted.
 However, the only hybrid UEFI/Bios boot I encountered so far are from live usb iso... And I definitively don't know hos to proceed to add writable partition on such devices...
 ​
 ​
 Any suggestions ?
    submitted by    /u/hl037  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel mismatch after update. Emergency shell]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tzvmgj/kernel_mismatch_after_update_emergency_shell/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tzvmgj/kernel_mismatch_after_update_emergency_shell/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T15:33:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So I'm writing this because I ran out of ideas on how to fix this. This all started when there was that big firmware update, after update my wi-fi wasn't working, because of a bug. I'm using lvm snapshots so I tried to revert it but it was unsuccessful. Somehow I got kernel mismatch, which is weird because I never had problems like that on my other PC. After that I went in live boot and updated system again. It fixed kernel mismatch. And since then 2 out of 3 updates ended in kernel mismatch.
 I already tried going in live boot and updating again, reverting snapshot. In the latest attempt to update I'm 100% sure boot partition was mounted because mount printed /dev/nvme0n1p1 mounted on /boot/EFI (nvme0n1p1 is boot partition). It was a while ago when I was trying to fix this issue and I forgot everything that I tried. I tried searching ArchWiki and forums and noting helped me. I did however discover that when you are updating your system, that your boot partition needs to be mounted and if you unmount it it should be empty. If I unmount my partition it's not empty (stat initramfs-linux.img shows file was indeed copied there at last update).
 When I try to boot I get:
  
[FAILED] failed to start Load Kernel modules.[FAILED] failed to mount /boot/EFI[DEPEND] Dependency failed for Local File System
  
Then I get emergency shell.
 journalctl -xb mentions:
  
/boot/EFI: unknown filesystem type 'vfat'
  
cat /etc/fstab
  
UUID=ZE69-C2EC /boot/EFI vfat rw,realtime, .... , errors=remount-ro 0 2
  
uname -a
  
5.16.10-arch1-1 ...
  
pacman -Q
  
5.17.1.arch1-1
  
Last time I updated I gave up trying to fix it because only kernel downgrade worked. Today I tried to update it again since I hoped it would be fixed by update, like the first time, but that didn't happen.
 I'm also using LVM on Luks if this is important.
 Does anyone have any ideas what else I can try or where else can I look for solution? Anyway thanks for reading.
    submitted by    /u/IdeaForNameNotFound  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenRazer 3.3 Released With Support For More Razer Devices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=OpenRazer-3.3</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=OpenRazer-3.3"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T15:29:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new release of OpenRazer is available as the community project providing open-source Linux drivers for various Razer devices from their keyboards and mice to headsets and other peripherals from the popular gaming device manufacturer...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Update AMD Graphics Drivers in Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=post-ideas&amp;p=304696</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/11949588/update-amd-graphics-drivers-windows"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AMD is one of the behemoths of graphics on PC. Granted, Nvidia is miles ahead in terms of actual sales, but if you want great value for the money and comparable performance, then AMD could be the way to go. Updating graphics drivers should usually be a simple process, but there are certainly better and worse ways to do it.
    
Sometimes taking the default GPU update route can lead to a misbehaving graphics card, so we show you how to update your AMD drivers so that they work properly after the update in bot Windows 10 and 11.
   

Content

Update AMD Drivers – Basic Method
Update AMD Drivers through File Explorer
Update AMD Drivers Using DDU

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:AMD Radeon Software Settings – What Do They All Mean?
    
Update AMD Drivers – Basic Method
   ... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Zak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did GLIBC 2.35 break xz-java?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tzve3x/did_glibc_235_break_xzjava/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tzve3x/did_glibc_235_break_xzjava/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T15:22:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[sometime after the glibc update I started getting
 java.lang.RuntimeException: org.tukaani.xz.CorruptedInputException: XZ Index is corrupt
 in filebot and others are getting this error in jdownloader2. I can recreate with various levels of java and xz-java using the developer's XZDecDemo.java sample. They work on my macOS and ubuntu/pi and fail on my archlinux.
 Can't really downgrade glibc to test my hypothesis, can I?
    submitted by    /u/Sardonimous  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Android banking malware remotely takes control of your device]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-android-banking-malware-remotely-takes-control-of-your-device/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-android-banking-malware-remotely-takes-control-of-your-device/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T15:02:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new Android banking malware named Octo has appeared in the wild, featuring remote access capabilities that allow malicious operators to perform on-device fraud. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Save a Microsoft Outlook Email as a PDF]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=793632</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/793632/how-to-save-a-microsoft-outlook-email-as-a-pdf/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T15:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To save your Microsoft Outlook emails as PDF for offline use, utilize your desktop computer’s virtual PDF printer to print your emails in PDF format. We’ll show you how to do that in Outlook’s desktop and web versions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does Wayland video acceleration work right now in Firefox or Chromium ?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tztv0d/does_wayland_video_acceleration_work_right_now_in/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tztv0d/does_wayland_video_acceleration_work_right_now_in/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T14:04:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm curious since the situation seems to change every version jump
    submitted by    /u/Lehner82  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft: Windows Autopatch steals the 'fun' from Patch Tuesdays]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-windows-autopatch-steals-the-fun-from-patch-tuesdays/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-windows-autopatch-steals-the-fun-from-patch-tuesdays/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft announced that Windows Autopatch, a service designed to automatically keep Windows and Office software up to date, will be released in July 2022. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Bluetooth Trackers of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=724315</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/724315/best-bluetooth-trackers/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nobody likes losing their items, which is why there’s a large market for Bluetooth trackers. These handy little gadgets can help you keep track of almost anything. Which one is the best? We have a few recommendations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[Question] Hey everyone, does anyone know how to install packages that are inside a text file? I have a file that has a lot of packages but it will take ages to install one by one]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tztotp/question_hey_everyone_does_anyone_know_how_to/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tztotp/question_hey_everyone_does_anyone_know_how_to/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T13:55:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/Mitass  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cannot open gruvbox theme with nautilus in arch linux when downloading material in brave?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tztjmd/cannot_open_gruvbox_theme_with_nautilus_in_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tztjmd/cannot_open_gruvbox_theme_with_nautilus_in_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T13:47:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I download some things with brave, it seems like default theme working instead of gruvbox theme. However, chrome works well, I don't know why. Can someone help me, I'm using arch linux, thanks guys?
 https://reddit.com/link/tztjmd/video/7a4huobpcis81/player
    submitted by    /u/chk2k2  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[particle effects on x11 cursor?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tztgt5/particle_effects_on_x11_cursor/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tztgt5/particle_effects_on_x11_cursor/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T13:43:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is it possible to add particles effects to an x11 cursor? if it is, how do i?
    submitted by    /u/Background_Jacket273  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Proton AG acquires SimpleLogin, an email alias service]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=177925</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/04/09/proton-ag-acquires-simplelogin-email-alias-service/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T13:21:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Proton AG, the Swiss company behind the popular privacy-friendly products ProtonMail and ProtonVPN has acquired the email alias service SimpleLogin. SimpleLogin is an open source email alias service that has free, commercial […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Proton AG acquires SimpleLogin, an email alias service appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GNOME Application Grid isn't work correctly.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tzt2fi/gnome_application_grid_isnt_work_correctly/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tzt2fi/gnome_application_grid_isnt_work_correctly/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T13:20:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, I'm using Gnome as desktop environment. But today, I saw a problem on Application Grid. The problem is: The application icons not showing. Only Accerciser, Add/Remove Software and Avahi packages showing. How can I fix this?
 Image: Imgur
    submitted by    /u/Sonayraenn  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Solved the Biggest Annoyance With Batteries but You Can't Have It]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/114332/microsoft-solved-the-biggest-annoyance-with-batteries-but-you-cant-have-it/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/114332/microsoft-solved-the-biggest-annoyance-with-batteries-but-you-cant-have-it/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T13:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Batteries are useful but have a few issues. They can only hold so much charge; recharging them takes time if it’s even an option; there are many different types, and you have to insert them in a particular way. Microsoft has fixed that last issue, but you can’t have its solution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McQuilling</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Stream Every Harry Potter Movie in 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=794452</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/794452/how-to-stream-every-harry-potter-movie-online/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Based on the bestselling novels by J.K. Rowling, the Harry Potter movies are some of the most popular fantasy films ever released. They’ve grown to encompass an entire franchise of magical adventures. Here’s how to stream every Harry Potter movie.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Bell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Failing to load after 5.17 Update w/ nvidia optimus?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tzs9tw/failing_to_load_after_517_update_w_nvidia_optimus/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tzs9tw/failing_to_load_after_517_update_w_nvidia_optimus/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T12:33:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm wondering if anybody else has this problem, and/or what they've done about it?
 Looks to be related to optimus-manager and/or the nvidia drivers under Linux 5.17.x
 Basically bricks the system, thankfully I've got timeshift to save my butt - this is a work system after all.
 I've done the same update on a desktop not using nvidia-optimus and it's running perfectly fine but the laptop really doesn't like it...
    submitted by    /u/foobarhouse  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Guida Minecraft, il gioco di costruzione e sopravvivenza più giocato al mondo]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2014/11/guida-per-scaricare-e-iniziare-minecraft.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2014/11/guida-per-scaricare-e-iniziare-minecraft.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T12:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Minecraft è uno dei giochi più famosi su PC e su console, con una comunità di giocatori enorme su cui contare per trovare nuovi amici o nuove situazioni di gioco e migliaia di mod da installare per rendere il gioco ancora più bello.

 Minecraft è un gioco creativo di costruzione e di sopravvivenza con una grafica molto "cubettosa", infinite possibilità di movimento e di crescita che dipendono...


Continua a leggere su Navigweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Watch UFC 273 Volkanovski vs. The Korean Zombie Live Online]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=795918</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/795918/how-to-watch-ufc-273/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T12:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Broadcasting live from VyStar Veterans Memorial Arena in Jacksonville, Florida, at 7 p.m. PT / 10 p.m. ET on April 9, 2022, UFC 273 pits  Alexander Volkanovski against Chan Sung Jung, aka “The Korean Zombie.” Here’s how to stream it live.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Bell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stop Using Flashlight Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=796112</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/796112/stop-using-flashlight-apps/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T11:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Flashlight apps were once a clever tool inspired by everyone having a display in their pocket. Those days are long gone, though. You shouldn’t be using flashlight apps anymore. We’ll explain why and what you should use instead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[openSUSE Tumbleweed Prepares To Jump On GCC 12]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Tumbleweed-Preps-GCC-12</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Tumbleweed-Preps-GCC-12"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T10:50:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As of this week with openSUSE's Tumbleweed rolling-release distribution it is using GCC 12's libgcc standard libraries and preparing to shift to GCC 12 as the default compiler once ready...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some Older AMD GPUs + Intel Alder Lake Is Causing ASPM Problems For Linux Users]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-Disabling-ASPM-VI-ADL</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-Disabling-ASPM-VI-ADL"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T10:18:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Older AMD GPUs paired with Intel Alder Lake Platforms is leading to hangs during suspend/resume cycles so a patch is pending for the Linux kernel to disable Active State Power Management (ASPM) in such combinations...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD ROCm 5.1.1 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMD-ROCm-5.1.1-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMD-ROCm-5.1.1-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T09:33:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the end of March ROCm 5.1 released with CRIU checkpoint/restore support, continued enabling more ROCm components like MIOpen with RDNA(2) GPU compatibility, and other changes. Meanwhile on Friday the ROCm 5.1.1 release was published...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KDE Changes This Week "Overflowing With Positive Visual Changes"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=KDE-Changes-Start-April-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=KDE-Changes-Start-April-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T09:18:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KDE developer Nate Graham is out with his weekly summary of all the interesting changes to have landed this week for benefiting this open-source desktop environment...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bloatware Removal Tool: remove pre-installed Windows applications and more]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=177921</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/04/09/bloatware-removal-tool-remove-pre-installed-windows-applications-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T08:19:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bloatware Removal Tool is an open source script that Windows administrators may run to remove pre-installed Windows applications and other installed software from Windows systems. The script supports Windows 7 and newer […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Bloatware Removal Tool: remove pre-installed Windows applications and more appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I migliori software in sconto del 2022. Le offerte di primavera Mr Key Shop]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=I-migliori-software-in-sconto-del-2022-Le-offerte-di-primavera-Mr-Key-Shop_24368</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=I-migliori-software-in-sconto-del-2022-Le-offerte-di-primavera-Mr-Key-Shop_24368"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T07:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Con l'arrivo della primavera, magari sfruttando anche il breve periodo delle festività pasquali, si può fare un inventario dei software installati sui propri sistemi in modo da controllare ciò che manca e ciò che deve essere aggiornato.In questo periodo è possibile approfittare di tutta una serie di offerte software sia su prodotti utilizzati in ambito privato che in azienda.Mr Key Shop, azienda leader da oltre 18 anni nel mercato delle licenze software a prezzi vantaggiosi, ha avviato una campagna promozionale che offre a utenti privati, professionisti e imprese l'opportunità di assicurarsi i migliori software Microsoft e di altri produttori a un prezzo mai visto.

Le licenze commercializzate da Mr Key Shop sono già scontate del 70% rispetto agli store ufficiali.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch wiki account creation for non-arch users is way too onerous]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tzn8ht/arch_wiki_account_creation_for_nonarch_users_is/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tzn8ht/arch_wiki_account_creation_for_nonarch_users_is/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T06:26:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So I'm admittedly a Gentoo user, and not an Arch user, but I am reasonably knowledgeable about Firefox, its configuration and development, particularly on Linux.
 Accordingly, I wanted to create an account to contribute to the distro agnostic info on Firefox, however, I ran into issues with the captcha. The main issue is that there is advice on the page that is out of date and is breaking people's Firefox that needs to be amended. I've now dealt with multiple users in /r/firefox who have followed advice on the archwiki and run into this same problem.
 As I'm sure you all know, the captcha requires the output of a pacman command to be run. I understand this is intended to keep the wiki arch-focused, however, at least a significant portion of the wiki is used by the Linux community as a whole and is distro-agnostic. It seems absurd to put up significant barriers in this way, and only serves to lessen the likelihood of the provision of quality documentation for everyone. 
 In my view, to just say use the LiveISO, a docker image, install arch, build pacman from source, go hunting for an overlay, or use an online emulator is not a real answer, as people tend to contribute their in spare time, which may be fleeting, causing them to abandon contributing at all.
 Overall, I'm sympathetic to the aim of the captcha, but think it is doing more harm than good. What do you all think? I'll continue attempting to contribute, but is there not some way the output of a more distro-agnostic command could be used?
    submitted by    /u/u9mM54yySmSi  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Discord Keyboard Shortcuts]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=cheatsheet&amp;p=391030</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15208029/discord-keyboard-shortcuts"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T05:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discord is a VoIP platform that allows you to communicate with people through video and voice conferencing, as well as instant messaging. In addition, Discord also allows you to send and receive different file types, and setup and view live broadcasts. Essentially, the platform functions like TeamSpeak.
    
Discord’s community lives on different servers with several channels inside each. These channels can be for different games, internet personalities, interests, etc.
    
However, Discord is popular among gamers who play titles that require constant and real-time communication. Players of competitive multiplayer games such as Counter Strike: Global Offensive, CSGO, Call of Duty: Modern Warfare, and Call of Duty: Warzone use Discord to communicate with other players.
    
Essential Discord Keyboard Shortcuts
    
Within Discord, there are tons of actions you can take. To help you execute commands quickly, here’s a list of Discord shortcuts for Windows, Linux, and macOS.
    

Windows/LinuxmacOSFunction

Server and Channel Navigation  
Ctrl + Alt + ↑Command + Option + ↑Scroll up the list of servers.
Ctrl + Alt + ↓Command + Option + ↓Scroll down the list of servers.
Ctrl + Alt + →Ctrl... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Natalie dela Vega</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Took my laptop which uses Arch Linux with XFCE & i3 to work. Too many people asked how I got Windows to look like that lol]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tzm7hd/took_my_laptop_which_uses_arch_linux_with_xfce_i3/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tzm7hd/took_my_laptop_which_uses_arch_linux_with_xfce_i3/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T05:14:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What configs/.configs do you perpetually take with you or upload to git?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tzm2qq/what_configsconfigs_do_you_perpetually_take_with/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tzm2qq/what_configsconfigs_do_you_perpetually_take_with/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T05:05:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wendel from level one tech said he has carried his bashrc for like a decade or something. I can see the value of bashrc, .bashrc, vim configs, ranger configs, rc.local. And I am only in the "Oh I get it" stage with this. Now I am wondering about/realizing that I should make some of the launchers from kde settings aliases in my bashrc so when I port them elsewhere it is all setup. Or are there kde shortcuts stored on a different config I should backup? I'm sure as I thing about this differently there will be more "ooo" i gotta take that with me too configs. It's the cool thing about a journey all the new things to find/try.
 TL:DR. . . . Title says it all. . . .I'd love to hear and learn.
    submitted by    /u/Im-Mostly-Confused  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OBS window capture broken with Gnome 42]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tzhx27/obs_window_capture_broken_with_gnome_42/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tzhx27/obs_window_capture_broken_with_gnome_42/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T01:01:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey. Since the upgrade to Gnome 42 my window capture is broken. But this only affects OBS, Discord and other programs just capture things fine in wayland.
 I can select PipeWire as a capture method. And it also sees the windows, but if I select any of them the preview is just gray.
 https://media.discordapp.net/attachments/483318095985770517/962150875231576184/unknown.png?width=556&height=468https://media.discordapp.net/attachments/483318095985770517/962151215230246954/unknown.png?width=854&height=468
 Im using latest Nvidia 510 drivers and the zen kernel. I also installed xdg-desktop-portal and xdg-desktop-portal-gnome. OBS (27.2.4) is from flatpak (also tried the one from official repo)
 EDIT: Just saw that journalctl reports
 gnome-shell\[38192\]: Invalid buffer data
 Has anyone encountered this?
 Thanks in advance!
    submitted by    /u/ownedbynico  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fix High Memory Usage in Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=368672</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/13935098/fix-high-memory-usage-windows"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When the Task Manager is open in Windows, you may notice unexplained high memory usage. The memory spikes can slow down the application’s response time and cause frozen screens. Whether you are playing a memory-intensive game or keeping many browser windows open, you need to reduce these memory leaks as much as possible. 
    
The following are the the best methods to bring down the memory usage in Windows for any set of running programs. The sudden memory spikes happen due to a variety of reasons. Accordingly, there are diverse solutions. All these methods are safe to implement on any Windows 10 or Windows 11 device.
   

Content

1. Close Unnecessary Programs and Applications
2. Remove Unwanted Programs from Your PC
3. Check for Malware
4. Clean Up and Optimize the Disks 
5. Increase Virtual Memory through Registry NDU
6. Disable SysMain (Formerly Superfetch)
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sayak Boral</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How do I disable the beep sound on login when using the ly DM?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tzh9gt/how_do_i_disable_the_beep_sound_on_login_when/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tzh9gt/how_do_i_disable_the_beep_sound_on_login_when/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T00:23:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/Pay08  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Questions about the Debian packages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tzgp8m/questions_about_the_debian_packages/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tzgp8m/questions_about_the_debian_packages/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T23:52:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've noticed that debootstrap, dpkg, and the liquorix kernel are all available from the Arch Repos.
 My first thought was; "Why not just install a Deb based system?" And then I remembered; this is the Arch way.
 I'm quite intrigued by this conjecture.
 Is it possible to get a mostly debian based setup using the packages for Debian? 
 Does dpkg replace pacman, or work independently for Just a debian based Arch Install?
    submitted by    /u/RandomXUsr  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[kwin-low-latency issue | black screen with cursor/funky windows after update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tzf2pd/kwinlowlatency_issue_black_screen_with/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tzf2pd/kwinlowlatency_issue_black_screen_with/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T22:29:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[just wanted to post this here cause it took me a while to find the solution to my black screen problem after login.
 problem: black screen with cursor, able to open up krunner to open windows, no windows manager at all
 I thought I had a KDE Plasma issue. I read posts about uninstalling all KDE git packages and reinstalling non-git ones, but I found no git ones installed. then when I realized it was a KWin problem, I saw that I had kwin-low-latency installed instead of kwin
 solution: install kwin instead of kwin-low-latency
 tl;dr -- IF YOU HAVE KWIN-LOW-LATENCY, REPLACE WITH KWIN!
    submitted by    /u/torocat1028  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wine 7.6 Released With Updated Mono, More PE Conversion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Wine-7.6-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Wine-7.6-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T22:20:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wine 7.6 is out as the latest bi-weekly development release of this open-source software for enjoying Windows games and applications on Linux and other platforms...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anyone have a clue when LLVM 14 will be in the official repos?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tzevav/anyone_have_a_clue_when_llvm_14_will_be_in_the/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tzevav/anyone_have_a_clue_when_llvm_14_will_be_in_the/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T22:19:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There're some really cool clang features I wanna use for a personal project and was wondering when they'll be available
    submitted by    /u/LukeButWithaC  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch on an Intel Mac mini]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tzev7h/arch_on_an_intel_mac_mini/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tzev7h/arch_on_an_intel_mac_mini/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T22:19:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m currently trying to replace a slow, old Intel mac mini’s os with arch, but every time i looked at the official archwiki, they failed to mention if arch was compatible with this. Can arch work properly on the mac mini? What extra steps would i need to take to set it up (the macos on it is way too slow and buggy?)
    submitted by    /u/fordprefectpenguin  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Questa settimana su TLI (09 aprile 2022)]]></title>
        <id>3540|20220409000001</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/newsletter-turbolab.it-1349/questa-settimana-tli-09-aprile-2022-3540"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T22:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Non hai tempo di leggerci tutti i giorni? nessun problema! ecco a te il riepilogo di quanto proposto da TurboLab.it nel corso della settimana in conclusione.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[system starts in emergency mode when i tap ctrl+d i can acces to my system how can i solve that (it happened after i done something to fstab)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tzeag3/system_starts_in_emergency_mode_when_i_tap_ctrld/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tzeag3/system_starts_in_emergency_mode_when_i_tap_ctrld/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T21:51:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/KemalDGN  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GRUB can't find windows 10]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tze0ex/grub_cant_find_windows_10/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tze0ex/grub_cant_find_windows_10/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T21:37:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[i have reinstalled arch linux on my Thinkpad E14 without removing windows 10 uefi drive and system drive but now os-prober has no output so grub can't find my windows 10 what can i do ?
 GRUB_DISABLE_OS_PROBER="false" not worked
 ntfs-3g installed windows's disk is accesible
    submitted by    /u/KemalDGN  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Permanently Disable Windows Defender in Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=post-ideas&amp;p=178277</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/5530970/permanently-disable-windows-defender-windows-10"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When using Windows, you’ll notice that it comes with its own antivirus called Windows Defender (now called Windows Security in later versions of Windows 10 and Windows 11). For some, Windows Defender is more of a hindrance than a help. As such, they’ll want to disable Windows Defender completely. As you’ll discover in this tutorial, disabling Windows Defender isn’t as easy as it should be. Regardless, making sure Defender goes down and stays down isn’t very tricky at all.
   

Content

Why Not Use the Default Option?
Disabling Windows Defender Permanently
Using the Registry (Available for ALL Users)
Using Local Group Policy
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:Do I Need Antivirus Software If I Have Windows Defender?
    
Why Not Use the Default Option?
    
It may seem a little confusing that turning off Windows Defender permanently is trickier than... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Crystal Crowder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to File Your 2021 Taxes Online for Free in 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=786777</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/786777/how-to-file-your-2021-taxes-online-for-free-in-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The IRS is now accepting tax returns for 2021 with a deadline of April 18, 2022. There are some big changes to the free tax-filing tools we’ve previously recommended this year, but you can still file your taxes for free.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Snap-on discloses data breach claimed by Conti ransomware gang]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/snap-on-discloses-data-breach-claimed-by-conti-ransomware-gang/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/snap-on-discloses-data-breach-claimed-by-conti-ransomware-gang/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T20:35:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[American automotive tools manufacturer Snap-on announced a data breach exposing associate and franchisee data after the Conti ransomware gang began leaking the company's data in March. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Fi's New Unlimited Plan Pricing Is Hard to Pass Up]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/114521/google-fis-new-unlimited-plan-pricing-is-hard-to-pass-up/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/114521/google-fis-new-unlimited-plan-pricing-is-hard-to-pass-up/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T20:32:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Fi is updating its Simply Unlimited and Unlimited Plus plans with better pricing and more high-speed data. These changes are quite competitive, and existing customers will see them on their next bill. New customers can take advantage of the pricing change today and score up to $500 toward a new phone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Great Lumbar Cushions For Supporting Your Back While You Work]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/4161/7-great-lumbar-cushions-for-supporting-your-back-while-you-work/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/4161/7-great-lumbar-cushions-for-supporting-your-back-while-you-work/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When sitting, it’s important to keep your back well supported. After all, it’s a fundamental part of your body and skeletal structure. One great way of protecting it is through the use of a lumbar support pillow. Here are our top picks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Allen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VSCode Jupyter notebook bug]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tzccbm/vscode_jupyter_notebook_bug/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tzccbm/vscode_jupyter_notebook_bug/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T20:18:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey!
 im trying to get jupyther notebooks working with VSCode code package.
 i installed the code package and conda to manage python and have the jupyther notebook extension enabled but there are some weird errors happening
 Extension 'ms-toolsai.jupyter CANNOT USE these API proposals 'notebookConcatTextDocument, notebookControllerKind, notebookDebugOptions, notebookDeprecated, notebookEditor, notebookEditorDecorationType, notebookEditorEdit, notebookMessaging, notebookMime, notebookCellExecutionState, portsAttributes, textDocumentNotebook, quickPickSortByLabel'. You MUST start in extension development mode or use the --enable-proposed-api command line flag 
 am i missing something?
    submitted by    /u/Sirtario  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Does STFU Mean, and How Do You Use It?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=788997</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/788997/what-does-stfu-mean-and-how-do-you-use-it/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T20:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s almost impossible to browse the internet without seeing “STFU” at least once. Here’s what this intense acronym means and why you might want to avoid throwing it around.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vann Vicente</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[btrfs compression on a single subvolume... possible?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tzbsvb/btrfs_compression_on_a_single_subvolume_possible/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tzbsvb/btrfs_compression_on_a_single_subvolume_possible/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T19:52:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm trying to enable zstd compression on a single subvolume (out of five). I'd like all other subvolumes to be mounted without any compression.
  
When I mount all the subvolumes without compression, they're mounted that way.
 When I mount even a single subvolume with compression enabled (compress=zstd:1), all subvolumes are mounted with compression enabled.
  
Is that something which "must be" and is that how btrfs subvolumes work? Thank you.
    submitted by    /u/Original_Two9716  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Promised Us a Repair Program, Where the Hell Is It?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/114467/apple-promised-us-a-repair-program-where-the-hell-is-it/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/114467/apple-promised-us-a-repair-program-where-the-hell-is-it/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T19:43:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Customers and critics showered Apple with praise when it announced Self Service Repair, a program that lets you access authentic parts and repair guides for your Apple products. But Apple hasn’t mentioned the program since late last year, and it’s supposed to launch in “early 2022.” What’s wrong, Apple? You don’t want to brag about “customer choice” anymore?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save 30% on These SwitchBot Smart Home Products]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=479198</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15207284/switchbot-smart-home-products"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T19:25:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These SwitchBot Smart Home products can help make everyday tasks just a little easier. From opening and closing the curtains, to making dumb appliances smart, to monitoring the weather, these gadgets will put a little more time back in your day – and you can save 30% as well.
    
SwitchBot Curtain (U Rail)
    

    
You can make your curtains smart in just 30 seconds. Attach this small, wireless robot to your curtains to open and close them via your smartphone. Use a voice assistant, such as Alexa, Google Assistant, or Siri to direct your curtains. Measure the fit for your curtains to move smoothly. You can even set your curtains to close in the evening and open in the morning. No matter whether you have Rod, U Rail track, or I Rail track, SwitchBot Curtain will always fit.
    
Use the coupon code 10FZBANX to get 30% off and pay just $62.30 through April 13, 2022.
    
SwitchBot Curtain (U Rail)
    
SwitchBot Bot
    
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft: Windows 10 20H2 reaches end of service next month]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-windows-10-20h2-reaches-end-of-service-next-month/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-windows-10-20h2-reaches-end-of-service-next-month/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T19:04:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has reminded customers today that multiple editions of Windows 10 20H2 and Windows 10 1909 are reaching the end of service (EOS) on May 10, 2022. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Stop Safari From Automatically Unzipping Downloaded Files on Mac]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=789559</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/789559/how-to-stop-safari-from-automatically-unzipping-downloaded-files-on-mac/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T19:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By default, the Safari browser on Mac will extract ZIP files you’ve downloaded—and even discard the original compressed ZIP files. If this bothers you, there’s an easy way to turn it off, and you can keep your archived downloads in once piece. Here’s how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Desktop entry override and MIME]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tzaoex/desktop_entry_override_and_mime/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tzaoex/desktop_entry_override_and_mime/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T18:59:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I wanted to add couple more arguments to MPV so i copied it's desktop file from /usr/share/applications to ~/.local/share/applications and did my alterations to Exec. It worked, but now, for some reason, it is no longer the default application for anything. Or, more specifically, things like file managers no longer see it as such, however xdg-open still opens the files without issues and xdg-mime query default video/x-matroska still reports mpv.desktop.
 I tried removing the MIME part of the override's desktop file and removing the original file from usr, under the assumptions i might have made it ambiguous - nothing fixes it, except removing my override altogether.
 I'm not entirely sure what causes it, since it works with the xdg tools perfectly fine. I checked ArchWiki's entries for XDG Desktop and MIME but there wasn't anything about this issue. Thoughts?
 (inb4 - i don't use a DE so i can't just look up defaults in GUI there)
 UPD: Ok, i think i figured it out: i needed to run update-desktop-database ~/.local/share/applications. I guess that was on me since i go used to rofi picking up desktop entries by itself without needing to manually update the database, and for assuming that running the command by itself would try to update the current user's database, not the one in /usr/.
 Still no idea why presence of mpv.desktop in the local applications nullifies the MIME associations for it already present in the /usr/ though
    submitted by    /u/NekoiNemo  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel Arctic Sound M Support Added To Mesa 22.1 Drivers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-ATS-M-For-Mesa-22.1</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-ATS-M-For-Mesa-22.1"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T18:42:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ahead of next week's expected feature freeze / code branching for Mesa 22.1, Intel today committed Arctic Sound M "ATS-M" support for their open-source OpenGL and Vulkan drivers...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why is my server more stable while mining (xmr) the when it isn't.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tza59o/why_is_my_server_more_stable_while_mining_xmr_the/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tza59o/why_is_my_server_more_stable_while_mining_xmr_the/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T18:34:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During the winter, I decided to start mining xmr to heat up my room. I had just repurposed my old computer into a server that was just sitting there doing nothing, and I decided to let it go ham on mining. The temperature started to warm up again. Therefore, I stopped mining.
 ​
 All of a sudden, I am having stability problems left and right with my server. I've updated the bios, left it on default settings (which unfortunately means I'm running 2133Mhz on 3200Mhz ddr4). Cleared cmos. Everything!!!
 ​
 I decided to let it start mining, and voila! stable. It's been up 3 days without a freeze whereas before it would only go 40 minutes without hard freezing.
 ​
 Advice would be appreciated. FYI, i just ran the server quickstart in the archinstall script.
 ​
 Specs:
 r7 1700X
 ddr4 3200mhz 32gb
 1TB HDD
    submitted by    /u/slohobo  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Explains Why You Can't Move the Windows 11 Taskbar]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/114501/microsoft-explains-why-you-cant-move-the-windows-11-taskbar/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/114501/microsoft-explains-why-you-cant-move-the-windows-11-taskbar/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T18:28:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever since the first preview build arrived, users have asked Microsoft to make it an option to move the Windows 11 taskbar location to the left or right side of the screen. Unfortunately, it doesn’t look like that’s happening anytime soon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iwlwifi 0000:00:14.3: Can find a correct rfid for crf id 0x816 | Network issue]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tz9ygi/iwlwifi_000000143_can_find_a_correct_rfid_for_crf/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tz9ygi/iwlwifi_000000143_can_find_a_correct_rfid_for_crf/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T18:26:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've updated my system few weeks ago and I can't use my network card (wifi + bluetooth) since then. It's unblocked inside rfkill, but I can't see it inside nmcli. I have the newest version of linux-firmware and linux installed. I can't seem to find any issues inside journalctl, but inside dmesg | grep wifi this shows up:
 [ 1.566907] iwlwifi 0000:00:14.3: enabling device (0000 -> 0002) [ 1.568255] iwlwifi 0000:00:14.3: Can find a correct rfid for crf id 0x816 [ 1.568273] iwlwifi: probe of 0000:00:14.3 failed with error -22 
 ​
 I couldn't find the solution on internet, so if someone knows why is this happening, please tell me.
    submitted by    /u/Stranavad  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD SEV-SNP Appears Ready For Upstreaming In Linux 5.19]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMD-SEV-SNP-TIP-Linux-5.19</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMD-SEV-SNP-TIP-Linux-5.19"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T18:15:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduced last year with the AMD EPYC 7003 "Milan" processors was SEV-SNP as the latest iteration of their Secure Encrypted Virtualization technology. SEV-SNP adds additional integrity protections and safeguards as part of this "Secure Nested Paging" extension of SEV. Finally with Linux 5.19 the SEV-SNP support should premiere in the mainline kernel...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is N-Key Rollover (NKRO)?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=789557</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/789557/what-is-n-key-rollover-nkro/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T18:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[N-key rollover, referred to as NKRO, is a feature seen in many mechanical keyboards. It allows the user to press multiple keys at once, registering each key press individually. This is particularly useful for gamers who press simultaneous keys.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Georgie Peru</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub can now alert of supply-chain bugs in new dependencies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/github-can-now-alert-of-supply-chain-bugs-in-new-dependencies/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/github-can-now-alert-of-supply-chain-bugs-in-new-dependencies/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T18:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub can now block and alert you of pull requests that introduce new dependencies impacted by known supply chain vulnerabilities. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 3.1: come provare il sistema operativo che debuttò 30 anni fa]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-31-come-provare-il-sistema-operativo-che-debutto-30-anni-fa_24374</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-31-come-provare-il-sistema-operativo-che-debutto-30-anni-fa_24374"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T17:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Questa settimana Microsoft festeggia ben 30 anni dal rilascio della versione finale di Windows 3.1, una versione importante dell''ambiente operativo', molto più di quanto non suggerisca la numerazione a suo tempo utilizzata: '3.1' fa pensare a una 'release minore' piuttosto che a un rilascio in grande stile.Abbiamo scritto 'ambiente operativo' perché all'epoca Windows non era ancora un sistema operativo vero e proprio: si presentava come un'interfaccia grafica da caricarsi al di sopra di MS-DOS o di PC DOS.Microsoft rilasciò Windows 3.1 a inizio aprile 1992, solo due anni dopo l'arrivo di Windows 3.0. Il predecessore di Windows 3.1 fu accolto positivamente dall'industria e dagli utenti finali ma mancava di componenti chiave, soffriva di tanti difetti (bug), usava font bitmap e veniva espressamente presentato come una sorta di add-on per MS-DOS.Rendendosi conto della necessità di rimanere competitivi con i Mac di Apple e in vista del salto ai 32 bit con il successivo Windows 95, Microsoft aveva assolutamente necessità di stringere i tempi e rilasciare Windows 3.1 nel più breve tempo possibile.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[aspell not printing accents from portuguese]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tz96ho/aspell_not_printing_accents_from_portuguese/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tz96ho/aspell_not_printing_accents_from_portuguese/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T17:50:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The interactive mode of aspell is not showing most accent and symbols. This error is either in the text part and the suggestions section. For example the phrase:"Existe um longo histórico de erros técnicos" print as "Existe um longo hist rico de erros t cnicos".
 This is not a font, bash, or terminal emulator problem. vim and others parts of the terminal, the accents are printed just fine.
 The packages aspell, the dictionary aspell-pt are up do date.
 One yer ago aspell was working in portuguese and english texts, since then there have been NO updates in this packages, so I suspect that this issue is caused by and update on some aspell dependence.
 Aspell is correcting the words correctly, the only issue is not printing characters with portuguese accents.
    submitted by    /u/JCBecker  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Windows CMD Environment Variables]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=789660</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/789660/how-to-use-windows-cmd-environment-variables/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T17:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is easy to add or modify an environment variable with Command Prompt (CMD), but removing one is much more complicated. Here are a few different ways you can do it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Lewis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come pulire lo schermo di smartphone, monitor e TV]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2014/07/come-si-pulisce-lo-schermo-lcd-di.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2014/07/come-si-pulisce-lo-schermo-lcd-di.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gli schermi dei dispositivi elettronici come i monitor, le TV ed anche gli smartphone soffrono le ditate, le impronte e la polvere. Quando puliamo uno schermo moderno è importante sempre non utilizzare un prodotto per la casa e per i vetri, visto che macchieranno in maniera indelebile il sottile strato protettivo dello schermo.

 Non si devono quindi utilizzare detergenti e bisogna evitare...


Continua a leggere su Navigweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla's Three Most-Delayed EVs Arrive in 2023, According to Elon Musk]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/114468/teslas-three-most-delayed-evs-arrive-in-2023-according-to-elon-musk/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/114468/teslas-three-most-delayed-evs-arrive-in-2023-according-to-elon-musk/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T16:36:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While Tesla is extremely busy pumping out its leading lineup of Model S, 3, X, and Y electric vehicles, we’re still waiting for the Tesla Cybertruck, Roadster, and Semi. But, in a bold statement, Elon Musk says they’re all coming next year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Raspberry Pi OS: aggiornamento nome utente, Bluetooth e supporto Wayland]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Raspberry-Pi-OS-aggiornamento-nome-utente-Bluetooth-e-supporto-Wayland_24373</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Raspberry-Pi-OS-aggiornamento-nome-utente-Bluetooth-e-supporto-Wayland_24373"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T16:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Di recente avevamo dato spazio alle celebrazioni per i primi 10 anni di Raspberry Pi ripercorrendo brevemente la storia di un successo mondiale.I single-board computer Raspberry permettono l'installazione di più sistemi operativi ma la piattaforma ufficiale rimane Raspberry Pi OS recentemente rilasciata nella versione a 64 bit.Con un annuncio pubblicato sul blog della fondazione viene presentato un nuovo importante aggiornamento di Raspberry Pi OS Bullseye.Una delle principali novità consiste nell'abbandono, da parte di Raspberry, dell'utente predefinito pi: d'ora in avanti, durante la procedura d'installazione del sistema operativo, l'utente sarà chiamato a impostare le proprie credenziali.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best way to access arch NAS/SMB from outside LAN?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tz6vlt/best_way_to_access_arch_nassmb_from_outside_lan/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tz6vlt/best_way_to_access_arch_nassmb_from_outside_lan/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T16:04:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Exactly this. Want to reach my Arch box outside the network, more specifically its NAS/SMB share.
 Is Wireguard the best way to do this?
    submitted by    /u/aj_thenoob  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Spoof Your Location on Android]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=795277</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/795277/how-to-spoof-your-location-on-android/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It should be no surprise that your Android phone knows your location. There are times when you may not want your phone—or other people—to track you. We’ll show you how to easily fake your location and set your location to anywhere.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This LEGO 'Muppets' Collection Teaser Has Me Feeling Green]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/114453/this-lego-muppets-collection-teaser-has-me-feeling-green/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/114453/this-lego-muppets-collection-teaser-has-me-feeling-green/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T15:42:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LEGO recently posted an image on Twitter of a LEGO Kermit the Frog hiding behind the show curtains, teasing a reveal of the LEGO Muppets collection. The company plans to release an entire group of LEGO Muppets minifigures.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Continuing sound issues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tz6479/continuing_sound_issues/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tz6479/continuing_sound_issues/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T15:30:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a battle between me and my system; so far the system is winning.
 I have what I suspect is a standard setup with ALSA and PulseAudio, with Jack for help in playing MIDI files. I'd like to replace PulseAudio with Pipewire, but attempts to add any Pipewire packages leads to conflicts with PulseAudio, which I can't remove as it's needed for something else... and so on.
 Last week I could use speakertest in the terminal, and also play MP3 files using mpg123. Today - remarkably enough - I can still play MP3 files, but I can't use speakertest; I get an error that 
 Unable to set hw params for playback: Cannot allocate memory 
 Setting of hwparams failed: Cannot allocate memory
 Well, I can live without speakertest. At least I can play MP3s.
 What I can't do though, is get any sound from my browser with streaming services like YouTube. And this is constant across all browsers; at least the ones I've tried. (Chrome, Firefox, Vivaldi.)
 But surely, getting sound working shouldn't be that hard? All I want is for sound to, you know, work. It's crazy that it's as difficult and as non-intuitive as it seems to be.
 Anyway, if anybody has any bright ideas about how to manage sound (my machine is a Lenovo X1 Carbon 3rd generation), I'd be thrilled.
    submitted by    /u/amca01  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fix Windows MBR from Ubuntu]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=post-ideas&amp;p=267222</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/10090619/fix-windows-mbr-from-ubuntu"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you have tried to dual boot your Windows system with Linux, then you probably encountered some changes that may not be welcome. When installing Linux in this environment, the GRUB bootloader will overwrite the Windows bootloader within the Master Boot Record (MBR).
    
This is also true in reverse: If you have installed Linux first and then decide to install Windows, the Windows bootloader will overwrite GRUB. You will then find that there is no way to boot into your Linux Desktop.
    
Lastly, any major change in Windows can also modify your bootloader rendering it unusable. This is the case for the Anniversary Update in Windows 10 and the Windows 11 upgrade.
    
Any of these scenarios can be problematic for the new user, but thankfully with a little patience and care, there are ways to restore the bootloader, and in the process, repair the MBR.
   

Content

Requirements
Booting into Ubuntu live USB
Method One: Boot Repair Utility
Method Two: Updating your GRUB Configuration
Method Three: Syslinux
Method Four: mbr
Method Five: LILO
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramces Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come funziona il metaverso di Peter Moore basato su Unity Metacast]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Come-funziona-il-metaverso-di-Peter-Moore-basato-su-Unity-Metacast_24372</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Come-funziona-il-metaverso-di-Peter-Moore-basato-su-Unity-Metacast_24372"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T15:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unity è un motore grafico multipiattaforma che facilita lo sviluppo di videogiochi e di altri contenuti interattivi: si pensi a visualizzazioni architettoniche e animazioni 3D in tempo reale.Non ha bisogno di presentazioni: nella versione standard è completamente gratuito (si possono realizzare progetti commerciali senza pagare il software, a patto di avere un giro d'affari inferiore a 100.000 dollari) ed è stato utilizzato da centinaia di aziende per realizzare progetti di successo.Gli sviluppatori apprezzano Unity per via delle API di scripting C# e dell'integrazione con Visual Studio direttamente supportata. È inoltre possibile usare JavaScript come linguaggio di scripting e MonoDevelop come IDE per coloro che vogliono un'alternativa a Visual Studio.Quasi tutto può essere animato con Unity: i creatori di contenuti e gli artisti se ne servono per creare scene 3D o costruire animazioni 2D da zero. Poiché Unity esiste ormai dal 2005 ha potuto raccogliere un enorme seguito di utenti in tutti questi anni e portare a maturazione un'incredibile libreria di risorse.

Nella foto Peter Moore, classe 1955.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Raspberry Pi Just Made Two Huge Changes for Security and Convenience]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/114448/raspberry-pi-just-made-two-huge-changes-for-security-and-convenience/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/114448/raspberry-pi-just-made-two-huge-changes-for-security-and-convenience/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T15:10:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new update to Raspberry Pi OS (formerly Raspbian) offers several improvements over previous releases, though one of these “improvements” may be a bit controversial. On the one hand, setup is more convenient and the Pi is more secure. But it’s time to say goodbye to the default user.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dell XPS 13 (2020 model) showing battery status of "Unknown" when fully charged]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tz5oyr/dell_xps_13_2020_model_showing_battery_status_of/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tz5oyr/dell_xps_13_2020_model_showing_battery_status_of/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T15:10:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[❯ cat /sys/class/power_supply/BAT0/uevent POWER_SUPPLY_NAME=BAT0 POWER_SUPPLY_TYPE=Battery POWER_SUPPLY_STATUS=Unknown POWER_SUPPLY_PRESENT=1 POWER_SUPPLY_TECHNOLOGY=Li-poly POWER_SUPPLY_CYCLE_COUNT=0 POWER_SUPPLY_VOLTAGE_MIN_DESIGN=7600000 POWER_SUPPLY_VOLTAGE_NOW=8601000 POWER_SUPPLY_CURRENT_NOW=1000 POWER_SUPPLY_CHARGE_FULL_DESIGN=6707000 POWER_SUPPLY_CHARGE_FULL=5451000 POWER_SUPPLY_CHARGE_NOW=5062000 POWER_SUPPLY_CAPACITY=92 POWER_SUPPLY_CAPACITY_LEVEL=Normal POWER_SUPPLY_MODEL_NAME=DELL FP86V01 POWER_SUPPLY_MANUFACTURER=BYD POWER_SUPPLY_SERIAL_NUMBER=360 
 When the battery enters a fully-charged state, the status is reported as Unknown. Is this a case where I am missing a package necessary for the battery status to be reported properly? Web searches showed several similar issues, but they all seemed to involve batteries that refused to charge. In my case, the battery appears to be working fine. Additionally, the status is correctly reported as Discharging when unplugged, and Charging when charging. It's only when the battery gets full that it starts showing Unknown.
    submitted by    /u/terminalmage  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make Name Tags in Microsoft Word]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=793704</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/793704/how-to-make-name-tags-in-word/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T15:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re holding an event where you want participants to wear name tags, you can make them easily in Microsoft Word. We’ll show you two ways to create name tags using Word’s label feature and a free template.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mirai malware now delivered using Spring4Shell exploits]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/mirai-malware-now-delivered-using-spring4shell-exploits/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/mirai-malware-now-delivered-using-spring4shell-exploits/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T14:40:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Mirai malware is now leveraging the Spring4Shell exploit to infect vulnerable web servers and recruit them for DDoS (distributed denial of service) attacks. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GDM 42 keeps crashing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tz5174/gdm_42_keeps_crashing/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tz5174/gdm_42_keeps_crashing/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T14:39:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, does also anybody else have complete GDM freezes after the 42 upgrade? GNOME 42 seems stable but not the GDM. Screen completely unresponsive from time to time.
 Edit. amdgpu (Wayland)
    submitted by    /u/Original_Two9716  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come resettare la console (PS4, PS5, Xbox e Switch)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/04/come-resettare-la-console-ps4-ps5-xbox.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/04/come-resettare-la-console-ps4-ps5-xbox.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T14:32:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Le console di gioco sono a tutti gli effetti dei computer e, come quest'ultimi, possono incappare in problemi all'avvio, errori di sistema e improvvisi spegnimenti, specie sulle console con qualche anno sulle spalle. Per fortuna i produttori forniscono delle procedure di ripristino per resettare la console bloccata, così da farla tornare alle impostazioni originali e risolvere (si spera) il...


Continua a leggere su Navigweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best PS5 SSDs of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=756323</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/756323/best-ps5-ssd/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Sony PlayStation 5 supports an additional SSD to expand your game and app storage. The installation process is simple, but determining which SSDs will work can be complicated. Here are the best SSDs for your PS5.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Colp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chiamate indesiderate difficili da bloccare: il numero di telefono non è quello reale]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Chiamate-indesiderate-difficili-da-bloccare-il-numero-di-telefono-non-e-quello-reale_24371</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Chiamate-indesiderate-difficili-da-bloccare-il-numero-di-telefono-non-e-quello-reale_24371"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T14:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[State ricevendo in continuazione chiamate da numeri di cellulare che pubblicizzano questo o quel servizio? Le chiamate indesiderate vi assillano a qualunque ora del giorno e alla risposta si sente sempre una voce preregistrata? Sappiate che non siete i soli; succede anche a noi.Abbiamo visto com'è possibile bloccare le chiamate indesiderate sia su mobile che sulle numerazioni fisse ma da un po’ di tempo a questa parte gli scocciatori hanno cominciato a usare tattiche fraudolente: chiamano con numeri di utenze mobili sempre diversi. Anche insendoli nello spam e segnalandoli come tali le chiamate indesiderate continuano ad arrivare.Se si risponde una voce registrata dice: 'la segreteria di (...) ti dà il benvenuto'. Oppure, ancora, si fa presente che le tariffe di luce, gas, telefonia di cas…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[help with Dual Booting Arch and Windows.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tz4d3z/help_with_dual_booting_arch_and_windows/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tz4d3z/help_with_dual_booting_arch_and_windows/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T14:07:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[im trying to install arch on my laptop with alongside windows. i used Archfi manual partitioning each OS has its own EFI partitionin (i tried on the same EFI part but that almost nuked my whole drive) after i was done installing i reboot and i cant see an entry for the syatem i just installed. only windows. i even tried to add a grubx64.efi entry to the windows boot maneger but i cant find it... ill attach a photo of the whole filesystem tree of the EFI directory from a windows program.
 im just at a loss. i tried multiple different distros to no avail. the only thing the bios can see is windows.
 my setup: Lenovo Legion 5, Ryzen 7 5800H, RTX 3050, 16Gb Ram, 512Gb NVME SSD, Windows 11.
    submitted by    /u/Soullessboi_iii  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best iPad Air Cases of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=767166</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/767166/best-ipad-air-case/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The iPad Air is one of the best tablets you can buy, so of course you want to keep it safe. Whether you’re looking for mild protection or military-grade armor, we’ll help you find the perfect case.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kris Wouk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NetworkManager crashes on wifi change while wireguard is connected]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tz442m/networkmanager_crashes_on_wifi_change_while/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/tz442m/networkmanager_crashes_on_wifi_change_while/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T13:56:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I dont know where else too post this so here we go. I set up an wireguard server with pivpn on an orangepi pc. Also tried it manually but with the same result. The server works like it should, I can connect to it from my smartphone or my laptop. On my laptop I imported the wireguard config in network manager. Everything works as expected, it even automatically connects to the VPN after suspend or hibernate and also after disabling and reenabling WiFi in the gnome settings. However as soon as I switch to an different WiFi network NetworkManager goes complete nuts. The nmcli command line program as well as the gnome network settings become completely unresponsive. While I can ping IP addresses with ping and resolve hostnames with nslookup no websites load and trace route gets stuck after some hops. Rebooting fixes the issue. Neighter dmesg nor journalctl give any relevant info, they behave like nothing happened except for ah coredump when gnome-settings crashes. I tried some of the dns related stuff in the wiki like the systemd-resolved symlink or using openresolv but that didn't change a thing. I honestly have no idea where to take it from here. Maybe someone knows what's wrong. 
 Thanks in advance
 Edit: The config nmcli import created(minus the keys and endpoint address):
 [connection] id=wg0 uuid=c93606c2-979a-4b04-8857-0f8f0396d67d type=wireguard interface-name=wg0 timestamp=1649423799 [wireguard] private-key= [wireguard-peer.ArdXN8ABnf4RpKMepNmKdmokye8L3afKvlAnYHVTD0k=] endpoint= preshared-key= preshared-key-flags=0 allowed-ips=0.0.0.0/0;::/0; [ipv4] address1=10.6.0.5/24 dns=192.168.1.1; dns-search=~; method=manual [ipv6] addr-gen-mode=stable-privacy method=disabled [proxy] 
    submitted by    /u/aFineDarkSoul  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US eases sanctions that may lead to Russia's Internet isolation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/us-eases-sanctions-that-may-lead-to-russias-internet-isolation/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/us-eases-sanctions-that-may-lead-to-russias-internet-isolation/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T13:43:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, the U.S. has announced exemptions on previously imposed sanctions on Russia related to telecommunications and internet-based communications, likely to prevent Russians from being isolated from Western news sources. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>