<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-04-12T01:42:51.875Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[(Pipewire) redream and dolphin-emu not going to default audio output]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u1n6qx/pipewire_redream_and_dolphinemu_not_going_to/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u1n6qx/pipewire_redream_and_dolphinemu_not_going_to/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-12T01:26:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[redream (Dreamcast emulator) and Dolphin (GCN/Wii emulator) are sending audio to my laptop's speakers, instead of my USB audio interface.
 Everything else I've tested (elisa, firefox, virt-manager) sends audio to the default output just fine.
 I've tried googling, but if I include "pipewire" in the search, all I get are people who have pipewire entirely nonfunctioning, and if I exclude it, all I get is alsa/pulseaudio. I can't be the only person with this issue.
    submitted by    /u/Deliphin  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 of the Best Markdown Editors for Android and iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=137656</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/2541543/markdown-editors-android"/>
        <updated>2022-04-12T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Markdown editors are tools that help web writers easily format text without any fuss. In fact, there are many desktop Markdown editors. However, as people move on to mobile devices more and more, many people are looking to use Markdown on their phones. If you’re looking for an app to help you knock out some web-writing tasks, browse through some of the best markdown editors for Android and iOS that we have listed here.
   

Content

1. iA Writer
2. JotterPad
3. Joplin
4. Inkdrop
5. Obsidian
6. Wiz Note
7. Simplenote
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:Markdown Cheatsheet
    
1. iA Writer
    
If you’re looking for a crisp, uncluttered Markdown editor, then look no further than iA Writer (Android | iOS). After just a few minutes with this app, it’s easy to see why over half a million people worldwide have downloaded this substantial tool.
 ... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Megan Glosson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA warns orgs of WatchGuard bug exploited by Russian state hackers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisa-warns-orgs-of-watchguard-bug-exploited-by-russian-state-hackers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisa-warns-orgs-of-watchguard-bug-exploited-by-russian-state-hackers/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T22:24:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has ordered federal civilian agencies and urged all US organizations on Monday to patch an actively exploited bug impacting WatchGuard Firebox and XTM firewall appliances. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why does this happen]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u1j4vr/why_does_this_happen/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u1j4vr/why_does_this_happen/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T22:11:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Given that I followed the wiki guide to install Arch I did the partition property then I reboot to see all my progress gone to waste by the way I’m running off a usb cause I’m installing it right now. 
 But as I was saying it’s not saving the progress I made I spend 8hours trying to figure out this but still idk ?
 but that doesn’t matter it’s like the is has Anesthesia cause everything erases upon shut down anyway to stop this. You guys are going to say did you follow the wiki yes I did
    submitted by    /u/Puzzleheaded_Way4140  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ubuntu in Hyper-V a schermo intero: come modificare la risoluzione in full HD (1920x1080)]]></title>
        <id>3542|20220412000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/virtualizzazione-535/ubuntu-hyper-v-schermo-intero-come-modificare-risoluzione-full-hd-1920x1080-3542"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dopo aver installato Ubuntu in Hyper-V ci si ritrova con una finestra minuscola, e la risoluzione fissata sui 1024x768 pixel. Lavorare in questo modo è davvero impossibile! Per ottenere una buona esperienza d'uso sarebbe infatti necessario impostare la risoluzione della macchina virtuale a 1920x1080 pixel (full HD) e portare così il desktop di Ubuntu a schermo intero. In questa guida vedremo dunque come procedere per raggiungere il risultato cercato
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Guides on Instagram]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=475943</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15212564/create-guides-on-instagram"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Instagram is constantly adding new features, in a bid to offer an increasing superior experience to its users. Case in point, one of the most recent ones that was introduced during the early phase of the pandemic was Guides. However, the option might have flown under the radar for a lot of users, especially since it was initially available only for select accounts. That is no longer the case, however, and so this article aims to shed some light on Guides and show you how you can create your first Guide ever.
   

Content

What Are Guides?
How to Create Your First Guide
Three Types of Guides
Share Your Guides on Instagram
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Manage Comments on Instagram
    
What Are Guides?
    
Guides are basically collections that mix both text and visuals and allow the creator to easily share recommendations and tips... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexandra Arici</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rise in npm protestware: another open source dev calls Russia out]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/rise-in-npm-protestware-another-open-source-dev-calls-russia-out/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/rise-in-npm-protestware-another-open-source-dev-calls-russia-out/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T21:02:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers are increasingly voicing their opinions through their open source projects in active use by thousands of software applications and organizations. Most recently, the developer of the 'event-source-polyfill' npm package peacefully protested Russia's "unreasonable invasion" of Ukraine, to Russian consumers. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ax Sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Updated AMDGPU Firmware Published To Deal With A Possible VCN Hang]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMDGPU-FW-Avoid-VCN-Multi-Hang</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMDGPU-FW-Avoid-VCN-Multi-Hang"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T21:02:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In addition to the AMD Zen 1/2/3 updated CPU microcode and long-awaited NVIDIA Ampere GPU signed firmware being merged today into linux-firmware.git, new AMD graphics firmware was also merged this morning for dealing with a hang with the VCN block under certain situations...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to See All Open Windows at Once on a Chromebook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=795966</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/795966/how-to-see-all-open-windows-at-once-on-a-chromebook/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you find yourself knee-deep in open apps and windows on your Chromebook, you may want some help to find what you need. Chrome OS has a similar feature to “Task View” on Windows 10 and 11. Chrome OS calls it “Overview.” Let’s use it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qbot malware switches to new Windows Installer infection vector]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/qbot-malware-switches-to-new-windows-installer-infection-vector/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/qbot-malware-switches-to-new-windows-installer-infection-vector/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T20:58:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Qbot botnet is now pushing malware payloads via phishing emails with password-protected ZIP archive attachments containing malicious MSI Windows Installer packages. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung Galaxy Z Fold 4: Everything We Know So Far]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/114684/samsung-galaxy-fold-4/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/114684/samsung-galaxy-fold-4/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T20:51:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While Samsung’s foldables are hard to recommend, they’re a clear blueprint for the future. But how soon will that future come? Judging by early leaks and rumors, Samsung Galaxy Z Fold 4 could be the first foldable that’s truly worth buying—well, maybe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is reflector still working?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u1gk2z/is_reflector_still_working/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u1gk2z/is_reflector_still_working/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T20:21:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve been trying to use reflector to the point I went to an arch iso but it simply won’t work, I keep getting failed to rate/download timed out.
 https://imgur.com/a/fO79vy1
 edit: https://youtu.be/1G9n8jAYvQc
    submitted by    /u/battler624  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Update Google Play Services]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=792258</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/792258/update-google-play-services/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T20:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Updating the Google Play Services app on your Android phone or tablet can fix bugs and bring new features. The app usually automatically updates, but you can also trigger a manual update. Here’s how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackBerry Is Dead, But This Phone Could Take Its Place]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/114700/blackberry-is-dead-but-this-phone-could-take-its-place/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/114700/blackberry-is-dead-but-this-phone-could-take-its-place/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T19:48:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the idea of a modern BlackBerry smartphone with a QWERTY keyboard died a long time ago, we’ve seen several brands try to revive it with little luck. However, one company is still making BlackBerry-like devices with physical keyboards, and it has a new phone coming soon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save $120 on an LG 27″ Ultrascreen Gaming Monitor]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=479734</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15212434/lg-27-ultrascreen-gaming-monitor"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re a gamer and looking for a new monitor, the LG 27″ Ultrascreen Gaming Monitor could be the right one for the job. It has a 1ms response time, 240Hz refresh rate, a thin bezel, and NVIDIA G-SYNC compatible with AMD FreeSync Premium. This is the right time to pick it up, too, as it’s $120 off.
    
This gaming monitor is designed to work with you. It has the latest hardware, specs, and ergonomics, as well as the most sensory experience you will find. It has vivid, responsive IPS and a 16:9 screen ratio (1920 x 1080) with enhanced contrast, clarity, and details.
    
The HDR10 provides a more dynamic visu-al experience and enhances the color even more. The verified NVIDIA G-SYNC compatibility will bring faster, smoother gaming with less screen tearing and minimized stuttering and input lag. The AMD FreeSync Premium is built in.
    

    
You’ll enjoy the great speed and ultra-fast 1ms response rate of the LG Ultrascreen Gaming Monitor. LG’s highest 240Hz refresh rate lets... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Screen Record on iPhone 12]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=796669</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/796669/how-to-screen-record-on-iphone-12/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T19:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To save what’s happening on your iPhone’s screen, you might reach for a screenshot. But when capturing a sequence of events is important, a screen recording video is your best option. Luckily, it’s easy to record the screen on your iPhone 12, 12 Mini, 12 Pro, or 12 Pro Max. Here’s how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Luxury fashion house Zegna confirms August ransomware attack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/luxury-fashion-house-zegna-confirms-august-ransomware-attack/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/luxury-fashion-house-zegna-confirms-august-ransomware-attack/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T18:32:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Italian luxury fashion company Ermenegildo Zegna has disclosed a ransomware incident from August 2021 that has resulted in an extensive IT systems outage. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Atlassian says ongoing outage might last two more weeks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/atlassian-says-ongoing-outage-might-last-two-more-weeks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/atlassian-says-ongoing-outage-might-last-two-more-weeks/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T18:10:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software development and collaboration tool maker Atlassian estimates it might take two more weeks to restore all customer instances impacted by a week-long ongoing outage affecting its cloud services. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is GPIO, and What Can You Use It For?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=787928</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/787928/what-is-gpio/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T18:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you own a Raspberry Pi or other similar hobbyist computer, you may have noticed it has a GPIO (General-Purpose Input-Output) feature. Most users will never use GPIO, but if you want to build things, GPIO is essential.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sydney Butler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Edge più veloce: cosa sono le schede in sospensione]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Edge-piu-veloce-cosa-sono-le-schede-in-sospensione_24380</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Edge-piu-veloce-cosa-sono-le-schede-in-sospensione_24380"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T17:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[La novità era stata presentata tempo fa ma con il rilascio di Edge 100, nuova versione del browser Microsoft, diventa disponibile per tutti gli utenti.Schede in sospensione è una funzione che si occupa di rendere 'dormienti' le tab di navigazione del browser che non si stanno utilizzando e i cui elementi sono ancora caricati in background. Per impostazione predefinita le schede del browser inattive vengono 'addormentate' ovvero poste in uno stato di sospensione dopo 5 minuti ma il periodo di tempo è personalizzabile digitando edge://settings/system nella barra degli indirizzi di Edge.Le risorse macchina (memoria e processore) precedentemente occupate dalle schede inattive e liberate grazie alla 'sospensione', vengono reindirizzate alle tab attive o alle pagine Web appena aperte.La funzione…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PrivadoVPN Review: Easy to Install and Use and Very Solid]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=475558</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15212175/privadovpn-review"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T17:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the modern age of cyberwar, spam, and various other invasions of privacy, there’s no better time to consider getting a VPN. For proper VPN-masked IP protection, ideally you really need a paid, supported solution. PrivadoVPN is a Swiss-made VPN app that provides many nice features, covering all your needs in one package. This review takes a look at how it stacks up against other options.
    
This is a sponsored article and was made possible by PrivadoVPN. The actual contents and opinions are the sole views of the author who maintains editorial independence even when a post is sponsored.
    
This Time It’s Personal
    
PrivadoVPN is a VPN, or virtual private network, which masks your IP from prying eyes. If your IP address is visible, then your ISP and any other traffic-spying organizations can see where you are and what you’re up to. IP masking removes this insult to personal privacy and lets you browse and download without being observed. 
    

    
PrivadoVPN works as an app: you install it on... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phil South</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firmware upgrade: Dualboot or update from Arch?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u1culf/firmware_upgrade_dualboot_or_update_from_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u1culf/firmware_upgrade_dualboot_or_update_from_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T17:21:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I want to upgrade firmware on my laptop but Lenovo does not issue firmware packages for other than Windows. Can this be done from Arch?
 On hindsight, I reserved a piece of one of the drives in order to install it there in case there is no other way, but then I don't know if it will break bootloader and wont be able to boot back to Arch. 
 Help!
    submitted by    /u/codezerodnb  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft: Moving Windows 11 taskbar may never be an option again]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-moving-windows-11-taskbar-may-never-be-an-option-again/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-moving-windows-11-taskbar-may-never-be-an-option-again/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T17:15:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are waiting for Windows 11 side-taskbar support before upgrading to the latest operating system, you may be waiting for a long time, according to a recent Microsoft Ask Me Anything (AMA) session. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migliori Browser per la privacy, privati e senza tracciamento dati]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2014/08/browser-privati-per-proteggere-la-privacy.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2014/08/browser-privati-per-proteggere-la-privacy.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T17:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Il browser è il programma chiave della navigazione su internet ed è quello che deve rimanere protetto e sicuro da intrusioni e spionaggio. I browser più comuni sono Google Chrome e Microsoft Edge ma non sono perfetti nel proteggere la privacy, visto che tracciano gli utenti.

 Con la privacy su Internet continuamente sotto attacco e ormai quasi impossibile da mantenere dobbiamo scegliere dei...


Continua a leggere su Navigweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Scan a Document on Windows 10 or Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=791848</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/791848/how-to-scan-a-document-on-windows-10-or-windows-11/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smartphones have replaced scanners for a lot of common tasks. But if you need to get digital copies of old photos, slides, or negatives, or a high-quality scan of paper, phones still can’t beat specialized equipment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Lewis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Old Apps Will Soon Disappear from the Google Play Store]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/114661/old-apps-will-soon-disappear-from-the-google-play-store/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/114661/old-apps-will-soon-disappear-from-the-google-play-store/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T16:58:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an effort to increase Android security, Google will hide thousands of old Play Store apps on November 1st of 2022. If an app’s “target API level” is more than two years old, it will not show up in Play Store searches.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Drive backup in Windows: come procedere da riga di comando]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Google-Drive-backup-in-Windows-come-procedere-da-riga-di-comando_18366</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Google-Drive-backup-in-Windows-come-procedere-da-riga-di-comando_18366"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T16:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mentre Google Drive è il famoso servizio di storage cloud dell'azienda di Mountain View, Google One è il contenitore di tutte le app online offerte dalla società di Larry Page e Sergey Brin. Con Google One è possibile conoscere in tempo reale lo spazio occupato sul cloud e sapere com'è distribuito tra le varie applicazioni.Chiunque disponesse di un account Google può effettuare il backup dei propri file utilizzati a casa, in ufficio o in azienda, anche sfruttando i 15 GB di spazio gratuito che la società mette gratuitamente a disposizione di tutti.I file memorizzati sui server di Google sono protetti con la crittografia quindi non possono essere letti e modificati da parte di terzi non autorizzati anche se, nel caso di file personali e informazioni riservate, il consiglio è quello di crittografare a priori in proprio tutti i file che si inviano sui server cloud di Google.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come stampare un’area precisa di Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/04/come-stampare-unarea-precisa-di-excel.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/04/come-stampare-unarea-precisa-di-excel.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T16:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stampare un intero foglio di calcolo su Excel è piuttosto semplice: non dobbiamo far altro che premere in alto su File -> Stampa e scegliere la stampante da utilizzare; in alternativa possiamo anche utilizzare la scorciatoia da tastiera CTRL+P per stampare velocemente tutto il foglio di calcolo. Ma se dobbiamo stampare solo un'area precisa del foglio Excel? Come possiamo stampare sempre e solo...


Continua a leggere su Navigweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch-Based EndeavourOS  "Apollo" Released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=EndeavourOS-Apollo-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=EndeavourOS-Apollo-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T16:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For those looking for an easy-to-use flavor of Arch Linux, EndeavourOS continues in this area of being a robust desktop-minded Linux distribution powered by Arch. Out today is EndeavourOS "Apollo" as its newest ISO of this rolling-release distribution...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch Linux on Acer Chromebook 514 no sound problem]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u1b237/arch_linux_on_acer_chromebook_514_no_sound_problem/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u1b237/arch_linux_on_acer_chromebook_514_no_sound_problem/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T16:02:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So basically, last night i managed to install Arch Linux on my chromebook, and so far everything seems to work well except the sound just wont work. I tried with PulseAudio but that doesn't seem to work unless im doing something wrong. Been browsing through forums but nothing helped so far.
 So i decided to reach out to you guys for help, maybe i should mention that im not an advanced Linux user, and yes i know that Arch is not a very good distro for beginners but y'all can't change my mind, i like challenges.
 Im running Arch Linux with Gnome and the Chromebook's model is Acer Chromebook 514 (cb514-1h)
 Hope y'all can help me out :)
    submitted by    /u/DDevil_Rengar  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keep Your Guacamole Green with This Delicious Hack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lifesavvy.com/123817/keep-your-guacamole-green-with-this-delicious-hack/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lifesavvy.com/123817/keep-your-guacamole-green-with-this-delicious-hack/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T16:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to easily spoiled foods, guacamole might top the list. The delicious dip is prone to browning, and while it’s still edible, it doesn’t exactly look appetizing. Luckily, there’s a hack to keep your guac green.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shea Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Download Emails From Gmail]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=791699</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/791699/download-emails-from-gmail/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T16:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to save an email for offline use, or you’d like to send that email as an attachment to someone, Gmail allows you to download your emails in an offline EML format. We’ll show you how to do that on your desktop as you can’t yet do it on mobile.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Android banking malware intercepts calls to customer support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/android-banking-malware-intercepts-calls-to-customer-support/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/android-banking-malware-intercepts-calls-to-customer-support/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T15:54:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A banking trojan for Android that researchers call Fakecalls comes with a powerful capability that enables it to take over calls to a bank's customer support number and connect the victim directly with the cybercriminals operating the malware. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Ilascu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fitbit Will Automatically Check for Heart Conditions Thanks to New FDA Clearance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/114654/fitbit-will-automatically-check-for-heart-conditions-thanks-to-new-fda-clearance/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/114654/fitbit-will-automatically-check-for-heart-conditions-thanks-to-new-fda-clearance/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T15:49:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fitbit has offered continuous heart rate monitoring since 2018, but users still have to manually use the EKG function to check their heart rhythm. That will change “soon,” as Fitbit just gained FDA clearance for an algorithm that passively checks for atrial fibrillation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla's Roadster Takes a Big Step Toward a 2023 Release]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/114649/teslas-roadster-takes-a-big-step-toward-a-2023-release/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/114649/teslas-roadster-takes-a-big-step-toward-a-2023-release/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T15:44:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla’s sleek all-electric sports car might finally arrive in 2023. We’re talking about the Tesla Roadster that debuted in 2017 but didn’t hit the streets in 2020 as promised. Roadster reservations are open again, giving would be buyers a glimmer of hope.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Username e password: salvati al sicuro e sincronizzati tra più dispositivi]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Username-e-password-salvati-al-sicuro-e-sincronizzati-tra-piu-dispositivi_24379</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Username-e-password-salvati-al-sicuro-e-sincronizzati-tra-piu-dispositivi_24379"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T15:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[La gestione delle password e la loro memorizzazione su un supporto sicuro sono essenziali per evitare che utenti non autorizzati o criminali informatici possano servirsene per sottrarre l'identità altrui, rubare dati riservati e causare danni di vario genere.Abbiamo visto come nasce un attacco informatico e quanto la corretta conservazione di username e password sia fondamentale per scongiurare qualunque tipo di aggressione sia in ambito professionale che privato.Abbiamo già visto quanto sia semplice trovare le password salvate in un PC Windows e quanto i browser Web non siano strumenti sicuri per memorizzare le proprie credenziali di accesso.Chi fosse 'allergico' ai servizi per la gestione delle password sul cloud può optare per soluzioni professionali come Psono che consentono di salvare in sicurezza username e password con la possibilità di condividere queste informazioni con i collaboratori di un'azienda.Ancora più famoso è tuttavia KeePass, un software libero e open source che si propone come un password manager sicuro e 'a prova di aggressione'.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Install Your Own Federated Twitter with Pleroma]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=465587</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15211929/install-federated-twitter-pleroma"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microblogging is a wonderful way to express your thoughts. It is short, succinct and sweet. In this regard, Twitter has been one of the most popular microblogging platforms in the world. However, relying on this particular company for your microblogging needs not be the best solution for everyone.
    
Fortunately, there are alternatives such as Pleroma which is a self-hosted Twitter. This is a lightweight federated microblogging platform. Using federation allows the platform to communicate with other federated instances which means that you do not need to gather a lot of people for your own private Twitter to start sharing information. This article aims to help you get started with Pleroma.
   

Content

The Issue with Twitter
What Is Federation and How Does it Work
How to Install Pleroma
1. Set Up Your A and AAAA DNS Records
2. Obtain the Pleroma Dependencies
3. Create the Pleroma User
4. Download Pleroma
5. Prepare and Install Pleroma
6. Configure the Pleroma Install
7. Media-specific Configurations
8. Finalize Your Pleroma Configuration
9. Start the Pleroma Database
10. Start Your Pleroma Server
11. Final Configurations
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramces Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is this configuration compatible with arch linux?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u19s0z/is_this_configuration_compatible_with_arch_linux/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u19s0z/is_this_configuration_compatible_with_arch_linux/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T15:02:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Processor: AMD Ryzen ™ 5 5500U Processor (6 Core, 2.10 GHz, up to 4.0 GHz with Max Boost, 3MB L2 Cache / 8MB L3 Cache) Operating System: No operating system Operating System Language: No operating system language Onboard Memory: 8 GB DDR4 3200MHz Selectable Memory: 8 GB SO-DIMM DDR4 3200MHz Total Memory: 8GB 3,200MHz DDR4 (soldered) + 8GB 3,200MHz DDR4 (SODIMM) First Solid State Drive: SSD 256 GB M.2 2242 Display: 15.6 "FHD (1920x1080) TN, anti-glare, 250 nits, thin bezel, NTSC 45%, non-touch, 60Hz Graphic Card: Integrated graphics card Wireless: 11AX (2x2) & Bluetooth® 5.0 TPM Setting: Discrete TPM 2.0 enabled Absolute BIOS Selection: Absolute BIOS enabled Display Panel: 15.6 "TN Full HD (1920 x 1080) anti-glare, 250 nits, thin bezel, 45% NTSC, non-touch, 60 Hz, 720p HD camera with cover, black 
 The laptop is a customized ThinkPad E15 Gen 3
 In particular the ryzen processor worries me. is the whole setup compatible?
    submitted by    /u/overclock351  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use INDEX and MATCH in Microsoft Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=793270</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/793270/index-and-match-in-excel/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the VLOOKUP function is good for finding values in Excel, it has its limitations. With a combination of the INDEX and MATCH functions instead, you can look up values in any location or direction in your spreadsheet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get Back Into Reading with Amazon's Kindle and Fire Tablet Sale]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/114640/get-back-into-reading-with-amazons-kindle-and-fire-tablet-sale/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/114640/get-back-into-reading-with-amazons-kindle-and-fire-tablet-sale/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T14:57:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Getting back into reading often means dropping a ton of money on new books or e-reader devices. But with today’s Amazon sale, reading is a lot cheaper than usual. For a limited time, you can grab a Kindle e-reader or Fire tablet for up to 45% off.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[how to stop key repeat when using rofi]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u19je9/how_to_stop_key_repeat_when_using_rofi/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u19je9/how_to_stop_key_repeat_when_using_rofi/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T14:51:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[when i am using rofi/dmenu and when i press escape key it is echoed to the focused window how can i stop this from happening
    submitted by    /u/h4636oh  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes some games refuse to launch on Steam.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u18shs/sometimes_some_games_refuse_to_launch_on_steam/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u18shs/sometimes_some_games_refuse_to_launch_on_steam/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T14:16:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello there, I have a problem that occurs from time to time. One day my steam games works perfectly fine, other days they just launch and instantly close themselves. It sometimes gets more complicated and some of them work and some of them don't and the other times none of them works. I play from ntfs external hard drives, and I did Steam's recommended fstab configuration. There is no problem with the fstab file, drives mount perfectly fine but like I said games sometimes does not run. Any game on my ext4 internal drive works perfectly and I only have this problem with the games on my external drives. Any ideas?
    submitted by    /u/flakanat  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Capture Cards of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=741966</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/741966/best-capture-cards/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Streaming on services like Twitch is a popular way for gamers to share their hobby, but you need the right capture card to make the most of it. Don’t worry, we have the perfect recommendations for everyone’s setup.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sydney Butler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[going back to ubuntu?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u182bl/going_back_to_ubuntu/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u182bl/going_back_to_ubuntu/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T13:42:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I don't mean to put down arch Linux, I am sure it is great, but I use ubuntu everywhere, and don't want to have to learn arch in order to use junest... does anyone have an ubuntu alternative or a method to convert the distro type from arch to ubuntu?
    submitted by    /u/ChainSword20000  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Streaming Devices of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=733629</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/733629/best-streaming-devices-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Streaming services make it easy to watch your favorite movies and shows, but it can be hard to stream them on your TV. Our streaming device recommendations will make it easy to put on Netflix and enjoy hassle-free.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Henges</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Just another arch noob trying to get audio to work]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u17jfj/just_another_arch_noob_trying_to_get_audio_to_work/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u17jfj/just_another_arch_noob_trying_to_get_audio_to_work/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T13:16:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Edit: In typical fashion, I solved this problem 5 mins after posting haha. I simply had to do: sudo pacman -S sof-firmware and then reboot (:
 ​
 I couldn't get things to work on pulseaudio so I figured I'd try pipewire but still no luck. I installed pipewire and pipewire-pulse, tried both pipewire-media-session and wireplumber, added my user to the audio group, and un-muted the master volume with alsamixer.
 What's odd is when I click on the volume icon in my panel, the bar is bouncing indicating that it's picking up on the audio. Same with alsamixer, the bars are bounding and everything looks good but still no audio.
 I've spent 4 days working on this and would really love some help.
 ​
 The add image icon is grayed out so here's some imgur links:
 Audio is bouncing:
 https://imgur.com/d…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monoprice CrystalPro Monitor Review: Sturdy, Gorgeous, and Adjustable]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/113506/monoprice-crystalpro-monitor-review-sturdy-gorgeous-and-adjustable/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/113506/monoprice-crystalpro-monitor-review-sturdy-gorgeous-and-adjustable/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T13:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The standard resolution for monitors and TVs across the board used to be 1920 x 1080. But now? Move over, FHD, and make some room for stunning 4K monitors that don’t cost an arm and a leg, like Monoprice’s 32-inch CrystalPro monitor.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Chaney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Is Google Called Google?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=789647</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/789647/why-is-google-called-google/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve used the internet or a smartphone, chances are high you’ve encountered Google, a successful tech firm that pioneered search engine technology in the late 1990s. But where did it get its weird name? We’ll explore the history behind it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WhatsApp: foto e video inviati come messaggi effimeri o chat temporanee non vengono più salvati]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=WhatsApp-foto-e-video-inviati-come-messaggi-effimeri-o-chat-temporanee-non-vengono-piu-salvati_24378</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=WhatsApp-foto-e-video-inviati-come-messaggi-effimeri-o-chat-temporanee-non-vengono-piu-salvati_24378"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T12:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A fine 2020 erano stati portati al debutto i messaggi effimeri in WhatsApp: si tratta di una funzione che provvede a cancellare chat e allegati dopo il loro invio una volta superata la finestra temporale specificata dall'utente.Dopo le critiche iniziali, gli sviluppatori di WhatsApp hanno fatto in modo di poter impostare la durata dei messaggi effimeri a 24 ore, 7 giorni oppure 90 giorni.

Per attivare le chat temporanee in WhatsApp basta toccare sul nome dell'utente o del gruppo quindi scorrere la schermata fino a individuare Messaggi effimeri.Purtroppo la scelta tecnica di WhatsApp è lontana anni luce da quella implementata in Telegram che permette di impostare liberamente un timer di autodistruzione dei messaggi bloccando di default anche l'inoltro delle conversazioni e la creazione di screenshot, cosa che invece su WhatsApp si può fare.E c'è un aspetto del quale in tanti non si erano accorti: gli allegati come le foto e i video inviati e ricevuti all'interno di una chat temporanea, quindi trattati come messaggi effimeri, venivano rimossi soltanto all'interno delle conversazioni ma continuavano a restare nella galleria del dispositivo mobile.Un imminente aggiornamento WhatsApp sta per modificare questo comportamento facendo sì che i file inviati come allegati in una chat temporanea (messaggi effimeri) non vengano più salvati nella galleria fotografica.Gli utenti che lo vorranno, tuttavia, avranno la facoltà di continuare a memorizzare nella galleria locale tutti i file e i video, compresi quelli inviati nelle conversazioni temporanee..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here's Everything Coming to Netflix the Week of April 11, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lifesavvy.com/123797/heres-everything-coming-to-netflix-the-week-of-april-11-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lifesavvy.com/123797/heres-everything-coming-to-netflix-the-week-of-april-11-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T12:30:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The beginning of the month drop has happened, and Bridgerton has been fully watched. What do you watch now?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shea Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Would You Consider a Microchip Implant for Contactless Payments?]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=479598</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15211579/microchip-implant-for-contactless-payments"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T12:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s no doubt contactless payments make life much easier. Paying for purchases through your smartphone or smartwatch alleviates the need to carry cash, a credit card, etc. There is also a very small section of the public who do contactless payments via a microchip implant embedded in their skin. Is this something you would consider?
   
Also read:Ring Doorbell Patents Show Future Uses of Biometric Data
    
How the Microchip Implant Works
    
Not that microchip implants are a new idea – the first human implant was in 1998. Now that they are commercially available, Walletmor says it is the first to offer implantable payment microchip implants for sale to the public, with 500 sold so far.
    
“The implant can be used to pay for a drink on the beach in Rio, a coffee in New York, a haircut in Paris – or at your local grocery store,”said Wajtek Paprota, founder and chief executive at... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD EPYC: il nuovo modello ha 96 core grazie all'uso di ben 12 chiplet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=AMD-EPYC-il-nuovo-modello-ha-96-core-grazie-all-uso-di-ben-12-chiplet_24377</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=AMD-EPYC-il-nuovo-modello-ha-96-core-grazie-all-uso-di-ben-12-chiplet_24377"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T12:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Parlando di migliori processori Intel e AMD abbiamo visto come la società guidata da Lisa Su abbia da tempo convintamente investito sull'architettura multichip (MCM) allontanandosi dallo schema monolitico ancora scelto in casa Intel.AMD rafforzerà la sua offerta di processori EPYC destinati ai server: la gamma 7004 (nome in codice Genoa) utilizzerà il nuovo socket SP5 LGA-6096 ma soprattutto introdurrà varianti che punteranno molto sull'aspetto della potenza.La società di Sunnyvale ha presentato processori EPYC con 8 chiplet per un massimo di 64 core a livello di CPU ma la nuova generazione sarà disponibile in una versione a 12 chiplet per un totale di ben 96 core fisici e 192 thread. L'immagine sottostante (fonte: AMD TF Malaysia) è più eloquente di tante parole.

Il risultato è stato ottenuto riducendo le dimensioni dei chip grazie all'adozione del processo litografico a 5 nm di TSMC, alla nuova architettura Zen 4 dei core e a un processo di incapsulamento che di fatto consente di usare i chiplet senza soluzione di continuità.AMD rilascerà versioni dotate di alcuni core disabilitati: un processore con 12 chiplet non è detto che abbia tutti i 96 core attivi.Ogni die CCD Zen4 ha un'area di 72 mm2, ridotta di 8 mm2 rispetto agli EPYC Milan realizzati con l'architettura Zen 3.Anche il die I/O è più piccolo, circa 397 mm2 rispetto ai 416 mm2 delle CPU EPYC di precedente generazione.La nuova piattaforma SP5 di AMD supporterà fino a 12 canali di memoria DDR5 e l'interfaccia PCIe Gen5.AMD sta già fornendo i primi chip Genoa ai suoi clienti con l'intera serie EPYC 7004 che verrà lanciata entro la fine di quest'anno..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Fast Will Wi-Fi 7 Be?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=796134</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/796134/how-fast-will-wi-fi-7-be/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T12:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Upgrading to a new version of Wi-Fi sounds great, but how much faster will the Wi-Fi 7 standard’s transfer speeds actually be? Let’s compare current standards with Wi-Fi 7 (also called 802.11be) and learn how your actual speed may vary.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jordan Gloor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pacman Wrapper for C++/Node]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u15ydy/pacman_wrapper_for_cnode/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u15ydy/pacman_wrapper_for_cnode/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T11:52:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is there a pacman wrapper for C++/Node, e.g. where I could do pacman.install('xyz');
    submitted by    /u/Dragonizedpizza  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Internet speed achingly slow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u15pn7/internet_speed_achingly_slow/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u15pn7/internet_speed_achingly_slow/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T11:39:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm not entirely sure if it's an arch based problem, but I couldn't find anything remotely related to my problem using Google.
 Edit: I'm saying wifi a lot here, but it's the same for ethernet/wired connections.
 When I'm connected to my home wifi, the internet is relatively fast and responsive, meaning if I load for example example.com, it will load almost instantly. But if I'm connected to ANYTHING else but my home wifi, it will take a quite concerning amount of time. And I'm not talking about internet speed! I was connected to wifis with over 500Mbit/s download AND upload and still, establishing connections takes forever. The task of going to speedtest.net, clicking the button and waiting until the download is being tested can sometimes take more than a minute, sometimes failes entirely. But when it succeedes, it will show the correct internet speed of the respective network, eg. 500 Mbit/s up and down. Even pings take forever.
 To get a grasp of how painful this is in my daily life, take a look at this demo. First I'm connected to my home network. Then I switch to my hotspot from my phone. I'm using plain wpa_supplicant (was using NetworkManager before, same problem) and my home wifi isn't configured in some weird way.
 https://youtu.be/4oooGGRnLzU
 ​
 So yeah, do you have any ideas how solve this issue?
 ​
 Edit: I might add some additional information about my system:
  
Arch Linux on a 82LM IdeaPad 5
 wpa_supplicant v2.10
 Router: FRITZ!Box 7490
 Home Wifi fast on both 5 and 2.4 GHz (latter using a repeater)
 ISP is o2 for DSL internet and also o2 for my mobile service. I have a Xiaomi Mi 9, but that's irrelevant, since it's slow on any wifi/ethernet connection except the one I'm using at home
  
   submitted by    /u/cubernetes  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NVIDIA Publishes Signed Ampere Firmware To Finally Allow Accelerated Open-Source Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=NVIDIA-Ampere-Firmware-Blobs</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=NVIDIA-Ampere-Firmware-Blobs"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T11:35:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Days after new open-source kernel driver code appeared in a Tegra code drop, NVIDIA happens today to have published signed firmware images for their RTX 30 "Ampere" graphics processors for finally allowing open-source driver support to proceed for these latest-generation GPUs...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Symantec says that hackers distributed a modified version of VLC and exploited it for malware attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=177942</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/04/11/symantec-says-that-hackers-distributed-a-modified-version-of-vlc-and-exploited-it-for-malware-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T11:31:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week, news began circling around that VLC was being abused by hackers to inject some malware. The issue came to light after Symantec published a report on its Security Threat Intelligence […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Symantec says that hackers distributed a modified version of VLC and exploited it for malware attacks appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla releases Extended Color Management add-on for Firefox]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=177943</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/04/11/mozilla-releases-extended-color-management-add-on-for-firefox/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T11:28:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla released the Extended Color Management in collaboration with the visual effects studio Industrial Light & Magic for the Firefox web browser. Designed to provide a simple on-off toggle for using the […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Mozilla releases Extended Color Management add-on for Firefox appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come funziona una rete domestica: router, ethernet, wifi]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2014/09/come-funziona-una-rete-casalinga-router.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2014/09/come-funziona-una-rete-casalinga-router.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T11:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quando parliamo di rete domestica dobbiamo prendere in esame tutti i dispositivi che permettono a PC e altri dispositivi (smartphone, tablet, smart TV) di accedere ad Internet. Si parla quindi soprattutto di router, ma anche di switch, wifi e cavi che possono essere presenti o meno in casa a seconda delle esigenze.

 La tecnologia di rete non è una materia facile, ma avendo una minima padronanza...


Continua a leggere su Navigweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PSA: Your Old Gadgets Are a Fire Hazard, Here’s What to Do]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=795732</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/795732/psa-your-old-gadgets-are-a-fire-hazard-heres-what-to-do/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T11:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Who among us doesn’t have a gadget junk drawer or box on a closet shelf with some old phones? Those old gadgets aren’t just clutter, though: They’re a potential fire hazard. Here’s what you need to know.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Fitzpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trucchi WhatsApp: i più utili e i meno conosciuti]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Trucchi-WhatsApp-i-piu-utili-e-i-meno-conosciuti_17834</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Trucchi-WhatsApp-i-piu-utili-e-i-meno-conosciuti_17834"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T10:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WhatsApp è la piattaforma di messaggistica istantanea nata a inizio 2009 anni fa che ha fatto segnare una crescita vorticosa per poi stabilizzarsi negli ultimi tempi a causa della pressione esercitata dalle soluzioni concorrenti e per via di alcuni scivoloni in termini di comunicazione con gli utenti (privacy e termini di utilizzo del servizio).Nel 2014 WhatsApp è stata acquisita da Facebook con un investimento da 19 miliardi di dollari e a gennaio 2022 (fonte Statista) WhatsApp vantava 2 miliardi di utenti attivi mentre ad esempio Telegram circa 550 milioni.Facebook Messenger, al secondo posto, viene accreditato di 990 milioni di utenti attivi, in decrescita rispetto all'anno precedente.Di seguito vi proponiamo una raccolta di trucchi WhatsApp. Si tratta di suggerimenti per utilizzare al meglio l'applicazione; spunti interessanti ma spesso sconosciuti anche a coloro che utilizzano giornalmente l'app di messaggistica sui propri dispositivi mobili e su PC desktop.
I trucchi per usare al meglio WhatsApp e WhatsApp Web
Usare WhatsApp Web come se fosse una normale applicazione Windows
 Quando si lavora su un PC desktop, un notebook o un convertibile, agguantare in continuazione lo smartphone per leggere i messaggi WhatsApp in arrivo fa davvero perdere tanto tempo e rende molto meno produttivi.Com'è noto, una possibile soluzione consiste nell'utilizzo di WhatsApp Web.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD P-State vs. ACPI CPUFreq Testing With Ryzen Laptops On Linux 5.17]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31024</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31024"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T10:19:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most prominent features of Linux 5.17 for end-users was the introduction of the AMD P-State driver that is designed to deliver better energy efficiency than the generic ACPI CPUFreq frequency scaling driver relied on by AMD Ryzen processors up to this point. For those wondering how the performance and efficiency currently compare for Ryzen laptops, here are some benchmarks recently carried out on Linux 5.17 for both drivers and testing both the Schedutil and Performance governors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 controlla le applicazioni nelle quali vengono inserite password e credenziali di accesso]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-11-controlla-le-applicazioni-nelle-quali-vengono-inserite-password-e-credenziali-di-accesso_24376</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-11-controlla-le-applicazioni-nelle-quali-vengono-inserite-password-e-credenziali-di-accesso_24376"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 presto integrerà una funzione che attacca alla radice una delle peggiori e più comuni abitudini di molti utenti. Di cosa stiamo parlando? Della memorizzazione delle password in comuni file di testo, ad esempio file TXT o DOCX salvati in locale.Annotare le credenziali di accesso in un semplice file è assolutamente insicuro: in primis perché non essendo in alcun modo protetto il contenuto di tale file può cadere preda di malintenzionati e componenti malware. Per secondo perché se il sistema non è protetto ad esempio con soluzioni quali BitLocker o VeraCrypt, che cifrano tutto il contenuto del disco, avviando la macchina da un supporto di boot tutti i file in essa contenuti possono essere facilmente sottratti. Ne abbiamo parlato negli articoli dedicati a come accedere a Windows 10 senza password e come fare in caso di password Windows 11 dimenticata.Tramite un aggiornamento della tecnologia SmartScreen, Windows 11 22H2 avvertirà l'utente non appena proverà a inserire una password in un software considerato potenzialmente non sicuro.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[using arch linux for music production]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u13oit/using_arch_linux_for_music_production/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u13oit/using_arch_linux_for_music_production/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T09:27:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[as a beginner in music I always wanted to have a great music producing software and setup on linux so in this guide I will walk you through what you need to do to make arch linux optimized for music production and use all your favorite VST plugins
 you should follow these steps:
 1: first you need a DAW (Digital Audio Workstation) and I personally recommend using a native linux one but if you are so used to the windows or mac DAW that you use you can try and see how it runs under wine
 2: you need to configure PAM limits so that your DAW has full access to your memory so for that first install the package realtime-privileges then you need to add your user to the realtime group so:
 sudo usermod -a -G realtime yourUserID
 then reboot your pc
 3: to use windows VST plugins I strongly suggest using yabridge it's a really great tool and It will make most of your VST to work If yabridge wasn't enough for you, you can also see this which has some more ways
 BTW I'm not a professional arch user so correct me If I made a mistake and I'm not responsible if you break something on your system, these steps worked perfectly on my arch linux so keep that in mind. hope this helps people to use DAWs like how they used them on windows and make amazing musics with them!
    submitted by    /u/sirius1377  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What packages do you need to gain fuctionality that DEs give you on a WM?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u13d6i/what_packages_do_you_need_to_gain_fuctionality/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u13d6i/what_packages_do_you_need_to_gain_fuctionality/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T09:05:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! So, I want to use DWM as a daily driver but I don't really know what programs people use for basic stuff that DEs have by default like taking screenshots, browsing files, reading PDFs, viewing pictures, etc. What programs do you use? Could you please help me choose? Any help would be appreciated.
    submitted by    /u/everonek  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SimpleLogin: email alias e invio anonimo dei messaggi di posta. Adesso acquisito da Proton]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=SimpleLogin-email-alias-e-invio-anonimo-dei-messaggi-di-posta-Adesso-acquisito-da-Proton_24375</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=SimpleLogin-email-alias-e-invio-anonimo-dei-messaggi-di-posta-Adesso-acquisito-da-Proton_24375"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T08:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Proton AG, azienda svizzera che sviluppa i noti servizi ProtonMail e ProtonVPN, ha annunciato di aver acquisito SimpleLogin.Si tratta di una mossa interessante perché SimpleLogin è un apprezzato servizio che permette di creare email alias per ricevere e inviare email in forma anonima. SimpleLogin consente infatti di creare indirizzi email completamente diversi da quelli che si usano abitualmente in modo da non rivelarne l'esistenza ad altri utenti o sul Web.Anche nel piano free di SimpleLogin, completamente gratuito, si possono creare fino a 15 email alias che provvedono a inoltrare i messaggi ricevuti verso l'account 'reale' indicato dall'utente.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMS Si prega di contattare il centro dell'impiego al numero 899]]></title>
        <id>3545|20220411090846</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/truffe-5953/sms-si-prega-contattare-centro-impiego-numero-899-3545"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T07:08:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In questi giorni ha ripreso a circolare con insistenza un messaggio che invita a contattare il "centro dell'impiego" ad un numero che inizia con 899. Di cosa si tratta?
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to block all notifications or notifications from specific apps in Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=177933</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/04/11/how-to-block-all-notifications-or-notifications-from-specific-apps-in-windows-11/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T05:11:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11's notification system may be used by applications to send notifications to the user's desktop. Apps may use it to send reminders to the user. A common scenario that is supported […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post How to block all notifications or notifications from specific apps in Windows 11 appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GNOME 42 audio overamplification]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u0zv8f/gnome_42_audio_overamplification/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u0zv8f/gnome_42_audio_overamplification/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T04:59:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm noticing that after updating to GNOME 42, I'm having issues with audio overamplification; loud noises are now being overdriven and are distorting. I went into the audio settings, and I am noticing that there no longer is a setting to enable or disable overamplification. So I'm guessing that something changed, and overamplification got enabled by default, and now I cannot disable it from the settings.
 Has anyone encountered this issue? What can I do to fix this?
    submitted by    /u/Izerpizer  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux 5.18-rc2 Released With The Kernel So Far Looking "Fairly Normal"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.18-rc2-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.18-rc2-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T00:58:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following last week's first release candidate of Linux 5.18 that capped off the two week merge window, Linux 5.18-rc2 was just issued as the newest weekly release candidate...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can't port forward, how can I tell if its my (Arch setup) problem or ISP/modem?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u0ut0s/cant_port_forward_how_can_i_tell_if_its_my_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u0ut0s/cant_port_forward_how_can_i_tell_if_its_my_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T00:13:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have xfinity and I can simply not get port forwarding to work
 ​
 On the xFi app it shows that it was successful, yet any online port checker says that the port is closed.
 running iptables -nL gives me
 Chain INPUT (policy ACCEPT) target prot opt source destination LIBVIRT_INP all -- 0.0.0.0/0 0.0.0.0/0 Chain FORWARD (policy ACCEPT) target prot opt source destination DOCKER-USER all -- 0.0.0.0/0 0.0.0.0/0 DOCKER-ISOLATION-STAGE-1 all -- 0.0.0.0/0 0.0.0.0/0 ACCEPT all -- 0.0.0.0/0 0.0.0.0/0 ctstate RELATED,ESTABLISHED DOCKER all -- 0.0.0.0/0 0.0.0.0/0 ACCEPT all -- 0.0.0.0/0 0.0.0.0/0 ACCEPT all -- 0.0.0.0/0 0.0.0.0/0 LIBVIRT_FWX all -- 0.0.0.0/0 0.0.0.0/0 LIBVIRT_FWI all -- 0.0.0.0/0 0.0.0.0/0 LIBVIRT_FWO all -- 0.0.0.0/0 0.0.0.0/0 Chain OUTPUT (policy ACCEPT) target prot opt source des…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Has anyone had success with audio inputs on 3rd Gen Focusrite Interfaces recently?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u0uisf/has_anyone_had_success_with_audio_inputs_on_3rd/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u0uisf/has_anyone_had_success_with_audio_inputs_on_3rd/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-10T23:58:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I can’t get my mic to work reliably in Arch (gnome shell). Through a large amount of fiddling with pipewire, pulse, JACK, and. ALSA I’ve gotten to a point where I can sort of get it working temporarily if I switch my interface’s driver from output + input to just input and back again in PAVU. But I haven’t found any way to just have it work. No driver configuration has lead to the mic being recognized by gnome settings either. 
 Is there a general way to set up focusrite interfaces for recording or just general mic use (discord, etc) in gnome/arch? If someone has a solution they use I’d love to hear it.
    submitted by    /u/EmEsTwenny  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dev/sdb3 does not exist need help fixing it]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u0tq5q/devsdb3_does_not_exist_need_help_fixing_it/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u0tq5q/devsdb3_does_not_exist_need_help_fixing_it/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-10T23:17:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello I’m new to arch Linux currently installing it manually I just have one problem the tutorial I was watching showing that I had to mount the /dev/sdb3 part which was listed under Lsblk but isn’t. But I see a lot of you know more then I do 
 but I add that this subreddit is probably full of long time users but me being the noob. Of arch I ask for guidance 
 So As I was saying I’m trying to figure out if it’s normal for sdb3 to not exist but I can’t back out now as I completely formatted my disk cause I’m creating the partitions like the boot and all that for the disk right now but all I wanted to say is I need help fixing this issue 
 Can I please get help
    submitted by    /u/Puzzleheaded_Way4140  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Error with yay whilst installing packages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u0slki/error_with_yay_whilst_installing_packages/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u0slki/error_with_yay_whilst_installing_packages/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-10T22:20:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Im getting  The unauthenticated git protocol on port 9418 is no longer supported. Please see https://github.blog/2021-09-01-improving-git-protocol-security-github/ for more information.  Does this have to do with the AUR or is this just some github issue?
    submitted by    /u/MattioC  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here are the new features coming to Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/here-are-the-new-features-coming-to-windows-11/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/here-are-the-new-features-coming-to-windows-11/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-10T22:19:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 version 22H2 is arriving later this year and it won't be a massive release, but there will be several improvements and bugs fixes. During the Hybrid work event, Microsoft officially teased new features coming to the operating system this year. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mayank Parmar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best way to go about re-installing Cinnamon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u0sdc0/best_way_to_go_about_reinstalling_cinnamon/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u0sdc0/best_way_to_go_about_reinstalling_cinnamon/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-10T22:09:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have numerous issues with Cinnamon after updates over the last few months. The main ones being that some of my apps won't display properly; such as Steam, when i go to launch steam via the cinnamon menu, it starts a fully black box where the steam window should be. Thus, I can only start steam in the terminal to actually see/use it - strange since it references the same command. I also am unable to change some of the themes (namely the icon theme or the mouse pointer theme). I have tried a few things now, but it's just really getting on my nerves. I'm assuming that if I can just wipe cinnamon off and re-install it fresh, I'm hoping it will just resolve all the problems I've got. I'm not sure what impact or problems I might create doing this on my main PC, so I wanted to ask advice on how to best do this without making myself more headaches afterwards. I tried just removing it via the usual command below, but after I re-install cinnamon, it simply restored my previous settings/problems (I'm assuming it keeps the config files, maybe do I need Rsc? I am a little worried on running the -c option if so).
 $sudo pacman -Rns cinnamon $sudo pacman -S cinnamon 
 FYI I start my PC, and launch X via typing $ startx, and my xinitrc file simply just has the exec set to the below. So I should be ok to do this before running startx.
 exec cinnamon-session 
    submitted by    /u/sg4rb0sss  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come abilitare il mute audio direttamente dal tab aperto di Chrome]]></title>
        <id>3537|20220411000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/browser-455/come-abilitare-mute-audio-direttamente-tab-aperto-chrome-3537"/>
        <updated>2022-04-10T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Con l’arrivo di Chrome 100 è stata riabilitata, anche se nascosta, la possibilità di zittire una scheda aperta del browser che trasmette dell’audio. Se vi trovate nella condizione di avere tante schede aperte e una di queste vi disturba, senza doverla aprire, potete cliccare direttamente sopra l’icona dell’altoparlante per metterla a tacere.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Turn Off In-App Purchases on Android or iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=791336</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/791336/turn-off-in-app-purchases-android-iphone/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-10T21:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To avoid accidentally buying in-app items on your Android, iPhone, or iPad, disable the in-app purchase option so that you have to verify each purchase before it’s confirmed. Here’s how you can do just that on your phone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build Your Own Roomba with iRobot's Create 3 Kit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/114559/build-your-own-roomba-with-irobots-create-3-kit/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/114559/build-your-own-roomba-with-irobots-create-3-kit/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-10T20:04:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In celebration of National Robotics Week, iRobot is launching the Create 3 kit. It’s an educational robot based on the modern Roomba design, minus the ability to vacuum. But hey, it can detect walls and is insanely customizable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thinking about going full Arch as a daily desktop, have some doubts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u0poxm/thinking_about_going_full_arch_as_a_daily_desktop/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u0poxm/thinking_about_going_full_arch_as_a_daily_desktop/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-10T20:01:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm no stranger to Arch, though I dual-boot it with Debian Stable for work, as I really want stability for work purposes but prefer bleeding-edge for gaming, and I do like both for what they are. But at some point I migrated my work to a separate, dedicated Debian laptop, and now my main rig is back to being my personal system again. Now I wonder if I should just ditch the dual-boot and go back to using full dedicated Arch (I did in the past but with derivatives like Manjaro and Antergos - when it was still alive that is).
 After I got a better grasp on how dependencies and software development are tied together (partly thanks to work, partly due to Valve embracing Arch as a base for their work - which gave me further insights on how to essentially not be tied to specific distros, or TL;DR…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Browse Files on a Mac]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=790698</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/790698/how-to-browse-files-on-a-mac/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-10T20:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you need to find, move, copy, or delete files on your Mac, you’ll need to use Finder, which is similar to File Explorer on Windows. We’ll show you some basics about how to browse for files and manage them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GNOME-Console not in official repos?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u0p09k/gnomeconsole_not_in_official_repos/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u0p09k/gnomeconsole_not_in_official_repos/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-10T19:29:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why is the gnome-console (the new terminal) not in the official repos but in the AUR?
 Is there a reason for it, is it because it is in beta? Will it move to the official repos somewhen?
    submitted by    /u/oldominion  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[100% CPU Usage in Windows? Here’s How to Fix it]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=299568</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/11447327/fix-windows-100-cpu-usage"/>
        <updated>2022-04-10T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve all been there. You turn on your PC, and instead of getting straight to work, you’re faced with horrific slowdown and loud-running fans. Hit Ctrl + Shift + Escape, and you will see that your CPU usage is inexplicably at 100%.
    
It’s a common problem that’s, luckily, not usually too hard to solve. Here are several fixes for the 100% CPU usage problem in Windows.
   

Content

Disable SysMain (formerly known as Superfetch)
WMI Provider Host Using 100% CPU
Reset Your Power Plan
Check Your Power Supply
100% CPU Usage in Games
Disable Third-Party Antivirus Software

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:Hidden Windows 11 Features for Power Users
    
Disable SysMain (formerly known as Superfetch)
    
SysMain is a process by which Windows 10 learns which apps you use most often, then pre-fetches them for you so they load quicker each time you use them.... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Zak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows Disk partitioning grub rescue hell and recovery tips]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u0orst/windows_disk_partitioning_grub_rescue_hell_and/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u0orst/windows_disk_partitioning_grub_rescue_hell_and/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-10T19:18:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am a lost soul that tried to install arch on a separate disk of my windows machine. I followed the dual boot with windows wiki. I am now stuck in grub rescue unless I choose to boot from the liveusb.
 My main confusion is how 2 Windows disk partitions got created on my linux only ssd? https://imgur.com/gallery/OMxyu8j Sdb1&2 were made entirely by some magic beyond me.
 Any advice on how to proceed? Really only interested in recovery first but don't have many ideas regardless. I know I shouldn't have tried this but I get bored and break things...
 The live usb works great, but it's all I got now lol
    submitted by    /u/AManWhoSaysNo  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Find Archived Messages on Facebook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=791272</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/791272/find-archived-messages-facebook-messenger/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-10T19:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to take a look at your archived messages, and perhaps unarchive one or more of those conversations? If so, Facebook makes it easy to find and unarchive your chats on both your desktop and mobile phone. We’ll show you how to do that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Audio-Technica's Popular M20x Headphones Go Wireless for $79]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/114567/audio-technicas-popular-m20x-headphones-go-wireless-for-79/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/114567/audio-technicas-popular-m20x-headphones-go-wireless-for-79/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-10T18:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Audio-Technica recently unveiled a new pair of wireless headphones to replace one of its most popular monitor-quality headphones. Of course, we’re talking about the new ATH-M20xBT, and they’re only $79.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Find Your Current Location on Google Maps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=791110</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/791110/how-to-find-your-current-location-on-google-maps/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-10T18:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Maps makes it extremely easy to find your current location on the map. It even shows the direction you’re facing so you know where you’re heading. Here’s how to see where you are right now in Maps on both desktop and mobile.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make a Chromebook Easier on Your Eyes at Night]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=795563</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/795563/how-to-make-a-chromebook-easier-on-your-eyes-at-night/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-10T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nobody likes looking at a bright blue-white display in a dark room. Switching as many apps as possible to Dark Mode is a good start, but if you have a Chromebook, you should also use the “Night Light” feature.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How is the --assume-installed flag used?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u0lp4e/how_is_the_assumeinstalled_flag_used/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u0lp4e/how_is_the_assumeinstalled_flag_used/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-10T16:54:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was looking through the pacman flags, and was unsure how the --assume-installed flag is used. Can it also be used multiple times?
    submitted by    /u/Dragonizedpizza  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fiido's X Electric Bike Recalled Due to Slight Case of Snapping in Half]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/114546/fiidos-x-electric-bike-recalled-due-to-slight-case-of-snapping-in-half/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/114546/fiidos-x-electric-bike-recalled-due-to-slight-case-of-snapping-in-half/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-10T16:34:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fiido is an affordable direct-to-consumer electric bike manufacturer with several different e-bikes available around the globe. Unfortunately, we have bad news if you have the popular Fiido X folding e-bike, as the company just issued a recall over fears of it breaking in half.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reiser5 Issues New Development Release, Performance Numbers For Scaling Out]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Reiser5-April-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Reiser5-April-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-04-10T16:28:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While Reiser4 never made it to mainline and has lacked any major corporate backing while Linux 5.18 is deprecating the older ReiserFS driver for removal later on, former Namesys developer Edward Shishkin continues progressing development on "Reiser5" as the evolution of Reiser4. Out today is the newest Reiser5 snapshot and some performance numbers from Shishkin...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why You Should Use Peer-to-Peer Messaging Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=790612</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/790612/why-you-should-use-peer-to-peer-messaging-apps/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-10T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peer-to-Peer messaging is as reliable as Facebook Messenger or Discord, but you maintain control of your data and don’t rely on a third-party server to talk with people. It’s a better way to do communicate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Lewis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ShobuArch: Automated Arch Linux Tools (Written in Go)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u0kh1a/shobuarch_automated_arch_linux_tools_written_in_go/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u0kh1a/shobuarch_automated_arch_linux_tools_written_in_go/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-10T15:55:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/ShobuPrime  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows sucks but i have to program in VHDL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u0k7n0/windows_sucks_but_i_have_to_program_in_vhdl/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u0k7n0/windows_sucks_but_i_have_to_program_in_vhdl/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-10T15:42:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[​
 Ok so i am avid (although nooby) arch user. I like Dark Souls, i like Sekiro and likewise i like Arch. 
 I use i3-wm + ranger + gh cli + code/vim on a daily basis. I seek a substitute for Lattice vhdl IDE.
 For now i have already installed ghdl with LLVM backend and made a Makefile.
 I only require two more things: a way to assign pins (like pin planner) and a way to upload program to fpga stream.
 ​
 Do you know any solutions to my problem?
    submitted by    /u/Winkerlied  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Screen recording tools for wayland]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u0jmpc/screen_recording_tools_for_wayland/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u0jmpc/screen_recording_tools_for_wayland/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-10T15:13:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am looking for a screen recording tool.Something similar to Gnome inbuilt screencast/screenshot tool but for KDE plasma wayland. I tried few stuff from AUR, but it was either made for xorg or gnome.. Also could not use wf-recorder which throws this error compositor doesn't support wlr-screencopy-unstable-v1 ( i am guessing it works on select few wayland compositors ). 
 Audio recording is not a priority so I can do without it. I want to be able to bind it to a shortcut and it should be able to select rectangular region for capture.
    submitted by    /u/trueleo8  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Meta information stealer distributed in malspam campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-meta-information-stealer-distributed-in-malspam-campaign/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-meta-information-stealer-distributed-in-malspam-campaign/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-10T15:12:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Independent analyst Brand Duncan has spotted a malspam campaign delivering META, a new info-stealer malware that appears to be rising in popularity among cybercriminals. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Delete Multiple Emails in Microsoft Outlook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=793596</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/793596/how-to-delete-multiple-emails-in-microsoft-outlook/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-10T15:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re looking to get rid of several emails at once, Microsoft Outlook allows you to selectively remove multiple emails at the same time. You can do this in Outlook’s web, desktop, and mobile versions. We’ll show you how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Need help installing i3-gaps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u0iofy/need_help_installing_i3gaps/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/u0iofy/need_help_installing_i3gaps/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-10T14:26:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was trying to install i3-gaps and did the following: - installed i3-gaps, i3blocks, i3lock and i3status - installed xorg, xorg-xinit - copied /etc/X11/xinit/xinitrc to my home directory with the filename being .xinitrc - modified .xinitrc and removed the lines below 'fi' then i added 'exec i3 - ran startx and it showed a small white block in the middle of the screen - waited a bit and nothing happened
 Can anyone help me?
 Edit: I did not install any fonts, a simple 
 sudo pacman -S ttf-dejavu
 Did the trick!
    submitted by    /u/7_S3M_7  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Edge gets performance boost with updated sleeping tabs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-edge-gets-performance-boost-with-updated-sleeping-tabs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-edge-gets-performance-boost-with-updated-sleeping-tabs/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-10T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has tweaked the Microsoft Edge sleeping tabs feature to further improve the web browser's overall responsiveness and performance. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best iPad Accessories of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=757335</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/757335/best-ipad-accessory/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-10T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The best iPad accessories are designed to make your viewing, browsing, and tasking experience more intuitive. They can protect your device or reinvent the way you interact, listen to music, and type.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Prince</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>