<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-07-24T02:14:00.103Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hi guys can you share the arch.zip file for creating a bootable usb the tool I am using can't use iso and I couldnt find a .zip file on the download page. HELP PLEASE?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6iuzg/hi_guys_can_you_share_the_archzip_file_for/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6iuzg/hi_guys_can_you_share_the_archzip_file_for/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T00:46:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/Piano-Nerd  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux x86 32-bit Is Vulnerable To Retbleed But Don't Expect It To Get Fixed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/news/Linux-x86-Retbleed</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/news/Linux-x86-Retbleed"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T23:39:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While relevant Intel and AMD processors have been mitigated for the recent Retbleed security vulnerability affecting older generations of processors, those mitigations currently just work for x86_64 kernels and will not work if running an x86 (32-bit) kernel on affected hardware. But it's unlikely to get fixed unless some passionate individual steps up as the upstream developers and vendors have long since moved on to just caring about x86_64...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to install MacBook keyboard and trackpad drivers?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6hdf0/how_to_install_macbook_keyboard_and_trackpad/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6hdf0/how_to_install_macbook_keyboard_and_trackpad/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T23:33:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey guys, just installed XeroLinux on my MacBook Pro. I am currently using an external keyboard and mouse but was wondering if it was possible to get the native keyboard and trackpad to work with this installation. This is my first time trying Linux.
    submitted by    /u/FaMaterial  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qtile failing to run with wayland module not found wlroots]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6h51n/qtile_failing_to_run_with_wayland_module_not/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6h51n/qtile_failing_to_run_with_wayland_module_not/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T23:22:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As far as im aware i installed everything i needed but when i try to start qtile i have installed everything else i thought i need but im still getting this error and am not sure where to go
    submitted by    /u/OutsideNo1877  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[archfi]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6h4em/archfi/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6h4em/archfi/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T23:21:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve tried to install arch using archfi tool However when I finish the installation and reboot it brings me back to the console What should I do??
    submitted by    /u/_ch0ck  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[i did it again O.o git and aur replacement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6gsp4/i_did_it_again_oo_git_and_aur_replacement/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6gsp4/i_did_it_again_oo_git_and_aur_replacement/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T23:05:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[hi there again, i need your help again. 
 i started using linux-hardened and trying using kazium but this is one of the packages that stopped working using a "safer" kernel. and here it comes someone on the internet recommended to not to use flatpak may solve the bwrap restrictions of this kernel. 
 SO the dump me tought lets try the AUR kalzium-git without checking what packages it would install.
 And after a lot of :"yes sure why i wouldn't replace a lot of kde's packages with their outdated unmaintained packages" i found out i may made a mistake. Don't use:
 yes | yay package name 
 is there a way to replace all git packages with their pacman match, they all have git- in there name.
 and i runned a backup a few days ago with:
 rsync -aAXHvz --exclude={"/dev/*","/proc/*","/sys/*","/tmp/*…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fail to mount.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6ehnu/fail_to_mount/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6ehnu/fail_to_mount/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T21:21:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was screwing around trying to get League of Legends to work.
 After I rebooted, I get a message saying a dependency in /home/ failed, and I get a failure to mount /dev/sda1 From the emergency shell, I can run mount -a, systemctl enable sddm, exit and it boots/works just fine after that. I found it can be a problem with /etc/fstab but can't seem to locate the issue.
 /etc/fstab
  Static information about the filesystems. # See fstab(5) for details. # <file system> <dir> <type> <options> <dump> <pass> # /dev/sda2 UUID=85b9b5a1-3272-4606-a72a-4f292cabe8de / ext4 rw,relatime 0 1 # /dev/sda1 UUID=98C7-00DB /boot vfat rw,relatime,fmask=0022,dmask=0022,codepage=437,iocharset=ascii,shortname=mixed,utf8,errors=remount-ro 0 2 # /dev/sdb1 UUID=d9db346f-3279-4861-b073-19ec0962accd /home ext4 rw,relatime 0 2 
 lsblk -f
 NAME FSTYPE FSVER LABEL UUID FSAVAIL FSUSE% MOUNTPOINTS sda ├─sda1 vfat FAT32 98C7-00DB 402.5M 21% /boot └─sda2 ext4 1.0 85b9b5a1-3272-4606-a72a-4f292cabe8de 182.1G 12% / sdb └─sdb1 ext4 1.0 d9db346f-3279-4861-b073-19ec0962accd 2.5T 2% /home zram0 [SWAP] 
 I'm absolutely sure I'm missing something dumb here, just not sure what. Thank you so much in advance.
    submitted by    /u/Autistigasmatic  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[two questions about archinstall (the pacman version not the default one)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6eh5q/two_questions_about_archinstall_the_pacman/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6eh5q/two_questions_about_archinstall_the_pacman/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T21:20:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have two question's about the script after archinstall is done, both of which are in the "/dev/(disk)" section.
  
what does the "encrypted" option do; obviously it encrypts, but if I change it from true to false will it really just encrypt the partition or do you have to do anything else too? and if so, what kind of encryption will it perform?
 what does the "wipe" option do?
  
ty.
 edit: here's a link to what I'm talking about
    submitted by    /u/Amber___yo  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Don’t Need a Product Key to Install and Use Windows 10]]></title>
        <id>http://www.howtogeek.com/?p=244678</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/244678/you-dont-need-a-product-key-to-install-and-use-windows-10/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft allows anyone to download Windows 10 for free and install it without a product key. It’ll keep working for the foreseeable future, with only a few small cosmetic restrictions. And you can even pay to upgrade to a licensed copy of Windows 10 after you install it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thinkpad P50 DWM problem on wake from lid closed sleep]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6dslx/thinkpad_p50_dwm_problem_on_wake_from_lid_closed/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6dslx/thinkpad_p50_dwm_problem_on_wake_from_lid_closed/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T20:49:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi all,
 I am running Arch on a Thinkpad P50 with DWM as my window manager. I'm experiencing a problem with waking the computer from lid-closed sleep, where the computer wakes but the screen is black, except for a small horizontal line at the topmost left corner of the screen. The keyboard won't respond in this state, so I can't get another terminal open to diagnose or kill the display manager. 
 Arch is otherwise running perfectly on the P50, but this issue is really annoying and I would love to resolve it. The problem is that I don't know where to start, and would really appreciate some guidance / tips from the community. I perused the forums and reddit, and couldn't find a post with the same issue - but I am sure that this is not unique to me. I'm running 5.18.13-arch1-1. No display manager is used; just a call to exec dwm in .xinitrc. 
 I can provide whatever logging info would be helpful. I have the same build running on a Thinkpad X220, and that installation is bullet proof - so I wonder if it has to do with the hybrid graphics setup on the P50? I have the following graphics drivers installed: mesa, lib32-mesa, nvidia.
 Thanks again.
    submitted by    /u/Away_Inflation_411  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HarfBuzz 5.0 Released With Progress On Supporting The "Boring Expansion" Font Spec]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/news/HarfBuzz-5.0-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/news/HarfBuzz-5.0-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T20:38:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HarfBuzz is the open-source text shaping engine that is widely used by many different libraries and applications. The HarfBuzz code is critical to the Linux desktop and many open-source applications while this weekend is celebrating its big "5.0" release. With HarfBuzz 5.0 the developers have been working on the "Boring Expansion" font spec support...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can multiple instances of aurutils aur sync -Sc pkgname1 pkgname2... be run parallel?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6damp/can_multiple_instances_of_aurutils_aur_sync_sc/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6damp/can_multiple_instances_of_aurutils_aur_sync_sc/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T20:26:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/doskanoness  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Change Directories in Command Prompt on Windows 10]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=659411</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/659411/how-to-change-directories-in-command-prompt-on-windows-10/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the first things you’ll need to learn as you become more familiar with Command Prompt on Windows 10 is how to change directories in the operating system’s file system. There are a few ways you can do this, so we’ll walk you through them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marshall Gunnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[16 Interesting Discord Servers to Join (And Where You Can Find More)]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=post-ideas&amp;p=425157</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/14777747/best-discord-servers"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While it was once a chat app that lived and breathed as a place for gamers to communicate, Discord has evolved into “Your Place to Talk and Hang Out.” It is available on Windows, macOS, iOS, and Android, and you can jump in and out of conversations as often as you would like. In fact, the biggest challenge with Discord may be where to find the best servers for your situation. Fortunately, we can help with that.
   

Content

1. Your Favorite Podcast/Streamer/YouTuber/Subreddit
2. r/CryptoCurrency
3. Movies & Filmmaking
4. Minecraft and/or Any Other Games
5. Fantasy Football Chat
6. Invincible
7. ChillZone
8. Anime Soul Discord
9. Game Dev League
10. Boiler Room Trading
11. Apple
12. Xbox/PlayStation
13. Marvel Studios
14. The Car Community
15. Memeology
16. Study Together
Finding More Discord Servers
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Change Your Username and Nickname... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexandra Arici</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Relive Your Favorite Music Concerts with Setify]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/123912/relive-your-favorite-music-concerts-with-setify/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/123912/relive-your-favorite-music-concerts-with-setify/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T19:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever loved the set list at a live concert so much that you wish you could easily listen to it over and over again? Or missed a concert by your favorite artist but still want to hear each song? If so, the web app Setify is worth checking out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Photo Album in Microsoft PowerPoint]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=812552</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/812552/how-to-create-a-photo-album-in-microsoft-powerpoint/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T19:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Slideshows are great for more than just business-related presentations. You can use Microsoft PowerPoint to create a photo album and add music or visual effects for a memorable show.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pulseaudio monitor acting weird with bluetooth earphones]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6a5vs/pulseaudio_monitor_acting_weird_with_bluetooth/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6a5vs/pulseaudio_monitor_acting_weird_with_bluetooth/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T18:04:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This issue as far as i know has been limited to my bluetooth earphones [Oneplus Wireless Z2]
 This started after i switched the profiles from a2dp to hfp to use the inbuilt microphone for a video call
 Now i am not able to get output in cava and also not able to get desktop audio in obs when the bluetooth earphones are connected 
 I have tried:
 1)change the audio source in cava to the monitor corresponding to the earphones 
 2) changed sources in obs but to no avail
 3) unpairing and repairing the earphones
 I am using KDE Plasma
 Here are the outputs inxi -A, pacmd list-sources : https://pastebin.com/DM4gmDHr
 Please let me know if i left out some important information
 Thanks for all the help
    submitted by    /u/its_RaCl  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Turn Off Caps Lock on a Chromebook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=820198</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/820198/how-to-turn-off-caps-lock-on-a-chromebook/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T18:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chromebooks have very unique keyboard layouts. Where most keyboards have a Caps Lock key, Chromebooks have a search key instead. Using Caps Lock takes a little extra work, which means turning it off is a little more complex too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HFP Audio is no longer available, stuck on troubleshooting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w69mij/hfp_audio_is_no_longer_available_stuck_on/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w69mij/hfp_audio_is_no_longer_available_stuck_on/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T17:40:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi,
 I've been using a set of bluetooth headphones for the last several months. A2DP has always worked great for listening to music and videos but obviously I needed to switch to HFP in order for the microphone to work. I'm using pulseaudio and was able to enable the HFP profile pretty painlessly with pavcontrol.
 This was fine until a couple of weeks ago, now my system is showing unavailable in `pactl list`:
 Profiles: a2dp_sink: High Fidelity Playback (A2DP Sink) (sinks: 1, sources: 0, priority: 40, available: yes) handsfree_head_unit: Handsfree Head Unit (HFP) (sinks: 1, sources: 1, priority: 30, available: no) off: Off (sinks: 0, sources: 0, priority: 0, available: yes) 
 I followed the steps in the wiki relating to HFP issues. But I'm at a bit of a dead end. I tried running:
 dbus-send --print-reply --system --dest=org.ofono /phonesim org.ofono.Modem.SetProperty string:"Powered" variant:boolean:true 
 With the error
 Error org.freedesktop.DBus.Error.UnknownObject: Method "SetProperty" with signature "sv" on interface "org.ofono.Modem" doesn't exist 
 So I checked to make sure I have activated the modem, but downloading the git repo for ofono and running test/list-modems just creates a draggable text area on my screen for some reason, then exits out.
 I then went and checked the python code and ran the first couple of lines:
 import dbus bus = dbus.SystemBus() manager = dbus.Interface(bus.get_object('org.ofono', '/'),'org.ofono.Manager') modems = manager.GetModems() print(modems) >>> dbus.Array([], signature=dbus.Signature('(oa{sv})')) 
 So looks like modems is empty and I'm not sure where to go from here?
 Any help much appreciated.
 Also curious why the headset is only recently not working, have had no similar issues on my phone.
 Thank you
    submitted by    /u/jzia93  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD Sensor Fusion Hub "SFH1.1" Support Coming In Linux 5.20 For Newer Laptops]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/news/AMD-Sensor-Fusion-Hub-SFH-1.1</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/news/AMD-Sensor-Fusion-Hub-SFH-1.1"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T17:23:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the upcoming Linux 5.20 cycle is support for AMD's Sensor Fusion Hub v1.1 revision being found in newer Ryzen laptops...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mattel Teams Up With Elon Musk's SpaceX to Create New Toys]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/123923/mattel-teams-up-with-elon-musks-spacex-to-create-new-toys/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/123923/mattel-teams-up-with-elon-musks-spacex-to-create-new-toys/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T17:13:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Popular toy maker Mattel is teaming up with Elon Musk’s SpaceX company to produce a new line of space-themed toys and rockets. On Wednesday, the two announced a multi-year deal to deliver Matchbox brand SpaceX toys and merchandise by 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Share a Wi-Fi Password From Mac to iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=814352</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/814352/how-to-share-a-wi-fi-password-from-mac-to-iphone/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T17:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you need to share a Wi-Fi password from a Mac to an iPhone, you can do it fairly easily between your own devices and those of friends or family. Here’s how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean hackers attack EU targets with Konni RAT malware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/north-korean-hackers-attack-eu-targets-with-konni-rat-malware/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/north-korean-hackers-attack-eu-targets-with-konni-rat-malware/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T16:08:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat analysts have uncovered a new campaign attributed to APT37, a North Korean group of hackers, targeting high-value organizations in the Czech Republic, Poland, and other European countries. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up Facebook Marketplace Alerts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=819768</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/819768/how-to-set-up-facebook-marketplace-alerts/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T16:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Facebook Marketplace has become the go-to place for selling things online. If you’re on the lookout for a specific item, an alert can help you snag a great deal before everyone else. We’ll show you how to do it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Banana Pi BPI-W3 Lets You Build a Powerful Router or NAS Device]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/123901/the-banana-pi-bpi-w3-lets-you-build-a-powerful-router-or-nas-device/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/123901/the-banana-pi-bpi-w3-lets-you-build-a-powerful-router-or-nas-device/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T15:23:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While it still doesn’t have a price, the new Banana Pi BPI-W3 looks like a dream—especially if you want a custom NAS solution. Not only is it the most powerful Banana Pi router board to date, but it packs impressive specs that you rarely see on a single-board computer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome use subject to restrictions in Dutch schools over data security concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/chrome-use-subject-to-restrictions-in-dutch-schools-over-data-security-concerns/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/chrome-use-subject-to-restrictions-in-dutch-schools-over-data-security-concerns/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T15:12:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ministry of Education in the Netherlands has decided to place a conditional ban on the use of the Chrome OS and Chrome web browser until August 2023 over concerns about data privacy. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Close Are We to Uploading Your Mind?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=814693</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/814693/how-close-are-we-to-uploading-your-mind/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T15:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mind uploading, technically known as “whole brain emulation,” is the idea that you can digitize a brain (and presumably the mind) and have that mind live on within the computer long after the body is dust. But how realistic is this idea?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sydney Butler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating custom keyboard layouts that work across DE's and WM's]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w65t2g/creating_custom_keyboard_layouts_that_work_across/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w65t2g/creating_custom_keyboard_layouts_that_work_across/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T14:51:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Long story short, I only type on the workman keyboard layout, it's the only layout I'm proficient in. Most DE's and Linux installs already have the vanilla English version of it, however, I also type in Spanish and French, so I'd like to have a (preferably GUI) program to remap some of the keys in order to have the special characters unique to those languages. I already did some research and apparently xbindkeys is that sort of program but I can't seem to get it to work, has anyone else had this problem? Anyhow, I'm also looking for alternatives to tackle this problem. Thanks in advance!
 Note: before switching to Linux, I had this problem sorted on Windows 10 with a program called Keytweak, it let me remap keys to my liking, this would be the kind of thing I'm looking for. There was also a Windows layout creator that was very useful.
 Extra question: is there a way to bind ctrl+delete to delete the entire word on Arch/KDE plasma.
    submitted by    /u/basedand-sarahpilled  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel GuC Firmware Fix Submitted For Linux 5.19]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/news/Intel-GuC-Firmware-Fix-Linux</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/news/Intel-GuC-Firmware-Fix-Linux"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T14:29:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sent in on Friday night were this week's batch of Direct Rendering Manager (DRM) driver fixes for Linux 5.19-rc8 due out on Sunday. While usually the late-stage changes tend to be not too eventful, this pull does carry some extra interest since it does fix the Intel GuC firmware breakage I wrote about last week that ended up breaking Alder Lake P graphics on Linux 5.19 unless also upgrading the firmware version...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Massive Microsoft 365 outage caused by faulty ECS deployment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/massive-microsoft-365-outage-caused-by-faulty-ecs-deployment/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/massive-microsoft-365-outage-caused-by-faulty-ecs-deployment/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T14:04:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a preliminary post-incident report, Microsoft has revealed that this week's 5-hour-long Microsoft 365 worldwide outage was triggered by a faulty Enterprise Configuration Service (ECS) deployment that led to cascading failures and availability impact across multiple regions. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Gaming Monitors of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=746224</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/746224/best-gaming-monitors/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is no one-size-fits-all gaming monitor. Some people look for the highest refresh rates for an edge in competitive gaming, others want to bask in high-fidelity visuals. Let’s break down the best monitors for every gamer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You may now buy Windows 11 licenses directly from Microsoft (but shouldn't)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179902</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/07/23/you-may-now-buy-windows-11-licenses-directly-from-microsoft-but-shouldnt/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T13:52:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may purchase Windows 11 Home and Windows 11 Pro licenses directly from Microsoft. While that may sound like the logical path to grab licenses, it is not the best deal that […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post You may now buy Windows 11 licenses directly from Microsoft (but shouldn't) appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What to Look For in a Chromebook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/121726/what-to-look-for-in-a-chromebook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/121726/what-to-look-for-in-a-chromebook/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T13:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re after a simple device that can browse the internet and run basic programs, a Chromebook is the perfect option! Lightweight and budget-friendly, Chromebooks are fantastic for students and frequent travelers. But how do you narrow it down from the plethora of choices?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Chaney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 10 Best Horror Movies to Stream for Free in 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=791392</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/791392/best-free-horror-movies-stream-online/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You don’t have to sign up for a subscription service in order to stream great horror movies. There are numerous free streaming outlets with a range of horror options. Here are the 10 best horror movies to stream for free.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Bell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migliori Tablet-PC 2 in 1 con tastiera removibile]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2017/09/migliori-tablet-con-tastiera-2-in-1-da.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2017/09/migliori-tablet-con-tastiera-2-in-1-da.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T12:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dopo la morte dei netbook una nuova categoria di prodotti ha preso piede per sostituirli: i tablet con tastiera, detti anche PC convertibili o tablet 2 in 1. Questi tablet, oltre ad essere comodi da usare quando vogliamo uno schermo più grande di un semplice smartphone, possono diventare dei veri e propri "piccoli notebook" grazie all'aggiunta di una tastiera (anch'essa di ridotte dimensioni), collegata sia tramite connettori sia tramite Bluetooth.
 Se siamo interessati a questo tipo di prodotto ma non sappiamo quale scegliere, in questa guida vedremo insieme i migliori modelli di tablet con tastiera removibile utilizzando i prodotti disponibili su un sito di e-commerce come Amazon, così da avere una buona garanzia sul prodotto e risparmiare sempre qualcosa rispetto all'acquisto in un nego…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adreno 619 Support Added To Mesa - Enables Fairphone 4 GPU Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/news/Freedreno-Adreno-619</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/news/Freedreno-Adreno-619"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T12:49:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linux 5.20 is adding Qualcomm Adreno 619 GPU support to the MSM DRM/KMS driver and now the Freedreno Gallium3D driver is also enabling that A619 GPU support which in turn enables open-source OpenGL acceleration on devices like the  Fairphone 4...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Laptop Keyboard Not Working After Shutdown]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w62y6b/laptop_keyboard_not_working_after_shutdown/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w62y6b/laptop_keyboard_not_working_after_shutdown/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T12:31:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello. I use an ASUS Q408UG laptop on which I recently installed Arch. I've noticed that whenever I start my laptop from shutdown, the keyboard doesn't work. The keyboard does work in bios and grub. 
 One temporary solution I've found is to plug in a USB keyboard, which works, and reinstall linux-firmware. Once I reboot, the laptop keyboard works again, and will after subsequent reboots, but if I ever shut the laptop down the keyboard stops working again. 
 Could this be a driver related problem? If so, does anyone know which drivers might help? Thanks for your help!
    submitted by    /u/bloodghoul6666  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reinstalling arch linux again keep running into this problem before when i used this command it just would usually skip to asking me another command none of this happend before installing in virtual box.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w62vji/reinstalling_arch_linux_again_keep_running_into/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w62vji/reinstalling_arch_linux_again_keep_running_into/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T12:28:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[i use timedatectl set-ntp true 
 before it would jsut complete and root would ask me for another command now it starts telling me network time syncnorization
 system time set all that jazz and i am stuck on it.
    submitted by    /u/AwabKhan  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dark Mode Is Overrated, and Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=812186</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/812186/dark-mode-is-overrated-and-heres-why/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the last few years, dark mode has become increasingly popular for smartphones, laptops, and tablets. Some people believe that dark mode is always beneficial, but that opinion isn’t backed by science. Here’s why dark mode is overrated.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Restore backlight brightness during initramfs phase.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w61nu0/restore_backlight_brightness_during_initramfs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w61nu0/restore_backlight_brightness_during_initramfs/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T11:18:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is there a way to do it? It gets in my eyes every time I (re)boot my PC.
 I looked at the mkinitcpio hooks and couldn't find anything (mkinitcpio -L)
    submitted by    /u/EmbarrassedActive4  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Tips to Keep Your Tech From Overheating]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=820039</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/820039/7-tips-to-keep-your-tech-from-overheating/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T11:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Summer heatwaves are a hazardous time to be a computer, game console, smartphone, or gadget that produces heat. Here are seven tips that will help your electronics survive the hottest weather.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Upgrade to Docker Compose v2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?post_type=devops&amp;p=803652</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/devops/how-to-upgrade-to-docker-compose-v2/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T10:40:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After almost a year in beta, Docker Compose v2 is generally available as the container management tool’s stable release. Most users should be able to make the switch today. In this guide, we’ll show you how to prepare and apply your upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GNU C Library Finally Adds arc4random Functions For Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/news/GNU-Glibc-arc4random-Functions</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/news/GNU-Glibc-arc4random-Functions"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T09:28:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The arc4random, arc4random_buf, and arc4random_uniform functions have been common on the BSDs for years to provide higher quality random number generation than rand/random and alternative functions. But now as of yesterday the GNU C Library (Glibc) has finally added the arc4random functions for use on Linux!..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KDE Plasma 5.26 Will Start Faster, Many Other KDE Improvements Abound]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/news/More-KDE-Plasma-5.26-July</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/news/More-KDE-Plasma-5.26-July"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T09:09:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even with the summer heat, KDE developers remain very busy working towards Plasma 5.26 later this year as well as the next rounds of KDE Frameworks 5 and KDE application updates...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Are Kubernetes Custom Resource Definitions (CRDs)?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?post_type=devops&amp;p=800688</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/devops/what-are-kubernetes-custom-resource-definitions-crds/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T08:04:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Custom Resource Definitions (CRDs) are Kubernetes API extensions which can define new object types. Pods, ReplicaSets, ConfigMaps, and Ingresses are examples of common built-in resources. CRDs let you add entirely new types to this list, then manage them using familiar Kubernetes tools such as Kubectl.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simple shell script for copying passwords from keepassxc database to clipboard.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w5ybgu/simple_shell_script_for_copying_passwords_from/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w5ybgu/simple_shell_script_for_copying_passwords_from/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T07:48:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is a simple shell script for copying passwords, OTPs, and usernames from a keepassxc database to system clipboard. It uses keepassxc-cli, pass, and rofi. The password of the database is encrypted with user's gpg key. pass is used to decrypt it when user wants to read data from keepassxc database.
 rofi-keepassxc:
 #!/bin/bash KEEPASSXC_PASS_PATH="passwords/misc/keepassxc/main" KEEPASSXC_DATABASE_PATH=$(readlink -f ~/.config/keepassxc/main.kdbx) CLIP_TIMEOUT="45" passCommand() { while getopts "a:e:" opt; do case "$opt" in a) ARGS="$OPTARG" ;; e) ELEMENT="$OPTARG" ;; *) echo "ERROR: incorrect flag!" ;; esac done : "${ARGS=}" COMMAND=" pass ${KEEPASSXC_PASS_PATH} | keepassxc-cli clip ${ARGS} ${KEEPASSXC_DATABASE_PATH} ${secret} ${CLIP_TIMEOUT} & notify-send --icon=dialog-information \"${…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch BTRFS subvolumes partial restricting access from other Linux in general]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w5x9w8/arch_btrfs_subvolumes_partial_restricting_access/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w5x9w8/arch_btrfs_subvolumes_partial_restricting_access/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T06:45:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So I have been playing around with Fedora for quite a while and notice some difference in some implementation.
 ​
 I have noticed before fedora can freely access my Arch root including home btrfs subvolume top level while Arch cannot access it directly. UNLESS, Fedora / drive is mounted by command.
 ​
 mount /dev/sdx3 /mnt -o subvolid=5
 ​
 So I have done same thing on my Arch with BTRFS subvolumes
 ​
 Steps on how to do it:
 ​
 # btrfs subvolume list /
 ​
 find the ID number of @ or / subvolume. In my case was 260
 ​
 # btrfs subvolume set-default 260 /
 ​
 I have tested it and fedora or any other linux cannot freely access my Arch btrfs top-level subvolume unless mounted as above.
 ​
 Hope this helps
    submitted by    /u/Ja-KooLit  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make Docker Compose Wait for Dependency Containers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?post_type=devops&amp;p=800690</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/devops/how-to-make-docker-compose-wait-for-dependency-containers/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T06:02:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This isn’t always good enough though. Some of your containers might have dependencies on each other that break the application if they can’t be fulfilled. In this guide, we’ll show how you can configure your Compose services to accommodate these dependencies, making it possible to start containers in order.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for a utility that can stress CPU and GPU at the same time]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w5wcu6/looking_for_a_utility_that_can_stress_cpu_and_gpu/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w5wcu6/looking_for_a_utility_that_can_stress_cpu_and_gpu/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T05:52:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I need to stress test both of them to see the power draw in linux.
 I have an HP Victus Ryzen 5 5600H and RX5500M laptop. 
 Gaming on Windows make my CPU power go beyond 70 Watts, while stress testing CPU alone in linux only caps at 44 Watts, so I need to stress them both.
    submitted by    /u/B99fanboy  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Guarda cosa ho trovato. Virus di Messenger si diffonde a macchia d'olio]]></title>
        <id>3626|20220723073340</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/social-network-514/guarda-cosa-ho-trovato.-virus-messenger-si-diffonde-macchia-d-olio-3626"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T05:33:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sto ricevendo plurimi messaggi sull'app di Messenger da vari miei contatti. E tutti mi scrivono la stessa cosa: Guarda cosa ho trovato. Seguono due emoticon che ridono e un link che sembra riferirsi ad una foto. Ma fortunatamente, memore di un virus analogo di qualche tempo fa, non cado nella trappola!
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Next Windows 11 delays brute force attacks by default]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179899</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/07/23/next-windows-11-delays-brute-force-attacks-by-default/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T04:51:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft plans to roll out new default settings in the next major Windows 11 release that delay brute force attacks against accounts on the system. Brute-force attacks are commonly used by threat […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Next Windows 11 delays brute force attacks by default appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is it possible to get full disk encryption with archinstall? (dumb question, ik)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w5urr9/is_it_possible_to_get_full_disk_encryption_with/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w5urr9/is_it_possible_to_get_full_disk_encryption_with/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T04:27:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/Amber___yo  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Week in Ransomware - July 22nd 2022 - Attacks abound]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/the-week-in-ransomware-july-22nd-2022-attacks-abound/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/the-week-in-ransomware-july-22nd-2022-attacks-abound/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T03:52:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New ransomware operations continue to be launched this week, with the new Luna ransomware found to be targeting both Windows and VMware ESXi servers. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Need help transforming linux kernel into .efi files]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w5sqay/need_help_transforming_linux_kernel_into_efi_files/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w5sqay/need_help_transforming_linux_kernel_into_efi_files/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T02:43:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am trying to transform my kernel into .efi files using dracut --uefi command however.. it doesnt work.. it stuck at /dev/gpt-auto-root. and throw me to maintenance mode. searching on wiki and google seems doesnt help me because its kinda confusing.. especially when people said "dracut seems workin fine on me" without any instruction how.. my bootloader is refind and i use linux-tkg.. Iam not sure where is the problem.. thank you
    submitted by    /u/JnZann  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trouble installing wine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w5q0n5/trouble_installing_wine/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w5q0n5/trouble_installing_wine/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T00:29:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi guys, so I recently installed arch on my computer and I really need wine but the thing just keeps getting an error because a lot of dependencies couldn't be installed. Based on past experiences, the problem is probably something very silly but I just couldn't figure it out.
 Here's what I did:
 First I tried with pacman
 sudo pacman -Syu
 sudo pacman -S wine
 resolving dependencies...
 warning: cannot resolve "libcap=2.65", a dependency of "lib32-libcap"
 warning: cannot resolve "lib32-libcap", a dependency of "lib32-systemd"
 warning: cannot resolve "lib32-systemd", a dependency of "lib32-dbus"
 warning: cannot resolve "libdbus-1.so=3-32", a dependency of "lib32-libpcap"
 warning: cannot resolve "lib32-libpcap", a dependency of "wine"
 warning: cannot resolve "libcap=2.65", a dependenc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Customize the Menu Bar in macOS]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=504237</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15449260/customize-menu-bar-macos"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Menu Bar is an essential tool for macOS users looking to supercharge their productivity without overcrowding the desktop with too many active windows. Learn how to effortlessly customize the Menu Bar by rearranging items, freeing toggles from Control Center, and adding glanceable info such as battery percentage in a few clicks. Optimizing the Menu Bar to directly cater to your distinct workflow(s) can help you get more done in less time.
   

Content

Rearranging Menu Bar Items
Adding New Items to the Menu Bar 
Quickly Removing Items From the Menu Bar 
Adding Battery Status in the Menu Bar
Frequently Asked Questions 

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Install macOS in VirtualBox
    
Rearranging Menu Bar Items
    
To reorder items in the Menu Bar, hover over a toggle with your cursor. In this tutorial, we are going to move the Wi-Fi button. 
   
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brahm Shank</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FFmpeg 5.1 Released With Many Improvements To This Important Multimedia Project]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/news/FFmpeg-5.1-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/news/FFmpeg-5.1-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T23:43:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FFmpeg 5.1 "Riemann" was released on Friday afternoon as a new feature update to this widely-used, open-source multimedia project for video encode/decode and a variety of other purposes...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bluetooth not working after suspension]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w5ms0f/bluetooth_not_working_after_suspension/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w5ms0f/bluetooth_not_working_after_suspension/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T22:04:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have a laptop and when I boot it the bluetooth works just fine but as soon as I close it and reopen it the bluetooth adapter doesn't get detected anymore. I have the ACPI package, Optimus Manager and this driver (my system info says I have a Realtek 8852AE module for BT and WLAN) installed. This is the output of sudo dmesg | grep -i Bluetooth. I have tried to restart the bluetooth service via sudo systemctl restart bluetooth but that didn't help. Any other ideas? Thanks for reading my post. I also followed the tutorial on the driver's GitHub telling me to set up a script that unloads the module on suspension and reloads it when waking up again. I also saw this entry in the arch wiki but since my adapter is connected via PCI this doesn't work out.
    submitted by    /u/Trqhxrd  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacker selling Twitter account data of 5.4 million users for $30k]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hacker-selling-twitter-account-data-of-54-million-users-for-30k/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hacker-selling-twitter-account-data-of-54-million-users-for-30k/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T22:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter has suffered a data breach after threat actors used a vulnerability to build a database of phone numbers and email addresses belonging to 5.4 million accounts, with the data now up for sale on a hacker forum for $30,000.  [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Recursively Search Directory Names in Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?post_type=devops&amp;p=800682</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/devops/how-to-recursively-search-directory-names-in-linux/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T22:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everything in Linux is stored in directories, and when writing bash scripts, it’s often useful to search for directories by name. Luckily, you can use the find command to recursively search directory names and display matches.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Heddings</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Questa settimana su TLI (23 luglio 2022)]]></title>
        <id>3625|20220723000001</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/newsletter-turbolab.it-1349/questa-settimana-tli-23-luglio-2022-3625"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T22:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Non hai tempo di leggerci tutti i giorni? nessun problema! ecco a te il riepilogo di quanto proposto da TurboLab.it nel corso della settimana in conclusione.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Windows 11 Performance Monitor]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=500321</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15449145/windows-performance-monitor"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re curious about how your computer performs or need to make sure your computer is performing as well as it’s meant to, the Windows Performance Monitor (WPM), sometimes referred to as “Windows Performance Meter,” is an excellent tool for the job. This tutorial shows how to use the Windows 11 Performance Monitor and what the readings mean.
    
Note: the instructions here will work for Windows 10 as well as Windows 11.
   

Content

Before You Use WPM, Consider Task Manager
What Does the Windows Performance Monitor Do?
1. Start Up Windows Performance Monitor
2. Quick Tour of the Performance Monitor
3. Adding Counters to the Performance Monitor
4. Custom Data Collector Sets
5. Running Collector Sets and Getting Reports
6. Real-Time Monitoring
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:Latest Windows 10 Update Problems and How to Fix Them
  ... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sydney Butler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Edit Your Hosts File on Windows, Mac, or Linux]]></title>
        <id>http://www.howtogeek.com/?p=27350</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/howto/27350/beginner-geek-how-to-edit-your-hosts-file/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Occasionally you may need to edit the hosts file on your machine. Your host file might have been edited maliciously in an attack, or as a prank. Alternatively, you may just want to control access to certain websites or control network traffic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christopher Welker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Digital security giant Entrust breached by ransomware gang]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/digital-security-giant-entrust-breached-by-ransomware-gang/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/digital-security-giant-entrust-breached-by-ransomware-gang/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T20:44:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Digital security giant Entrust has confirmed that it suffered a cyberattack where threat actors breached their network and stole data from internal systems. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why You Should Replace Old Surge Protectors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/123840/why-you-should-replace-old-surge-protectors/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/123840/why-you-should-replace-old-surge-protectors/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T20:24:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s nothing better than knowing that your valuable electronics are safe. And surge protectors give you that peace of mind for a very low price—but only if you replace them every few years. While the old surge protectors in your home may seem to function normally, they likely offer zero protection for your electronics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cut Your Summer Electric Bill by Supercooling Your Home]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=814826</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/814826/cut-your-summer-electric-bill-by-supercooling-your-home/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Energy prices are rising and summers aren’t getting any cooler. If you’re looking to save money and stay comfortable this summer, you should consider using a trick called supercooling to keep your house chillier for less.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Fitzpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save 72% on a Meta Portal Video Calling Display]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=404490</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/14526271/facebook-portal-video-calling-display"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If your son or daughter is going off to college in a few weeks, and you want an easy way to connect with them, a Meta Portal Video Calling Display would be a great choice. Get 72% off and check in with your college-bound child, as well as other family and friends. It will make the distance seem a lot shorter.
    
This 10″ HD touchscreen display sits in a black or white frame that would complement any decor in nearly any room and would certainly fit in with a dorm room atmosphere. You can easily place video calls to your student with a Portal. They don’t have to own one, though, as they can also use WhatsApp, Facebook Messenger, or Zoom on their computer or mobile device. But at this price, you can buy one for all your family members.
   
 
   
The smart camera on the Meta Portal Video Calling Display will automatically pan and zoom to keep up with your motion. It will keep up with you no matter where you move and while... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 6 Best Cases For Your New Pixel 6a]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/123614/the-6-best-cases-for-your-new-pixel-6a/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/123614/the-6-best-cases-for-your-new-pixel-6a/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T19:13:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you just bought Google’s affordable new Pixel 6a smartphone, the next thing you’ll want to do is get a case for it. The best Pixel 6a cases will keep it safe from drops, damage, and all of life’s daily hazards while also adding a bit of style or functionality.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Show Surrounding Lines Around Matches With grep for Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?post_type=devops&amp;p=800692</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/devops/how-to-show-surrounding-lines-around-matches-with-grep-for-linux/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T19:03:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[grep is a search utility for finding strings and patterns in files and console input. By default, it prints the line that contains the match, but it’s also useful to print out the preceding lines around a match for context.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Heddings</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“AirDrop” for Windows: How to Use Nearby Sharing in Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=819931</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/819931/airdrop-for-windows-how-to-use-nearby-sharing-in-windows-11/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T19:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you love the ease of sharing files wirelessly on a Mac with AirDrop, you might be delighted to learn that you can do something similar in Windows 11 with Nearby Sharing, which comes built-in. Here’s how to use it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Bring Your Own Vulnerable Driver” Attacks Are Breaking Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=820374</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/820374/bring-your-own-vulnerable-driver-attacks-are-breaking-windows/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T18:56:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Digital security is a constant cat-and-mouse game, with new vulnerabilities being discovered just as quickly (if not faster) as older problems are fixed. Lately, “Bring Your Own Vulnerable Driver” attacks are becoming a complex problem for Windows PCs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apache OpenOffice 4.1.13 Released For Those Not On The LibreOffice Train]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/news/Apache-OpenOffice-4.1.13</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/news/Apache-OpenOffice-4.1.13"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T18:30:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's been nearly 12 years since LibreOffice forked from OpenOffice.org following Oracle's acquisition of Sun Microsystems and then the subsequent creation of Apache OpenOffice in 2011. While LibreOffice has become the dominant open-source office suite, Apache OpenOffice continues limping along and today marks its v4.1.13 release...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can I use an Arch linux system to use arch-chroot to chroot into a NON Arch linux system?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w5hjaj/can_i_use_an_arch_linux_system_to_use_archchroot/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w5hjaj/can_i_use_an_arch_linux_system_to_use_archchroot/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T18:22:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Im looking to do a reinstall of my computer.
 My goal partition would be as such. 
  
EFI 
 Recovery partition (Arch Linux minimal install) 
 Encrypted partition (BTRFS subvols for Arch,Artix,Gentoo,etc) 
  
I know the arch-chroot command we use in arch is different than the basic chroot command used in gentoo for instance. I believe the archchroot mounts /dev and some other stuff as well. 
 I was wondering if I can use this archchroot command to chroot into a non systemd and non pacman distro such as artix,gentoo,void etc. 
 ​
 ​
 ​
 Somewhat related question. 
 Would it be worthwhile to instead of having to re-enter the boot loader to switch systems you simply boot into a base distro and then just chroot into the other distros? Instead of using a boot loader you have a chroot loader? Or is this a stupid idea?
    submitted by    /u/NoCSForYou  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do You Need a Cleaner App for Your Mac?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=805940</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/805940/do-you-need-a-cleaner-app-for-your-mac/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T18:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re looking for a one-click solution to delete junk files and potentially speed up macOS, you might be tempted to buy a cleaner app. So what exactly do these apps do, and are they worth your time and money?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11: torna il suono all'avvio del sistema operativo]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-11-torna-il-suono-all-avvio-del-sistema-operativo_24806</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-11-torna-il-suono-all-avvio-del-sistema-operativo_24806"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T17:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ci avete fatto caso? Se avete installato Windows 11 o aggiornato al nuovo sistema operativo Microsoft a ogni avvio viene riprodotto un suono, immediatamente prima della schermata di logon.Era da qualche versione di Windows che i suoni al'avvio del sistema operativo non si sentivano più. Con un certo 'effetto nostalgia' in questo video su YouTube potete ascoltare tutti i suoi scelti da Microsoft al boot di Windows.Sebbene nel video si possano ascoltare, per impostazione predefinita Windows 8.x (Windows 8.1 sarà ritirato a inizio 2023) e Windows 10 non riproducono alcun effetto sono all'avvio. I suoni sono comunque attivabili su richiesta anche in questi sistemi operativi.Con il lancio di Windows 11, di default il sistema riproduce un jingle di pochi istanti.La curiosità è che nelle attuali versioni stabili di Windows 11 quell'effetto sonoro è salvato sotto forma di file audio con un bitrate di 2304 kbps mentre con il futuro Windows 11 22H2 sarà ridotto a 1536 kbps, esattamente come la maggior parte dei file WAV di sistema usati nello storico e indimenticabile Windows 95.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SonicWall: Patch critical SQL injection bug immediately]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/sonicwall-patch-critical-sql-injection-bug-immediately/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/sonicwall-patch-critical-sql-injection-bug-immediately/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T17:01:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SonicWall has published a security advisory today to warn of a critical SQL injection flaw impacting the GMS (Global Management System) and Analytics On-Prem products. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Where Are Google Chrome Bookmarks Stored on My Computer?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=819125</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/819125/where-are-google-chrome-bookmarks-stored-on-my-computer/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T17:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Chrome can keep your bookmarks in a few different places. There’s a bookmarks bar, the “Other Bookmarks” folder, and a sidebar. The bookmarks are also stored in a folder on your Windows PC or Mac.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trasferimento dati negli Stati Uniti: perché il caso Google Analytics è solo la punta dell'iceberg]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Trasferimento-dati-negli-Stati-Uniti-perche-il-caso-Google-Analytics-e-solo-la-punta-dell-iceberg_24805</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Trasferimento-dati-negli-Stati-Uniti-perche-il-caso-Google-Analytics-e-solo-la-punta-dell-iceberg_24805"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T16:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pur essendo in qualche modo attesa, ha destato grande scalpore la decisione del Garante Privacy del 9 giugno 2022 con cui di fatto è stato dichiarato inaccettabile l'uso di Google Analytics, almeno in una specifica configurazione.A margine del provvedimento, il Garante ha ritenuto opportuno richiamare l'attenzione di tutti i gestori italiani di siti Web, pubblici e privati, rispetto all'illiceità dei trasferimenti di dati effettuati verso gli Stati Uniti invitando allo stesso tempo a verificare la conformità con la normativa in materia di protezione dei dati personali degli strumenti utilizzati, ponendo l'accento in particolare su a Google Analytics e su altri servizi analoghi.
Il provvedimento del Garante Privacy riguarda Google Analytics ma le conseguenze sono dirompenti
 Sebbene si parli con grande enfasi di Google Analytics, il problema non deriva solamente da questo servizio bensì da tutti quelli che pongono in essere un trasferimento di dati verso l'estero.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wink Hubs Will Rise From the Dead "In the Coming Days"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/123825/wink-hubs-will-rise-from-the-dead-in-the-coming-days/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/123825/wink-hubs-will-rise-from-the-dead-in-the-coming-days/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T16:53:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a nearly month-long outage, Wink is emailing customers to say that it’s servers are almost back online. You can expect your Wink Hub to regain functionality “in the coming days.” Still, Wink hasn’t explained the reason for this outage, and its continued lack of transparency has turned faithful customers into hardcore haters.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come guadagnare spazio sulla memoria dello smartphone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2013/10/guadagnare-spazio-memoria-su-smartphone.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2013/10/guadagnare-spazio-memoria-su-smartphone.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T16:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Qualsiasi cellulare utilizziamo, ci ritroveremo (prima o poi) davanti al problema dello spazio esaurito, specie sui modelli che dispongono di meno di 128 GB di memoria interna. Tra i due sistemi operativi più diffusi Android è il più leggero ma viene installato anche in smartphone economici, con memoria limitata.
 Di contro l'iPhone non è espandibile con una microSD quindi dovremo farci bastare la memoria interna; su Android la micro SD (dove disponibile) va bene solo per tenere foto e musica (si possono anche spostare alcune app ma non tutte).
 Se bisogna per forza cancellare qualcosa, il miglior modo di guadagnare spazio sullo smartphone è sfruttare i servizi cloud che salvano dati online. Vediamo qui i principali e gratuiti sistemi per salvare online foto, video, musica e come risparmia…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NASA's Artemis I Mega Moon Rocket Launch Teased In New Video]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/123822/nasas-artemis-i-mega-moon-rocket-launch-teased-in-new-video/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/123822/nasas-artemis-i-mega-moon-rocket-launch-teased-in-new-video/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T16:19:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NASA recently confirmed its Artemis I mega-rocket could embark on its mission to space on August 29, September 2, or September 5, depending on the conditions. Now, NASA released an official rocket launch teaser video giving us a glimpse of what to expect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the wc Command in Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=812441</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/812441/wc-command-in-linux/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T16:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Counting the number of lines, words, and bytes in a file is useful, but the real flexibility of the Linux wc command comes from working with other commands. Let’s take a look.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKay</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox Presents: A nerdcore rap artist defying expectations]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.mozilla.org/?p=69408</id>
        <link href="https://blog.mozilla.org/en/internet-culture/firefox-presents-nerdcore-rap-lex-the-lexicon-artist/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T15:53:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As far as music subgenres go, nerdcore hip-hop wouldn’t exist in its current form without the internet. Those who create it — self-proclaimed nerds who rap about video games, science fiction or just everyday life as a misfit — record music at home, collaborate via web file transfers and find cheerleaders out of strangers online.  […]
The post Firefox Presents: A nerdcore rap artist defying expectations appeared first on The Mozilla Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kristina Bravo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Crafty Raspberry Pi Pico Hack Adds Four New GPIO Pins]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/123814/this-crafty-raspberry-pi-pico-hack-adds-four-new-gpio-pins/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/123814/this-crafty-raspberry-pi-pico-hack-adds-four-new-gpio-pins/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T15:52:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you need more GPIO for your Pi Pico project? A creative keyboard maker named HealthyCabinet found a way to unlock up to four new GPIO pins on the Raspberry Pi Pico or Pi Pico W. It requires a bit of soldering work, but nonetheless, it’s a surprisingly simple modification.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Backtracks on Android App Permissions After Outcry]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=820320</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/820320/google-backtracks-on-android-app-permissions-after-outcry/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T15:50:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever since app permissions were introduced in Android, the Google Play Store has listed all requested permissions on the listings for every app. Google started to hide the permissions section, but now the company is backtracking.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RX6700 Fans Not Spinning?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w5dofa/rx6700_fans_not_spinning/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w5dofa/rx6700_fans_not_spinning/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T15:39:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It seems the fans on my RX6700 aren't spinning. Psensor reports 0RPM on the fans, and 102C on the GPU. Is there a way I can force them to spin? amdguid and amdgpu-fan don't seem to be working (or I'm doing it wrong, which is entirely possible).
 When I'm running Far Cry 6, everything is fine, and all of the sudden I get like 5 FPS, and it's clear something is really struggling. My CPU averages 65-70C, but the utilization jumps from 60% down to 25% when this happens, so maybe it's a CPU thing (i7-6800k), but with GPU temps that high, I have to wonder if it's a GPU thing.
    submitted by    /u/vwagenjetta  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Customize Your Linux Terminal Prompt Using Starship]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=507517</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15448704/customize-linux-terminal-prompt-using-starship"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starship is a cross-shell prompt build using rust language. This is a very minimal and blazingly fast terminal prompt. The key reason for its popularity is its customizability. You can easily customize it using a TOML config file. If you are shifting to a different device or different shell, just move the config file to the appropriate location, and automatically your beautiful-looking shell becomes ready.
   

Content

Prerequisite 
Install Starship
Customize Starship
How to Add Starship Presets 
How to uninstall starship?
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Resize and Optimize Images From the Linux Terminal
    
Prerequisite 
    
Before using Starship, you need to install a nerd font on your computer. Nerd font is a beautiful blend of font and icons. Go to Nerd Fonts and download your favorite one. If you can’t make up... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hrishikesh Pathak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Celestiq Is Cadillac's Most Luxurious EV You Can't Have]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/123807/the-celestiq-is-cadillacs-most-luxurious-ev-you-cant-have/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/123807/the-celestiq-is-cadillacs-most-luxurious-ev-you-cant-have/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T15:23:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a year of teasers and releasing a few images back in June, GM unveiled its new Cadillac Celestiq ultra-luxury sedan today, and it’s rather stunning. The $300,000 hand-crafted electric vehicle will go into limited production sometime in 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Atlassian: Confluence hardcoded password was leaked, patch now!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/atlassian-confluence-hardcoded-password-was-leaked-patch-now/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/atlassian-confluence-hardcoded-password-was-leaked-patch-now/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T15:05:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Australian software firm Atlassian warned customers to immediately patch a critical vulnerability that provides remote attackers with hardcoded credentials to log into unpatched Confluence Server and Data Center servers. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does It Matter Where My VPN Is Based?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=813030</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/813030/does-it-matter-where-my-vpn-is-based/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T15:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VPN providers love to tout the location they’re based in as if that’s a big deal. They’ll often cite the amazing privacy laws of the country they’re headquartered in, claiming that this acts as a second layer of protection on top of their other measures, like not keeping logs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fergus O'Sullivan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Now Pre-Order the Pixel 6a and Pixel Buds Pro]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/123792/you-can-now-pre-order-the-pixel-6a-and-pixel-buds-pro/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/123792/you-can-now-pre-order-the-pixel-6a-and-pixel-buds-pro/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T14:52:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can now pre-order Google’s excellent Pixel 6a and the Pixel Buds Pro—Google’s first wireless earbuds with ANC. Both devices ship July 28th, and notably, Google has some awesome trade-in offers for the Pixel 6a smartphone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wifi usb dongle seems to cap speed at around 50 Mbps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w5c6yn/wifi_usb_dongle_seems_to_cap_speed_at_around_50/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w5c6yn/wifi_usb_dongle_seems_to_cap_speed_at_around_50/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T14:36:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi all,
 I connect to the internet through a Wifi USB dongle. In particular, the one I use is a TP-link TL-WN823N V2.
 This website (http://en.techinfodepot.shoutwiki.com/w … -WN823N_v2) says that its speed is up to 300 Mbps.
 Previously I had DSL with speed of 50 Mbps download and 10 Mpbps upload. Today I got it upgraded to fibre with speeds of 300/100. Every other device in my house, when doing a speed test, shows those speeds, but this computer, which connects with that wifi dongle, shows 50 download / 60 upload. Initially I thought it'd be the dongle, but as said it is rated at 300. And from 300 to 50 there's a massive jump. The signal strength is "good". Doing a speed test using my phone from exactly the same spot, it shows 300/100.
 lsusb -v shows the following information:
 Bus 001 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft warns that new Windows updates may break printing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-warns-that-new-windows-updates-may-break-printing/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-warns-that-new-windows-updates-may-break-printing/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft warned that starting with this week's optional preview updates, temporary mitigation provided one year ago to address Windows Server printing issues on non-compliant devices will be removed, potentially breaking printing. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Meet Is Bringing Back a Hangouts Feature]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=820292</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/820292/google-meet-is-bringing-back-a-hangouts-feature/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T14:26:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Meet is the Zoom-like video conferencing service from Google. The predecessor to Meet used to allow streaming calls to YouTube, and now Google is bringing the functionality back.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IOGEAR Dock Pro Review: Maximize Your Setup Anywhere]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/122965/iogear-dock-pro-review/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/122965/iogear-dock-pro-review/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T14:24:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most annoying parts about working from a laptop computer is the limitations that occur due to its size. External accessories help, but what do you do with all of the peripherals you need to hook up? You can turn to a docking station such as the IOGEAR Dock Pro USB-C 6 in 1 Dock Stand!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Megan Glosson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>