<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-07-26T02:21:22.862Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CosmicStrand UEFI malware found in Gigabyte, ASUS motherboards]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cosmicstrand-uefi-malware-found-in-gigabyte-asus-motherboards/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cosmicstrand-uefi-malware-found-in-gigabyte-asus-motherboards/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T01:37:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese-speaking hackers have been using since at least 2016 malware that lies virtually undetected in the firmware images for some motherboards, one of the most persistent threats commonly known as a UEFI rootkit. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Ilascu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Test Your Webcam in Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=506072</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15453624/test-webcam-windows"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your webcam needs to be set up and configured for video calls, so it’s important to test it beforehand, especially the first time you use it. It can be easily tested with the built-in camera app, but if you’re using a third-party video-chatting application, it would be best to test the webcam using that same app. This tutorial shows you how to test your webcam in both situations.
   

Content

How to Test Your Webcam Using the Camera App
1. Google Meet
2. Skype
3. Zoom
4. Slack
5. Discord
Customize Privacy Settings in Windows
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Fix Webcam or Camera Not Working in Windows
    
How to Test Your Webcam Using the Camera App
    
The built-in camera app is the most convenient method to test the webcam and is easy to use. Follow... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Saurav Dey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I keep having keyring errors, and I have absolutely idea what to do with them (beginner user) [steamos]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w846y0/i_keep_having_keyring_errors_and_i_have/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w846y0/i_keep_having_keyring_errors_and_i_have/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T23:51:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever since I started to use Arch, 50% of my terminal installs have looked like this:
 -I type in "sudo pacman -S [whatever package I need]"
 -I get asked if I should "Import PGP key [name] [email]?", I say yes
 -I get an error of this structure:
 error: lib32-glib-networking: signature from "[name] <email>" is unknown trust
 :: File /var/cache/pacman/pkg/lib32-glib-networking-2.70.1-1-x86_64.pkg.tar.zst is corrupted (invalid or corrupted package (PGP signature)).
 Do you want to delete it? [Y/n]
 No matter what I say here, the packages don't install.
 Truth be told, I have absolutely no idea what a keyring is. I have never gotten an error like this in other linux distros. I have tried to search it up on ArchWiki, but as a newbie to all things programming-related, I have absolutely no idea what they're talking about.
 Can anyone please explain to me what a keyring is, why it's needed for installing packages and how to fix these errors?
    submitted by    /u/alekdmcfly  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Error when installing GRUB]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w81s7t/error_when_installing_grub/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w81s7t/error_when_installing_grub/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T22:08:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[grub-install: error: failed to get canonical path of `/boot/grub'. When running grub-install --target=x86_64-efi --efi-directory=/boot
    submitted by    /u/Pinjataguy1  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come avviare Firefox in modalità risoluzione problemi]]></title>
        <id>3629|20220726000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/browser-455/come-avviare-firefox-modalita-risoluzione-problemi-3629"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Come Windows ha la sua modalità provvisoria, anche Firefox ha qualcosa di simile che ci permette di avviare il browser con funzioni ridotte, quando non si riesce ad utilizzarlo o a navigare correttamente per qualsiasi motivo, si tratta della Modalità risoluzione problemi. In questa modalità vengono disattivati i temi, tutte le estensioni, che spesso e volentieri sono la fonte del problema, e alcune personalizzazioni.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Install Android Studio and SDK Tools in Windows]]></title>
        <id>http://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=96684</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/11099254/install-android-sdk-in-windows"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Android SDK (Software Development Kit) is a large and powerful tool that’s essential if you’re looking to get into Android app development. It serves a number of other purposes, too, such as using the command line to sideload apps onto your Android phone.
    
There are quite a few details and things to consider when installing the Android SDK on your Windows PC. The following guide should help you wade through the process.
   

Content

Install the Latest Version of Java
Install SDK Command Line
Getting Started With SDK Command Line
Install Android Studio
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Install Google Play Store on Windows 11
    
Install the Latest Version of Java
    
If you don’t want to use Android Studio and just want the Android SDK command line version, then you’ll need to first download... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexandra Arici</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ssd with arch installation that was once removable medium doesn't work after inserted into ssd slot.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w80n6t/ssd_with_arch_installation_that_was_once/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w80n6t/ssd_with_arch_installation_that_was_once/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T21:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi,
 months ago I have installed arch on my previous laptop's ssd and have been using it in an ssd enclosure as an external ssd alongside my laptop which has Windows in its internal ssd. Because my laptop happens to have two ssd slots (one of which is unoccupied) I wanted to take the arch ssd out of the enclosure and into my laptops second ssd slot. My expectation is to use both windows and arch in a dual-boot manner but without the disadvantages of dual-boot (two seperate ssd's: lesser chance of things going wrong, not tight on space, etc.). 
 Yesterday I have opened up my laptop for the first time and installed the arch ssd into the empty slot and put the laptop back together. When I start the laptop, I can choose between arch and windows but when I boot arch, the following error occurs: 
 "ERROR: device ‘UUID=<device\_uuid>’ not found. Skipping fsck"
 I know that this error is occuring because the UUID is different now that it is in an ssd slot instead of being connected by USB. So, naturally I have to somehow edit the UUID that the OS searches for when booting. But I just couldn't figure out how to and was unsuccessful with finding similar cases in the internet forums. 
 As a result, I'm here, asking for your help.
    submitted by    /u/Free_Transition_4746  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why I Left Google Maps For Waze]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/124008/why-i-left-google-maps-for-waze/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/124008/why-i-left-google-maps-for-waze/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T21:17:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to maps and navigation, you probably want something that gets you from point A to B as quickly as possible and avoids traffic, police, or accidents. And while there are many options available, I switched from Google Maps to Waze this year, and I’m not switching back.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cant do sudo. Password doesnt work]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w80izl/cant_do_sudo_password_doesnt_work/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w80izl/cant_do_sudo_password_doesnt_work/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T21:16:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So basically if i try to do sudo su or literally any sudo command it says the password is wrong. But i know im typing in the right password and that its correct, i even followed this tutorial and used the second method. I rebooted and still it just says wrong password. Does anyone have any clue what could be happening?
    submitted by    /u/Sigillum_Dei  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does the Length of a USB Cable Affect Charging?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=810652</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/810652/does-usb-cable-length-affect-charging/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From smartphones to laptops, we charge multiple devices each day, and many of them use a USB cable for delivering power. But if you use a cable with more length, are you risking longer charge times? Here’s everything you need to know.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gaurav Shukla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Splash Screen Animation on Arch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w80308/splash_screen_animation_on_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w80308/splash_screen_animation_on_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T20:58:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have 2 seperate animations that I want to play while my PC is starting: one during boot and one just before or just after the display manager login. I have already figured out the boot animation using Plymouth, but I can't seem to get the other animation working. Does anybody know how this can be done? I prefer if the animation is played just before the login, however it would also work if it's played like a KDE splash screen after login.
 Note: This must work on Arch and it shouldn't depend on a specific desktop environment.
    submitted by    /u/victorfloyd  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Now (Officially) Buy a Windows 11 Key From Microsoft]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=820871</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/820871/you-can-now-officially-buy-a-windows-11-key-from-microsoft/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T20:43:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 has been available for almost a full year, but surprisingly, it hasn’t been officially available to purchase as a digital product key from Microsoft. Now, that has finally changed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Turn Yourself Into a Real LEGO with the Official Minifigure Factory]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/124028/turn-yourself-into-a-real-lego-with-the-official-minifigure-factory/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/124028/turn-yourself-into-a-real-lego-with-the-official-minifigure-factory/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T20:31:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve ever dreamed of becoming a LEGO minifig, it’s time to pull out your credit card. The LEGO website now features a Minifigure Factory that lets you customize and order a LEGO minifig for just $12. It’s still in beta, but it’s already a load of fun.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Device Permission issues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w7z6xs/device_permission_issues/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w7z6xs/device_permission_issues/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T20:21:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am working with a Raspberry Pi Pico micro controller. When it is connected, it is supposed to show up as a mass storage device. It does not do this. 
 It works with picotool when run as root but gives a error otherwise.. Picotool is the software used to connect and upload to them form the command line. 
 The error I get from picotool when it is not root is "Device at bus 1, address 57 appears to be a RP2040 device in BOOTSEL mode, but picotool was unable to connect. Maybe try 'sudo' or check your permissions."
 ​
 My device shows up with lsusb. 
 ​
 Anyone know how to change the permissions so my non-root account can access it?
    submitted by    /u/BoguesUser  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Find Archived Emails in Gmail]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=660347</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/660347/how-to-find-archived-emails-in-gmail/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deleting emails from your Gmail account is final — they’re lost forever once you empty your trash folder. If you want to hide emails, rather than delete them, you can archive the messages instead. This allows you to find and retrieve the emails at a later date.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Stockton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save $80 on Bose QuietComfort Noise-Cancelling Earbuds]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=440864</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/14874198/bose-quietcomfort-noise-cancelling-earbuds"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enjoy your tunes this summer, whether you’re out for a run, enjoying a peaceful day in the sun, or even relaxing at home. Get the Bose QuietComfort Noise-Cancelling Earbuds, with noise cancellation, great acoustics, and a long battery life. Take $80 off in the process.
    
These earbuds have the popular noise-cancellation feature as well as the Transparency Mode that allow you to still hear and keep up with what’s happening around you. The acoustic architecture of the earbuds allows you to listen to your music, podcasts, videos, and games with a crisp, balanced sound, thanks to Volume-Optimized Active EQ.
   
 
   
The Bose QuietComfort Noise-Cancellin’g Earbuds handle both sides of their name. While the noise cancellation handles the quiet part, the StayHear Max ear tips tackle the comfort. The earbuds ship with three sizes of silicone ear tips to ensure you get a secure fit. The QuietComfort are IPx4-rated as well to withstand sweat, water, and some nasty weather conditions.
    
The touch controls on the earbuds are as easy as tap, swipe,... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFL’s New Streaming Service Can’t Replace Cable TV Yet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=820784</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/820784/nfls-new-streaming-service-cant-replace-cable-tv-yet/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T19:22:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re probably all feeling some burnout from the ocean of streaming services currently available, but just in case you need one more, the National Football League has launched its own service called NFL+.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Microsoft Sway]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=818463</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/818463/how-to-use-sway/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T19:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you a Microsoft Office user who’s interested in quickly creating a web-based presentation, interactive report, or personal portfolio? PowerPoint can be intimidating to learn and put to use, so consider using the lighter alternative, Microsoft Sway.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Install Pamac GUI Package Manager in Arch Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w7wxhb/how_to_install_pamac_gui_package_manager_in_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w7wxhb/how_to_install_pamac_gui_package_manager_in_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T18:51:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/ConversationOk7357  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anker's New GaNPrime Chargers Come In Some Wild Form Factors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/124005/ankers-new-ganprime-chargers-come-in-some-wild-form-factors/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/124005/ankers-new-ganprime-chargers-come-in-some-wild-form-factors/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T18:48:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As if crazy-fast charging wasn’t enough, Anker’s new line of GaN charges come in some of the most bizarre form factors imaginable. And I mean that in a good way—if you’ve ever wanted a wireless charging power strip or a wall wart that turns into a portable battery, you’ll go crazy for this stuff.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Source code for Rust-based info-stealer released on hacker forums]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/source-code-for-rust-based-info-stealer-released-on-hacker-forums/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/source-code-for-rust-based-info-stealer-released-on-hacker-forums/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T18:30:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A malware author released the source code of their info-stealer for free on hacking forums earlier this month, and security analysts already report observing several samples being deployed in the wild. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PREEMPT_RT Might Be Ready To Finally Land In Linux 5.20]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/news/520-Maybe-Real-Time-PREEMPT_RT</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/news/520-Maybe-Real-Time-PREEMPT_RT"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T18:30:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After years in the works, the "PREEMPT_RT" support for building a real-time Linux kernel might finally be mainlined for the upcoming Linux 5.20 cycle if the last few remaining bits are reviewed/signed-off on in time for next week's merge window...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NsCDE 2.2 Released As Retro Desktop Inspired By Unix's CDE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/news/NsCDE-2.2-Desktop-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/news/NsCDE-2.2-Desktop-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T18:13:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NsCDE 2.2 has been released as the newest feature version of the "Not so Common Desktop Environment" that takes its inspiration from the CDE desktop once common with Unix workstations...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to require strong passwords on your shared Windows PC]]></title>
        <id>8b96a804-156c-4e95-9819-cafe50e26366</id>
        <link href="https://www.zdnet.com/article/how-to-require-strong-passwords-on-your-shared-windows-pc/#ftag=RSSbaffb68"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T18:05:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can make sure that everyone who uses a shared Windows PC at your home or business creates a password that can't easily be cracked.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest stories for ZDNet in Windows</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add Months to a Date in Microsoft Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=812297</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/812297/how-to-add-months-to-a-date-in-microsoft-excel/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T18:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to see what date it will be after you’ve a certain number of months have passed? Using Microsoft Excel’s EDATE function, you can add (or subtract) months to a specific date in your spreadsheets. Here’s how to use it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Your Windows 11 Start Menu Broken? Microsoft Is Fixing It]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=820755</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/820755/is-your-windows-11-start-menu-broken-microsoft-is-fixing-it/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T17:47:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft is working on many improvements in Windows 11’s Start Menu and taskbar for future updates, but in the meantime, the company accidentally broke the Start Menu on some people’s PCs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grub No Space Left on device]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w7vbwj/grub_no_space_left_on_device/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w7vbwj/grub_no_space_left_on_device/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T17:47:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do I clean out my EFI partition? It somehow filled up when I mounted it wrong a few times after installation...
    submitted by    /u/chikaorange  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFL+ Leaves Your TV Out of Its Streaming Service]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/124001/nfl-leaves-your-tv-out-of-its-streaming-service/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/124001/nfl-leaves-your-tv-out-of-its-streaming-service/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T17:43:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier this year, we reported on the NFL’s plans to eliminate its free out-of-market and primetime streaming options on Yahoo! Sports and other apps and replace them with a paid service. Today, the “Shield” officially announced and launched NFL+, its first streaming service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finecam Review: Webcam Software for iPhone and Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=505000</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15453233/finecam-webcam-review"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T17:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Webcams have experienced a massive rise in use over the last 4 years, thanks to the increase in remote working during the pandemic. But many of us are still conducting business and having meetings over the Internet. To be more ecological, you can use software to create a “webcam” instead of buying another device. In this review we examine Finecam, software which helpfully turns any old iPhones (or new ones for that matter) into handy webcams for your Zoom, Skype, OBS, YouTube or other video calling or live streaming adventures.
    
This is a sponsored article and was made possible by Fineshare. The actual contents and opinions are the sole views of the author who maintains editorial independence even when a post is sponsored. 
    
Finecam: Virtual Camera Assistant
    
Finecam is a software tool, which when teamed with an iOS client on your iPhone, turns the iPhone easily and quickly into an additional or even main webcam for any software that can access a camera. You can do this either with Wi-Fi or with a USB-to-Lightning cable.
   
 Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phil South</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come trasferire foto da iPhone al PC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2019/01/come-trasferire-foto-da-iphone-al-pc.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2019/01/come-trasferire-foto-da-iphone-al-pc.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T17:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Con un iPhone possiamo ottenere delle belle foto e di fatto rimpiazzare del tutto le fotocamere digitali compatte, visto che il telefono è sempre a portata di mano in tasca o in borsa quindi possiamo scattare subito in pochi secondi.
 L'unico problema è che le fotografie e le immagini ricevute via chat o via Facebook occupano spazio nella memoria che, prima o poi, si riempie fino ad esaurirsi. Qualsiasi telefono si utilizza, anche fosse il più costoso e con la memoria interna più grande, bisogna sempre scaricare le foto da qualche parte, in modo da poterle conservare al sicuro, liberare la memoria e poterne fare di nuove.
 Nella guida che segue vi mostreremo tutti i metodi per trasferire foto da iPhone a PC utilizzando i metodi di caricamento più comodi ed efficaci (sincronizzazione cloud,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Rotate Your PC’s Screen on Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=819580</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/819580/how-to-rotate-your-pcs-screen-on-windows-11/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T17:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 supports rotating your screen just about any way you want it. If you’ve got an extra monitor you want to use in portrait mode, it can be especially useful. Here are the easiest ways to change your screen orientation in Windows 11.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Lewis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Chrome is blocking all downloads from Portable Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179921</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/07/25/google-chrome-is-blocking-all-downloads-from-portable-apps/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T16:55:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Chrome is blocking all downloads from the third-party website Portable Apps currently and returning "dangerous" as the reason for that. Portable Apps is a popular destination for downloading Windows applications that […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Google Chrome is blocking all downloads from Portable Apps appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[About Renpy outdate package.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w7tihe/about_renpy_outdate_package/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w7tihe/about_renpy_outdate_package/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T16:35:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi there.
 Forgive me if this is a stupid question, I'm still a bit of a noob.
 Does anyone know why in the Arch repositories, Renpy is still version 7.4.11?
 According to the Renpy page, that version is from December 2, 2021.
 Currently the latest version is 8.0.1 and precisely in this they included new features that I would need for my project.
 Does anyone know something?
    submitted by    /u/Seiyokuma  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An AI-powered research tool for learning about and finding free resources on Arch Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w7t5ph/an_aipowered_research_tool_for_learning_about_and/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w7t5ph/an_aipowered_research_tool_for_learning_about_and/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T16:20:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[​
 Generating an Arch Linux learning map on the Albera app
 Hi! We're Albera, a research engine that aims to save users a bunch of time and effort when trying to learn online.
 Using AI, Albera generates learning roadmaps on any topic (like the one above on Arch Linux), which are then populated with free resources (articles, courses, videos, blog posts, etc), allowing for a structured, efficient, and distraction-free learning experience.
 We've recently launched an iOS app, and we're hoping you guys can try it out and share your thoughts with us (using the platform and the app also helps train the AI to provide better results). Thanks!
    submitted by    /u/albera_com  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It's Not Just You: The Xbox Series X/S Are Booting Way Faster]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/123992/its-not-just-you-the-xbox-series-x-s-are-booting-way-faster/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/123992/its-not-just-you-the-xbox-series-x-s-are-booting-way-faster/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T16:17:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several members of the Xbox Insider test program have noticed significantly faster boot-up times on the Xbox Series X and S, and now, a Microsoft employee has confirmed the change. The company cut the start time by more than half, letting gamers get into the action faster than ever.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers exploited PrestaShop zero-day to breach online stores]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-exploited-prestashop-zero-day-to-breach-online-stores/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-exploited-prestashop-zero-day-to-breach-online-stores/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T16:16:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers are targeting websites using the PrestaShop platform, leveraging a previously unknown vulnerability chain to perform code execution and potentially steal customers' payment information. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung's Upcoming Foldables Could Get a Flippin' Price Hike]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/123987/samsungs-upcoming-foldables-could-get-a-flippin-price-hike/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/123987/samsungs-upcoming-foldables-could-get-a-flippin-price-hike/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T16:09:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung will reveal the upcoming Galaxy Z Fold 4 and Flip 4 smartphones in just two weeks. But customers hoping for a deal may be disappointed—new leaks indicate that these phones are more expensive than their predecessors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Google Slides Features for Eye-Catching Presentations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=811907</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/811907/best-google-slides-features/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T16:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Assembling a professional slideshow can be intimidating if you don’t feel creative or artistic. But that doesn’t mean you can’t make an appealing and successful presentation. Google Slides provides features to help you design an attractive slideshow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft issues emergency fix for broken Windows 11 start menu]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-issues-emergency-fix-for-broken-windows-11-start-menu/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-issues-emergency-fix-for-broken-windows-11-start-menu/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T16:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has addressed a known issue that was causing the start menu on some Windows 11 to malfunction after installing recent Windows updates. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Docs Is Getting Better on Android Tablets & Foldables]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=820430</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/820430/google-docs-is-getting-better-on-android-tablets-foldables/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T16:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following years of neglect, Google is finally starting to improve its apps on the best Android tablets and folding phones. Several new features are now coming to Google Docs on Android specifically for large devices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Play Offers Savings to Celebrate Its 10th Anniversary]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=820673</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/820673/google-play-offers-savings-to-celebrate-its-10th-anniversary/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T16:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Play is the one-stop shop for apps, games, movies, TV shows, and other digital content on Android. Now the store is officially 10 years old, and Google is celebrating the occasion with a deal and a new logo.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Play Store Offers 10x the Rewards Points for Its Anniversary]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/123970/google-play-store-offers-10x-the-rewards-points-for-its-anniversary/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/123970/google-play-store-offers-10x-the-rewards-points-for-its-anniversary/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T16:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Exactly one decade ago, Google transformed its Android Market into the modern Play Store. And to celebrate this anniversary, Google is offering 10x the Play Points rewards for all purchases. The company is also updating Play Store’s logo, which now matches the color scheme of other Google app logos.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why a MacBook Isn’t the “Best Laptop” for Everyone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=820687</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/820687/why-a-macbook-isnt-the-best-laptop-for-everyone/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T15:59:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple’s M1 and M2 MacBooks are amazing pieces of technology. They run cool, get amazing battery life, and are some of the best laptops you can buy. So why do so many technology websites not brand them the “best laptop?”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Where is the xinitrc file stored in Arch Linux?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w7s7mk/where_is_the_xinitrc_file_stored_in_arch_linux/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w7s7mk/where_is_the_xinitrc_file_stored_in_arch_linux/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T15:43:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello people, this is my first post on this subreddit. I just wanted to ask where the xinitrc file is stored. I just installed Arch with LXDE. when I type startx, it just shows "command not found - startx" and I read the arch linux wiki. And it did not help. Please help me
    submitted by    /u/StillUsingWindows7  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Phishing Attacks Are Now Using the Windows Calculator]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=820691</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/820691/phishing-attacks-are-now-using-the-windows-calculator/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T15:37:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows has become better and better at stopping viruses and malware, even if you don’t have the best antivirus software installed. Malware developers have to get creative to infect systems, which now includes utilizing the Windows 7 Calculator application.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel Raptor Cove sarà una revisione dell'architettura Golden Cove per i core ad alte prestazioni]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Intel-Raptor-Cove-sara-una-revisione-dell-architettura-Golden-Cove-per-i-core-ad-alte-prestazioni_24812</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Intel-Raptor-Cove-sara-una-revisione-dell-architettura-Golden-Cove-per-i-core-ad-alte-prestazioni_24812"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T15:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[L'architettura utilizzata per i core ad alte prestazioni dei futuri nuovi processori Intel Raptor Lake (tredicesima generazione) si chiama Raptor Cove.L'offerta Raptor Lake arriverà sul mercato probabilmente tra settembre e ottobre di quest'anno anche se il lancio dei nuovi processori avverrà lungo diverse fasi, come già accaduto con le generazioni precedenti. Il processore top di gamma potrebbe essere l'Intel Core i9-13900K, del quale si parla già da tempo, e i nuovi arrivati nel catalogo Intel avranno il compito di continuare sulla buona strada imboccata con gli Alder Lake raccogliendone l'eredità.I core ad alta efficienza dei processori Intel Raptor Lake manterranno  invece l'architettura Gracemont: solo i core più performanti saranno forieri quindi di miglioramenti a livello di IPC.

Nuove 'voci di corridoio' pongono quasi sullo stesso piano i nuovi core Raptor Cove con gli attuali Golden Cove (architettura dei core ad alte prestazioni usata negli Alder Lake) presentandoli sì come una versione migliorata ma, tutto sommato, come un aggiornamento minore.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is the Rc Shell and How to Install It in Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=477252</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15453107/what-is-rc-shell-linux"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rc shell is a simple and innovative command interpreter built for the Plan 9 family of operating systems. It is currently a part of plan9port, which is a suite of Plan 9 software that is available for Linux.
    
Rc aims to improve on the default UNIX shell and it introduces a cleaner syntax for writing scripts. It is also built to be as simple to understand as possible. This makes rc a good program for someone that wants to learn how a shell works.
   

Content

What is Plan 9?
Installing the Rc Shell
Using and Writing Basic Rc Scripts
Basic Flow Control in Rc Shell
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:The Best Linux Desktop Environments of 2022
    
What is Plan 9?
    
In a basic sense, Plan 9 is the successor to the UNIX operating system. It was... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramces Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD Radeon 680M Graphics Are A Great Upgrade With RDNA2, Excellent On Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/review/amd-radeon-680m</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/review/amd-radeon-680m"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T15:15:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week when posting my initial Linux benchmarks of the AMD Ryzen 7 PRO 6850U performance (and also looking at the AMD Rembrandt Windows vs. Linux speed), there were two main areas to get excited about with these AMD Zen 3+ SoCs: nice power efficiency improvements across many real-world workloads and the graphics upgrade with the integrated Radeon 680M. In this article are more tests of the Radoen 680M graphics looking at the integrated graphics speed-up with RDNA2 finally replacing Vega as a big upgrade and also how this compares to the Intel Alder Lake P Xe Graphics performance for Linux laptops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Disabled a Big Pixel Camera Feature Without Telling Anyone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/123973/google-disabled-a-big-pixel-camera-feature-without-telling-anyone/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/123973/google-disabled-a-big-pixel-camera-feature-without-telling-anyone/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T15:09:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s Pixel phones have some amazing camera features, and for the last several years, “Frequent Faces” has been one of our favorites. However, we recently learned that Google quietly disabled it despite still being highlighted as a feature on phones, including the new Pixel 6a.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch takes a long time to start up after making modifications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w7r9b0/arch_takes_a_long_time_to_start_up_after_making/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w7r9b0/arch_takes_a_long_time_to_start_up_after_making/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T15:04:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello people. I have been using Arch Linux as my main system on my PC for a while now.
 The thing is that I decided to try other distributions on other partitions of my SSD.
 Both Tumbleweed and Fedora could be installed without problems, but they did not recognize the Arch partition in Grub.
 I decided to do a chroot and go back to the Arch Grub, and so I was able to enter my Arch partition, but with a very high boot time.
 I must have done something wrong when chrooting, because before it was booting very fast, with no problems.
 Also, as it didn't recognize my Tumbleweed partition in Grub, I decided to reinstall Tumbleweed, and now my Arch partition appears in Grub. I think I simply chose the wrong /boot partition before.
 But the thing is that it still takes a long time to boot Arch.
 After selecting it in Grub, it stays on a black screen with the text on the top left:
 Starting version 251.3-1-arch 
 And then, after a good wait, it brings up the following lines:
 [ TIME ] Timed out waiting for device /dev/disk/by-uuid/31fe4ea4-003c-4c31-947c-88874131ccd3. [DEPEND] Dependency failed for /dev/disk/by-uuid/31fe4ea4-003c-4c31-947c-88874131ccd3. [DEPEND] Dependency failed for Swaps. [ TIME ] Timed out waiting for device /dev/disk/by-uuid/eBe49236-2233-42c3-8fe4-3a1f7af04b10. [DEPEND] Dependency failed for /dev/disk/by-uuid/eBe49236-2233-42c3-8fe4-3a1f7af04b10. 
 Doing systemd-analyze 
 Startup finished in 5.267s (firmware) + 5.226s (loader) + 4.793s (kernel) + 1min 31.668s (userspace) = 1min 46.956s graphical.target reached after 1min 31.666s in userspace. 
 As I say, I can get into my ARch partition, in fact I'm writing this from it, but I think I must have done something wrong to cause this boot time delay.
 Any help would be very welcome.
 Thank you very much.
 Regards, Juan.
    submitted by    /u/jbellas  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft warns Windows 10 USB printing breaks due to recent updates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-warns-windows-10-usb-printing-breaks-due-to-recent-updates/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-warns-windows-10-usb-printing-breaks-due-to-recent-updates/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T15:01:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft is warning customers that Windows updates released since June 28 will trigger printing issues on devices connected using USB. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Long Can an Ethernet Cable Be?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=813419</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/813419/how-long-can-an-ethernet-cable-be/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T15:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you want to wire your entire house or are just looking to run a cable to the next room, you are bound to wonder about Ethernet cable length limits, and whether you’re risking connection problems. Here’s everything you need to know.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gaurav Shukla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do you keep a "just works" Distro loaded in your machine?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w7r3sg/do_you_keep_a_just_works_distro_loaded_in_your/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w7r3sg/do_you_keep_a_just_works_distro_loaded_in_your/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T14:59:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I an an arch newbie and was just wondering how many of you guys use arch as your only daily driver linux distro or do you have a just works distro setup on the side??
 ​
 Backstory: I "tried" arch around christmas 2021 after approximately 9 months of diving into linux headfirst from hackintoshing. It quickly became my daily driver and my linux mint languished. Currently I have fedora 36 spins setup as "just works". . . I never use it but keep it for now just in case my Arch breaks. At this point I feel like I can just spin up another arch PDQ. . . or use any distro live usb to fix what may be broken. I'm considering deleting fedora spins and adding it to my mdadm raid home partition.
    submitted by    /u/Im-Mostly-Confused  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Grub running on a disk?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w7qxgx/is_grub_running_on_a_disk/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w7qxgx/is_grub_running_on_a_disk/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T14:51:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My os bootloader is probablily broken,when I start up,the grub rescue page appears, and even if I try to install a new system using USB, it will tell me that the filesystem is unknown.I use the ls command, there will be (hd0) and (hd1), I am not sure which is the USB drive and which is my hard drive, and obviously, there is no partition.If I replace a hard drive, will he still show up.
    submitted by    /u/Macrohard13  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel produrrà chip per MediaTek: la conferma dell'accordo]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Intel-produrra-chip-per-MediaTek-la-conferma-dell-accordo_24811</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Intel-produrra-chip-per-MediaTek-la-conferma-dell-accordo_24811"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T14:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[L'aveva promesso il CEO Pat Gelsinger già a marzo 2021: Intel produrrà chip x86, ARM e RISC-V per conto terzi. Oggi arriva la notizia di un importante accordo.La nuova strategia Intel Device Manufacturing 2.0 (IDM 2.0) comincia a prendere forma con la conferma dell'intesa tra la società di Santa Clara e MediaTek.I portavoce di MediaTek hanno dichiarato di aver stipulato un accordo per 'costruire una catena di approvvigionamento più equilibrata e resiliente' che permetta quindi di sostenere tutti i vari prodotti dell'azienda. Direttamente interessata è quindi la produzione di SoC per dispositivi intelligenti, Chromebook e tablet. Secondo MediaTek le attività di fonderia di Intel dovrebbero migliorare significativamente le capacità espandere le quote di mercato sia negli Stati Uniti che in Europa.La partnership è una vittoria per Intel considerato che MediaTek attualmente si appoggia per la produzione di chip a TSMC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Curved Monitors of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=814702</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/814702/best-curved-monitor/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T14:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Curved monitors aren’t just stylish—they offer substantial benefits, from a more immersive media experience to wider display resolutions for productivity. We’ve hand-picked the best curved monitors you can buy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gaurav Shukla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come creare filtri dati su Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/07/come-creare-filtri-dati-su-excel.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/07/come-creare-filtri-dati-su-excel.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T13:53:00.006Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I filtri dati sono molto utili per filtrare i dati nelle tabelle del foglio di calcolo molto grandi e complesse, così da accedere subito alla parte di dati che ti interessano all'intero di una tabella o di un grafico. 
Su Excel possiamo creare rapidamente filtri dati utilizzando una funzione specifica del programma, che consigliamo a tutti di imparare ad utilizzare (specie se lavoriamo molto con Excel in ufficio).
 Nella guida che segue troveremo tutti i passaggi per creare filtri dati su Excel e per personalizzare i filtri dati eventualmente già presenti all'interno del foglio di calcolo. Se utilizziamo LibreOffice sul nostro computer, non è un problema: vi mostreremo come creare filtri dati anche sul gestore di fogli di calcolo presente nella suite gratuita e open source.
  
LEGGI ANCHE …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LockBit 3.0: cos'è e come funziona l'ultima versione del ransomware. Attacco ad Agenzia delle Entrate]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=LockBit-30-cos-e-e-come-funziona-l-ultima-versione-del-ransomware-Attacco-ad-Agenzia-delle-Entrate_24810</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=LockBit-30-cos-e-e-come-funziona-l-ultima-versione-del-ransomware-Attacco-ad-Agenzia-delle-Entrate_24810"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T13:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Il ransomware LockBit è attualmente una delle minacce più conosciute, attive e dirompenti mai rilevate finora. Scoperto per la prima volta a settembre 2019 è il ransomware è stato utilizzato per colpire aziende di primo piano ed enti pubblici in tutto il mondo.Stando a un'analisi elaborata da Cyble, il 33,3% delle vittime di LockBit sono soggetti che erogano servizi bancari, finanziari e assicurativi; seguono con il 22,2% le aziende che forniscono servizi professionali alla clientela.LockBit è il ransomware più veloce a crittografare i file degli utenti per poi chiedere un riscatto in denaro ed è gestito da un gruppo che si serve di 'tattiche' particolarmente avanzate per massimizzare la diffusione del malware e migliorarne di continuo le capacità di aggressione nonché le abilità che gli consentono di rimanere 'under-the-radar'.Per capire in che modo opera l'organizzazione 'dietro' a LockBit, basti pensare che gli autori di questo ransomware assoldano collaboratori infedeli promettendo ricompense milionarie e a fine giugno 2022 hanno avviato il primo programma bug bounty.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thunderbird's next milestone release will support Firefox Sync]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179914</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/07/25/thunderbirds-next-milestone-release-will-support-firefox-sync/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T13:09:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thunderbird 114, the next major version of the open source email client, will support Firefox Sync. Thunderbird, which shares a codebase with Mozilla's Firefox web browser, will get support for synchronizing data […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Thunderbird's next milestone release will support Firefox Sync appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Speaker Wire Gauges Explained: Which Do You Need?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=817769</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/817769/speaker-wire-gauges-explained-which-do-you-need/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T13:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With most cables and wires, all you need to worry about is how long they are and the connectors they use. With speaker wire, it’s more complicated, which is why we’re taking a look at speaker wire gauges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kris Wouk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wyze Scale X Review: a Feature Packed Smart Scale]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/123738/wyze-scale-x-review-a-feature-packed-smart-scale/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/123738/wyze-scale-x-review-a-feature-packed-smart-scale/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T13:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The weight loss world can be confusing with all the fad diets and weird exercise equipment on the market. However, by accurately tracking your progress, a smart scale could take a bit of weight off your mind as you attempt to take some weight off your body.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McQuilling</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[So, how's F2FS now?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w7ocjb/so_hows_f2fs_now/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w7ocjb/so_hows_f2fs_now/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T12:59:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Got a new drive and I was thinking of using it (over ext4). There seems to be a lot of "just be warned though" whenever I read up on it. Whether it be about data corruption or gc bugs. 
 Do you use it? What's your experience with it now?
    submitted by    /u/BidFew207  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here's Everything Coming to Netflix the Week of July 25, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lifesavvy.com/138182/heres-everything-coming-to-netflix-the-week-of-july-25-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lifesavvy.com/138182/heres-everything-coming-to-netflix-the-week-of-july-25-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T12:30:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July has been a big month for Netflix. As the end of the month nears, there are a few more releases for subscribers to watch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shea Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I cannot autostart a script in dwm.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w7nj2m/i_cannot_autostart_a_script_in_dwm/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w7nj2m/i_cannot_autostart_a_script_in_dwm/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T12:20:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have tried everything but i cannot autostart a script in dwm all i wanna do is put nitrogen --restore command so it runs at startup so i dont have to change the wallpaper everytime i login so i put it in .xinitrc .bash_profile and even in .bashrc it didnt work so then i made a script to run this command used chmod +x /home/user/filename.sh to make it executable used crontab -e to set it for user and root doesnt work so i thought lets try a simple command to execute terminal at startup then deleted the previous .sh file made a new one just in case followed all the steps still doesn't work even though when i run the script it runs fine and even those commands run fine on the terminal but cannot make an autostart file to run it on startup any help on what am i doing wrong.
    submitted by    /u/AwabKhan  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why You Need an Offline Backup]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=818193</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/818193/why-you-need-an-offline-backup/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maybe you’re using cloud backups or backups to attached media such as an external hard drive or a NAS. But these days, you also need an offline backup: A copy of your data that is detached from your machine and the Internet. Here’s why.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ricerca tramite immagine per trovare foto simili (Google e altri siti)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2011/06/ricerca-tramite-immagine-in-google-per.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2011/06/ricerca-tramite-immagine-in-google-per.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Una delle funzionalità più interessanti di Google è la ricerca tramite immagini, che permette di trovare le immagini simili o identiche a una che abbiamo noi e che usiamo per la ricerca.
 Lo scopo di questo tipo di ricerca non è soltanto quello di trovare immagini simili, ma anche quello di scoprire se una foto è vera oppure se una nostra fotografia è stata usata senza il nostro permesso da qualche sito web oppure anche per cercare di capire cosa sia l'oggetto ritratto in foto (per esempio il nome di un monumento o l'artista di un quadro), identificare che posto sia, o anche per riconoscere una persona.
 Nella seguente guida vi mostreremo come usare la ricerca delle immagini per trovare foto simili o identiche, oltre a poter identificare quello che è presente in una determinata foto o in u…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Much Energy Does Energy Saving Mode on TVs Really Save?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=819309</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/819309/how-much-energy-does-energy-saving-mode-on-tvs-really-save/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T11:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every TV has a number of different “Picture Modes” to choose from. There’s almost always an “Energy Saver” or “Power Saving” mode that tends to look the worst. How much energy does this mode actually save? Is it worth using?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cartelle Windows: come aprirle e passare da una all'altra]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Cartelle-Windows-come-aprirle-e-passare-da-una-all-altra_24809</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Cartelle-Windows-come-aprirle-e-passare-da-una-all-altra_24809"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T10:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quando si lavora con le cartelle Windows e si aprono più finestre di Esplora file, ad esempio per copiare o spostare file, può capitare di perdersi tra le tante directory aperte. Di seguito presentiamo alcuni semplici trucchi per aprire cartelle in Windows e passare dall'una all'altra molto semplicemente senza usare utilità (file manager) di terze parti.
Differenza tra cartelle e directory
 I termini cartella e directory sono generalmente intercambiabili.Il nome 'directory' è quello più classico perché si utilizzava anche prima dell'arrivo sul mercato dei sistemi operativi dotati di interfaccia grafica. Una directory viene infatti considerata come un oggetto a livello di file system.Viceversa una cartella è un oggetto che è parte integrante dell'interfaccia utente o GUI del sistema operativo: l'utilizzo di questo termine è storicamente più familiare agli utenti di Windows.
Aprire cartelle Windows velocemente
 Per aprire una cartella Windows in modo rapido si può usare un semplice trucco che noi usiamo comunemente.Utilizzando la combinazione di tasti Windows+R compare la finestra di dialogo Esegui.Iniziando a digitare un percorso a partire dall'unità (ad esempio C:\), Windows propone la lista delle varie sottocartelle presenti.

Si può scegliere un percorso tra quelli proposti: non appena si digita la barra rovesciata finale ( \ ), Windows indica quali sottocartelle sono presenti.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why You Should Use Kubernetes for Your Development Environments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?post_type=devops&amp;p=804053</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/devops/why-you-should-use-kubernetes-for-your-development-environments/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T10:40:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes has become one of the most popular ways to run containerized workloads in production. It simplifies deploying, scaling, and maintaining the containers that run your service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ByteDance Working To Make It Faster Kexec Booting The Linux Kernel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/news/Bytedance-Faster-Kexec-Reboot</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/news/Bytedance-Faster-Kexec-Reboot"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ByteDance as the Chinese company behind TikTok has been working on a number of Linux kernel optimizations the past few years and their most recent work is for faster Kexec rebooting of the kernel. With their massive fleet of servers powering TikTok and other apps, they will do whatever they can to shave milliseconds off the boot/reboot time of their servers and that is what most of their Linux optimizations have been about -- including this newest patch series for faster Kexec reboots...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GNOME Desktop]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w7lgyp/gnome_desktop/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w7lgyp/gnome_desktop/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T10:33:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I switched from Ubuntu 22.04 LTS to Arch Linux yesterday and everything works fine for me, but I got a problem with my desktop. There is nothing on desktop except wallpaper and when I right click to desktop it only shows settings and change wallpapers, nothing more. How can I solve this issue?
    submitted by    /u/henryxavery  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mouse won't show up in i3]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w7lf93/mouse_wont_show_up_in_i3/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w7lf93/mouse_wont_show_up_in_i3/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T10:30:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, I am a complete beginner to Arch, so sorry if this is a really trivial question.
 I got gpm working so that when I press Control+Alt+F1 I can see my cursor, but when I open i3 with startx I can't see any mouse cursor, and I still don't see it when I open PuTTY with Alt+Enter.
 What do I do?
    submitted by    /u/MrPiggens  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung Post Linux Patches For Trinity NPU Accelerator Driver]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/news/Samsung-Trinity-NPU-Linux-AI</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/news/Samsung-Trinity-NPU-Linux-AI"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T10:20:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung has posted a set of Linux kernel patches for enabling their Trinity neural processing unit (NPU) hardware as accelerators found within some of their embedded systems. Samsung Trinity NPUs have been in use since 2018 and their newer Trinity "TRIV2" accelerator is found within the latest Samsung TVs for AI purposes.  Samsung hopes to upstream this new Linux driver simply named "trinity" into the mainline kernel...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MediaTek Partners With Intel Foundry Services For Some Of Its Future Chips]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/news/MediaTek-Intel-IFS-Partners</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/news/MediaTek-Intel-IFS-Partners"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T09:56:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intel and MediaTek have just announced a strategic partnership where some future chips for MediaTek will be manufactured by Intel Foundry Services (IFS)...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux VKMS Driver Patches Making It Easier To Build Your Own Virtual Graphics Devices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/news/Linux-VKMS-ConfigFS-Virtual</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/news/Linux-VKMS-ConfigFS-Virtual"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T09:41:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The VKMS driver within the Linux kernel allows for virtual kernel mode-setting as a software-only KMS/DRM driver that can be used for virtual testing purposes and other uses around headless systems. New patches out of Google are working on ConfigFS support for this virtual display driver and from there making it easy to build out your own virtual graphics device configuration with VKMS...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lampada da soffitto Bluetooth con ventilatore integrato: ecco la promo estiva]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Lampada-da-soffitto-Bluetooth-con-ventilatore-integrato-ecco-la-promo-estiva_24808</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Lampada-da-soffitto-Bluetooth-con-ventilatore-integrato-ecco-la-promo-estiva_24808"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T09:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Durante il periodo estivo gli ambienti delle case, degli uffici, delle strutture ricettive e del mondo della ristorazione tendono a diventare roventi.Se non vi piace usare il condizionatore e non lo tollerate quando vi trovate fisicamente nella stanza, un dispositivo come la lampada LED Lixada con ventilatore può essere una buona soluzione.

Si tratta di una lampada LED a soffitto molto luminosa e di dimensione circolare che nella parte centrale integra un ventilatore a 3 velocità.Di diametro pari a 52 cm, la lampada Lixada consente di regolare l'intensità dell'emissione luminosa (è dimmerabile) e consente di scegliere tra tre possibili combinazioni: luce calda, luce bianca e luce naturale.La temperatura della luce è inoltre regolabile tra 3.000 e 6.000K; un apposito timer, inoltre, consente di regolare l'accensione della lampada e della ventola.Questa lampada con ventola offre una luce più naturale grazie al paralume in acrilico morbido: esso garantisce un'elevata trasmittanza della luce, senza abbagliare.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prop nvidia + amdgpu + display port usb c hub.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w7ke3t/prop_nvidia_amdgpu_display_port_usb_c_hub/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w7ke3t/prop_nvidia_amdgpu_display_port_usb_c_hub/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T09:29:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So I've been using arch for many years different computers and always managed to solve any issues but scratching my head with this one.
 My current laptop has nvidia rtx 3070 attached to usb c display port.
 The amd gpu is attached to hdmi port
 I was successfully using render offload to use two external monitors one via hdmi and one via usb c / display port.
 I have just purchased a usb c display port hub so I can add another monitor and run all three from the display port.
 This is where it gets a bit strange.
 Initially both external screens and laptop screen worked fine once plugged in however an occasional issue where one external monitor wouldn't show the desktop until reboot.
 I re did xranr auto etc as stated on arch wiki in which the laptop screen would not display but both externals now displayed but on removing the externals the laptop screen would still not show which is not good for when mobile.
 Tried again using render offload and xrandr auto etc and this time all displayed once more on reboot and laptop screen worked as it should but same issue with one of external screens would sometimes not work unless reboot.
 Attempted to reinstall amdgpu driver which resulted in all working but very slow due to using the on board graphics.
 Once again followed render offload on wiki and rebooted, nvidia card now being used once more so fast but same issue occurs with one screen sometimes not working unt reboot.
 Very frustrating.... is there anyone else with the same issues or a work around, ideally want it sorting before my third monitor arrives.
 Thanks
    submitted by    /u/dreamsuk  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RISC-V Default Linux Kernel Configuration Tweaked So It's Easier Running Docker, Snaps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/news/RISC-V-Docker-Linux-Config</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/news/RISC-V-Docker-Linux-Config"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T09:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the upcoming Linux 5.20 cycle the RISC-V CPU architecture's default kernel configuration "defconfig" is being tweaked so it's capable of running Docker out-of-the-box...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aspirapolvere lavapavimenti smart M7S PRO a circa 165 euro in offerta]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Aspirapolvere-lavapavimenti-smart-M7S-PRO-a-circa-165-euro-in-offerta_24807</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Aspirapolvere-lavapavimenti-smart-M7S-PRO-a-circa-165-euro-in-offerta_24807"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T08:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Il periodo estivo è da sempre uno dei migliori periodi per fare acquisti a prezzo scontato. Se state cercando un potente e versatile aspirapolvere lavapavimenti smart controllabile anche con la voce grazie al supporto Google Assistant e Amazon Alexa, LIECTROUX M7S PRO è in offerta speciale a soli 165,49 euro con spedizione veloce ai magazzini tedeschi del venditore.La promozione è valida soltanto fino al 31 luglio prossimo e salvo esaurimento delle scorte di magazzino (accertarsi, inoltre, di selezionare Germany Warehouse al momento dell'invio dell'ordine).

LIECTROUX M7S PRO è un dispositivo che assicura una potenza di aspirazione massima pari a 4.000 Pa e un'ottima autonomia (attività di pulizia fino a 110 minuti) grazie alla batteria integrata da 4.400 mAh.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Kubernetes Hooks to Track Container Lifecycles]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?post_type=devops&amp;p=800686</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/devops/how-to-use-kubernetes-hooks-to-track-container-lifecycles/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T08:04:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hooks are commonly used to log container events, implement clean-up scripts, and run asynchronous tasks after a new Pod joins your cluster. In this article, we’ll show how to attach hook handlers to your Pods and gain more control over container lifecycles.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch does not upgrade - list of possible ways of solving]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w7iu66/arch_does_not_upgrade_list_of_possible_ways_of/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w7iu66/arch_does_not_upgrade_list_of_possible_ways_of/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T07:52:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As I read this subreddit I saw many post about errors and problems with # pacman -Syu, so I decided to create this post with possible ways of solving those problems.
 pacman shows errors with mirrors
  
check if you are connected to internet; try ping google.com - if it works, you are connected; if not try ping 8.8.8.8 (it's Google DNS server); if it works - you have problem with DNS, read wiki and wiki; if not - you don't have internet
 try running # pacman -Syyu - it forces a refresh of all databases; if it doesn't work, use Reflector to retrieve latest mirrors and execute # pacman -Syyu
  
pacman shows error with signing and keyring
  
try # pacman -Sy archlinux-keyring && pacman -Su (probably the only package which can be upgraded with # pacman -Sy) wiki
  
db lock
  
wiki%22_error)
  
other errors
  
Conflicting files error%22_error) (may happen if make install puts files in /usr/bin instead of /usr/local/bin) wiki)
 Invalid / corrupted package%22_error)
 Package version is too high - run pacman -Syuu (-uu allows downgrades; man page)
 if some hook aborted transaction - read files in HookDir [from /etc/pacman.conf, default = /etc/pacman.d/hooks] and /usr/share/libalpm/hooks
 Read wiki and other pacman-related articles
 (thanks to u/PineappleScanner) enabling multilib repo in /etc/pacman.conf with archinstall script enables also multilib-testing repo
  
   submitted by    /u/Potega_Punktu  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Updating Windows 11 to new versions may soon be quicker on new devices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179911</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/07/25/updating-windows-11-to-new-versions-may-soon-be-quicker-on-new-devices/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T07:47:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft published a preview update for Windows 11 on July 21 that includes new functionality to improve the update process on new Windows 11 devices. The updating functionality that KB5015882 contains, will […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Updating Windows 11 to new versions may soon be quicker on new devices appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Upgrade to React 18]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?post_type=devops&amp;p=800687</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/devops/how-to-upgrade-to-react-18/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T06:02:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React 18 evolves the popular JavaScript component framework with new features built around concurrent rendering and suspense. It promises better performance, more capabilities, and an improved developer experience for apps that make the switch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wrote my first Rust app! Calibrates my wacom tablet on Sway]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w7dixj/wrote_my_first_rust_app_calibrates_my_wacom/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w7dixj/wrote_my_first_rust_app_calibrates_my_wacom/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T02:56:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/Infinite_Strike  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Help! Does not boot after -Syu]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w7ddaq/help_does_not_boot_after_syu/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w7ddaq/help_does_not_boot_after_syu/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T02:49:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After usual update with pacman -Syu and after reboot I was forced into emergency mode and got this.
 ​
 Starting version 251.3-1-arch
 You are in emergency mode. After logging in, type "journalctl -xb" to view system logs, "systemctl reboot" to reboot, "systemctl default" or "exit" to boot into default mode.
 Give root password for maintenance
 (or press Control-D to continue):
 [root@Hadess ~]# mount -a
 mount: /boot: unknown filesystem type 'vfat' .
 dmesg(1): may have more information after failed system call.
 [root@Hadess ~]# systemctl status boot.mount
 x boot.mount - /boot
 Loaded: loaded (/etc/fstab; generated)
 Active: failed (Result: exit-code) since mon 2022-07-25 22:28:58 AEST; 8 min ago
 Where: /boot
 What: /dev/disk/by-label/EFIBOOT
 Docs: man:fstab(5)
 man:systemd-fstab-generator(8)
 CPU: 3ms
 ​
 Jul 25 22:28:58 Hadess systemd[1]: Mounting /boot...
 Jul 25 22:28:58 Hadess mount[404]: mount: /boot: uknown filesystem type 'vfat' .
 Jul 25 22:28:58 Hadess systemd[1]: boot.mount: Mount proccess exited, code=exited, status=32/n/a
 Jul 25 22:28:58 Hadess systemd[1]: boot.mount: Failed with result 'exit-code' .
 Jul 25 22:28:58 Hadess systemd[1]: Failed to mount /boot
 [root@Hadess ~]#
    submitted by    /u/rotteegher39  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Expected Challenges Switching to Arch?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w7bzmq/expected_challenges_switching_to_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w7bzmq/expected_challenges_switching_to_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T01:43:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've always been an Ubuntu guy (now Lubuntu) but I'd like to step my game up and move to Arch so I can learn a bit more. Is there anything I need to prepare for as far as getting the system up and running, and to stay running? Thanks.
    submitted by    /u/frenetickticktick  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trying to teach someone shell scripting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w789uf/trying_to_teach_someone_shell_scripting/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w789uf/trying_to_teach_someone_shell_scripting/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T22:48:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trying to teach my friend shell scripting. This is what I came up with: ```
 !/bin/bash
 eegrep(){ echo $@; } bzz(){ bzip2 $@; } nogrep=/dev/null grepmo=50 [ -z $grepc ] && { cd -- mkdir grep.rd &> $nogrep cd grep.rd [ ! -f grep.sh ] \ && cat dirname $0/basename $0 \ | tee grep.sh \ && chmod +x grep.sh export grepc=$grepmo }
 mkdir grep.d cp grep.sh grep.d cd grep.d
 eegrep fgrep > grep.f cp grep.f grep.2bz bzz grep.2bz grep fgrep grep.f bzgrep fgrep *.bz2
 [ $grepc -gt 0 ] && { eegrep $grepc greps && { a=$PWD cd $HOME/grep.rd exa --tree --level=$grepmo cd $a } export grepc=$((grepc - 1)) ./grep.sh cd .. rm -rf grep.d } ```
    submitted by    /u/TheTsar  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come avviare più facilmente windows in modalità provvisoria]]></title>
        <id>3627|20220725000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/windows-10/come-avviare-piu-facilmente-windows-modalita-provvisoria-3627"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[La modalità provvisoria di Windows permette di avviare il sistema operativo in modo ridotto nelle funzioni, nei servizi e nei driver. Questo può permettere, non è sempre detto che ci si riesca, di riprendere il controllo di un computer dove un driver danneggiato, o un servizio che non parte, impediscono il normale avvio del sistema operativo. Però, come vedete in questo articolo, arrivare alla modalità provvisoria può richiedere numerosi passaggi che magari non abbiamo voglia, o la capacità, di fare. Così un modo molto più veloce per arrivare alla modalità provvisoria è quello offerto dal programma portable Safe Mode Launcher.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch doesn’t display full output of command on fresh arch install?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w769xt/arch_doesnt_display_full_output_of_command_on/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w769xt/arch_doesnt_display_full_output_of_command_on/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T21:20:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EDIT: Turns out the console was set in the wrong resolution, so I used fbset to correct it
 ​
 I‘m trying to use Pacman to install a desktop environment on bash but when I run the command the output gets cut off and I can’t scroll down to read it.
 ​
 I’ve tried:
  
using the ‘less’ command with Pacman however I don’t think that works since Pacman requires input
 Increasing the frame buffer and updating grub
  
Any suggestions would be greatly appreciated
    submitted by    /u/ChewyCashew614  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dropped into emergency shell after installing with archinstall]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w75zrx/dropped_into_emergency_shell_after_installing/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w75zrx/dropped_into_emergency_shell_after_installing/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T21:08:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So I’m trying to dual-boot with Windows 10, I have a btrfs partition and am using my EFI partition as my boot partition. Archinstall went fine until I rebooted and got this error. This is my first time using Arch and all help is appreciated.
    submitted by    /u/Osoa_  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux 5.19-rc8 Released With More Retbleed Fixes, Intel GuC Firmware Fix]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/news/Linux-5.19-rc8-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/news/Linux-5.19-rc8-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T21:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As was expected given all the recent kernel activity, Linux 5.19-rc8 was released today rather than going straight to the Linux 5.19 stable release, which has been diverted now to next Sunday. Linux 5.19-rc8 ships with many last minute fixes for this summer 2022 kernel update...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Enable the Ultimate Performance Power Plan in Windows 10]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=368781</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/368781/how-to-enable-ultimate-performance-power-plan-in-windows-10/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has added an “Ultimate Performance” power scheme to Windows 10 April 2018 Update. It’s built upon the High-Performance power scheme but tries to eke out every little bit of performance possible. Here’s how to enable it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brady Gavin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Where does the archlinux wallpaper pack get installed to]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w74oli/where_does_the_archlinux_wallpaper_pack_get/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w74oli/where_does_the_archlinux_wallpaper_pack_get/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T20:11:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I downloaded the arch linux wall paper pack to use in my qtile install but im not sure where it actually downloads the pngs to by default
    submitted by    /u/OutsideNo1877  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your Phone Has a Biometric Kill Switch, Here’s Why You Should Use It]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=814149</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/814149/your-phone-has-a-biometric-kill-switch-heres-why-you-should-use-it/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern iPhones and Android phones have super-convenient biometric security, but it isn’t always the best idea to leave it on. Luckily your phone probably has a biometric killswitch that can disable any biometric lock in seconds. All you have to do is learn how to use it!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sydney Butler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 Search Bar Not Working? Here’s 9 Ways to Fix It]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=430149</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/14805200/windows-11-search-bar-not-working"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For many Windows users, the Windows Search bar is the most important utility. On a Windows 11 device, however, you may find this option disabled. This is, in fact, a common issue facing those who plan to get the free upgrade from Windows 10 to Windows 11. There’s no single reason behind it being disabled. Therefore, our solutions below range from quick, easy fixes to more elaborate troubleshooting, including a reset option.
   

Content

Why Is Windows 11 Search Disabled?
1. Enable Search Button on Taskbar
2. Check for Windows Updates
3. Use Search and Indexing Troubleshooter in Windows 11
4. Restart the Windows Search Service
5. Tweak the Touch Keyboard and Handwriting Panel Service
6. Enable Search History on Device and Clear Past Search History
7. Ensure Your Search Results Aren't Within Excluded Folders
8. Use CTRL + ALT + DEL
9. Reset Windows 11
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sayak Boral</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Portable Console Runs on a Pi Pico, and You Can Actually Buy It!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/123914/this-portable-console-runs-on-a-pi-pico-and-you-can-actually-buy-it/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/123914/this-portable-console-runs-on-a-pi-pico-and-you-can-actually-buy-it/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T19:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Believe it or not, but the tiny Raspberry Pi Pico is perfectly capable of running games. In fact, it’s such a fun little platform that Pimoroni turned it into a portable console—the PicoSystem. And you can buy this console pre-assembled for $59.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Clear the Cache in Microsoft Edge]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=818358</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/818358/how-to-clear-cache-in-edge/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T19:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you want to fix specific website issues or resolve other problems with your browser, it’s easy to clear Microsoft Edge’s cache on your desktop and mobile devices. You can also get the browser to automatically delete your cache on each exit. We’ll show you how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Uninstall Steam Games]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=818914</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/818914/how-to-uninstall-steam-games/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T18:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you don’t play a specific game anymore, it makes sense to uninstall it from Steam on your computer. Doing so frees up your storage space and declutters your Steam library. We’ll show you two different ways to do that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Screen flickering black for a milisecond every few minutes. Even in TTY.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w71ciq/screen_flickering_black_for_a_milisecond_every/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w71ciq/screen_flickering_black_for_a_milisecond_every/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T17:46:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am using 180hz 2560x1440 lg 27GP850. I recently bought it as a new one.
 It works fine on windows, no flickering but on linux it turns screen black every few minutes for a millisecond. Sometimes it flickers like a 3 times a row and stops for a next few minutes. I saw that It doesn't happen in full screen games. I am using xwayland gnome but I checked on x11 KDE plasma and it also happens. 
 XRANDR output
 Screen 0: minimum 16 x 16, current 4000 x 1599, maximum 32767 x 32767
 XWAYLAND0 connected primary 2560x1440+0+0 (normal left inverted right x axis y axis) 700mm x 390mm
 2560x1440 179.90*+
 1920x1440 179.86 
 [some other resolutions...]
 inxi -G output 
 Graphics:
 Device-1: AMD Navi 23 [Radeon RX 6600/6600 XT/6600M] driver: amdgpu
 v: kernel
 Display: wayland server: X.org v: 1.21.1.4 with: Xwayland v: 22.1.3
 compositor: gnome-shell v: 42.3.1 driver: X: loaded: amdgpu
 unloaded: modesetting,vesa gpu: amdgpu resolution: 1: 2560x1440~180Hz
 2: 1440x900~75Hz
 OpenGL: renderer: AMD Radeon RX 6600 XT (dimgrey_cavefish LLVM 14.0.6
 DRM 3.46 5.18.13-arch1-1)
 v: 4.6 Mesa 22.1.3
 CPU: I5 10400F
 GPU: RX 6600 XT (bought 3 months ago as a new one)
 RAM: 16GiB
 Monitor settings: 
 Overclock: ON (It doesn't change anything if I turn this off only refresh rate goes from 165 to 180hz)
 response time: faster (It also doesn't change anything)
 Energy saving: OFF
 HDR: off 
 motion blur reduction: off
 VRR: ON (in gnome settings)
    submitted by    /u/efoxpl3244  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nerf Ditches the Dart In Its New "Gelfire" Blaster]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/123925/nerf-ditches-the-dart-in-its-new-gelfire-blaster/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/123925/nerf-ditches-the-dart-in-its-new-gelfire-blaster/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T17:13:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The famous foam darts are missing from Nerf’s latest product, the Gelfire Mythic blaster. It shoots new “Gelfire” rounds, which are small hydrated balls that explode on impact. And oddly enough, it comes with some eye protection.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Turn Off the Touch Screen on Chromebook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=820175</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/820175/how-to-turn-off-the-touch-screen-on-chromebook/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T17:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many Chromebooks have touchscreen displays, which are great if you like to use your laptop in “tablet mode.” However, if you don’t use the touchscreen, it may just be a source of accidental touches. You can turn it off.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Restore my grub efi entry for my linux install]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6z8c4/restore_my_grub_efi_entry_for_my_linux_install/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6z8c4/restore_my_grub_efi_entry_for_my_linux_install/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T16:14:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So basically I dual boot windows and arch but one day I logged into windows after like a month of not opening it to use a school software and it f**king decides to do some update and completely delete my bootable arch system, it didn't delete the partition though so my data was still safe. I decided to install another os by just making a 60gb partition and now I can boot into my previous original arch install through the grub of the new one and everything works. 
 Question is I can't figure out how to get the old grub entry back into my efi so I can delete this new one and not have an unnecessary install just to boot into my other install. I tried doing grub-mkconfig -o /boot/grub/grub.cfg but that didn't work. Help would be appreciated as I can't find clear answer on the net either for this specific problem
    submitted by    /u/Previous_Royal2168  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amadey malware pushed via software cracks in SmokeLoader campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/amadey-malware-pushed-via-software-cracks-in-smokeloader-campaign/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/amadey-malware-pushed-via-software-cracks-in-smokeloader-campaign/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T16:11:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new version of the Amadey Bot malware is distributed through the SmokeLoader malware, using software cracks and keygen sites as lures. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 Ways to Insert a Video in Google Docs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=811491</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/811491/insert-a-video-in-google-docs/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T16:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While Microsoft Word lets you add and play a video directly in your document, Google Docs doesn’t currently offer this same feature. If you want to embed a video to your Google Doc, we’ll show you a few workarounds to make it happen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Zari 0.1.0: A command to run all your tasks in one go!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6ykin/announcing_zari_010_a_command_to_run_all_your/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6ykin/announcing_zari_010_a_command_to_run_all_your/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T15:45:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Project Page. The Release Page.
 Hey everyone! I too wrote some code and I'd like to share it with you. The project is called Zari and it has now reached a state in which I feel like it's worthy of a 0.1.0 release. 
 Of course, since this is my first Rust project and with it being just the first release I bet there are some coding guidelines or standards I'm breaking, so please let me know if you see any improvements!
 What is it?
 Zari is a task execution program with a focus on simplicity and giving control to the user.
 In short, it allows you to configure multiple one-liners which will be executed sequentially. By letting Zari handle these commands, you can configure once and forget about it. An example would be to update all the various package managers on your system!
 Where to f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can't update my system. [error: failed retrieving file 'core.db'] Any help is appreciated.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6yga8/cant_update_my_system_error_failed_retrieving/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6yga8/cant_update_my_system_error_failed_retrieving/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T15:39:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Edit: SOLVED. Canada's mirrors weren't working for some reason, but US mirrors did work. 
 When I try to sudo pacman -Syu or sudo pacman -Syyu, it prompts an error:
  core.db failed to download error: failed retrieving file 'core.db' from mirror.0xem.ma : The requested URL returned an error: 503 error: failed to syncronize all databases (failed to retrieve some files) 
 I've tried going into /etc/pacman.d/mirrorlist and changed the mirror, but I get the same error. 
 Thanks.
    submitted by    /u/tonystark29  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nintendo Wii U and 3DS eShops Get an Official Closing Date]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/123904/nintendo-wii-u-and-3ds-eshops-get-an-official-closing-date/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/123904/nintendo-wii-u-and-3ds-eshops-get-an-official-closing-date/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T15:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In February, Nintendo revealed that the Wii U and popular Nintendo 3DS eShops would officially close sometime in 2023, marking the end of purchases. This means gamers can no longer buy any content, including games, apps, wallpapers, themes, and anything else.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QBot phishing uses Windows Calculator sideloading to infect devices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/qbot-phishing-uses-windows-calculator-sideloading-to-infect-devices/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/qbot-phishing-uses-windows-calculator-sideloading-to-infect-devices/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T15:18:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The operators of the QBot malware have been using the Windows Calculator to side-load the malicious payload on infected computers. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Edge-Lit vs. Direct-Lit vs. Full-Array TVs: What’s the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=818768</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/818768/edge-lit-vs-direct-lit-vs-full-array-tvs/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T15:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern LCD TVs rely on LED backlighting to produce the visuals you see on the screen. But their picture quality and price can differ based on their backlighting system. So, what are these backlighting systems, and how are they different?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gaurav Shukla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Debug Options]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6xi3c/debug_options/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6xi3c/debug_options/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T14:57:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello folks, after reading today’s news on phoronix.com related to DEBUG versus performance impact, I wonder how many of us disabled those debugging flags ? Or what kind of options you turn on or off, and how do you set things on or off? In other words I’m seeking a proper guide for newbies :)) Thanks
    submitted by    /u/Balauru_Nr1  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aur builder that checks pkgbuilds?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6x9cr/aur_builder_that_checks_pkgbuilds/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6x9cr/aur_builder_that_checks_pkgbuilds/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T14:46:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been using chaoticaur due to speed/convenience but later learned that it's a blind builder. Are there any similar services that actually check the pkgbuild to ensure it hasn't been compromised?
    submitted by    /u/Zackptg5  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>