<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-05-06T01:42:18.045Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[replacing grub with a tiny script !]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujc7ps/replacing_grub_with_a_tiny_script/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujc7ps/replacing_grub_with_a_tiny_script/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T01:23:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone, im seeking for help to remove grub and use a tiny script to boot into my os. I don't use anything other than arch on my laptop.So is it possible to replace grub with a Script to boot into my os? If so then how? Please send some help. 
 Regards Nabeen0x01
    submitted by    /u/Nabeen0x01  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[anyone know how to install redis insight gui on arch btw i found that it's only available on debian or ubuntu in thier offical website :)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujbqht/anyone_know_how_to_install_redis_insight_gui_on/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujbqht/anyone_know_how_to_install_redis_insight_gui_on/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T00:58:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/iamshubh69  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Laptop doesn’t use battery power when not plugged in]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujbmp6/laptop_doesnt_use_battery_power_when_not_plugged/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujbmp6/laptop_doesnt_use_battery_power_when_not_plugged/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T00:52:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The battery isn’t faulty, it charges when plugged in but when it’s not plugged in I want the laptop to use the battery it comes with. When I unplug the laptop it immediately turns off
 In Xfce4’s power settings my laptop battery appears to be 100 percent charged
 [SOLVED] silly me I forgot to put the screws on a year ago
    submitted by    /u/9934d  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How would i make my own local arch caching repo]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujbauz/how_would_i_make_my_own_local_arch_caching_repo/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujbauz/how_would_i_make_my_own_local_arch_caching_repo/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T00:28:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I would like to setup and make and arch repo that would cache packages automatically if it does not have them because multiple people in my house use arch and i want to limit the load on the repos and have faster updates at the same time but i dont want to manually download and set up each package every update so can i set up a self hosted repo such that if it is asked about a package that it does not have it would download and forward that the cache the package
    submitted by    /u/whypickthisname  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[9 Simple Ways to Open Device Manager in Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=483844</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15276969/ways-open-device-manager-windows"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a Windows user, you probably open the Device Manager quite frequently. After all, it’s the one-stop shop for managing all of the devices and hardware attached to your computer. It is also a critical part of troubleshooting. But despite the important role it plays, it’s somewhat hidden.
    
Fortunately getting into Device Manager is pretty easy. In this article, we’ll look at nine different ways to access Device Manager on your PC. The first two are the fastest and easiest methods. However, more tech-savvy users who don’t shy away from digging through extensive menu options or running commands might prefer the rest of the methods outlined. The techniques presented in this post are compatible with Windows 10, as well as Windows 11. 
   

Content

1. Use the Quick Access Menu
2. Via the Settings App
3. With Task Manager
4. Use the Run Command
5. With Control Panel
6. Use File Explorer
7. Give Command Prompt/Powershell a Try
8. Through the Computer Management Tool
9. Create a Shortcut

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Claire Moraa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mesa 22.2 Lands The Big Removal Of Old GLSL-To-TGSI Path, Now Always Going Through NIR]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Mesa-22.2-NIR-Always</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Mesa-22.2-NIR-Always"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T23:50:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Emma Anholt's perseverance the past year has paid off in freeing Mesa of the "glsl_to_tgsi" function with now all Mesa drivers going the route of from GLSL to the NIR intermediate representation. For Mesa drivers lacking native NIR consumption, there is then the NIR-to-TGSI path for going back to that traditional Gallium3D IR...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Krita g'mic plugin reliably crashes Krita 5.0.6]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uj8hmk/krita_gmic_plugin_reliably_crashes_krita_506/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uj8hmk/krita_gmic_plugin_reliably_crashes_krita_506/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T22:01:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Opening any image in Krita and trying to start the gmic plugin from the menubar's filter > Start G'MIC-Qt reliably crashes Krita.
 ​
 Running Krita from a terminal and doing this prints:
 *** stack smashing detected ***: terminated
 fish: Job 1, 'krita' terminated by signal SIGABRT (Abort)
 ​
 afaik my system is up to date and I don't have anything relevant to qt/gmic/krita installed from the AUR.
 ​
 Does anybody know what's going on here? Using G'MIC directly in Krita is useful to my workflow.
 Specifically the G'MIC tool to extract a foreground from a background by manually specifying foreground/background control points.
 I've tested it and I can do my G'MIC work in GIMP and load it into Krita as a workaround but oof. Since I already have a workaround I'm not really looking for another one, fixing this problem directly would be nice.
 ​
 package versions:
 gmic 3.1.0-1
 krita 5.0.6-1
 krita-plugin-gmic 3.0.2.2-2
 gimp 2.10.30-2
 gimp-plugin-gmic 3.1.0-1
    submitted by    /u/PreviousHighlight7  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come disattivare Snap Assist Flyout da Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>3555|20220506000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/manutenzione-156/come-disattivare-snap-assist-flyout-windows-11-3555"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Se con il mouse passate sopra al pulsante per ingrandire/rimpicciolire una schermata di Windows 11, quella di un browser, di Word o di esplora risorse, vi appare un menu dove potete scegliere un layout diverso per il vostro schermo. La cosa potrà essere utile per chi ha grandi schermi ed è magari abituato a suddividerli per gestire più cose sullo stesso monitor. A me questa funzione non serve, e non riesco ad abituarmi ad utilizzarla, quindi questa comparsa del menu la voglio eliminare.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is it possible to install Pacman on Busybox arch?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uj80gu/is_it_possible_to_install_pacman_on_busybox_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uj80gu/is_it_possible_to_install_pacman_on_busybox_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T21:39:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I want to replace gnu with busybox on my arch install, but gnu is needed for pacman. Is it possible to install pacman(or another package manager) on arch Linux with busybox? Also would yay work without gnutils and gnucore?
    submitted by    /u/Enter_The_Void6  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Raspberry Robin worm uses Windows Installer to drop malware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-raspberry-robin-worm-uses-windows-installer-to-drop-malware/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-raspberry-robin-worm-uses-windows-installer-to-drop-malware/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T21:36:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Canary intelligence analysts have discovered a new Windows malware with worm capabilities that spreads using external USB drives. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Turn Off Do Not Disturb While Driving]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=415798</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/14683758/turn-off-do-not-disturb-while-driving"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Often some services that are designed to help people can cause more annoyance rather than provide support. One such functionality is the Do Not Disturb mode while driving. I made the mistake of activating it by accident, and what followed was a barrage of missed notifications every time I was in the car. Fortunately, it’s easy to turn off Do not Disturb while driving on Android and iPhone, as we will demonstrate in this article. 
   

Content

How to Turn Off Do Not Disturb While Driving on iPhone in iOS15+
How to Turn Off Do Not Disturb While Driving on iOS 14 and Below
How to Turn Off Do Not Disturb While Driving on Android
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Get Bedtime Mode on Your Android Device
    
How to Turn Off Do Not Disturb While Driving on iPhone in iOS15+
... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mehvish Mushtaq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Triggering a script when a device connects to bluetooth?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uj7ehk/triggering_a_script_when_a_device_connects_to/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uj7ehk/triggering_a_script_when_a_device_connects_to/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T21:11:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have a logitech mouse that I use with logiops (logid). However, I've found that I have to manually run:
 sudo systemctl restart logid
 each time the mouse disconnects and reconnects. Is there a way that I can automate this? I'd also like to have the script trigger upon login.
    submitted by    /u/manafuzer  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Remove Malware Quickly with Malwarebytes’ Anti-Malware]]></title>
        <id>http://www.howtogeek.com/?p=2875</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/howto/2875/remove-malware-quickly-with-malwarebytes-anti-malware/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malwarebytes is one of the best anti-malware programs ever made. It has both free and paid versions, but even the free version is worth having around. Here’s how you can use it to remove malware from your PC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Lewis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fortnite Returns to iPhone and iPad With Xbox Cloud Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=803546</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/803546/fortnite-returns-to-iphone-and-ipad-with-xbox-cloud-gaming/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T20:54:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The popular online game Fortnite has been missing from iPhone and iPad ever since August 2020, when Apple removed it from the App Store over in-app purchase violations. Now the game is once again available for free on iOS devices, thanks to the magic of cloud gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memory slowly fills, process list gives no useful explanation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uj64xr/memory_slowly_fills_process_list_gives_no_useful/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uj64xr/memory_slowly_fills_process_list_gives_no_useful/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T20:12:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello,
 I've recently noticed that as my PC stays turned on for a while, the amount of free memory steadily decreases until it is around 97-98% full. This causes tabs to unload in Firefox and sometimes the whole system slows down.
 I've checked the process list, but nothing uses up even remotely enough memory to justify these numbers. Listing the processes under root doesn't help either. I use XFCE, have at most 4-5 programs running, the heaviest of these is Discord.
 Also I made sure that the memory is actually reported as "used" by free instead of "available" and the "cache" numbers are very low:
  total used free shared buff/cache available Mem: 15Gi 14Gi 762Mi 42Mi 743Mi 1.0Gi Swap: 14Gi 1.6Gi 13Gi 
 Is there anything I could do to figure out what's causing this?
    submitted by    /u/Nemin32  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[White House: Prepare for cryptography-cracking quantum computers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/white-house-prepare-for-cryptography-cracking-quantum-computers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/white-house-prepare-for-cryptography-cracking-quantum-computers/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T20:01:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[President Joe Biden signed a national security memorandum (NSM) on Thursday asking government agencies to implement a set of measures that would mitigate risks posed by quantum computers to US national cyber security. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Turn Off Lens Search in Google Chrome]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=797147</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/797147/turn-off-google-lens-chrome/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T20:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Chrome makes it easy to disable the Lens search feature and bring back the traditional “Search Google for This Image” context menu option. Here’s how you can do that in Chrome on desktop and Android.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dish’s Long-Awaited 5G Network Arrives As ‘Project Genesis’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=803512</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/803512/dishs-long-awaited-5g-network-arrives-as-project-genesis/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T19:27:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dish Network has been building its own cellular network in the United States, mostly with leftover wireless spectrum acquired from T-Mobile’s merger with Sprint. Now the network is starting to go live… in one city, anyway.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does the efibootmgr package do anything by itself?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uj55h8/does_the_efibootmgr_package_do_anything_by_itself/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uj55h8/does_the_efibootmgr_package_do_anything_by_itself/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T19:27:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I first learned how to install Arch I saw a youtuber installing it and he was doing an UEFI installation and he installed efibootmgr, but then he configured grub for efi. Since it was my first time doing it I did the same, but now I think efibootmgr is not doing anything in my system. I don't think it does anything if you are not using it to manage efi. Can this package be uninstalled with no downsides if you are not actively using it? It doesn't seem to be doing anything passively.
    submitted by    /u/nyvec  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get an Amazon Kindle, Ad-Supported, for Under $55]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=439314</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/14856197/amazon-kindle-ad-supported"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Getting ready for the summer reading season? Do it all from one device instead of making multiple trips to the library and book store. An Amazon Kindle will be your special beach buddy. While it may be ad-supported, that helps keep the cost down. Buy now and get it for a 39% discount.
    
The Kindle is designed just for reading rather than for multiple uses like smartphones and tablets. It has a 167 ppi glare-free display to make you feel like you’re reading on paper, even if you’re reading in direct sunlight. The adjustable brightness allows you to read comfortably, wherever you are, inside, at the beach, at the park, etc., regardless of the time of day.
    

    
Another difference from a tablet is that the Amazon Kindle will last for weeks on a single battery charge compared to just hours, making it the perfect vacation companion. It has 8GB of storage, allowing you to keep thousands of books at the ready, all on one device. You only have to pack one... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Systemd 251-rc2 Released With More Features]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=systemd-251-rc2</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=systemd-251-rc2"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T19:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just over one month after systemd 251-rc1 was released, a second release candidate to this next systemd installment is now available for testing. Systemd 251-rc2 brings yet more features to this Linux init system and service manager...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Pause Audio on Apple AirPods]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=797130</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/797130/how-to-pause-airpods/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T19:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you use Apple’s AirPods, you don’t have to reach for your phone to play or pause your music. You can use your AirPods’ built-in music controls to do that, and we’ll show you how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ukraine’s IT Army is disrupting Russia's alcohol distribution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ukraine-s-it-army-is-disrupting-russias-alcohol-distribution/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ukraine-s-it-army-is-disrupting-russias-alcohol-distribution/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T18:57:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hacktivists operating on the side of Ukraine have focused their DDoS attacks on a portal that is considered crucial for the distribution of alcoholic beverages in Russia. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your Nanoleaf Lines Are Begging for These Official Skins]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117078/your-nanoleaf-lines-are-begging-for-these-official-skins/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117078/your-nanoleaf-lines-are-begging-for-these-official-skins/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T18:22:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Out of the box, Nanoleaf Lines smart lights look a little plain. The lights themselves are colorful, for sure, but the hardware is just white. That’s why Nanoleaf now sells official matte black and pink skins for its Lines smart lights—prepare to drop $20 on these puppies; you definitely want them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Brings CGI Product Placement to Prime Video & Freevee]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=803476</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/803476/amazon-brings-cgi-product-placement-to-prime-video-freevee/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T18:19:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Product placement is nothing new for movies and TV shows, but Amazon is interested in pushing the idea a bit further with some content on Prime Video and Freevee (formerly IMDb TV).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NIST updates guidance for defending against supply-chain attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/nist-updates-guidance-for-defending-against-supply-chain-attacks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/nist-updates-guidance-for-defending-against-supply-chain-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T18:15:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST) has released updated guidance on securing the supply chain against cyberattacks. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Wi-Fi “Wardriving” and How Can You Protect Yourself?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=794732</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/794732/what-is-wi-fi-wardriving-and-how-can-you-protect-yourself/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T18:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[War, what is it good for? Well, when we’re talking about wardriving, it’s away to find unsecured Wi-Fi, sometimes with malicious intent. Wardriving is hard to detect, but with preparation you can protect your home network from being targeted.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sydney Butler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fedora Linux 36 Being Released Next Week]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Fedora-Linux-36-Next-Week</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Fedora-Linux-36-Next-Week"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After being delayed a few weeks from their original release target, Fedora 36 is now primed for release next week Tuesday...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTC to force ISP to deploy fiber for 60K users to match speed claims]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/ftc-to-force-isp-to-deploy-fiber-for-60k-users-to-match-speed-claims/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/ftc-to-force-isp-to-deploy-fiber-for-60k-users-to-match-speed-claims/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T17:43:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Federal Trade Commission (FTC) today proposed an order requiring Connecticut-based internet service provider Frontier Communications to stop "lying" to its customers and support its high-speed internet claims. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Problems connecting to MariaDB from Python (pyodbc)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uj2rm8/problems_connecting_to_mariadb_from_python_pyodbc/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uj2rm8/problems_connecting_to_mariadb_from_python_pyodbc/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T17:38:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been trying to connect to a database using this Python script but it gives me the folllowing error:
 pyodbc.connect('DRIVER=ODBC Driver for MySQL;User=user;Password=pass;Database=tareabd_1;Server=server;Port=3306;')
 error:
 pyodbc.Error: ('01000', "[01000] [unixODBC][Driver Manager]Can't open lib 'CData ODBC Driver for MariaDB' : file not found (0) (SQLDriverConnect)")
 ​
 If I chage the input to:
 pyodbc.connect(('DRIVER=/usr/lib/libmaodbc.so;User=user;Password=pass;Database=tareabd_1;Server=server;Port=3306;')
 the error changes to:
 pyodbc.Error: ('HY000', "[HY000] [ma-3.1.15]Unknown server host 'server' (-2) (2005) (SQLDriverConnect)")
 ​
 The output from "cat odbcinst.ini" is :
 [MySQL]
 Description = ODBC Driver for MySQL
 Driver = /usr/lib/libmaodbc.so
 FileUsage = 1
 ​
 The ouput from "cat /etc/odbc.ini" is:
 [CData MariaDB Source]
 Driver = CData ODBC Driver for MariaDB
 Description = Tarea 1 Bases de Datos
 User = user
 Password = pass
 Database = tareabd_1
 Server = server
 Port = 3306
 ​
 I followed the guide from the ArchWiki at first, but it doesn''t seem to work.
    submitted by    /u/LordMikeVTRxDalv  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can't get ArchLinux install flash drive to work.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uj2om5/cant_get_archlinux_install_flash_drive_to_work/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uj2om5/cant_get_archlinux_install_flash_drive_to_work/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T17:34:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I just can't get 2022.05.01 ArchLinux iso image to work as an install flash drive on HP EliteBook 840 G5. 
 I didn't find a way to get the text output, so I at least took a photo of it. https://imgur.com/tQGVNCg 
 Strange thing is that it works fine using 2021.01.01 iso. Did anyone experience similar problem? Is there even anything I can do about that?
    submitted by    /u/TheBCX  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NVIDIA Finally Offers 4K Cloud Gaming for Windows and Mac Users]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117068/nvidia-finally-offers-4k-cloud-gaming-for-windows-and-mac-users/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117068/nvidia-finally-offers-4k-cloud-gaming-for-windows-and-mac-users/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T17:28:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It took NVIDIA a few years to get here, but the company is finally offering its GeForce Now cloud gaming service at 4K and 120FPS for those on Windows and macOS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Acer Proves That Powerful Chromebooks Don't Need to Be Expensive]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117047/acer-proves-that-powerful-chromebooks-dont-need-to-be-expensive/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117047/acer-proves-that-powerful-chromebooks-dont-need-to-be-expensive/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T17:12:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Because Chromebooks run a lightweight operating system, they require far less horsepower than Windows or Mac computers. But power users are willing to pay out the nose for a speedy computer; they don’t care that $1,000 is “overpriced for a Chromebook.” So, Acer is giving those power users a much more affordable alternative.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can't install Spotify from the AUR]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uj21oo/cant_install_spotify_from_the_aur/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uj21oo/cant_install_spotify_from_the_aur/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T17:06:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When downloading Spotify using yay, I get the following error:
 ==> Validating source files with sha512sums...
 spotify.protocol ... Passed
 LICENSE ... Passed
 spotify-1.1.84.716-x86_64.deb ... FAILED
 spotify-1.1.84.716-1-Release ... Skipped
 spotify-1.1.84.716-1-Release.sig ... Skipped
 spotify-1.1.84.716-1-x86_64-Packages ... Skipped
 ==> ERROR: One or more files did not pass the validity check!
 -> error downloading sources: spotify
 context: exit status 1
 I've tried most of the solutions posted on https://aur.archlinux.org/packages/spotify, including importing a new GPG key, changing the sha512sums on the PKGBUILD file and deleting the yay and pacman cache, all resulting in the same error once again.
 Any help is highly appreciated.
    submitted by    /u/Sad-Mixture-1953  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lenovo Yoga 2022: la nuova serie di notebook, convertibili e all-in-one è sorprendente]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Lenovo-Yoga-2022-la-nuova-serie-di-notebook-convertibili-e-all-in-one-e-sorprendente_24477</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Lenovo-Yoga-2022-la-nuova-serie-di-notebook-convertibili-e-all-in-one-e-sorprendente_24477"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T17:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Il marchio Lenovo Yoga è da anni divenuto un vero e proprio punto di riferimento nel suo segmento. L'azienda ha iniziato con l'idea dei convertibili per poi ampliare la gamma con un ventaglio di portatili ultraleggeri, notebook gaming, Chromebook, tablet, 2-in-1 e anche desktop.Gli obiettivi della serie Yoga sono rimasti inalterati nel tempo ma l'ultima generazione convince ancora di più grazie all'adozione delle ultime piattaforme Intel e AMD, agli schermi PureSight e alle tecnologie di Lenovo come l'insieme di caratteristiche per aumentare le prestazioni X Power e il sistema A.I. Engine+ che sfrutta l'intelligenza artificiale per anticipare le esigenze dell'utente in termini di potenza e batteria sulla base dell'attività che si sta svolgendo.Lenovo ha svelato oggi la nuova generazione di…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Face ID?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=800426</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/800426/what-is-face-id/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T17:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Certain models of Apple iPhone and iPad include an authentication feature called “Face ID,” which uses a special camera on the front of your device to verify your identity. But why do we need Face ID, and how does it work? We’ll explain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced SystemCare per velocizzare Windows (gratuito)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2012/10/configurazione-pc-ottimale-con-systemcare.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2012/10/configurazione-pc-ottimale-con-systemcare.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T16:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced SystemCare di IOBit è uno dei programmi Windows più popolari per ottimizzare e ripulire Windows. Avviando questo programma potremo trovare la giusta configurazione del computer, correggendo automaticamente gli errori di sistema, ripulendo il disco da riferimenti e file non più validi o obsoleti e riconoscendo quali servizi disattivare per far andare il pc più veloce.

 Si tratta di una...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft, Apple, and Google to support FIDO passwordless logins]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-apple-and-google-to-support-fido-passwordless-logins/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-apple-and-google-to-support-fido-passwordless-logins/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T16:19:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft, Apple, and Google announced today plans to support a common passwordless sign-in standard (known as passkeys) developed by the World Wide Web Consortium (W3C) and the FIDO Alliance. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google fixes actively exploited Android kernel vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/google-fixes-actively-exploited-android-kernel-vulnerability/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/google-fixes-actively-exploited-android-kernel-vulnerability/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T16:11:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has released the second part of the May security patch for Android, including a fix for an actively exploited Linux kernel vulnerability. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla Drivers Discover an Unannounced Swivel Display Upgrade]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117040/tesla-drivers-discover-an-unannounced-swivel-display-upgrade/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117040/tesla-drivers-discover-an-unannounced-swivel-display-upgrade/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T16:06:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla could finally be ready to upgrade what many drivers and passengers interact with the most, the in-car infotainment display. New videos have confirmed that Tesla’s upgraded Model S and Model X displays will have a motorized swivel feature.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Help with CDM Install]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uj0rdh/help_with_cdm_install/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uj0rdh/help_with_cdm_install/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T16:04:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I followed the instructions on the wiki, but the wiki said a script in /etc/profile.d (called zzz-cdm.sh) should be generated, but when I check /etc/profile.d, nothing is there.
 Pacman says the package "cdm" is installed. I installed the AUR package from a non-root user because I'm not supposed to makepkg from root.
    submitted by    /u/Hefty_Ad2383  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Undo Typing on a Samsung Galaxy Phone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=800644</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/800644/how-to-undo-typing-on-a-samsung-galaxy-phone/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T16:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ability to “Undo” the last thing you typed is something we take for granted on PCs. The iPhone also happens to have a handy undo gesture—and, if you use a Samsung Galaxy phone, you do too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making This Coffee Switch Could Help Your Stomach]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lifesavvy.com/127742/making-this-coffee-switch-could-help-your-stomach/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lifesavvy.com/127742/making-this-coffee-switch-could-help-your-stomach/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T16:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coffee drinkers with sensitive stomachs are well aware that, sometimes, that morning cup doesn’t sit right. One change could make all the difference, though.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shea Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mesa's "Rusticl" Implementation Now Manages To Handle Darktable OpenCL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Rusticl-Darktable-Milestone</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Rusticl-Darktable-Milestone"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rusticl as what started out as a Rust language experiment for Mesa and has now matured into a working OpenCL 3.0 implementation for Mesa drivers is still making progress and on a path towards eventually being mainlined...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Working From Home? Boost Your Productivity With Setapp for Mac]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=798968</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/798968/working-from-home-boost-your-productivity-with-setapp-for-mac/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T15:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Working from home has become wildly popular over the past few years, but it has also introduced us to challenges we hadn’t considered. Pets, projects around the house, random distractions on the internet — all serve to deter focus and hamper productivity. Can a suite of work-focused apps help you get back on track? We’ll discuss how to stay productive while working from home with Setapp, a popular subscription service with more than 200 incredible apps for Mac.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sponsored</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Arch wants to mount my secondary hard drive at boot?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uj0e07/why_arch_wants_to_mount_my_secondary_hard_drive/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uj0e07/why_arch_wants_to_mount_my_secondary_hard_drive/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T15:47:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everytime that I boot, it appears this box ( https://imgur.com/a/ugYvoSW ) that asks the root password for mounting my hard drive (/dev/sda2). Why? How can I disabled this? it's so annoying.
 ​
 This is my /etc/fstab:
 ​
 [sh4ttered@arch-sh4ttered ~]$ cat /etc/fstab 
 # Static information about the filesystems.
 # See fstab(5) for details. 
 # <file system> <dir> <type> <options> <dump> <pass>
 # /dev/sdb2
 UUID=e8fce133-159e-4740-b4cd-7e56dfea74cd / ext4 rw,relatime 0 1 
 # /dev/sdb1
 UUID=DA0E-C048 /boot vfat rw,relatime,fmask=0022,dmask=0022,codepage=437,iocharset=ascii,shortname=mixed,utf8,errors=remount-ro 0 2
    submitted by    /u/lox689  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chromebooks Are Getting Super-Fast AMD Ryzen 5000 Processors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=803373</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/803373/chromebooks-are-getting-super-fast-amd-ryzen-5000-processors/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T15:42:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chromebooks don’t have the same options for hardware as traditional PCs, and more recently, many of the best Chromebooks have been behind on new processors. That’s now changing, with the introduction of AMD Ryzen 5000 C-Series chips for Chrome OS computers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[moving an existing arch install to a live usb drive]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uj072z/moving_an_existing_arch_install_to_a_live_usb/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uj072z/moving_an_existing_arch_install_to_a_live_usb/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T15:38:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, I have a fully working install of arch on my laptop but I could do with having a portable clone of it on a USB drive that I can boot to from any PC for work. I have looked on the wiki and can see steps to clone your install etc but I can't find a guide to clone the OS To a live usb. Can anyone point me in the right direction?
 I've seen guides on how to clone an install from usb to hdd but not the other way around
 Thanks!
    submitted by    /u/PWICHex  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google, Apple, and Microsoft Agree to Make Passwords a Thing of the Past]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117029/google-apple-and-microsoft-agree-to-make-passwords-a-thing-of-the-past/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117029/google-apple-and-microsoft-agree-to-make-passwords-a-thing-of-the-past/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T15:28:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Passwords are a hassle, and unfortunately, they’re often a security risk. Even when a password is nice and complicated (they usually aren’t), it may be compromised through brute-force attacks, leaks, or malware. That’s why Apple, Google, and Microsoft are now collaborating on our passwordless future through the FIDO standard.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[System doesn't boot completely after changing from NVIDIA to AMD]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uizyaj/system_doesnt_boot_completely_after_changing_from/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uizyaj/system_doesnt_boot_completely_after_changing_from/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T15:27:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[sry if anything here is weird to read but english isn't my first language (i'm from germany)
 I'm currently trying to get away from Windows (due to win11 being absolutely horrendous). After trying out a bunch of linux distros in virtual machines over several years, a portable Archlinux install on a flash drive and now also on my Steam Deck i actually installed Archlinux on my computer that i use for gaming and work.
 So far it worked great with sddm and KDE Plasma but the drivers for my NVIDIA GTX 1060 were awful to use. As i was already searching for a new GPU anyway i changed my plans a bit and purchased an AMD RX 6800 XT instead of another NVIDIA card.
 I thought that i could simply remove all nvidia drivers, install xf86-video-amdgpu and mesa and everything should work fine. Well, at boot i'm now stuck with:
 [ ok ] Reached Target Graphical Interface 
 By pressing Ctrl + Alt + F2 i've logged into the system and ran journalctl -b -p err to see what's wrong. Turns out systemd still tries to load the nvidia drivers:
 Failed to find module 'nvidia-uvm' 
 Besides that there seemed to be 3 errors regarding sddm not being able to launch because it couldn't connect to any display.
 I tried to look at the Arch Wiki systemd Article to tell it to not load the nvidia drivers but i honestly couldn't figure it out. Is there an way to fix that?
 Sidenote: My zsh ist configured to run neofetch at start (just for fun) but my GPU ist described as AMD RX 6800 / 6800 XT / 6900 XT. Does that mean it couldn't figure out which GPU is installed or am i overthinking things and this is normal?
 Edit: I had to delete the xorg.conf file from /etc/X11/ that was apparently also created by the nvidia drivers. Everything works now again.
    submitted by    /u/Jefson_Morinskey  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PS4/PS5 Controller Alternatives for Those Who Prefer the Xbox One Controller]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=340576</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/13491528/ps4-controllers-alternatives"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sorry Sony, but the DualShock and the DualSense controllers don’t hold a candle to the Xbox controller. Microsoft’s controller features a more comfortable offset analog stick layout and proper shoulder triggers instead of clunky bumpers. While it can be argued that the Sony consoles have a significantly better game library than the Xbox and despite both connecting through Bluetooth, there’s no way to use your Xbox One controller on your PlayStation natively. If you’re a PS4/PS5 fan but have always been envious of the Xbox One controller, there are a few third-party controller manufacturers that have answered your prayers.
   

Content

Do Any of these Controllers Work on PlayStation 5?
1. Hori ONYX
2. Nacon Asymmetric Wireless
3. Nacon Revolution Unlimited Pro
4. SCUF Vantage
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Connect a PS4/PS5 Controller to Your Android Phone
    
Do... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Lynch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are Curved Monitors Worth It?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=794986</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/794986/are-curved-monitors-worth-it/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T15:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Curved monitors aren’t curved for a stylistic choice. They provide valuable benefits such as a wider field of view and wider display resolutions. However, they won’t benefit everyone. Let’s discuss whether curved monitors are right for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Nguyen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bonus Internet 300 euro senza limiti ISEE: cos'è e come funziona]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Bonus-Internet-300-euro-senza-limiti-ISEE-cos-e-e-come-funziona_24476</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Bonus-Internet-300-euro-senza-limiti-ISEE-cos-e-e-come-funziona_24476"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T14:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Con l'obiettivo di estendere la diffusione della connettività a banda ultralarga in Italia, il Ministero dello Sviluppo Economico (MISE) sta lavorando su un nuovo provvedimento con cui verranno erogati 300 euro di bonus alle famiglie che attiveranno abbonamenti capaci di assicurare in downstream, almeno commercialmente, non meno di 30 Mbps.A novembre 2020 avevamo parlato del bonus Internet, PC e tablet che metteva sul piatto un voucher da 500 euro per la 'digitalizzazione' delle famiglie italiane con ISEE non superiore a 20.000 euro.Attingendo ai fondi del PNRR (Piano nazionale ripresa resilienza), questa volta il MISE offre un bonus Internet da 300 euro ai richiedenti senza limiti di reddito. Attraverso Infratel Italia, società in-house del MISE, chiamata a gestire l'intera operazione, saranno stanziati poco meno di 410 milioni di euro suddivisi tra le varie regioni d'Italia.Come già avvenuto nel caso dei precedenti 'bonus', compreso quello di marzo 2022 destinato alla digitalizzazione delle imprese, anche in questo caso il voucher del valore di 300 euro sarà riconosciuto solo ed esclusivamente per l'attivazione di servizi di connettività ad almeno 30 Mbps di velocità massima in download, realizzati con qualsiasi tecnologia disponibile.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Se il Bluetooth del Amazon Echo non funziona, come risolvere]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/05/se-il-bluetooth-del-amazon-echo-non.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/05/se-il-bluetooth-del-amazon-echo-non.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T14:38:00.007Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I dispositivi Amazon Echo possono essere utilizzati come semplici casse Bluetooth: non dobbiamo far altro che lanciare il comando vocale "Alexa, accendi il Bluetooth" e utilizzare il menu Bluetooth del telefono o del computer per associarlo, così da poter riprodurre musica o suoni con una potenza maggiore rispetto alle casse integrate. Purtroppo non sempre l'associazione va a buon fine o, in...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMS truffa da Banca BPER: un dispositivo anomalo si è collegato alla vostra area privata]]></title>
        <id>3567|20220505163350</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/truffe-5953/sms-truffa-banca-bper-dispositivo-anomalo-si-collegato-area-privata-3567"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T14:33:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sta circolando con estrema velocità un SMS truffaldino inviato da furbetti che si fingono Banca BPER, il cui testo questa volta spicca per originalità. Vediamo di cosa si tratta
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New NetDooka malware spreads via poisoned search results]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-netdooka-malware-spreads-via-poisoned-search-results/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-netdooka-malware-spreads-via-poisoned-search-results/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T14:28:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new malware framework known as NetDooka has been discovered being distributed through the PrivateLoader pay-per-install (PPI) malware distribution service, allowing threat actors full access to an infected device. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Budget Smartwatches of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=794371</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/794371/best-budget-smartwatch/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T14:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Buying a budget smartwatch can feel daunting given the sheer number of options from both popular and relatively unknown brands. But we’re here to help. Here are our handpicked recommendations for the best budget smartwatches.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gaurav Shukla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don't Forget This Curb Appeal Task Before Selling Your Home]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lifesavvy.com/127735/dont-forget-this-curb-appeal-task-before-selling-your-home/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lifesavvy.com/127735/dont-forget-this-curb-appeal-task-before-selling-your-home/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T14:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to selling a home, there are a few things nearly everyone knows can increase the selling price. For example, you can upgrade fixtures or spruce up the lawn. However, there’s another exterior detail you might be forgetting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shea Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Realtà aumentata: Google compra Raxium e la sua tecnologia a micro LED]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Realta-aumentata-Google-compra-Raxium-e-la-sua-tecnologia-a-micro-LED_24475</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Realta-aumentata-Google-compra-Raxium-e-la-sua-tecnologia-a-micro-LED_24475"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T13:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dopo quelli che possiamo oggi definire come 'tentativi' e progetti embrionali (si pensi ai Google Glass), l'azienda di Mountain View starebbe lavorando su un prodotto per la realtà aumentata decisamente più mainstream ma, allo stesso tempo, utilizzabili da professionisti e imprese.Ne è una conferma l'acquisizione di Raxium, una startup nata 5 anni fa che ha sviluppato una tecnologia basata su micro LED che potrebbe rappresentare la chiave per completare la realizzazione della nuova generazione prodotti per la realtà aumentata, virtuale e mista di Google.

Con i micro LED sarebbe possibile progettare e realizzare display per la realtà aumentata più efficienti dal punto di vista energetico rispetto ad altre soluzioni.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How can I restart my keyboard? Caps lock being remapped to Esc]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uixbwt/how_can_i_restart_my_keyboard_caps_lock_being/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uixbwt/how_can_i_restart_my_keyboard_caps_lock_being/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T13:21:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For some reason, since yesterday, my keyboard has stopped working properly on Arch, it's remapping the Caps Lock to the Escape key, xev gives me exactly the same output for both keys.
 Logging out and in again or rebooting makes everything work again but it's annoying.
    submitted by    /u/PenaflorPhi  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fix Pale Moon browser not passing Cloudflare's "Checking Your Browser" verification]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178411</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/05/05/fix-pale-moon-browser-not-passing-cloudflares-checking-your-browser-verification/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T13:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Pale Moon web browser runs into an infinite "checking your browser" loop on sites that use Cloudflare's browser integrity check feature. I confirmed the issue in the latest release versions of […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Fix Pale Moon browser not passing Cloudflare's "Checking Your Browser" verification appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Addio password: alleanza tra Apple, Google e Microsoft intorno allo standard FIDO]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Addio-password-alleanza-tra-Apple-Google-e-Microsoft-intorno-allo-standard-FIDO_24474</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Addio-password-alleanza-tra-Apple-Google-e-Microsoft-intorno-allo-standard-FIDO_24474"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T13:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Non è un caso che l'annuncio sia stato diramato durante il World Password Day.La notizia è importante perché Apple, Google e Microsoft hanno deciso di formare un'alleanza per abbandonare l'utilizzo delle password.L'autenticazione con la classica coppia username-password si conferma come uno dei maggiori problemi di sicurezza sul Web e la gestione di così tante credenziali comincia a diventare problematica.L'obiettivo è quello di incentivare l'utilizzo di meccanismi passwordless basati sull'utilizzo della crittografia end-to-end. Basandosi sugli standard proposti dalla FIDO Alliance e dal World Wide Web Consortium (W3C), gli utenti potranno accedere ai loro servizi e applicazioni usando un PIN oppure con la semplice verifica di alcuni parametri biometrici (impronta digitale, riconoscimento facciale,...).Centinaia di aziende tecnologiche e fornitori di servizi di tutto il mondo hanno lavorato all'interno della FIDO Alliance e del W3C per creare standard di accesso che non prevedano l'utilizzo delle password.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Find an EV Charging Station Near You]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=795296</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/795296/how-to-find-an-ev-charging-station-near-you/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T13:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The availability of electric car charging stations is a valid concern for those looking to switch from gas cars. Luckily, there are lots of websites and apps that make finding a charging station near you — and what it’ll cost if you have to pay — very easy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Bogna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 Side Hustles to Earn Extra Cash]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/116035/8-side-hustles-to-earn-extra-cash/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/116035/8-side-hustles-to-earn-extra-cash/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s economic environment, everybody could use a little extra cash. The good news is that there are plenty of earning opportunities to pursue. From giving people a ride and selling merchandise to narrating books and becoming a teacher, your skill is in demand. Read on for the possibilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Chadwick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD Begins Working On "GFX11" Support For Open-Source Mesa Linux Graphics (RDNA3)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMD-GFX11-RDNA3-Mesa</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMD-GFX11-RDNA3-Mesa"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T12:33:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following AMD's recent AMDGPU Linux kernel patches for the "GFX11" graphics block to be found with next-gen RDNA3 GPUs, AMD has now submitted the initial Mesa-side patches for GFX11/RDNA3 with a focus on their RadeonSI Gallium3D driver...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Limitare l'uso del PC solo per certe ore e giorni]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2016/04/limitare-luso-del-pc-solo-per-certe-ore.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2016/04/limitare-luso-del-pc-solo-per-certe-ore.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T12:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Se i nostri figli stanno troppo tempo al computer oppure per qualsiasi altro motivo si vuole fare in modo che il PC non venga utilizzato tutto il giorno ma solo in certe ore possiamo utilizzare delle funzioni del sistema operativo e dei programmi di parental control per assegnare un limite di tempo d'uso del computer: superato il tempo a disposizione il computer di bloccherà e non sarà più...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[14 Google Sheets Functions That Microsoft Excel Needs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=795930</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/795930/google-sheets-functions-that-microsoft-excel-needs/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T12:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Excel is a full-featured, commonly used spreadsheet application, but it’s not perfect. Its longtime rival Google Sheets offers features that Excel does not, including many helpful functions. Let’s take a look!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel Has A Solution For Hot Linux Laptops Draining The Battery While Trying To Sleep]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-S0ix-Linux-Failure-Hot</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-S0ix-Linux-Failure-Hot"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For those with Intel laptop models that are quick to run hot and happen to find your laptop battery quickly being drained even when it should be in a deep sleep state, a solution is in the works for the Linux kernel that ultimately stems from S0ix failing due to the PCH overheating...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tor project upgrades network speed performance with new system]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/tor-project-upgrades-network-speed-performance-with-new-system/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/tor-project-upgrades-network-speed-performance-with-new-system/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T11:26:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Tor Project has published details about a newly introduced system called Congestion Control that promises to eliminate speed limits on the network. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Working On Linux Encrypted Hibernation Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-Encrypted-Hibernation</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-Encrypted-Hibernation"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T11:18:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google engineers are working on encrypted hibernation support for the Linux kernel as part of offering strong hibernation support for Google Chromebook usage...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ghacks Deals: Password Boss Premium: Lifetime Subscription (Unlimited Devices)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178407</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/05/05/ghacks-deals-password-boss-premium-lifetime-subscription-unlimited-devices/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T11:11:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Password Boss is a cross-platform password manager, that has a strong focus on security. The premium version of the password manager allows one user to install the password manager on an unlimited […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Ghacks Deals: Password Boss Premium: Lifetime Subscription (Unlimited Devices) appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VMware's SVGA Gallium3D Driver Getting NIR'ed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=VMware-SVGA-NIR-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=VMware-SVGA-NIR-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T11:10:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following the open-source NVIDIA "Nouveau" driver switching to NIR by default, the VMware SVGA Gallium3D driver has also landed NIR-to-TGSI support in mainline...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch guided install is pretty good now]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uiv0xr/arch_guided_install_is_pretty_good_now/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uiv0xr/arch_guided_install_is_pretty_good_now/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T11:07:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[just checked out the archinstall script on a vm to see how easy it is. I wanted to see if it's not too hard for me recommend a friend to try arch. 
 It took me like 1hr to get this on a VM and install stuff like aur helper and add chaotic aur to the repos. the install process is extremely easy to get this set up very quickly. 
 If I have friends who want to start using linux and if they are the kind of people who can read wiki or browse forum thread if they have issues, I will just recommend vanilla arch + kde from now on. 
 If I could change 1 thing, it's uncomment the line in visudo to allow wheel group users to do sudo
    submitted by    /u/Incalculas  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lenovo's New Slim 9i Laptop Is Drop-Dead Gorgeous]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/116975/lenovos-new-slim-9i-laptop-is-drop-dead-gorgeous/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/116975/lenovos-new-slim-9i-laptop-is-drop-dead-gorgeous/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T11:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lenovo is continuing its successful Slim laptop lineup with five new machines, including the gorgeous and glassy Slim 9i. All of these laptops cater to an on-the-go lifestyle, though some have an explicit focus on hybrid work, creativity, or gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Achtung! How Wolfenstein 3D Shocked the World, 30 Years Later]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=802248</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/802248/how-wolfenstein-3d-shocked-the-world-30-years-later/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T11:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thirty years ago today, id Software released Wolfenstein 3D, a thrilling first-person shooter game set during World War II. It broke new ground for action-based PC games and continued a string of growing successes for id Software. With help from John Carmack, John Romero, and Tom Hall, we’ll take a look at what made it special.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VirtualBox installation: vboxdrv module not found]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uiurka/virtualbox_installation_vboxdrv_module_not_found/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uiurka/virtualbox_installation_vboxdrv_module_not_found/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T10:50:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, I'm trying to install VirtualBox with this tutorial: https://wiki.archlinux.org/title/Virtua … inux_hosts
 I'm running into the issue that I can't load the vboxdrv or any other vbox kernel module because the kernel modules are installed in the wrong folder somehow. More on that later.
 Here is precisely what I've done so far:
 # pacman -S virtualbox-host-modules-arch virtualbox-guest-iso
 # pacman -S linux-headers
 # reboot
 After the reboot I get the following error when trying to load a module
 # modprobe vboxdrv
 modprobe: FATAL: Module vboxdrv not found in directory /lib/modules/5.17.3-arch1-1
 When looking into the /lib/modules folder I find: 
 # pacman -Ql linux-headers | grep vbox
 linux-headers /usr/lib/modules/5.17.5-arch1-1/build/drivers/gpu/drm/vboxvideo/
 linux-headers /usr/lib/modules/5.17.5-arch1-1/build/drivers/gpu/drm/vboxvideo/Kconfig
 linux-headers /usr/lib/modules/5.17.5-arch1-1/build/drivers/virt/vboxguest/
 linux-headers /usr/lib/modules/5.17.5-arch1-1/build/drivers/virt/vboxguest/Kconfig
 linux-headers /usr/lib/modules/5.17.5-arch1-1/build/fs/vboxsf/
 linux-headers /usr/lib/modules/5.17.5-arch1-1/build/fs/vboxsf/Kconfig
 linux-headers /usr/lib/modules/5.17.5-arch1-1/build/include/linux/vbox_utils.h
 linux-headers /usr/lib/modules/5.17.5-arch1-1/build/include/uapi/linux/vbox_err.h
 linux-headers /usr/lib/modules/5.17.5-arch1-1/build/include/uapi/linux/vbox_vmmdev_types.h
 linux-headers /usr/lib/modules/5.17.5-arch1-1/build/include/uapi/linux/vboxguest.h
 # pacman -Q linux
 linux 5.17.3.arch1-1
 # uname -r
 5.17.3-arch1-1
 Ok so I understand the issue. Somehow the wrong version of vbox linux headers is installed. But why? I found a temporary fix: renaming the folders to my current kernel version. But this only works till the next kernel update.
 Is there a better solution?
    submitted by    /u/Hellstorme  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TLStorm 2.0: a rischio milioni di switch di rete. Applicare le patch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=TLStorm-20-a-rischio-milioni-di-switch-di-rete-Applicare-le-patch_24473</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=TLStorm-20-a-rischio-milioni-di-switch-di-rete-Applicare-le-patch_24473"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T10:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A marzo scorso avevamo parlato del problema di sicurezza scoperto nei gruppi di continuità APC Smart-UPS: battezzato TLStorm poteva essere utilizzato dai criminali informatici per modificare il comportamento dei dispositivi, causare sovraccarichi e provocare gravi danni.La causa principale di queste vulnerabilità derivava da un uso improprio di NanoSSL, una popolare libreria per la gestione dei dati utilizzando l'algoritmo crittografico TLS.I tecnici di Armis hanno però scoperto che il problema riguarda anche milioni di switch di rete a marchio Aruba Networks (HPE) e Avaya.Il problema di sicurezza riscontrato sugli switch di rete è stato battezzato TLStorm 2.0: in questo caso le varie vulnerabilità, sempre correlate con l'utilizzo della libreria NanoSSL, permetterebbero a un aggressore di assumere pieno controllo sugli switch utilizzati in aeroporti, ospedali, hotel e altre organizzazioni in tutto il mondo.Armis ha accertato che sia Aruba Networks che Avaya hanno a catalogo switch che espongono a vulnerabilità RCE (remote code execution) che possono essere sfruttate anche in modalità remota.L'utente malintenzionato o il criminale informatico possono così superare le politiche di segmentazione della rete facendosi largo all'interno della rete LAN e raggiungendo altri dispositivi.Diventa inoltre possibile modificare in profondità il comportamento dello switch con la possibilità di analizzare il traffico di rete ed estrarre dati personali e informazioni sensibili.Infine, è possibile usare le vulnerabilità individuate da Armis per superare eventuali captive portal ovvero le pagine di registrazione e autenticazione che molte realtà propongono agli utenti per raccogliere informazioni sulla loro identità prima di consentire l'accesso alla WiFi.Utilizzando le vulnerabilità TLStorm 2.0, un aggressore può abusare del captive portal e ottenere l'esecuzione di codice remoto sullo switch senza bisogno di autenticazione.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intuit Forced to Pay $141M for Deceiving TurboTax Customers]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=486258</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15275543/intuit-deceiving-turbotax-customers"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T10:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tax time is always stressful – you sit down at your computer and just want to get it done! It makes it easy to just take the first easy, cheap method you find when Googling. This is behind the agreement between Intuit and multiple states for Intuit to pay $141M to TurboTax customers who were deceived by advertisements promising “free.”
   
Also read:The Best All-In-One CRM Software for Freelancers and Creatives
    
“Free, Free, Free
    
All 50 states and the District of Columbia came together to agree that Intuit should repay customers who paid a fee to file their taxes with TurboTax when they could have done so for free. Additionally, Intuit will be required to suspend TurboTax’s deceptive “free, free, free” ads. 
    
News of this agreement appeared on New York Attorney General Letitia James’s official blog. New York TurboTax customers will receive more than $5.4 million collectively.
    
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does anyone know where I can install "lc3plus" ?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uiu54d/does_anyone_know_where_i_can_install_lc3plus/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uiu54d/does_anyone_know_where_i_can_install_lc3plus/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T10:05:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Been trying to build pipewire-git from the AUR and everytime it start the builds process, I get a missing dependency, see below:
 Run-time dependency lc3plus found: NO (tried pkgconfig and cmake)
 ../pipewire/spa/meson.build:59:6: ERROR: C header 'lc3plus.h' not found
    submitted by    /u/_KOALA420_  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alchemist/DG2 Compute, Tigerlake+ Security Fix Head To Intel's Linux 5.19 Graphics Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-More-GT-Next-5.19</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-More-GT-Next-5.19"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T09:53:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are nearing the cut-off for new feature code to land in the DRM-Next display/graphics drivers for Linux 5.19 while this morning Intel engineers sent in a final drm-intel-gt-next feature update ahead of this next kernel...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox 101 Beta brings back the download prompt allowing users to choose whether to open or save files]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178397</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/05/05/mozilla-firefox-101-beta-download-prompt-for-opening-and-saving-files/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T09:49:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla changed the download behavior of Firefox when it released version 97 of the browser, by skipping the prompt that allowed users to choose whether to Open a file, save it, or […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Firefox 101 Beta brings back the download prompt allowing users to choose whether to open or save files appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows non parte: risolvere i problemi in avvio con Macrium Reflect]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-non-parte-risolvere-i-problemi-in-avvio-con-Macrium-Reflect_24472</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-non-parte-risolvere-i-problemi-in-avvio-con-Macrium-Reflect_24472"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T09:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Una delle soluzioni più apprezzate per creare backup dei sistemi Windows e clonare hard disk su SSD è Macrium Reflect.In versione gratuita anche per professionisti e aziende Macrium Reflect integra tante caratteristiche meno conosciute nascoste 'sotto il cofano'.Una tra tutte è viBoot che permette di creare il backup di un PC e di avviarlo su un altro sistema come macchina virtuale Hyper-V o Virtualbox. E scusate se è poco…L'impostazione e l'effettuazione di backup pianificati è la principale caratteristica offerta da Macrium Reflect, un programma che può essere tuttavia utilizzato anche per risolvere i problemi all'avvio di Windows.Se Windows non parte e la riparazione automatica del sistema operativo al boot non funziona, Macrium Reflect integra uno strumento per risolvere.
Macrium Reflect: come risolvere i problemi all'avvio quando Windows non parte
 Macrium Reflect non semplifica soltanto il backup dei dati e la clonazione del sistema ma integra uno strumento per avviare Windows quando si verifica un problema al boot.

Il primo passo consiste nel creare il supporto di avvio di emergenza di Macrium Reflect: basta avviare il programma, cliccare sul menu Other Tasks quindi scegliere Create Rescue Media.

La schermata che appare consente di creare un supporto di boot perfettamente cucito sulle proprie esigenze: cliccando su Show more Macrium Reflect mostra con una serie di Sì/No (Y/N) le funzioni che saranno inserite nel supporto di avvio.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MediaTek MT8186 Display Support, Other SoC Enablement Coming To Linux 5.19]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=MediaTek-MT8186-Linux-5.19</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=MediaTek-MT8186-Linux-5.19"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T09:26:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MediaTek has not officially announced the MT8186 SoC yet but there has been references to it within Chrome OS sources for months and various speculations about this new Chromebook-focused SoC. With Linux 5.19 there is going to be a lot of MT8186 enablement code landing...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heroku admits that customer credentials were stolen in cyberattack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/heroku-admits-that-customer-credentials-were-stolen-in-cyberattack/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/heroku-admits-that-customer-credentials-were-stolen-in-cyberattack/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T08:06:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Heroku has now revealed that the stolen GitHub integration OAuth tokens from last month further led to the compromise of an internal customer database. The Salesforce-owned cloud platform acknowledged the same compromised token was used by attackers to exfiltrate customers' hashed and salted passwords from "a database." [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ax Sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C2 Backup e C2 Password: proteggere i dati su PC, workstation e server]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=C2-Backup-e-C2-Password-proteggere-i-dati-su-PC-workstation-e-server_24471</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=C2-Backup-e-C2-Password-proteggere-i-dati-su-PC-workstation-e-server_24471"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T08:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Proteggere i dati e applicare politiche di backup efficaci è essenziale per mantenere la continuità operativa anche in caso di incidenti. Abilitare la tecnica RAID su server, workstation e NAS è certamente buona cosa ma in caso di disastri può non essere sufficiente: si pensi a un sistema che viene fisicamente danneggiato o sottratto. In queste situazioni i dati che per maggior sicurezza sono stati copiati su più unità non risulteranno recuperabili.Per non parlare del fatto che in molti casi il versioning non viene attivato quindi non è possibile risalire al contenuto di una cartella o di una versione precedente dello stesso file: si pensi a un documento modificato in modo maldestro o a un'aggressione ransomware.Con la piattaforma Synology C2 i dati aziendali, del professionista e dell'utente privato vengono gestiti in totale sicurezza e con un approccio centralizzato.Obiettivo di Synology C2 è quello di snellire la complessità nella gestione delle configurazioni hardware e software.Formata da diversi 'moduli' che si occupano di gestire a 360 gradi le esigenze di privati, professionisti e aziende in tema di protezione dei dati, Synology C2 consta di due vere e proprie punte di diamante.La prima si chiama C2 Backup ed è una soluzione centralizzata per proteggere i workload aziendali e personali tenendo i dati al sicuro; la seconda è C2 Password, uno strumento evoluto per salvare, sincronizzare e gestire le credenziali di accesso avendole sempre a disposizione dove e quando serve.
Cos'è e come funziona Synology C2 Backup
 Alla base di C2 Backup vi è la volontà di rivoluzionare il concetto di backup tradizionale non limitandosi più soltanto ai file ma anche alla creazione di copie di sicurezza delle applicazioni e del contenuto di interi PC (cosiddetto backup bare-metal).

L'utente o l'amministratore del servizio non devono fare altro che pianificare la periodicità con cui devono essere creati i vari backup su ciascuna macchina e C2 Backup penserà al resto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creare password sicura: oggi ricorre il World Password Day]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Creare-password-sicura-oggi-ricorre-il-World-Password-Day_15456</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Creare-password-sicura-oggi-ricorre-il-World-Password-Day_15456"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T07:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oggi ricorre il World Password Day, importante evento a livello mondiale pensato per sensibilizzare gli utenti sull'importanza della scelta di password efficaci e della loro conservazione sicura.Diversi studi via via pubblicati dalle principali società attive nel settore della sicurezza informatica sono concordi: ancora oggi una buona fetta di utenti si serve della stessa password a protezione di più account. Si tratta di una pratica sconsiderata perché può esporre dati personali e informazioni sensibili alla mercé dei malintenzionati allorquando uno solo dei propri account venisse in qualche modo violato.

Recenti studi riportano che gli aggressori informatici lanciano ogni giorno una media di 50 milioni di attacchi alle password ovvero circa 580 al secondo. E sono molto efficaci: il 60% delle violazioni sui dati sono attribuite a credenziali compromesse.Un italiano su tre utilizza ancora oggi sempre la stessa password o varianti di una password principale mentre quasi la metà delle persone modifica la propria password una volta all'anno o non la cambia mai.Per quanto riguarda la gestione delle password in molti provano a tenerle a mente, altri le annotano su supporti cartacei mentre una minima parte usa password manager.Di primo acchito tenere a mente le password può sembrare una buona tecnica ma l'alta percentuale di utenti che ricorre a questa tecnica indica che molti utilizzano password facili da ricordare e quindi semplici da indovinare con attacchi di forza bruta e tecniche di social engineering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung Internet 17.0 Browser released: anti-tracking and usability improvements]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178392</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/05/05/samsung-internet-17-0-browser-released-anti-tracking-and-usability-improvements/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T04:30:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung Electronics released Samsung Internet 17.0, the company's official mobile browser, on May 4, 2022. The new version of Samsung's browser blocks Internet tracking automatically and improves the usability in several meaningful […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Samsung Internet 17.0 Browser released: anti-tracking and usability improvements appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[libtinfo.so.6 expecting an older version of GLIBC - How to resolve?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uioh0u/libtinfoso6_expecting_an_older_version_of_glibc/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uioh0u/libtinfoso6_expecting_an_older_version_of_glibc/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T03:40:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I get the following error
 libc.so.6: version `GLIBC_2.33' not found (required by /usr/lib/libtinfo.so.6) 
 My system has `GLIBC_2.35-3
 When I look at libtinfo.so.6 I see that it is symlinked libncursew.so.6
 Any tips on how I can run this issue down and find an solution?
    submitted by    /u/cvandyke01  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I created an AUR package which disabled malcontent/flatpak for extra/gnome-control-center]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uimg65/i_created_an_aur_package_which_disabled/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uimg65/i_created_an_aur_package_which_disabled/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T01:53:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Due to the recent update of extra/gnome-control-center, it depends on malcontent(which depends on flatpak) for parent control and entreprise login. I am wondering how many poeple using archlinux need these features and install flatpak on their system...
 So I simply disabled the malcontent flag in the PKGBUILD and removed the depends, it's a very easy work.
 https://aur.archlinux.org/packages/gnome-control-center-noflatpak
    submitted by    /u/Weiliang_1503  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to View Blurred Text on Websites]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=post-ideas&amp;p=473513</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15274503/view-blurred-text-websites"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you bump into a block of blurred text while browsing, there’s no need to turn your back in disappointment or impulsively pay for a subscription. You can unblur the text with one of the methods below and take the time to assess whether you really want to sign up for the content.
   

Content

Why Do Websites Blur Content?
1. Use Google Translate as a Proxy to View Hidden Text
2. View a Snapshot on Internet Archive 
3. Open the Page From Google Search
4. View Blurred Content With Inspect Element
5. Switch to Reader Mode
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:7 of the Best Google Chrome Extensions to Annotate Text on the Web
    
Why Do Websites Blur Content?
    
Websites blurring text is a common practice to keep their content... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Natalie dela Vega</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pulseaudio Issue]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uiknnv/pulseaudio_issue/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uiknnv/pulseaudio_issue/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T00:21:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey everyone, I'm running arch with gnome + pulse audio and nvidia gpu.
 I updated my system today and now pulseaudio is misbehaving, every time I go to watch a YouTube video or play anything that requires sound, I have to execute <pulseaudio -k> to restart PA and this seems to get it working for a bit. But when I move on to something else, I need to run the kill command again...
 Not sure what the issue is and any help is appreciated.
    submitted by    /u/AmbrosYTC  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[System76 Releases v1.1 Scheduler For Optimizing Linux Desktop/Laptop Responsiveness]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=System76-Scheduler-1.1</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=System76-Scheduler-1.1"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T22:42:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[System76 has released a new version of the System76-Scheduler, it's Rust-written CPU scheduler designed to improve desktop responsiveness on their Pop!_OS Linux distribution...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[F5 warns of critical BIG-IP RCE bug allowing device takeover]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/f5-warns-of-critical-big-ip-rce-bug-allowing-device-takeover/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/f5-warns-of-critical-big-ip-rce-bug-allowing-device-takeover/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T22:16:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[F5 has issued a security advisory warning about a flaw that may allow unauthenticated attackers with network access to execute arbitrary system commands, perform file actions, and disable services on BIG-IP. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come reinstallare il terminale di Windows 11 quando manca nel sistema operativo]]></title>
        <id>3552|20220505000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/windows-10/come-reinstallare-terminale-windows-11-quando-manca-sistema-operativo-3552"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dopo l’aggiornamento da Windows 10 a Windows 11 del mio portatile, oltre alla mancata apertura di Microsoft Defender, mi sono accorto che il Terminale di Windows era sparito.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Completely and securely wipe home folder such that the base system remains intact, but I can safely sell the computer with no remains of my home - how can I do that?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uihedb/completely_and_securely_wipe_home_folder_such/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uihedb/completely_and_securely_wipe_home_folder_such/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T21:44:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/kappaphw  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add a Different Wallpaper to Each Android Home Screen]]></title>
        <id>http://maketecheasier.com/?p=58591</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15274278/add-different-wallpaper-android-home-screen"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Android devices have many different home screens. The problem is, when you choose an image as the background wallpaper, it spans across all the screens or just repeats. While that may be fine, sometimes you want to see something different. Here we will show you how to add a different wallpaper to each Android home screen, with Multipicture Live Wallpaper.
   

Content

What Does Multipicture Live Wallpaper Do?
Adding an Image to an Android Home Screen
Things to Consider
Create Your Own Multi-Screen Wallpaper
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Turn a Picture into Wallpaper on Android (And Make It Fit)
    
What Does Multipicture Live Wallpaper Do?
    
Multipicture Live Wallpaper splits up all of your home screens so that the wallpaper and/or background can be chosen for each screen independently... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Crystal Crowder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft 3D Movie Maker From 1995 Is Now Open-Source]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=803277</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/803277/microsoft-3d-movie-maker-from-1995-is-now-open-source/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T21:15:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software and game preservation is an increasingly important topic, and the best way to keep software accessible for future generations is by releasing the original source code. That’s exactly what just happened for Microsoft 3D Movie Maker, originally released in 1995.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to split the tty in the installation screen?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uigkqr/how_to_split_the_tty_in_the_installation_screen/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uigkqr/how_to_split_the_tty_in_the_installation_screen/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T21:05:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I watching this video and I noticed the guy splitting the tty horizontally. How's this possible? I was under the impression you can only switch instances with alt+f1-f12, and that's always a fullscreen instance.
    submitted by    /u/AlpinDale  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the Avira Rescue System to Clean Your Infected PC]]></title>
        <id>http://www.howtogeek.com/?p=38889</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/howto/38889/how-to-use-the-avira-rescue-cd-to-clean-your-infected-pc/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you’ve got a PC completely infected with viruses, sometimes it’s best to reboot into a rescue disc and run a full virus scan from there. Here’s how to use the Avira Rescue System to clean an infected PC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lowell Heddings</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Upgrading personal security on Arch Linux/Windows 11 dual boot: disk encryption with FIDO2 and secure boot using sbctl]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uifn3q/upgrading_personal_security_on_arch_linuxwindows/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uifn3q/upgrading_personal_security_on_arch_linuxwindows/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T20:21:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/saligrama-a  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is it common for this problem to occur?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uif9r6/is_it_common_for_this_problem_to_occur/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uif9r6/is_it_common_for_this_problem_to_occur/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T20:04:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is it common for any of you guys to have a problem where your Desktop Environment doesn't boot up properly because of the "API mismatch error client has version x.x.x but this kernal module has y.y.y" after you do a full system update? I had this issue twice, one literally right now, and the other only months ago, I fixed it by regenerating my initramfs, but it's strange the same issue happened so soon after one another.
    submitted by    /u/cheeseDickies  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Turn Off Do Not Disturb Mode on iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=796556</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/796556/how-to-turn-off-do-not-disturb-on-iphone/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T20:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your iPhone’s Do Not Disturb mode blocks your calls, alerts, and notifications. If you’d like to start receiving those items, turn Do Not Disturb mode off on your phone. We’ll show you two different ways to do just that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco fixes NFVIS bugs that help gain root and hijack hosts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisco-fixes-nfvis-bugs-that-help-gain-root-and-hijack-hosts/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisco-fixes-nfvis-bugs-that-help-gain-root-and-hijack-hosts/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T19:58:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco has addressed several security flaws found in the Enterprise NFV Infrastructure Software (NFVIS), a solution that helps virtualize network services for easier management of virtual network functions (VNFs). [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does Running the A/C or Heat Lower Your EV Range?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/116956/does-running-the-a-c-or-heat-lower-your-ev-range/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/116956/does-running-the-a-c-or-heat-lower-your-ev-range/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T19:26:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re interested in buying a new electric vehicle (EV), you probably have several battery-related questions, including wondering, “does running the A/C lower my EV range?” No one wants to get stranded with a dead battery on a hot summer day or snowy winter evening.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save $50 on an Amazon Echo Show 15 Smart Display]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=485943</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15274070/amazon-echo-show-15-smart-display"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Echo Shows can do so many things that it leaves you wishing there was more space to do all those things. Now you can have that. To go along with the Echo Show 5 and Echo Show 8, there is now an Amazon Echo Show 15 Smart Display with a 15.6″ screen. It gives you a larger playing field while doing all the same things you love of the smaller displays and more. Despite just being released five months ago, it’s now $50 off.
    
The large Full HD smart display has a 5 MP camera and provides you with a natural place to organize your household. You get widgets, shared calendars, “sticky notes,” to-do lists, shopping lists, and reminders. You can also add your smart devices to the home screen to have quick access to them.
    
Get recipe ideas on the Amazon Echo Show 15 Smart Display, then cook while following step-by-step instructions. Run out of something? Add it to your shopping list. Don’t feel like cooking? Order a meal kit or takeout.
    
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mesa 22.1-rc4 Released With More Zink + Kopper Fixes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Mesa-22.1-rc4-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Mesa-22.1-rc4-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T19:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another week of fixes and backports have collected for Mesa 22.1 and now available for testing in the form of Mesa 22.1-rc4...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Start a New Line in a Cell in Google Sheets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=796302</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/796302/new-line-in-google-sheets-cell/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T19:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks to Google Sheets’ ability to create new lines within a single cell, you can prevent your cell’s content from overflowing. Your extra cell content is put on a new line, and here are two ways to make that happen in your spreadsheets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pixiv, DeviantArt artists hit by NFT job offers pushing malware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/pixiv-deviantart-artists-hit-by-nft-job-offers-pushing-malware/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/pixiv-deviantart-artists-hit-by-nft-job-offers-pushing-malware/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T18:46:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Users on Pixiv, DeviantArt, and other creator-oriented online platforms report receiving multiple messages from people claiming to be from the "Cyberpunk Ape Executives" NFT project, with the main goal to infect artists' devices with information-stealing malware. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Attackers hijack UK NHS email accounts to steal Microsoft logins]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/attackers-hijack-uk-nhs-email-accounts-to-steal-microsoft-logins/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/attackers-hijack-uk-nhs-email-accounts-to-steal-microsoft-logins/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T18:17:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For about half a year, work email accounts belonging to over 100 employees of the National Health System (NHS) in the U.K. were used in several phishing campaigns, some aiming to steal Microsoft logins. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Ilascu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Share a Playlist on Apple Music]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=796614</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/796614/how-to-share-a-playlist-on-apple-music/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T18:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sharing playlists is a great way to introduce friends to your favorite music. It’s easy on Apple Music, though sometimes you can run into problems. We’ll show you how to share your playlist, and what to do if you’re not seeing the option.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kris Wouk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Is the Best Time to Sell Your Home]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lifesavvy.com/127587/this-is-the-best-time-to-sell-your-home/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lifesavvy.com/127587/this-is-the-best-time-to-sell-your-home/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T18:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s definitely a seller’s market in real estate right now, so it’s no wonder that many people have been considering putting their property up for sale. But when it comes to getting even more of a return on your investment, is there a “best time” to sell?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shea Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heroku forces user password resets but fails to explain why]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/heroku-forces-user-password-resets-but-fails-to-explain-why/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/heroku-forces-user-password-resets-but-fails-to-explain-why/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T17:57:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Salesforce-owned Heroku is performing a forced password reset on a subset of user accounts in response to last month's security incident while providing no information as to why they are doing so other than vaguely mentioning it is to further secure accounts. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows Terminal: prompt dei comandi avanzato per Windows 10 e 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-Terminal-prompt-dei-comandi-avanzato-per-Windows-10-e-11_20541</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-Terminal-prompt-dei-comandi-avanzato-per-Windows-10-e-11_20541"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T17:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tutti conoscono il prompt dei comandi Windows (cmd) e la finestra di PowerShell di Windows 10 e Windows 11 normalmente accessibile premendo la combinazione di tasti Windows+X e scegliendo Windows PowerShell (amministratore) oppure Windows PowerShell, a seconda che si voglia aprire con i diritti di amministratore o meno (Terminale Windows e Terminale Windows (Admin) in Windows 11).Digitando Sostituisci il prompt dei comandi nella casella di ricerca di Windows 10 e attivando o disattivando l''interruttore' Sostituisci il prompt dei comandi con Windows PowerShell nel menu quando si fa clic con il pulsante destro del mouse nell'angolo inferiore sinistro o si preme il tasto Windows+X, è possibile scegliere se far apparire nel menu il prompt dei comandi tradizionale o Windows PowerShell.

In Windows 11 l'impostazione Sostituisci il prompt dei comandi non esiste più.In occasione della conferenza Microsoft Build 2019, ormai anni fa, i responsabili dell'azienda di Redmond presentarono Windows Terminal, un nuovo prompt dei comandi basato capace di adattarsi alle esigenze di ogni utente.Tramite Windows Terminal si possono comodamente avviare finestre del tradizionale prompt dei comandi, di Windows PowerShell, di Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSL) e di Azure Cloud Shell.Da luglio 2020 l'azienda di Redmond ha cominciato a distribuire aggiornamenti mensili di Windows Terminal migliorandone continuamente le funzionalità.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung’s UFS 4.0 Might Make Your Next Phone Faster]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=803156</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/803156/samsungs-ufs-4.0-might-make-your-next-phone-faster/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T17:40:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Universal Flash Storage, or UFS for short, is the storage technology used by many smartphones and other devices. Samsung has now unveiled its implementation of UFS 4.0, a faster upgraded version that might appear in your next phone or tablet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft 3D Movie Maker Released As Open-Source]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Microsoft-3D-Movie-Maker</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Microsoft-3D-Movie-Maker"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T17:14:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has made public the source code to the original Microsoft 3D Movie Maker software...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to “Undo” on iPhone: 4 Different Ways]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=800327</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/800327/how-to-undo-on-iphone/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve made a mistake while typing on an iPhone—or you accidentally deleted a bunch of text—you might wonder: Can you undo it? The answer is usually yes, and there are at least four different ways to do it. Here’s how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save Hundreds on These Roborock Robot Vacuums]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=803121</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/803121/save-hundreds-on-these-roborock-robot-vacuums/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While we can’t promise you the wisdom of the Jedi on this May Fourth, you can at least pretend your Midichlorian count is off the charts as you direct your brand new robot vacuum around the house without lifting a finger. Find a slew of discounts on Roborock vacuums, plus iPads, a Wi-Fi mesh system, and plenty more in this week’s How-To Geek Deals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zach Laidlaw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mint Mobile's Cheap Phone Plans Come to the Whole "Family"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/116944/mint-mobiles-cheap-phone-plans-come-to-the-whole-family/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/116944/mint-mobiles-cheap-phone-plans-come-to-the-whole-family/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T16:58:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Phone plans are expensive, especially for families. Mint Mobile, an MNVO that sells prepaid plans, has often laid claim to some of the most affordable plans—for individuals. Now the company is ready to offer family plans, and as expected, they come in at low prices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Hendrickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Razer's Stormtrooper Xbox Controller Will Probably Miss Every Shot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/116958/razers-stormtrooper-xbox-controller-will-probably-miss-every-shot/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/116958/razers-stormtrooper-xbox-controller-will-probably-miss-every-shot/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T16:55:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve ever wanted to shoot like a clumsy Stormtrooper, now’s the time to crack open your piggy bank. Razer just launched a limited Stormtrooper Xbox controller to celebrate Star Wars Day. It features a unique paint job and a speedy charging stand, though unfortunately, it’s a bit expensive.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[extra/gnome-control-center needs flatpak now?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uib37e/extragnomecontrolcenter_needs_flatpak_now/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uib37e/extragnomecontrolcenter_needs_flatpak_now/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T16:54:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[i recently switched from ubuntu gnome to arch gnome and after updating arch i found out that the gnome-control-center needs flatpak now? flatpak isn't even in the listed on the arch site. 
 i tried using it but i got a major pulseaudio bug so i uninstalled it right away. any ideas if intentional or not?
    submitted by    /u/dailyduude  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaricare Adobe Acrobat Reader DC per Windows 10 e 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2012/10/scaricare-adobe-reader-11-xi.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2012/10/scaricare-adobe-reader-11-xi.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T16:42:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adobe Acrobat Reader DC è il programma principale per aprire e leggere i documenti PDF, un formato creato dalla Adobe stessa e diventato in poco tempo un punto di riferimento per la condivisione dei documenti. Nel corso degli anni si sono susseguite varie versioni, ma la versione DC è ormai da tempo l'unica disponibile (anche se regolarmente aggiornata). Essa è perfettamente compatibile con...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[is it possible to enable hibernation using zram swap]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uiadnb/is_it_possible_to_enable_hibernation_using_zram/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uiadnb/is_it_possible_to_enable_hibernation_using_zram/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T16:23:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[i installed arch linux through archinstall and i added zram instead of swap. when i first tried to hibernate it simply shutdown my laptop so i went to arch wiki and saw that hibernation was not an easy task. first thing required is a swap partiton. i have a zram partition . is it possible for me to swap on zram and enable hibernation
    submitted by    /u/Arnavgr  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FBI says business email compromise is a $43 billion scam]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fbi-says-business-email-compromise-is-a-43-billion-scam/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fbi-says-business-email-compromise-is-a-43-billion-scam/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T16:19:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) said today that the amount of money lost to business email compromise (BEC) scams continues to grow each year, with a 65% increase in the identified global exposed losses between July 2019 and December 2021. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Open Sourced Its 3D Movie Maker Program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/116952/microsoft-open-sourced-its-3d-movie-maker-program/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/116952/microsoft-open-sourced-its-3d-movie-maker-program/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T16:10:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you think of 1995, you probably envision malls, baggy JNCO jeans, and MTV. But what you should picture is Microsoft’s weirdly fantastic 3D Movie Maker animation program. While the software was short-lived, you can now dive back in because Microsoft open-sourced it!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzanne Humphries</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Turn Your Raspberry Pi Into a DSLR with ArduCam's 64MP Camera Module]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/116928/turn-your-raspberry-pi-into-a-dslr-with-arducams-64mp-camera-module/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/116928/turn-your-raspberry-pi-into-a-dslr-with-arducams-64mp-camera-module/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T16:02:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Turning a Raspberry Pi into a camera is a relatively easy task, but the results aren’t always satisfactory. Official camera modules just don’t offer the resolution, autofocus, or digital zoom features that we expect from DSLRs or even smartphone cameras. Now, ArduCam is selling the Hawk-eye, an insane and fully-featured 64MP camera module for the Pi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Many eBooks Can Fit on a Kindle?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=801844</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/801844/how-many-ebooks-can-fit-on-a-kindle/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T16:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kindle eReaders have a few advantages over physical books. One of the biggest is simply the sheer quantity of books you can carry with you. Just how many eBooks can you fit on a Kindle? Let’s find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Plex Will Turn Your Raspberry Pi Into a DIY Chromecast Audio]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=803133</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/803133/plex-will-turn-your-raspberry-pi-into-a-diy-chromecast-audio/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T15:55:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plex is one of the best services for hosting your own media collection and streaming it to all your other devices, and now Plex’s developers are working on a way to stream your music to a Raspberry Pi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our New Favorite Robot Vacuum Is on Sale Now]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=801973</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/801973/our-new-favorite-robot-vacuum-goes-on-sale-today/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T15:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to robot vacuums, few companies push the boundaries of possibility as effectively as Roborock. Introducing features like advanced navigation with obstacle avoidance, industry-leading suction power, and an automatic bin emptying system, the company continues to redefine what a robot vacuum can do. This year, Roborock has truly outdone themselves by taking all of their fine-tuned innovations and cramming them into the brand new S7 MaxV Ultra, available for purchase starting today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zach Laidlaw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers stole data undetected from US, European orgs since 2019]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-stole-data-undetected-from-us-european-orgs-since-2019/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-stole-data-undetected-from-us-european-orgs-since-2019/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T15:46:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity analysts have exposed a lengthy operation attributed to the group of Chinese hackers known as "Winnti" and tracked as APT41, which focused on stealing intellectual property assets like patents, copyrights, trademarks, and other types of valuable data. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is the Matrix Protocol and How to Install It]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=470663</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15273557/install-matrix-protocol"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T15:25:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matrix is an innovative, open-source alternative to chat services such as Discord and Slack that is both feature-rich and easy to use. It fully supports end-to-end encryption and is available for almost all operating systems. You can also host it on your own server, making it a fully secure and private way to chat on the internet.
    
Here we will show you how you can install Matrix on your server.
   

Content

What Is the Matrix Protocol?
Why Use the Matrix Protocol?
Hosting Your Own Matrix Server
1. Installing Synapse
2. Set Up Synapse
3. Set Up SSL for Synapse
4. Create an User Account in Synapse
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:9 of the Best Email Clients for Linux
    
What Is the Matrix Protocol?
    
At its core, Matrix is a set of protocols that define how messages are... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramces Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polestar 2 EV Gets a Price Hike, but It's Not All Bad]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/116923/polestar-2-ev-gets-a-price-hike-but-its-not-all-bad/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/116923/polestar-2-ev-gets-a-price-hike-but-its-not-all-bad/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T15:24:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Polestar released a more affordable version of its popular Polestar 2 EV in the United States earlier this year, and now just a few months later, it’s getting a $2,500 price increase and a few new features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung Launches the Ultimate Dash Cam microSD Card]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/116919/samsung-launches-the-ultimate-dash-cam-microsd-card/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/116919/samsung-launches-the-ultimate-dash-cam-microsd-card/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T15:09:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’d think that microSD cards would be a bit more durable, given that they’ve been around for so long. But microSD cards are still somewhat unreliable. That’s why Samsung is now launching a PRO Endurance microSD card that can survive up to 16 years of continuous use in security cameras, dash cams, and other always-on devices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INDEX and MATCH vs. VLOOKUP vs. XLOOKUP in Microsoft Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=800574</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/800574/index-match-vs-vlookup-vs-xlookup/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T15:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lookup functions in Microsoft Excel are ideal for finding what you need when you have a large amount of data. There are three common ways to do this; INDEX and MATCH, VLOOKUP, and XLOOKUP. But what’s the difference?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub to require 2FA from active developers by the end of 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/github-to-require-2fa-from-active-developers-by-the-end-of-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/github-to-require-2fa-from-active-developers-by-the-end-of-2023/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub announced today that all users who contribute code on its platform (an estimated 83 million developers in total) will be required to enable two-factor authentication (2FA) on their accounts by the end of 2023. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AT&T Is Raising the Price of Grandfathered Cell Phone Plans]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=802983</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/802983/att-is-raising-the-price-of-grandfathered-cell-phone-plans/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T14:30:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mobile carriers like AT&T and Verizon rarely raise prices on existing phone plans, but it does happen from time to time. AT&T is now raising the monthly cost on select legacy plans, in an effort to push people to newer services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XPS 17 9710 Fingerprint?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ui7qqn/xps_17_9710_fingerprint/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ui7qqn/xps_17_9710_fingerprint/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T14:23:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Has anyone gotten the XPS 17 9710's integrated fingerprint sensor to be detected? I've been trying to get it to work with fingerprintd but it doesn't show up on the supported devices list.
    submitted by    /u/manafuzer  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UFS 4.0 raddoppia le prestazioni nella memorizzazione dei dati secondo Samsung]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=UFS-40-raddoppia-le-prestazioni-nella-memorizzazione-dei-dati-secondo-Samsung_24470</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=UFS-40-raddoppia-le-prestazioni-nella-memorizzazione-dei-dati-secondo-Samsung_24470"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T14:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung ha presentato l'ultima versione della sua memoria flash per lo storage dei dati sui dispositivi mobili. Si tratta di UFS 4.0 e promette significativi aumenti di prestazioni rispetto all'attuale versione 3.1.Oltre a progettare e produrre alcuni degli smartphone più popolari sul mercato (secondo Strategy Analytics Samsung detiene il 24% delle quote a livello globale) la società sudcoreana è uno dei produttori più 'gettonati' cui si affida buona parte dell'industria dei dispositivi mobili per l'acquisto di memorie flash.

Secondo i tecnici di Samsung UFS 4.0 permetterà di impegnare fino a 23,2 Gbps di banda per ogni canale raddoppiando le prestazioni di UFS 3.1. Si tratta di un throughput descritto come ottimale per i nuovi smartphone 5G vista la mole di dati che in futuro si troveranno a scaricare e gestire.La nuova memoria aiuterà anche a soddisfare i requisiti delle applicazioni per la realtà aumentata e virtuale.Combinando la settima generazione dei chip V-NAND Samsung e un controller proprietario, l'azienda è certa che sul mercato arriveranno presto dispositivi come smartphone e tablet in grado di leggere a 4.200 MB/s e scrivere fino a 2.800 MB/s.L'efficienza energetica è un altro vantaggio della nuova architettura che permetterà di trasferire dati nelle operazioni di lettura sequenziale fino a 6 MB/s per milliampere (mA).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come dimenticare una rete Wi-Fi su Android, iPhone e PC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/05/come-dimenticare-una-rete-wi-fi-su.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/05/come-dimenticare-una-rete-wi-fi-su.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T14:13:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quando ci connettiamo ad una rete Wi-Fi essa viene memorizzata all'interno del sistema operativo, così da poterci connettere automaticamente ogni volta che entriamo nella zona di copertura. Se nel frattempo abbiamo creato una nuova rete Wi-Fi o stiamo utilizzando un Range Extender, può essere una buona idea far dimenticare la vecchia rete, così da poterci connettere solo ed esclusivamente alla...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft: Windows 11 KB5012643 update will break some apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-windows-11-kb5012643-update-will-break-some-apps/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-windows-11-kb5012643-update-will-break-some-apps/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T14:06:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has warned Windows 11 users that they might experience issues launching and using some .NET Framework 3.5 applications. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using PowerShell to manage password resets in Windows domains]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/using-powershell-to-manage-password-resets-in-windows-domains/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/using-powershell-to-manage-password-resets-in-windows-domains/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With breaches running rampant, it's common to force password resets on your Windows domain. This article shows how admins can use PowerShell to manage password resets and introduce software that makes it even easier. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sponsored by Specops</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Gaming Chairs of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=793520</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/793520/best-gaming-chair/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T14:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you spend long hours at your computer or TV gaming, you need to make sure your chair is comfortable and properly supports your back and posture. These gaming chairs do all that and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sydney Butler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why is there a snap directory in my root even though I never used snap?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ui70et/why_is_there_a_snap_directory_in_my_root_even/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ui70et/why_is_there_a_snap_directory_in_my_root_even/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T13:49:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I just ran ls -l in /, and I noticed this interesting line of output:
 lrwxrwxrwx 1 root root 19 Jun 4 2021 snap -> /var/lib/snapd/snap 
 I never installed snap as far as I'm aware, does anyone know why this directory exists?
    submitted by    /u/yonatan8070  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>