<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-07-12T02:19:25.206Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Installing Nvidia drivers after successful boot leads to DE not starting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vwy4gr/installing_nvidia_drivers_after_successful_boot/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vwy4gr/installing_nvidia_drivers_after_successful_boot/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T00:51:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently wanted to get into arch, so I did my research and installed endeavour os. I booted it on my desktop (12700k and 3070) and everything worked fine. Installed Nvidia drivers using the Nvidia-installation-dkms package, restarted my computer and now I am stuck on a screen with a bunch of text. When I plug a usb device in, it'll come up listing the info, but it won't boot to the de. I am using KDE Plasma if that helps.
 Thanks again
    submitted by    /u/53-45-58-4D-41-4E  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MSI Click Bios 5 Doesn’t recognize linux as an option for booting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vwxwbp/msi_click_bios_5_doesnt_recognize_linux_as_an/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vwxwbp/msi_click_bios_5_doesnt_recognize_linux_as_an/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T00:40:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the title says, I can’t make Arch first (Or anywhere really) in boot priority.
 I can still just boot into Arch by mashing F11 as I boot up to then select Arch but that’s not exactly convenient
 I used archinstall to install Arch and I selected the systemd bootloader, feel free to ask for any other info
 What can I do to fix this?
    submitted by    /u/PearsArePrettyCool  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 Calling Apps to Make Free Phone Calls From Anywhere]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=486290</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15425821/free-phone-call-apps"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do expensive calling and texting plans keep you from staying in contact with friends and family? Ditch mobile calling plans and opt for calling apps to make free calls over Wi-Fi. They’ll also work over mobile data, but make sure you’ve got unlimited data so you don’t get hit with overages. While some of these apps give you your own number, others require both parties to have the same app. Either way, they’re free and you can call, text, and even video chat as much as you want.
   

Content

1. TextNow
2. Talkatone
3. Google Voice
4. Google Duo
5. Skype
6. Dingtone
7. TextFree
8. textPlus
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:6 Ways to Easily Send Text Messages (SMS) from Your PC
    
1. TextNow
    
Available for: iOS | Android | Windows
... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Crystal Crowder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD Is Hiring To Improve Its Linux Graphics Driver Installation Experience]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMD-Linux-Build-Engineer-Needed</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMD-Linux-Build-Engineer-Needed"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T23:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While AMD's open-source Linux graphics driver stack is wonderful if living on the bleeding-edge with a modern Linux distribution, for those on enterprise Linux distributions that tend to stick to older versions of packages for the support lifetime or where wanting to run a vetted/qualified driver stack, it can be more of a pain. For AMD's packaged Linux driver stack it only supports those select enterprise Linux distributions and can run into pain points trying to run elsewhere or even say running brand new LTS distributions at times can lack support. There are also challenges in installing/running the ROCm compute stack outside of the few officially supported Linux distributions by AMD. Fortunately, they are now hiring Linux build engineer(s) to work on such issues...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lenovo Yoga C390]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vwwozg/lenovo_yoga_c390/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vwwozg/lenovo_yoga_c390/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T23:42:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[anyone running arch on this? i was reading there were issues with the soundbar in the past, so I haven't switched it over yet but the impending doom of Win11 has me concerned.
    submitted by    /u/viewtifulstyle  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Installscript (archinstall) vs. manual Install]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vwwodp/installscript_archinstall_vs_manual_install/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vwwodp/installscript_archinstall_vs_manual_install/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T23:41:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The arch-wiki mentions that the (default) arch installscript has different defaults than the "regular installation". WikiArticle on archinstall
  
Is there a definition of the defaults resulting from a "regular installation" ?
 Where can I find a list of differences between the defaults from the installscript vs the defaults from "regular installation".
  
(I tried googling for about 15 minutes for both and found nothing, so: 3. What places (except the wiki)can I search to solve confusion/questions/problems like this on my own?)
 If there is it should probably be added to the wikiarticle, so that this source of confusion is removed.
 P.S.: please educate me on if this question should be asked in newcomer questions instead
    submitted by    /u/tristan_rw  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Owner report - Hp Victus 16 laptop with AMD RX5500M working perfectly with Arch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vwwbn6/owner_report_hp_victus_16_laptop_with_amd_rx5500m/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vwwbn6/owner_report_hp_victus_16_laptop_with_amd_rx5500m/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T23:24:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/btomik  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Plasma + Wayland on Laptop, Can't Detect External Monitors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vwvwr5/plasma_wayland_on_laptop_cant_detect_external/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vwvwr5/plasma_wayland_on_laptop_cant_detect_external/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T23:05:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi,
 I'll start this off by saying that I have a working Plasma + Xorg setup on this laptop. I'm trying to transition to Wayland based Plasma. I've gotten it working to the point where the laptop's display works, but it cannot detect other monitors.
 I've got a Intel cpu with a integrated graphics card in addition to a Nvidia dedicated GPU.
 So far I've tried to find a tool similar to xrandr (which I use to configure displays on my working setup) but for wayland, but non of the ones I've tried seem to support Plasma so far. I've also tried using KDE's display configuration tool, but it doesn't detect the displays either. 
 Any ideas, information to provide, or suggestions?
 ​
 Thanks
    submitted by    /u/SneakyTactician  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers can unlock Honda cars remotely in Rolling-PWN attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-can-unlock-honda-cars-remotely-in-rolling-pwn-attacks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-can-unlock-honda-cars-remotely-in-rolling-pwn-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T22:10:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A team of security researchers found that several modern Honda car models have a vulnerable rolling code mechanism that allows unlocking the cars or even starting the engine remotely. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come disattivare la navigazione anonima da Firefox]]></title>
        <id>3619|20220712000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/browser-455/come-disattivare-navigazione-anonima-firefox-3619"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Firefox è possibile utilizzare il browser in modalità anonima, cioè non lasciando traccia di quanto fatto in quella sessione di navigazione. Questo può andare bene quando si vuole aumentare la propria privacy, può andare meno bene in certi ambienti lavorativi, oppure in una biblioteca con un computer in uso a tutti o con i propri figli che vogliono nascondere di aver visitato certi siti. Vediamo quindi come fare per disattivare questa funzione.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Aqara Curtain Driver E1 Automates Your Existing Curtains]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/122815/the-aqara-curtain-driver-e1-automates-your-existing-curtains/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/122815/the-aqara-curtain-driver-e1-automates-your-existing-curtains/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T21:32:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re looking to bring aspects of your house into the modern era without going full-on smart home, Aqara has you covered. The popular smart home company just released its Aqara Smart Curtain Driver E1, which easily automates your existing curtains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Ways to Create and Share WhatsApp Profile Link]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=494152</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15425642/share-whatsapp-profile-link"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Social media accounts, in general, have a unique link that you share with others so that they can connect with you. You can do the same with WhatsApp as well by creating WhatsApp profile links. You can then proceed to use the profile link to share your WhatsApp account number with others. The recipient simply needs to open the profile link to connect directly with you on WhatsApp. Let’s look at 5 different ways to find and send someone your WhatsApp link.
   

Content

1. Share Your Phone Number Directly
2. Create a WhatsApp Link Manually
3. Generate WhatsApp Link Online
4. Generate WhatsApp Short Link on WhatsApp Business
5. Share WhatsApp QR Code
Bonus: Share WhatsApp Group Links
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:10 Best Sticker Packs for WhatsApp
    
1. Share Your Phone Number Directly
    
WhatsApp accounts do not have a username. Your phone number... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mehvish Mushtaq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up Amazon Household to Share Amazon Prime (and More)]]></title>
        <id>http://www.howtogeek.com/?p=248409</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/248409/how-to-set-up-amazon-household-and-share-prime-benefits-purchased-content-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Having multiple Amazon accounts can get pricey, if you pay for Prime multiple times, buy the same movies, and so on. Thankfully, Amazon Household makes it dead simple to share free shipping, purchases, and other benefits across multiple accounts in your household.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Fitzpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sony's Latest Rugged X-Series Bluetooth Speakers Are Ready to Party]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/122797/sonys-latest-rugged-x-series-bluetooth-speakers-are-ready-to-party/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/122797/sonys-latest-rugged-x-series-bluetooth-speakers-are-ready-to-party/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T20:49:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, Sony announced three new rugged Bluetooth speakers as part of its X-Series lineup, offering excellent sound at multiple price points, not to mention one with a retractable handle for outdoor adventures.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Massive Rogers outage caused by a maintenance update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/massive-rogers-outage-caused-by-a-maintenance-update/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/massive-rogers-outage-caused-by-a-maintenance-update/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T20:44:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the weekend, Rogers Communications CEO Tony Staffieri revealed the telecom company believes a maintenance update was what caused last week's massive outage. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Where efibootmgr entries located?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vwrnfo/where_efibootmgr_entries_located/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vwrnfo/where_efibootmgr_entries_located/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T20:04:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I installed Arch Linux with efibootmgr and I don't see an efi entry in the ESP, yes I can boot into Arch but where is this boot entry is located at? I have two ESPs, one for Windows and other for Arch Linux, I checked both in case it installs boot entry to other disk but no. While I can see Windows has a bootmgfw.efi file in it's own EFI partition, there is nothing related to Arch Linux or efibootmgr.
    submitted by    /u/vicelit47  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Prime Is More than Free Shipping: Here Are All of Its Extra Features]]></title>
        <id>http://www.howtogeek.com/?p=278486</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/278486/amazon-prime-is-more-than-free-shipping-here-are-all-of-its-extra-features/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Millions of people have an Amazon Prime subscription for one reason: you can get just about anything shipped to your house in two days, with no extra shipping fees. But Amazon Prime comes with a ton of other features that you may not know about. Here are all the ways you can maximize the value of your Prime membership.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Fitzpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Display laptop screen on TV through HDMI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vwrbr0/display_laptop_screen_on_tv_through_hdmi/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vwrbr0/display_laptop_screen_on_tv_through_hdmi/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T19:51:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, I have a laptop and a HDMI cable connected to both the laptop and the TV.
 I'm using X11 but I only have my eDP-1 laptop display on the xrandr output, and not the HDMI-1 that I also would expect. What could be causing this?
    submitted by    /u/SupremeOwlTerrorizer  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Now Try the iOS 16 and iPadOS 16 Public Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=817487</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/817487/you-can-now-try-the-ios-16-and-ipados-16-public-beta/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T19:37:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple showed off iOS 16 and iPadOS 16 last month at WWDC, the next major updates for the iPhone and iPad, respectively. Following several developer builds, the public beta is now ready for everyone to try.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save 25% on an LG 27″ Ultrascreen Gaming Monitor]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=479734</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15212434/lg-27-ultrascreen-gaming-monitor"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you spend much of your free time gaming, you want a monitor that’s going to work with you. The LG 27″ Ultrascreen Gaming Monitor could be the right one for the job. It has a 1ms response time, 240Hz refresh rate, a thin bezel, and NVIDIA G-SYNC compatible with AMD FreeSync Premium. This is the right time to pick it up, too, as it’s 25% off.
    
This gaming monitor is designed to work with you. It has the latest hardware, specs, and ergonomics, as well as the most sensory experience you will find. It has vivid, responsive IPS and a 16:9 screen ratio (1920 x 1080) with enhanced contrast, clarity, and details.
    
The HDR10 provides a more dynamic visual experience and enhances the color even more. The verified NVIDIA G-SYNC compatibility will bring faster, smoother gaming with less screen tearing and minimized stuttering and input lag. The AMD FreeSync Premium is built in.
   
 
   
You’ll enjoy the great speed and ultra-fast 1ms response rate of the LG Ultrascreen Gaming... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ransomware gang now lets you search their stolen data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ransomware-gang-now-lets-you-search-their-stolen-data/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ransomware-gang-now-lets-you-search-their-stolen-data/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T19:24:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two ransomware gangs and a data extortion group have adopted a new strategy to force victim companies to pay threat actors to not leak stolen data. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Ilascu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[System Wide Dark Mode?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vwqnyh/system_wide_dark_mode/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vwqnyh/system_wide_dark_mode/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T19:23:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey all,
 New to the Arch world and been loving it for the past few months, I've recently tried to customize my theme, and went ahead and installed all components necessary to run a Layan dark theme. 
 I've applied all the appearance settings to match that of Layan, yet my application windows (system settings, Dolphin) are wacky and not quite totally uniform/dark. The header will be black, yet the background will be white etc..
 ​
 See the screenshots here https://ibb.co/nmFH20g and https://ibb.co/FXdQ1P4.
 Some help would be greatly appreciated, I'm running the theme with Kvantum + am on X11 KDE plasma as my DE.
 ​
 Thank you :)
    submitted by    /u/lucatea  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Login to fish, instead of zsh in custom Arch ISO]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vwqfj9/login_to_fish_instead_of_zsh_in_custom_arch_iso/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vwqfj9/login_to_fish_instead_of_zsh_in_custom_arch_iso/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T19:14:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi,
 I am trying to make a custom Arch ISO, and wanted to know, how I can login to fish instead of the default zsh on startup. I mean, what files do I need to change? I am following the archiso wiki, currently. I found .zlogin, and .automated_script.sh in $work_dir/releng/airootfs/root/ so do I need to modify these files or do something else? Any help would be really appreciated.
 Thanks
    submitted by    /u/Clock_Suspicious  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Run Commands as Another User in Linux Scripts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=811255</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/811255/how-to-run-commands-as-another-user-in-linux-scripts/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T19:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Naturally enough, when you run a command or script the system executes it as a process that was launched by you. But you can run commands and scripts as another user.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKay</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Opera Browser is flooding the Windows Reliability Monitor with entries]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179654</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/07/11/opera-browser-is-flooding-the-windows-reliability-monitor-with-entries/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T18:02:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Opera users who run a recent version of the web browser on Windows may notice that the browser is flooding the Windows Reliability Monitor with entries. Opera Software released Opera 89 Stable […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Opera Browser is flooding the Windows Reliability Monitor with entries appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Disable the Firewall on Windows 10 and 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=811026</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/811026/how-to-disable-firewall-on-windows/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T18:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For troubleshooting, testing, or other similar purposes, you may need to turn off your Windows 10 or Windows 11’s firewall. It’s easy to disable this feature on your PC, and we’ll show you how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Any way to disable touchpad acceleration?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vwoj31/any_way_to_disable_touchpad_acceleration/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vwoj31/any_way_to_disable_touchpad_acceleration/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T17:53:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm on Wayland, relatively fresh install. The touchpad acceleration is driving me crazy, does anyone know how to disable it? Libinput reports accel-profile as flat, but it definitely is not.
    submitted by    /u/LiveTart335  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Chromecast with Google TV Finally Gets an Update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/122782/the-chromecast-with-google-tv-finally-gets-an-update/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/122782/the-chromecast-with-google-tv-finally-gets-an-update/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T17:48:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a very long wait, the Chromecast with Google TV is getting its first firmware update of 2022. Users should see a notification for the update (version QTS1.220504.008), which includes several small bug fixes and improvements.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Study Is Stupid, But EVs Won't Save the Environment Either]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/122768/this-study-is-stupid-but-evs-wont-save-the-environment-either/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/122768/this-study-is-stupid-but-evs-wont-save-the-environment-either/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T17:45:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The GMC Hummer EV is a huge, heavy vehicle, coming in at over 9,000 lbs and packing a massive 212.7-kWh battery that weighs 2,923 lbs itself. And while EVs have zero tailpipe emissions, creating enough electricity to charge electric vehicles still emits plenty of pollution. So are EVs saving the environment?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New in iOS 16 for iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809638</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809638/whats-new-in-ios-16-for-iphone/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T17:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple announced iOS 16 for the iPhone at WWDC 2022. As usual, this update is free and the release is expected in late September (2022). The update is packed with tweaks that will hopefully change the way you use your iPhone for the better.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LLVM Adds An HTTP Server For Debuginfod]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=LLVM-Adds-A-HTTP-Server</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=LLVM-Adds-A-HTTP-Server"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T17:30:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Merged prior to the weekend into LLVM 15 was a basic web server implementation...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla Sent Microsoft a Cake for Internet Explorer’s Death]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=817409</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/817409/mozilla-sent-microsoft-a-cake-for-internet-explorers-death/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T17:23:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Internet Explorer was officially retired in June, which was a happy occasion for nearly everyone in the tech industry. Following a long tradition of sending cakes to each other, the Firefox team at Mozilla sent a cake to Microsoft to celebrate the end of Internet Explorer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft: Windows Autopatch is now generally available]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-windows-autopatch-is-now-generally-available/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-windows-autopatch-is-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T17:21:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft says that Windows Autopatch, an enterprise service that automatically keeps Windows and Microsoft 365 software up to date, is generally available starting today. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Should You Install an iOS or iPadOS Beta on iPhone or iPad?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=814058</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/814058/should-you-install-an-ios-or-ipados-beta-on-iphone-or-ipad/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T17:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Installing a beta version of iOS or iPadOS on your iPhone or iPad is easy—but just because you can, that doesn’t necessarily mean you should. Here are some things to weigh up before you dip your toe into Apple’s pool of pre-release software.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here's the Top Deals of Best Buy's "Black Friday in July" Sale]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/122742/best-buy-black-friday-in-july-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/122742/best-buy-black-friday-in-july-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T17:16:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From now through July 13th, Best Buy is running a massive “Black Friday in July” sale. It’s the retailer’s latest attempt to undercut Amazon’s Prime Day, but as always, we’re just happy to get more discounted tech goodness. So, here are the best deals and discounts of “Black Friday in July.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Zero-Knowledge Encryption, and Why Should I Choose It?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=811527</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/811527/what-is-zero-knowledge-encryption/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T17:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Keeping your important data safe is an essential part of modern life, and encryption plays a big part in that. Zero-knowledge encryption, if done properly, is just about the best security method you can choose.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Russ Ware</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kick off Prime Week With MacBook Pro, SSD, and Bluetooth Speaker Deals]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=817319</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/817319/kick-off-prime-week-with-macbook-pro-ssd-and-bluetooth-speaker-deals/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T17:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let the Amazon Prime sales begin! Every day this week, we’re rounding up the absolute best of the best Amazon Prime deals and sharing them with you for your buying pleasure. We’re going to be covering a lot of gadgets, gear, and accessories this week, so sit tight and enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zach Laidlaw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft says decision to unblock Office macros is temporary]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-says-decision-to-unblock-office-macros-is-temporary/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-says-decision-to-unblock-office-macros-is-temporary/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T16:53:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft says last week's decision to roll back VBA macro auto-blocking in downloaded Office documents is only a temporary change. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quanto costa ricaricare un cellulare]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Quanto-costa-ricaricare-un-cellulare_24756</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Quanto-costa-ricaricare-un-cellulare_24756"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T16:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anche andando ad intuito, è facile ipotizzare che la ricarica della batteria di uno smartphone sia un'operazione poco costosa. Le batterie dei dispositivi più compatti sono comunque piccole potendo garantire una manciata di Wh (wattora).Con un'unità di misura come il wattora si esprime infatti l'energia complessiva fornita dalla batteria (potenza elettrica di un Watt mantenuta per un'ora).Nel caso degli smartphone e dei tablet di solito ci si limita a parlare dei mAh o milliampereora: questo valore indica la capacità di carica della batteria.Le batterie degli smartphone vengono confrontate usando i mAh e non i wattora perché la tensione non cambia tra i modelli dei vari produttori ed è sempre attestata tra 3,6 e 3,8 V.
Come calcolare quanto costa ricaricare la batteria
 Ci sono due modi per calcolare quanto costa ricaricare una batteria.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Any program where I can manually select an area of a picture to crop with an aspect ratio?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vwmg0x/any_program_where_i_can_manually_select_an_area/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vwmg0x/any_program_where_i_can_manually_select_an_area/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T16:25:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is there a program where I can call it on the command line with a picture argument like program picture.jpg -aspect-ratio 2/1 -output cropped.jpg and it will open picture.jpg and let me select a 2 to 1 width to height ratio part of the image to crop from that image and save to a new file cropped.jpg?
 Is there any program that does this or can I hack it together from a few different things like a program to select an area and then feed those coordinates to imagemagick or something like that?
    submitted by    /u/Status-Floor3119  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The $40 Chromecast With Google TV Is a Fantastic Deal Today]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=817351</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/817351/the-40-chromecast-with-google-tv-is-a-fantastic-deal-today/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T16:17:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google released the Chromecast with Google TV near the end of 2020, serving as a new competitor to the best streaming devices. Now it’s on sale for $40, a savings of $10 from the original price.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Score a 4K Fire TV for $239 This Prime Day]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=817096</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/817096/score-a-4k-fire-tv-for-230-this-prime-day/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T16:04:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Televisions are always a hot-ticket item during major sale events, and Prime Day is no different. Amazon has discounted prices on its Omni Series of 4K smart TVs, dropping them as low as $239.99.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is an IR Blaster?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=816367</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/816367/what-is-an-ir-blaster/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T16:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TVs—both smart and dumb—have some fancy technology inside that you probably don’t think twice about. IR blasters are one of those things and this little gadget can make your life a lot easier.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GCC Rust Approved By Steering Committee, Likely To Land For GCC 13]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=GCC-Rust-SC-Approved</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=GCC-Rust-SC-Approved"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The GCC Steering Committee has approved of the GCC Rust front-end providing Rust programming language support by the GNU Compiler Collection. This Rust front-end will likely be merged ahead of the GCC 13 release next year...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save Up To 44% on Roborock’s Robot Vacuums Through Prime Day]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=815542</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/815542/save-up-to-44-on-roborocks-robot-vacuums-through-prime-day/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T15:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon’s Prime Day sales extravaganza is well underway, and our friends at Roborock have unleashed their own torrent of discounts for your buying pleasure. Valid through July 16, you can save up to 44% on some of the hottest robot vacuums on the planet, but each sale happens during specific days, so be watchful as you seek out your savings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zach Laidlaw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come formattare un disco o una chiavetta su Mac]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/07/come-formattare-un-disco-o-una.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/07/come-formattare-un-disco-o-una.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T15:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quando colleghiamo un disco esterno USB o una chiavetta USB al Mac non è presente alcuna voce nel Finder per formattarla velocemente; anche se Mac è un sistema semplice da usare (nella maggior parte dei casi), Apple non ha ritenuto necessario introdurre un pulsante o una voce nel menu del tasto destro in grado di formattare velocemente una chiavetta o un qualsiasi dispositivo di storage senza...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Netboot eror after installing arch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vwl72w/netboot_eror_after_installing_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vwl72w/netboot_eror_after_installing_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T15:32:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone, recently I've installed Arch on my pc, but I have some issue with it. After fresh install of arch, got this eror message: CLIENT MAC ADDR: (my mac addr) GUID: DHCP My pc has dualboot( win 10 on ssd and arch on hdd)
    submitted by    /u/vidser  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Store will not ban legitimate paid open source programs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179650</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/07/11/microsoft-store-will-allow-paid-open-source-programs/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T15:26:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few days ago, Microsoft published an update to a policy, forbidding open source programs from being sold on the Microsoft Store. This didn't sit well with some developers, who caused an […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Microsoft Store will not ban legitimate paid open source programs appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use IRC in Emacs with ERC]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=497638</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15425247/use-irc-in-emacs-with-erc"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Emacs is a wonderful tool that can do just about anything. While it is a text editor, It can function as an email client, RSS reader and even music player too. If you are an Internet Relay Chat (IRC) user, it is also possible to use IRC from inside Emacs. This can be useful if you want to chat with others through IRC but do not want to leave your Emacs buffer.
   

Content

What is IRC and ERC?
Getting Started with ERC
Configuring ERC
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:5 Useful Emacs Packages for Better Productivity
    
What is IRC and ERC?
    
In a basic sense, IRC is a protocol that allows two or more people to communicate through text over the internet. Unlike newer chat platforms, IRC solely relies on being able to communicate over plain text. This approach, in turn,... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramces Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung's Galaxy S23 Might Dump Its Own Chipset]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/122740/samsungs-galaxy-s23-might-dump-its-own-chipset/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/122740/samsungs-galaxy-s23-might-dump-its-own-chipset/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T15:21:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung’s flagship Galaxy smartphones often come with two different processors and chipsets depending on the region. However, a new report from the highly respected analyst Ming-Chi Kuo suggests Samsung is ready to ditch its chipset and go all Qualcomm for the Galaxy S23.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 Ways to Insert a Command or Code Block in Microsoft Word]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=810091</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/810091/microsoft-word-code-block/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T15:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re creating an article, instructional piece, or essay in Microsoft Word, you may need to include a snippet of code. Whether HTML, JavaScript, or Python, you likely want it to appear different than the document text.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 10 e 11: disinstallare driver della scheda video in modo completo]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-10-e-11-disinstallare-driver-della-scheda-video-in-modo-completo_24755</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-10-e-11-disinstallare-driver-della-scheda-video-in-modo-completo_24755"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T14:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Per rimuovere i driver della scheda video in Windows 10 e in Windows 11 è possibile servirsi dell'utilità sviluppata e messa a disposizione dal produttore hardware. In alternativa si può premere Windows+X, scegliere Gestione dispositivi, cliccare su Schede video quindi usare il pulsante Disinstalla dispositivo nella scheda Driver.Spesso il processo di disinstallazione del driver della scheda video non viene completato puntualmente o lascia dei residui che possono causare problemi quando si caricano altri driver.Display Driver Uninstaller (DDU) è uno strumento che disinstalla completamente i driver grafici AMD e NVidia senza lasciare chiavi di registro, file, cartelle o altri elementi.Per disinstallare i driver della scheda video dal sistema Windows in uso, si può scaricare e avviare DDU.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['The Oregon Trail' Comes to Apple Watch as a Step Tracker Game]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/122679/the-oregon-trail-comes-to-apple-watch-as-a-step-tracker-game/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/122679/the-oregon-trail-comes-to-apple-watch-as-a-step-tracker-game/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T14:24:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve ever wanted to walk the Oregon Trail on foot, get an Apple Arcade subscription. The Oregon Trail remake for Apple Arcade can now pull data from your Health app, turning exercise into journey across America. There’s also a companion Apple Watch app for those who want to see their progress on the go.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux più veloce di Windows 11 con i nuovi Intel Alder Lake di dodicesima generazione]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Linux-piu-veloce-di-Windows-11-con-i-nuovi-Intel-Alder-Lake-di-dodicesima-generazione_24754</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Linux-piu-veloce-di-Windows-11-con-i-nuovi-Intel-Alder-Lake-di-dodicesima-generazione_24754"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Con i processori Alder Lake di dodicesima generazione Intel ha portato l'architettura ibrida nella sua piattaforma. L'aveva già fatto in passato con i suoi Lakefield (processori che avrebbero dovuto essere sfruttati per i sistemi Microsoft basati su Windows 10X ma che poi, alla fine, sono rimasti quasi inutilizzati) ma è con i nuovi Alder Lake che l'architettura basata su core ad alte prestazioni e core a basso consumo energetico trova la sua più moderna ed efficace espressione.Per gestire i carichi di lavoro tra core P e core E, Intel ha implementato la sua tecnologia Thread Director.Grazie a Thread Director Windows 11 ha potuto far registrare prestazioni molto superiori rispetto ai precedenti sistemi operativi.Come abbiamo visto nel nostro articolo, la tecnologia Thread Director è sbarcata su Linux e implementata a livello di kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get the Google Pixel 6 For Just $499 Today ($100 Off)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=817308</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/817308/get-the-google-pixel-6-for-just-499-today-200-off/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T14:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Pixel 6 and Pixel 6 Pro are two of the best Android phones available right now, thanks to their custom chipsets and affordable prices. Now the phones are even cheaper for a limited time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Ergonomic Mice of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=796113</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/796113/best-ergonomic-mouse/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ergonomics mice come in a variety of shapes, sizes, and price tags. Whether you’re looking for a vertical layout, trackball design, or lightweight product, here are six of the best ergonomic mice currently on the market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Bitner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come tradurre i documenti Word]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/07/come-tradurre-i-documenti-word.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/07/come-tradurre-i-documenti-word.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T13:44:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Con i documenti Word può capitare di ritrovarsi tra le mani un documento redatto in lingua inglese o o in un'altra lingua che non conosciamo. In questi casi possiamo benissimo affidarci al traduttore integrato all'interno della suite Office o, in alternativa utilizzare delle app per mobile o dei siti web per tradurre qualsiasi tipo di documento in formato .doc o .docx. 
Nei capitoli che seguono...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to auto block macros in Microsoft Office docs from the internet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/how-to-auto-block-macros-in-microsoft-office-docs-from-the-internet/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/how-to-auto-block-macros-in-microsoft-office-docs-from-the-internet/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T13:34:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Microsoft temporarily rolling back a feature that automatically blocks macros in Microsoft Office files downloaded from the Internet, it is essential to learn how to configure this security setting manually. This article will explain why users should block macros and how you can block them in Microsoft Office. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to See the Amazon Price History of a Product]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=734836</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/734836/how-to-see-amazon-price-histories/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prices on Amazon change constantly. Knowing the price history can give you an edge in finding good deals on Amazon Prime Day, Black Friday, Cyber Monday, and other major sales. So how do you track those prices?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jordan Gloor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Watch Out for Fake Prime Day Deals]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=816667</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/816667/watch-out-for-fake-prime-day-deals/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T13:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon’s annual Prime Day event is supposed to be a Black Friday-style sale in the middle of the summer for deep discounts online. However, just like Black Friday, not all Prime Day deals are the same. Don’t be fooled.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Acer Swift X Review: Portable but Pricey]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/122495/acer-swift-x-review-portable-but-pricey/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/122495/acer-swift-x-review-portable-but-pricey/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T13:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Laptops are meant to be practical and portable — with the Swift X, portability and power seem to be at the core of its design. But how much power can you cram into a device almost half an inch thick? And is the result worth the hefty price tag?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McQuilling</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux 5.19 Looking Real Good On The HP Dev One, XanMod + Liquorix Also Tested]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31280</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31280"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the very popular HP Dev One that is powered by an AMD Ryzen 7 PRO SoC and running Pop!_OS, a number of Phoronix readers inquired about seeing benchmarks of some of the alternative kernel flavors on the device. So here is a look at the stock Linux 5.17 kernel up against the Linux 5.18 and 5.19 (Git) kernels and then Liquorix and XanMod tossed in as alternative flavors running on the Pop!_OS 22.04 installation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IPTV e Chromecast: come vedere la TV con la chiavetta Google]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=IPTV-e-Chromecast-come-vedere-la-TV-con-la-chiavetta-Google_24753</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=IPTV-e-Chromecast-come-vedere-la-TV-con-la-chiavetta-Google_24753"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T12:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Con l'acronimo IPTV (Internet Protocol Television) si fa comunemente riferimento alla tecnologia che consente di trasferire flussi audio-video utilizzati nelle trasmissioni televisive sfruttando la rete Internet. Nella definizione di IPTV si cita il protocollo TCP/IP quando, all'atto pratico, lo streaming viene spesso poi gestito via UDP (User Datagram Protocol) in modo da velocizzare le trasmissioni e ottimizzare la resa del flusso multimediale anche in presenza di perdita di pacchetti (si pensi a reti congestionate o connessioni instabili come quella su rete mobile).Utilizzare un sistema IPTV è assolutamente legale, a patto di disporre dei diritti per accedere e visualizzare il contenuto. Ne parliamo nell'articolo in cui ci soffermiamo sul concetto di smart IPTV.Siti come iptv-org su GitHub offrono file M3U ovvero playlist per lettori multimediali.Si tratta di file che contengono riferimenti diretti ai server di streaming multimediale delle varie emittenti televisive: sono gli stessi network TV a pubblicare tali flussi e renderli disponibili agli utenti.Nelle pagine di iptv-org si trovano i canali IPTV suddivisi per categoria, lingua, nazione e regione.Ciascun file in formato M3U può essere aperto con un editor di testo in modo da verificarne il contenuto.
Casting IPTV sulla chiavetta Google Chromecast
 Per i possessori di un dispositivo Android e per chi utilizza Google Chrome in Windows o macOS, l'utilizzo della chiavetta Chromecast è diventato essenziale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fwupd 1.8.2 Released - Supports More Corsair, PixArt, SteelSeries, System76 Hardware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Fwupd-1.8.2-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Fwupd-1.8.2-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T12:35:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LVFS/fwupd lead developer Richard Hughes at Red Hat has released Fwupd 1.8.2 as the newest version of this open-source solution for handling firmware updates under Linux and other platforms...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here's Everything Coming to Netflix the Week of July 11, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lifesavvy.com/136120/heres-everything-coming-to-netflix-the-week-of-july-11-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lifesavvy.com/136120/heres-everything-coming-to-netflix-the-week-of-july-11-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T12:30:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, you’re just looking to sit back and relax. After all the Fourth of July fun, it’s time for a little marathon watching and snacks on your couch. Well, Netflix has you covered with its weekly releases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shea Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Which Amazon Fire Tablet Should You Buy?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=813982</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/813982/which-amazon-fire-tablet-should-you-buy/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon’s Fire Tablets are incredibly popular, mostly because they are cheap: the entry-level Fire 7 only costs $49.99 with ads. There’s more than just one model, though, so which one should you get?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Score a Cheap Amazon Prime Subscription for Prime Day]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=428318</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/428318/how-to-score-a-cheap-amazon-prime-subscription-for-prime-day/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon normally charges $139 a year for Prime. But you don’t have to pay that much to get access to the sales on Prime Day. There are some cheaper (even free!) ways to score Prime.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 10 Best Movies on Amazon Prime Video in 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=730543</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/730543/best-free-movies-on-amazon-prime-video/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Prime subscriptions include access to thousands of movies for free. If you’re looking for something to watch, here are the best movies to watch for free with Amazon Prime Video.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Bell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do Wi-Fi Extenders Deserve Their Bad Reputation?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=816374</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/816374/do-wi-fi-extenders-deserve-their-bad-reputation/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T11:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wi-Fi extenders have a bad reputation in the tech community. People will often discourage you from using them. But do they deserve their bad reputation, and why do so many people love their Wi-Fi extenders if they do?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Fitzpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Risolvere l'errore "La connessione non è privata" su Chrome]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/07/risolvere-lerrore-la-connessione-non-e.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/07/risolvere-lerrore-la-connessione-non-e.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T10:43:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tra i sistemi di sicurezza introdotti in Google Chrome troviamo anche Safe browsing, che confronta i certificati emessi dalle pagine web con i database ufficiali dei certificati SSL emessi dalle società incaricate dello scopo, alla ricerca di eventuali attacchi hacker o manomissioni di siti leciti. Con questo sistema avremo la certezza di visitare esattamente la pagina che abbiamo richiesto e non...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Many Old X.Org Components Saw New Releases This Weekend]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Xorg-July-2022-Update</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Xorg-July-2022-Update"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T10:23:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While no new X.Org "katamari" releases are planned for a collection of all the X.Org component updates combined, this weekend longtime X.Org contributor Alan Coopersmith of Oracle issued many new updates to various old, seldom-maintained X.Org projects...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RADV Vulkan Driver Lands Performance Query Extension]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=RADV-VK_KHR_performance_query</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=RADV-VK_KHR_performance_query"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T09:45:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the newest extensions now supported by the RADV Vulkan driver is VK_KHR_performance_query, which can be used by RenderDoc and other utilities...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GNOME Shell + Mutter 43 Alpha Released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=GNOME-Shell-Mutter-43-Alpha</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=GNOME-Shell-Mutter-43-Alpha"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T09:36:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In gearing up for the GNOME 43 Alpha release coming out soon, this weekend marked the release of the new alpha versions of GNOME Shell and Mutter...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Client di posta Android K-9 Mail con supporto OAuth 2.0: come funziona]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Client-di-posta-Android-K-9-Mail-con-supporto-OAuth-20-come-funziona_24752</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Client-di-posta-Android-K-9-Mail-con-supporto-OAuth-20-come-funziona_24752"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T09:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Uno dei client di posta per Android più conosciuti e apprezzati è K-9 Mail: software libero e open source, K-9 Mail è stato progettato per offrire massima libertà agli utenti proponendosi come alternativa all'app preinstallata dal produttore oltre che a Gmail e Outlook.Abbiamo detto che Thunderbird per Android si chiamerà proprio così e sarà basato proprio su K-9 Mail grazie a uno storico accordo tra Mozilla e lo sviluppatore del noto client email.La novità più importante recentemente aggiunta a K-9 Mail è il supporto per il protocollo OAuth 2.0 che consente di accedere agli account di posta che lo supportano senza digitare nomi utente e password.Dal 30 maggio 2022 Google ha deciso di bloccare l'accesso agli account usando app meno sicure: in pratica non è più possibile accedere al contenuto degli account Google usando indirizzo email e password principale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MSM DRM Driver Adds Adreno 619 Support With Linux 5.20]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=MSM-DRM-Driver-Linux-5.20</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=MSM-DRM-Driver-Linux-5.20"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T09:14:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rob Clark as the lead developer of the MSM DRM kernel driver and the Freedreno/TURNIP Mesa drivers for open-source Qualcomm Adreno graphics driver support has submitted the Direct Rendering Manager driver changes for the upcoming Linux 5.20 merge window...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Android tethering not working?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vwdyjw/android_tethering_not_working/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vwdyjw/android_tethering_not_working/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T09:06:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just installed Arch on my laptop, and in the installation process, my internet sharing via usb worked flawlessly. But now that I booted into my LXQt DE, it just doesn't work. Any suggestions?
    submitted by    /u/Hanoleyb  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ricerca Outlook non trova le email più recenti: come risolvere]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Ricerca-Outlook-non-trova-le-email-piu-recenti-come-risolvere_24092</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Ricerca-Outlook-non-trova-le-email-piu-recenti-come-risolvere_24092"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T08:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Torna di attualità un problema che in passato ha afflitto tanti utenti di Windows 10 e Windows 11: l'impossibilità di cercare le email più recenti con Outlook. La ricerca Outlook sembra non funzionare più correttamente tanto che i messaggi di posta elettronica più nuovi non appaiono tra i risultati. Osservando le date, le email si fermano ad alcune settimane prima.In passato Microsoft confermò che il malfunzionamento nella ricerca di Outlook interessava i sistemi Windows 10 sui quali era stato installato l'aggiornamento KB5008212 di dicembre 2021 e le macchine basate su Windows 11.A luglio 2022 Microsoft rivela che il problema è tornato a manifestarsi interessando, questa volta, soltanto gli utenti di Windows 11.In attesa che i tecnici Microsoft rilascino una patch correttiva o comunque pubblichino informazioni più dettagliate, per risolvere il problema si può disattivare temporaneamente la ricerca di Windows (Windows Search) lasciando che Outlook si affidi solo a quella interna.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is starting ssh-agent?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vwd651/what_is_starting_sshagent/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vwd651/what_is_starting_sshagent/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T08:08:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every time I boot I have to run ssh-add to add my key to the agent. I figured I'd just do that in my .zprofile. But when my profile is sourced, I don't have the relevant environment variables set, and pgrep tells me ssh-agent isn't running. (It does seem to have started 10s later.)
 If I knew what was starting it, I might be able to hook into that to run ssh-add? But I can't figure out how ssh-agent is getting started, or how the SSH_AGENT_PID and SSH_AUTH_SOCK variables get put in my environment. Using ack I can't find any references to them that would be having this effect in $HOME, /etc or /usr/share. The words ssh and agent don't show up in systemctl list-units.
 According to pstree the parent of ssh-agent is systemd(1), so I guess whatever did start it disowned it? Maybe there's no way to find this out in general, I dunno.
 Feels potentially relevant that I'm running xfce and use sddm as a login manager and zsh as my shell.
 (Probably another option is to do something like, wait 10s then fork a new non-login shell and do ssh-add in that? Haven't specifically checked if that will work. It feels a bit dirty, but I'll do it if there's nothing else.)
 ETA: If I log in on vt2 I get a login shell without the environment variables set, and opening a subshell there I still don't have them. So I guess this is somehow X-related.
    submitted by    /u/philh  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cross-platform ebook app Calibre 6.0 is out with full text search support. Drops Windows 8 support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179644</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/07/11/cross-platform-ebook-app-calibre-6-0-is-out-with-full-text-search-support-drops-windows-8-support/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T07:31:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Calibre 6.0 is the latest version of the popular cross-platform ebook management software Calibre. The new version introduces several new and improved features, including full text searching capabilities and support for new […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Cross-platform ebook app Calibre 6.0 is out with full text search support. Drops Windows 8 support appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Drivers on new XPS?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vwcmhx/drivers_on_new_xps/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vwcmhx/drivers_on_new_xps/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T07:29:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So I need to get a new laptopt that will mainly be used for programming, I was considered both Dell New XPS 13 and New XPS 13 Plus (don't know the exact models just that they're called new on their website).
 Anyway searching in Google I found out some posts of people installing Arch on the XPS 13 Plus and they were mentioning some driver issues, fingerprint not working, this kind of thing, and some other things they got to work after a lot of tinkering and manually modifying and then installing drivers, which is not something I'm interested on doing (I would be getting the Developer editions that ship with Ubuntu were everything works fine so I don't know why Arch would be different but there it is).
 So I was wondering if any of you have experience with the New XPS (no plus) and how everything works under Arch.
 I'm also open to other laptop recommendations (no Thninkpads tho, the laptop I'm replacing is a T495 and didn't have the best luck with it)
 ​
 Thanks!
    submitted by    /u/nerc0ck  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[stalld/stalld.git - daemon to detect stalled threads and temporarily boost for forward progress, Did somebody finds it useful?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vwc7q9/stalldstalldgit_daemon_to_detect_stalled_threads/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vwc7q9/stalldstalldgit_daemon_to_detect_stalled_threads/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T07:01:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/Balauru_Nr1  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using archinstall, would it be possible to use the existing Windows EFI partition instead of creating a seperate EFI partition?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vwc0w2/using_archinstall_would_it_be_possible_to_use_the/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vwc0w2/using_archinstall_would_it_be_possible_to_use_the/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T06:48:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/uxinung  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[how to setup ZRAM correctly autostarting automatically at boot?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vwbkhd/how_to_setup_zram_correctly_autostarting/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vwbkhd/how_to_setup_zram_correctly_autostarting/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T06:17:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I feel so dumb... 😅 I installed zram-generator. Configured /etc/systemd/zram-generator.conf by coping from zram-genrator.conf.example and edited these values from the example:  host-memory-limit = none compression-algorithm = zstd  And deleted zram1 section.
 But systemctl won't enable systemd-zram-setup@.service
 I am struck...
    submitted by    /u/Bombini_Bombus  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heroic Games Launcher: play Epic Games Store and Gog games on Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179641</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/07/11/heroic-games-launcher-play-epic-games-store-and-gog-games-on-linux/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T05:11:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to PC games, multiple gaming platforms and stores compete for a share of the market. While Valve's Steam has been the dominating platform for a long time, there are […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Heroic Games Launcher: play Epic Games Store and Gog games on Linux appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[School internet blocks any Linux devices, any ideas?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vw9xdz/school_internet_blocks_any_linux_devices_any_ideas/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vw9xdz/school_internet_blocks_any_linux_devices_any_ideas/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T04:36:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello,
 The other day I decided I wanted to use Linux on my primary school laptop mainly because I can't stand using Windows and its awful performance and awful battery performance.
 I installed endeavouros, mainly because I didn't have time to do an arch install and was planning to do one later.
 I, a couple of weeks ago, decided to boot up Linux at school and try to use it but I found that after half an hour I wasn't able to access the internet anymore, so I decided to boot up windows again since I hadn't committed to it yet so I was just dual-booting until I realised that I couldn't access the WIFI from windows either now. Thought it was weird so I decided to go to the IT department to try to let them figure it out and their network had auto blocked me cause it detected I connected from…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I am trying to extend my root partition (/) to the end of its current disk.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vw9ofr/i_am_trying_to_extend_my_root_partition_to_the/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vw9ofr/i_am_trying_to_extend_my_root_partition_to_the/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T04:22:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TLDR: need help extending root partition on the disk it resides on
 I am new to arch and made a mistake when allocating storage to the root partition because I only had one drive at the time. I ran into and issue with the root partition running out of space, so purchased an SSD and moved /home to the new drive and updated fstab accordingly. I then deleted the original home partition off the old disk and I want to extend the root partition to the end of the near empty disk it now resides on. However, I know messing with this is messy and I want to make sure I do it right! Thanks in advance for your help :)
    submitted by    /u/TactfulDeity  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wireless USB mouse triggers hibernation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vw7te8/wireless_usb_mouse_triggers_hibernation/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vw7te8/wireless_usb_mouse_triggers_hibernation/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T02:40:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greetings. 
 I have been using Arch for a while now on lap;top, and I have stumbled upon a problem that I could not find a way to fix.
 Basically, once I plug in the wireless USB adapter for the mouse, it starts to arbitrarily trigger hibernation. I use the same mouse on a desktop that also runs Arch Linux but there was never such kind of problem. 
 The best lead I could find was that the auto suspension features of the mouse on low battery would be caught by the system, thus causing hibernation. However, it still persists even when I put a brand new battery.
 I have tried the "USB Mouse sleeping after 5 seconds when on battery" from the Laptop Mode Tools scripts suite, but it does not seem to be related to this issue, all thing considered.
 Has anyone here encountered a similar problem ? Is there some solution that I might have looked over ? 
 Thank you in advance for your time, and best regards.
    submitted by    /u/dosssman  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mincraft on arch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vw6iov/mincraft_on_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vw6iov/mincraft_on_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T01:31:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[i have mincraft installed, and I'm trying to install forge, but I don't know how to do it. Can someone tell me how?
    submitted by    /u/Trickysituation69  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Applying custom patch to a PKGBUILD file]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vw5tlv/applying_custom_patch_to_a_pkgbuild_file/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vw5tlv/applying_custom_patch_to_a_pkgbuild_file/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T00:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I use a few packages from AUR and a couple of them use defaults that fit most users but not me. So I ended up creating patches for PKGBUILD.
 Everything works ok right now but package updates is something that can be boring as I need to pay attention to paru output and update patched packages separately by applying patches manually. 
 So I am looking for a way to auto apply my patches on top of recent changes in PKGBUILD and ignoring them when checking for updates in AUR.
    submitted by    /u/AgitatedDrag3886  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux 5.19-rc6 Released After A Fairly Normal Week]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-rc6-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-rc6-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T22:34:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linus Torvalds just announced the availability of Linux 5.19-rc6 as the latest routine test release for the upcoming Linux 5.19...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pacman update failed due to conflicting files]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vw2nyp/pacman_update_failed_due_to_conflicting_files/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vw2nyp/pacman_update_failed_due_to_conflicting_files/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T22:17:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When running sudo pacman -Syyu I recieve the following error message:
 error: failed to commit transaction (conflicting files) python-future: /usr/bin/futurize exists in filesystem python-future: /usr/bin/pasteurize exists in filesystem python-future: /usr/lib/python3.10/site-packages/future-0.18.2-py3.10.egg-info/PKG-INFO exists in filesystem ... 
 The list goes on with many more lines with files related to python-future: /usr/bin/python3.10/...
 First of all what is python-future and secondly how do I fix this? I've read the arch wiki and tried to look at similar questions being asked but nothing worked as of now.
    submitted by    /u/sustainablyWash  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come utilizzare robocopy per cancellare più velocemente, e dalla riga di comando, grandi numeri di file e cartelle]]></title>
        <id>3608|20220711000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/windows-10/come-utilizzare-robocopy-cancellare-piu-velocemente-riga-comando-grandi-numeri-file-cartelle-3608"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A chi di noi non è mai capitato di dover cancellare delle cartelle contenenti decine di migliaia di file, magari di piccole dimensioni, e vedere Windows rimanere in attesa di un fantomatico Calcolo in corso che sembra non concludersi mai se non dopo lunga attesa. Un metodo molto più rapido per l’eliminazione di queste cartelle è offerto dal comando robocopy che è già incluso nel sistema operativo.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is a System on a Chip (SoC)?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=769198</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/769198/what-is-a-system-on-a-chip-soc/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With so much talk about Apple’s M1 and smartphone chips these days, you might hear about the “system on a chip” (SoC) designs used in them. But what are SoCs, and how do they differ from CPUs and microprocessors? We’ll explain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using a flash drive to persistent boot arch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vw08p3/using_a_flash_drive_to_persistent_boot_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vw08p3/using_a_flash_drive_to_persistent_boot_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T20:25:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, has anyone or does anyone know if it is realistic to use a flash drive to create a persistent arch boot on a usb if it has fast enough read/write speeds? I will be trying this on an old 12 inch MacBook with 1.1ghz intel m4 and 8gb ram. Thanks!
    submitted by    /u/Inside-Pen-8395  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to SSH Into Your Raspberry Pi]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=768053</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/768053/how-to-ssh-into-your-raspberry-pi/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After setting up your Raspberry Pi, you may not need a display for it. When it comes time for maintenance tasks, like upgrades and reboots, you can use Secure Shell (SSH) instead of plugging in a monitor. We’ll show you how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Butts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[While moving with my wireless mouse, CPU load jumps up by over 20%]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vvymqw/while_moving_with_my_wireless_mouse_cpu_load/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vvymqw/while_moving_with_my_wireless_mouse_cpu_load/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T19:10:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, so I have this issue that is related to my wireless mouse (Logitech G305)
 Just about 20 minutes ago, when I was normally using my Arch, I noticed a laggy mouse movement, so I thought like: "Hmmm, maybe my picom is making trouble again".
 So I killed all the picom processes but that didn't helped, so I quit every other programs that were running in the background but that still wasn't enough, so I just opened gotop (system monitoring program) to check wtf is going on. CPU was on 0-3% so I was like: "Hmm, that's weird". But when I moved my mouse around, the CPU jumped to 20%, sometimes to 30% for all cores... So I booted into live Void Linux ISO to see if it's a problem with Arch/bspwm and it wasn't, the same thing was happening on Void Linux, then I changed my mouse to a wired one and... The issue was gone... 
 ​
 Anyone knows what is going on? Should I return my mouse? Thanks!
    submitted by    /u/DominiCzech  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Turn On Predictive Text on iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=813459</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/813459/how-to-turn-on-predictive-text-on-iphone/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T19:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To help you type faster and more conveniently, your iPhone offers a predictive text feature that automatically suggests the words that you’re likely to type. You can activate this feature from both Settings and your keyboard’s menu on your iPhone. We’ll show you how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Office Rolls Back a Major Security Feature]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/122664/microsoft-office-rolls-back-a-major-security-feature/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/122664/microsoft-office-rolls-back-a-major-security-feature/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T19:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security advocates got a major win in February, when Microsoft announced that Office applications would finally block VBA macros by default. But Microsoft is backtracking. The VBA macros block, which was initially slated for June of 2022, no longer has a release date.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PSA: You can control your desktop monitor's brightness via Linux with this driver]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vvx9rx/psa_you_can_control_your_desktop_monitors/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vvx9rx/psa_you_can_control_your_desktop_monitors/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T18:06:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/ballast69  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add an Image to Your Gmail Signature]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=814356</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/814356/how-to-add-an-image-to-your-gmail-signature/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T18:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you want to add your company logo to your business signature or a picture of your motto to your personal signature? You can add an image to your Gmail signature for all outgoing emails or only the current one.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimized memchr() Implementation For The Linux Kernel Up To ~4x Faster]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-Kernel-Faster-memchr</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-Kernel-Faster-memchr"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T17:58:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A set of proposed patches promise to make the Linux kernel's memchr() implementation faster for locating a character within a block of memory. In tests carried out by the developer, the new implementation can be nearly four times faster on large searches...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Turn Your Spotify Playlists Into a Dream Music Festival Poster]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/122650/turn-your-spotify-playlists-into-a-dream-music-festival-poster/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/122650/turn-your-spotify-playlists-into-a-dream-music-festival-poster/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T17:13:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to social media, people love sharing everything. Spotify wrapped year in review playlists are a popular social trend each year, and last week we shared the fun new Spotify Iceberg trend floating around social media. But what if you could create a music festival poster curated from your Spotify playlist?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can't explain what's going with WiFi]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vvw2va/cant_explain_whats_going_with_wifi/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vvw2va/cant_explain_whats_going_with_wifi/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T17:12:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I had not used my laptop for 1 week, but when I used it past week, probably after an update, the wifi interface did not show up.
 Thinking it was an issue with 5.18 kernel update (I also had 5.15-lts), I booted into Ubuntu live usb (old version). Same issue happened. Not able to connect to internet via wifi.
 Since I had left the laptop (unfortunately on power) for 1 week, I thought something short circuited and the issue is now permanent. Although, I had read issues regarding 5.18, and someone was able to get it back, when then rebooted to Windows and back again to Arch. In my case, I had given up. Since I had a WiFI dongle, I had managed till today.
 However, today after an update (kernel), Wifi is back again without the dongle (even after multiple reboot). Not sure, how this can happen.
 Currently, I can see this log:
 Jul 10 kernel: ath10k_pci 0000:04:00.0 wlp4s0: renamed from wlan0
 Which I did not see when it failed.
 These are my internet devices:
 03:00.0 Ethernet controller: Realtek Semiconductor Co., Ltd. RTL8111/8168/8411 PCI Express Gigabit Ethernet Controller (rev 15)
 04:00.0 Network controller: Qualcomm Atheros QCA6174 802.11ac Wireless Network Adapter (rev 32)
    submitted by    /u/xpressrazor  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Computer reboots due to a hardware error]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vvvxmz/computer_reboots_due_to_a_hardware_error/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vvvxmz/computer_reboots_due_to_a_hardware_error/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T17:05:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So, every time I try to play DOOM Eternal, my PC just reboots with a hardware error after 20-ish minutes of gameplay. journalctl -k --grep=mce gives the following output:
 journalctl -k --grep=mce Jul 10 17:51:36 archlinux kernel: mce: [Hardware Error]: Machine check events logged Jul 10 17:51:36 archlinux kernel: mce: [Hardware Error]: CPU 6: Machine Check: 0 Bank 1: fc800800060c0859 Jul 10 17:51:36 archlinux kernel: mce: [Hardware Error]: TSC 0 ADDR 39507b2c0 MISC d012000000000000 IPID 100b000000000 Jul 10 17:51:36 archlinux kernel: mce: [Hardware Error]: PROCESSOR 2:a20f10 TIME 1657471894 SOCKET 0 APIC c microcode a201009 Jul 10 17:51:37 archlinux kernel: MCE: In-kernel MCE decoding enabled. 
 This is an issue I can reproduce consistently. This started happening yesterday, and it seems to only happen when playing DOOM Eternal.
 I tried to use artificial stress tests like mprime and stress to see if my CPU is stable, but after 13 hours of mprime and 4 hours of stress, there were no crashes whatsoever. I also tried running memtest and it gave me no errors as well.
 Any clue what might be wrong? I have almost 1000 hours in this game on this machine with 0 issues, but now I'm getting these crashes and I have no idea why.
 Thanks in advance.
 EDIT: Forgot to add my specs
 CPU: Ryzen 7 5800x stock settings
 RAM: 32GB DDR4 3600MHz
 GPU: RX 6700XT
 Kernel: 5.18.10-zen1-1-zen
 amd-ucode version: 20220610.7b71b75-1
    submitted by    /u/doomenguin  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is an In-App Purchase?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=713303</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/713303/what-is-an-in-app-purchase/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T17:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re familiar with app stores on iPhone, iPad, Android, Windows, Mac, Chromebook, and beyond, you’ll encounter the concept of in-app purchases. What are they, and what do they do? We’ll explain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Snapper and BTRFS - booted from a snapshot , rolled back but FS is read-only]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vvvcj8/snapper_and_btrfs_booted_from_a_snapshot_rolled/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vvvcj8/snapper_and_btrfs_booted_from_a_snapshot_rolled/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T16:38:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I did something stupid , so booted from a snapshot to rollback  snapper --ambit classic rollback  it said it set a newer snapshot as read-write and default for /
 rebooted and its in the read write snapshot which was created on rolback
  btrfs subvolume get-default / ID 3092 gen 110644 top level 260 path @snapshots/2377/snapshot 
 ```
 2374 | pre | | Sun 10 Jul 2022 08:26:13 PM IST | root | number | pacman --remove -s -- linux-zen linux-zen-headers |
 2375 | post | 2374 | Sun 10 Jul 2022 08:26:20 PM IST | root | number | linux-zen linux-zen-headers pahole |
 2376 | single | | Sun 10 Jul 2022 08:55:25 PM IST | root | number | rollback backup | important=yes 2377+ | single | | Sun 10 Jul 2022 08:55:25 PM IST | root | | writable copy of #2373 |
 2378 | single | | Sun 10 Jul 2022 09:00:07 PM IST | root | timeline | timeline |
 2379 | single | | Sun 10 Jul 2022 10:00:14 PM IST | root | timeline | timeline |
 ```
 and still the filesystem is read only
    submitted by    /u/SnooMaps9383  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple's Business website is blocking Firefox. Here is how to gain access]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179636</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/07/10/apples-business-website-is-blocking-firefox-here-is-how-to-gain-access/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T16:35:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you open Apple's Business website in Mozilla Firefox, you are greeted by a "your browser is not supported" prompt. The message is displayed for all recent versions of Firefox, including Firefox […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Apple's Business website is blocking Firefox. Here is how to gain access appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KDE Connect over the internet?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vvupky/kde_connect_over_the_internet/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vvupky/kde_connect_over_the_internet/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T16:07:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey,
 This is how it goes. I have an Arch Linux PC, and a phone over the same network. Can I run KDE Connect over the internet, so it works even when my phone isn't connected to the same network?
 I can't really port forward due to ISP Restrictions, so any ideas would be helpful!
 ​
 :)
    submitted by    /u/WickedWizard3588  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Turn Off Sounds on a Roku]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=816166</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/816166/how-to-turn-off-sounds-on-a-roku/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T16:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roku devices are an easy way to get all your favorite streaming services onto your TV. They’re not without their annoyances though. Out of the box, the Roku interface makes a sound for every button press on the menu. Here’s how to turn that off.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can't install nvidia-470xx-dkms from the AUR, kernel modules do not install (kernel linux-5.18.10-arch1-1)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vvuhip/cant_install_nvidia470xxdkms_from_the_aur_kernel/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vvuhip/cant_install_nvidia470xxdkms_from_the_aur_kernel/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T15:57:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I tried running makepkg -si along with the PKGBUILD several times. My system is fully up to date and doesn't use testing repositories.
 My laptop has a GTX 660M gpu, which is a Kepler series graphics card. Other than that it has Intel integrated grahpics.
 Here's what pacman says:
 :: Running post-transaction hooks... (1/5) Creating system user accounts... (2/5) Reloading system manager configuration... (3/5) Reloading device manager configuration... (4/5) Arming ConditionNeedsUpdate... (5/5) Install DKMS modules ==> ERROR: Missing var kernel headers for module nvidia/470.129.06. ==> ERROR: Missing srv kernel headers for module nvidia/470.129.06. ==> ERROR: Missing lost+found kernel headers for module nvidia/470.129.06. ==> ERROR: Missing lib64 kernel headers for module nvidia/470.129.06. …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is something wrong with my $PS1?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vvu2mc/is_something_wrong_with_my_ps1/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vvu2mc/is_something_wrong_with_my_ps1/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T15:37:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Can you spot something wrong?
 PS1='\e[1;32m[\u@\h\e[0m \W\e[1;32m]\$ \e[0m'
 When I set my PS1 to this, writing some long command or simply spamming a key causes the text to wrap around before actually getting to the end of ther terminal window, and overwriting the beginning of the same line instead of going to the next one. The terminal will look something like this:
 rrrrrrrrhostname ~]$ rrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr
 Can someone point out what's wrong with it? Thanks
    submitted by    /u/art3m1s_d  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Now Experience SpaceX Starlink Internet on a Boat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/122666/you-can-now-experience-spacex-starlink-internet-on-a-boat/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/122666/you-can-now-experience-spacex-starlink-internet-on-a-boat/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T15:23:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk’s SpaceX company recently announced a new service called Starlink Maritime. which is essentially a satellite internet service for boats and yachts. The company offers an internet-from-space service for those unaware, and now it’s expanding to more places.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Google Chrome feature reduces CPU use to extend battery life]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/google/new-google-chrome-feature-reduces-cpu-use-to-extend-battery-life/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/google/new-google-chrome-feature-reduces-cpu-use-to-extend-battery-life/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T15:05:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google is testing a new 'Quick Intensive Throttling' feature that reduces CPU time by 10%, extending the battery life for laptops and mobile devices. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Table Template in Microsoft Word]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809437</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809437/create-a-table-template-in-word/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T15:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you have a document containing several tables, consistency is key. You can easily make each table and format it from scratch the same way. But to save time, create a table template that you can reuse in Word.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>