<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-05-14T02:06:49.674Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia Drivers - Proprietary vs Open Source]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/up5ug8/nvidia_drivers_proprietary_vs_open_source/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/up5ug8/nvidia_drivers_proprietary_vs_open_source/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-14T00:54:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quick question, I'm comming from popos that did the whole nvidia settling up for me.
 What is the best option in 2022 performance wise? Proprietary Drivers or Open Source?
    submitted by    /u/GreenRiot  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Chroot into installed Arch from USB Boot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/up5qcg/how_to_chroot_into_installed_arch_from_usb_boot/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/up5qcg/how_to_chroot_into_installed_arch_from_usb_boot/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-14T00:47:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[hi, so I successfully installed Arch Linux using a USB boot drive, but I forgot to install netctl or any other internet package alongside it. As a result, I now have no internet in Arch, I can't install it within arch because I need internet to install a package (catch 22). After looking around, I found that I could chroot into arch from my USB boot which had internet and then use Pacstrap to install netctl. However, I don't know which directory to chroot into?
    submitted by    /u/aatashii  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Question from a complete noob to linux.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/up5l00/question_from_a_complete_noob_to_linux/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/up5l00/question_from_a_complete_noob_to_linux/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-14T00:39:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I really like the idea of arch. The appeal to me is probably the same appeal to everyone else: complete customizeability, community-driven, fun to tinker with, etc.
 But I'm very much new to the Linux world and don't really know what sort of things Arch does that other don't, nor what I'm giving up by going Arch over other distributions.
 For example, I play League of Legends. The traditional way of getting League on Linux is through Play On Linux with a special Wine version. Is that something that's doable on Arch?
 Are all Proton Steam games available on Arch in a streamlined/easy way? Meaning, I just install steam, select the "proton experimental" button and suddenly I can download Apex Legends? Or are there more steps?
 Are there any difficulties with peripherals? Is my mouse/headset/Blue Yeti going to work easily?
 In short, am I giving up any software accessibility by going Arch or is everything that's available on other Linux distributions mostly available on Arch?
 And how difficult is the installation process *truly*? I get that it's supposedly difficult, but is it so difficult that even following a guide wouldn't be sufficient to get it installed correctly the first time?
 Thanks!
 ​
 Strong edit for some things I want to do on Linux:
  
Play League of Legends/Battle.net games/Steam Proton games.
 Install i3 Window Tiling Manager
 Custom keybinds
 Install Unreal Engine
 Vim
  
​
    submitted by    /u/mushroomgambit  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ArchScript might have effed up my bios. Help?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/up5k8z/archscript_might_have_effed_up_my_bios_help/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/up5k8z/archscript_might_have_effed_up_my_bios_help/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-14T00:38:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm trying my first install of Arch, i downloaded the iso from the wiki, flashed it on a drive, ran archinstall.
 I got a minimum install, grub as the booter, pipewire, set it to only mount one of my drives and auto config my partitions. Only firefox and vim as additional packages.
 Install went smooth, no errors. I rebooted and instead of finding myself on a bare minimum login screen I was on a command line asking for my user and password.
 I though that the minimum install would give me a desktop environment so I just though that I should reboot and reinstall with kde as an aditional package and I would be golden.
 That's when things went wrong.
 Firstly the bios refused to show up, the pc was dead. I tried reseting a few times while waiting a few minutes and nothing.
 Then out of nowhere, while doing some research of my phone on what I might have done wrong the bios showed up. The install must have done something weird to my sistem so I tried booting on the flashdrive again so I could reinstall Arch and try checking what I've done wrong.
 But it is soooo, sloooow, like, it takes minutes to leave the boot screen. Right now I've been waiting for the flashdrive to boot, it's so slow that I can't tell if it's worlking or stuck. When I press delete it instantle goes to the bios config screen so it is still respondive.
 Edit: I was able to get to the install again by restoring default bios config and booting the flash drive. Do you guys have any idea of what's going on? I might have made a mistake while configuring the disk layout, I'm having a hard time making heads or tailsof whats going on in the install, so my plan is to let it do what it want on the drive I want the system to be, and set the rest on a graphical interface later.
    submitted by    /u/GreenRiot  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I need help]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/up5k31/i_need_help/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/up5k31/i_need_help/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-14T00:38:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I try to chroot I get the error /bin/bash no such file or directory
    submitted by    /u/pikminfan12  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MX Snapshot equiv. for Arch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/up5i46/mx_snapshot_equiv_for_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/up5i46/mx_snapshot_equiv_for_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-14T00:34:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, I am looking for an equivalent of MX-Snapshot on arch which would allow to create an ISO like a carbon copy of my entire system w/ apps, settings that I can just reuse on another system and have everything again. Does it exist on Arch?
    submitted by    /u/akasaka99  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[11 Best Fixes for Chromebook Camera Not Working]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=473308</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15296557/best-fixes-chromebook-camera-not-working"/>
        <updated>2022-05-14T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No one would want to be in a situation where you have an important video call or an online exam coming up and your Chromebook’s camera suddenly stops working. Unfortunately, Chromebook users have been facing various issues related to camera. 
    
For instance, the camera refuses to turn on or shows a black screen. Similarly, some users see errors like “No camera found” and “Your camera is currently unavailable”. Even worse, others have reported seeing a black screen with a red light next to their camera lens. If you are experiencing a similar problems, follow us in this guide as we go through various ways to fix the Chromebook camera not working.
   

Content

1. Restart Your Chromebook
2. Check the Camera Lens
3. Look for Privacy Switch
4. Reset Chromebook Hardware
5. Update Your Chrome Browser
6. Update Your Chromebook's OS
7. Use Camera in a Different App
8. Check Camera Settings in Chrome
9. Grant Camera Permission in Chrome
10. Reset Your Chrome Browser
11. Reset Your Chromebook
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mehvish Mushtaq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stuck on Arch Install at Wireless Connection [newb]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/up50am/stuck_on_arch_install_at_wireless_connection_newb/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/up50am/stuck_on_arch_install_at_wireless_connection_newb/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-14T00:07:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Installing Arch from a bootable USB on Razer Blade 14. Stuck on connecting to the internet after booting live environment. 
 ip link only returns only 1: lo: ... (not the wlan0 I want)
 iwd# device list returns no devices. 
 lspci -k returns a bunch of stuff along with Network Controller: Qualcomm Atheros... w/ ath11k_pci kernel driver.
 I haven't figured out why my network interface is not listed. It seems to me I can detect the wireless adapter and the driver is installed. Not sure how to proceed. HALP.
    submitted by    /u/changodefuego  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Questa settimana su TLI (14 maggio 2022)]]></title>
        <id>3571|20220514000001</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/newsletter-turbolab.it-1349/questa-settimana-tli-14-maggio-2022-3571"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T22:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Non hai tempo di leggerci tutti i giorni? nessun problema! ecco a te il riepilogo di quanto proposto da TurboLab.it nel corso della settimana in conclusione.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dual booting two copies of Arch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/up2fut/dual_booting_two_copies_of_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/up2fut/dual_booting_two_copies_of_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T21:55:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My work is making me install one of those IT security management agents which auto-updates your packages or whatever. I do not feel like having a monitoring process watching over me the entire time and I've been looking to separate my personal/work files into two contexts anyway.
 Has anybody dual-booted two different, independent Arch OSes on one machine and is willing to share the process so I can save myself an evening and a lot of googling?
    submitted by    /u/v430net  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 of the Best Sticky Note Apps for Mac]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=485442</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15296345/best-sticky-note-apps-for-mac"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can create a sticky note to remind yourself of important tasks or stay on top of your to-do lists. Sticky notes are handy as they will appear all the time on the desktop, unless you choose to dismiss them. 
    
There are many classic note-taking apps for Mac, but only a handful are available when it comes to sticky note-taking. In this article, we’ve rounded up the best sticky note apps for Mac.
   

Content

1. Stickies
2. Simple Antnotes
3. Quick Note
4. Ghostnote
5. Unclutter
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Get Started with macOS Notes App
    
1. Stickies
    
Stickies come pre-installed with macOS. It allows users to create notes in post-it like fashion on the screen.
    

    
With Stickies,... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ratnesh Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do You Need a High Refresh Rate Monitor for Office Work?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=661319</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/661319/do-you-need-a-high-refresh-rate-monitor-for-office-work/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[High refresh rate monitors have traditionally been aimed at gamers, but they have a broader appeal. Device manufacturers like Apple and Samsung have started including displays with high refresh rates in their tablets and phones. So, should you get one for your office computer, as well?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Week in Ransomware - May 13th 2022 - A National Emergency]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/the-week-in-ransomware-may-13th-2022-a-national-emergency/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/the-week-in-ransomware-may-13th-2022-a-national-emergency/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T20:58:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While ransomware attacks have slowed during Russia's invasion of Ukraine and the subsequent sanctions, the malware threat continues to affect organizations worldwide. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is an ALR Projector Screen and Why Would You Want One?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117876/what-is-an-alr-projector-screen-and-why-would-you-want-one/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117876/what-is-an-alr-projector-screen-and-why-would-you-want-one/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T20:56:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Home theaters are ballooning in popularity, and projector owners are now obsessed with ALR or  “ambient light rejection” screens. Unlike standard white screens, which are shockingly affordable, ALR screens cost well over $600 and promise to improve image quality in unfavorable theater environments—particularly in rooms with lots of unwanted light.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Disk Encryption on Arch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/up14om/disk_encryption_on_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/up14om/disk_encryption_on_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T20:51:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi,
 Im looking for a way to encrypt my drive using Arch to where whenever my device goes to sleep or gets locked it also locks the disk. Would it be possible to also have a thumb drive to open it as an alternative method ? I already have Arch installed and am not willing to reinstall just for encryption (I was looking at some guides and they were about installing WITH disk encryption). I feel comfortable with Arch after starting last August but still do need some help here and there, this is definitely one of those areas. Im getting much better over time though so thx everyone :p
 Thanks so much!
    submitted by    /u/JSV007  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Link an Android Phone to a Windows 10 PC With Microsoft Phone Link]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=700733</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/700733/how-to-link-an-android-phone-to-a-windows-10-pc-with-microsofts-your-phone-app/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows and Android are very popular, so naturally, there are a lot of people who use both. Microsoft’s “Phone Link” app integrates your Android phone with your PC, giving you access to your phone’s notifications, text messages, photos, and more—right on your PC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Wallet on Android Wants to Replace Your Real Wallet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=805293</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/805293/google-wallet-on-android-wants-to-replace-your-real-wallet/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T19:46:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google revealed this week that it’s revamping how tap-to-pay purchases, card management, and passes work on Android devices. It’s all a bit complicated, but generally sounds like an improvement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PulseAudio crackling when adjusting volume.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uoznhd/pulseaudio_crackling_when_adjusting_volume/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uoznhd/pulseaudio_crackling_when_adjusting_volume/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T19:41:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've already consulted the arch wiki and various other posts involving me changing the pulseaudio config and reinstalling alsa but nothing seems to be fixing my issue.
 My output device is a Scarlett Solo Audio interface hooked up to 2 stereo monitors
 would greatly appreciate any help
 ​
 output of aplay -l 
 **** List of PLAYBACK Hardware Devices ****
 card 0: PCH [HDA Intel PCH], device 0: ALC269VC Analog [ALC269VC Analog]
 Subdevices: 0/1
 Subdevice #0: subdevice #0
 card 0: PCH [HDA Intel PCH], device 3: HDMI 0 [HDMI 0]
 Subdevices: 1/1
 Subdevice #0: subdevice #0
 card 0: PCH [HDA Intel PCH], device 7: HDMI 1 [HDMI 1]
 Subdevices: 1/1
 Subdevice #0: subdevice #0
 card 0: PCH [HDA Intel PCH], device 8: HDMI 2 [HDMI 2]
 Subdevices: 1/1
 Subdevice #0: subdevice #0
 card 0: PCH [HDA Intel PCH], device 9: HDMI 3 [HDMI 3]
 Subdevices: 1/1
 Subdevice #0: subdevice #0
 card 0: PCH [HDA Intel PCH], device 10: HDMI 4 [HDMI 4]
 Subdevices: 1/1
 Subdevice #0: subdevice #0
 card 1: NVidia [HDA NVidia], device 3: HDMI 0 [HDMI 0]
 Subdevices: 1/1
 Subdevice #0: subdevice #0
 card 1: NVidia [HDA NVidia], device 7: HDMI 1 [HDMI 1]
 Subdevices: 1/1
 Subdevice #0: subdevice #0
 card 1: NVidia [HDA NVidia], device 8: HDMI 2 [HDMI 2]
 Subdevices: 1/1
 Subdevice #0: subdevice #0
 card 1: NVidia [HDA NVidia], device 9: HDMI 3 [HDMI 3]
 Subdevices: 1/1
 Subdevice #0: subdevice #0
 card 2: USB [Scarlett Solo USB], device 0: USB Audio [USB Audio]
 Subdevices: 0/1
 Subdevice #0: subdevice #0
 ​
 ​
 me changing the volume from 0 to 100 repeatedly for reference:
 http://sndup.net/5pmz
    submitted by    /u/Choice_Brush4163  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is the best app/method to lock a app(browser), just like an app lock in android]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uozhms/what_is_the_best_appmethod_to_lock_a_appbrowser/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uozhms/what_is_the_best_appmethod_to_lock_a_appbrowser/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T19:34:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All i want to do is lock my browser as it has some nsfw stuff so any suggestions please...
 Also this might be odd but is there any way to open the other browser which i have if the password is incorrect 
 ​
 ps: i have removed password from my user using passwd -d and please don't suggest to just use that cause I don't want to change this.
 Thanks
    submitted by    /u/BirAmrit  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Connecting Intel Alder Lake Systems Via USB4/Thunderbolt Can Be Faster Come Linux 5.19]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Thunderbolt-XDomain-Bonding</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Thunderbolt-XDomain-Bonding"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T19:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A feature of Thunderbolt seemingly not widely leveraged is allowing two distinct hosts/systems to be connected over a Thunderbolt cable that can then be used for tunneling arbitrary data packets using high-speed DMA rings. Should you find yourself using such a setup, starting with Linux 5.19+ it should open the door for being much faster when running on latest-generation Intel hardware for USB4/Thunderbolt...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get an Insignia 24″ Class F20 Series Smart Fire TV for Under $100]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=489203</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15296208/insignia-f20-smart-fire-tv"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re not into keeping up with the Joneses and just want to watch some quality entertainment while not breaking the bank, check out this Insignia 24″ Class F20 Series Smart Fire TV. You’ll get the Alexa voice assistant and built-in Fire TV, yet you’ll be paying less than $100 for this 2020 model.
    
You’ll get much use of the Alexa voice remote. With just your voice, you can watch TV, launch apps, search for titles, play music, switch the HDMI inputs, and control your other smart home devices. You’ll find great detail, contrast, and colors from the Full HD picture and speed and performance with the quad-core CPU/Multi-core GPU.
    

    
With Fire TV built into this set, you’ll be able to watch more than 1 million streamed movies and TV episodes through access to the channels, apps, and Alexa skills. Get access to Prime Video, Netflix, Hulu, HBO Max, Apple TV+, Disney+, and more. The Fire TV will integrate live over-the-air broadcasts and streaming channels all in one smart space.
 ... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wyze Now Lets You Turn Cameras Into Home Security Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117900/wyze-now-lets-you-turn-cameras-into-home-security-systems/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117900/wyze-now-lets-you-turn-cameras-into-home-security-systems/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T19:13:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a long invite-only beta test, Wyze is finally making its new Cam Plus Pro subscription available to everyone. This subscription tier turns any eligible Wyze Cam into an affordable whole-home security system with live agents and emergency responses for $3.99 a month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fix “App Is Damaged and Can’t Be Opened” on Mac]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=803598</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/803598/app-is-damaged-and-cant-be-opened/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T19:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you received an error message that says an app “is damaged and can’t be opened” and “you should move it to the Bin” with a handy button for doing so? If you trust the file, you can get around this with a simple Terminal command.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Italian CERT: Hacktivists hit govt sites in ‘Slow HTTP’ DDoS attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/italian-cert-hacktivists-hit-govt-sites-in-slow-http-ddos-attacks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/italian-cert-hacktivists-hit-govt-sites-in-slow-http-ddos-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T18:16:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Italy's Computer Security Incident Response Team (CSIRT) has published an announcement about the recent DDoS attacks that key sites in the country suffered in the last couple of days. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Which iPhones Have Touch ID?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=802122</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/802122/which-iphones-have-touch-id/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T18:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[iPhones with Touch ID look different than iPhones with Face ID, and it can also change how you use certain features on your device. Here’s how to spot a phone with Touch ID—and a list of models that support the feature.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Teases a Wild AR Glasses Prototype]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=805222</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/805222/google-teases-a-wild-ar-glasses-prototype/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T17:54:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Glass was one of the first breakout attempts at augmented reality technology, but the product was never sold to the general public beyond the initial prototype. At the end of this year’s Google I/O keynote, Google teased a new type of glasses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google's Pixel 7 Won't Deliver on a Big Promise]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117890/googles-pixel-7-wont-deliver-on-a-big-promise/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117890/googles-pixel-7-wont-deliver-on-a-big-promise/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T17:52:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a surprise move, Google announced the upcoming Pixel 7 and Pixel 7 Pro in May, months ahead of the expected release date. Unfortunately, after promising a “soft touch glass” finish, Google has already changed its mind on the much-requested feature.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft: Sysrv botnet targets Windows, Linux servers with new exploits]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-sysrv-botnet-targets-windows-linux-servers-with-new-exploits/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-sysrv-botnet-targets-windows-linux-servers-with-new-exploits/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T17:48:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft says the Sysrv botnet is now exploiting vulnerabilities in the Spring Framework and WordPress to ensnare and deploy cryptomining malware on vulnerable Windows and Linux servers. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dual Boot with Windows 10 question.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uox75v/dual_boot_with_windows_10_question/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uox75v/dual_boot_with_windows_10_question/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T17:45:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1 - Will OS Prober sort out the boot menu automatically?
  
- Arch Wiki has me a bit confused. I have Windows10 installed UEFI/NTFS on one drive (M.2). I have a spare SATA drive I want to put Arch on. If I choose the SATA drive during Arch install will it just work? The bit about UEFI/MBR/GPT has me a bit confused. 
  
Any advice is most appreciated. I generally go by the "learn by doing" mantra, but I can do without having to redo Windows. I just did it fresh, like a few hours ago. 
 Thanks.
    submitted by    /u/North-Champion9934  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel IPI Virtualization Ready For Linux 5.19]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-IPI-Virtualization-5.19</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-IPI-Virtualization-5.19"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T17:41:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following the groundwork laid in Linux 5.18, Intel VT-x's IPI Virtualization support is set to be introduced with the Linux 5.19 kernel for supporting this new hardware capability found with Xeon Scalable 4th Gen "Sapphire Rapids" server processors...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia drivers don't seem to be working]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uowwhz/nvidia_drivers_dont_seem_to_be_working/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uowwhz/nvidia_drivers_dont_seem_to_be_working/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T17:31:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[Not really solved, but I've realized that for reasons outside of this issue that Windows fits me better for now. This mainly comes down to compatibility as well as most of my friends playing Valorant. Thanks for the help either way.]
 ​
 As the title says, they don't seem to be working. Games run extremely poorly and it seems to not be utilizing my GPU at all.
 pacman -Qs nvidia tells me I have nvidia-utils, nvidia-settings, nvidia, libxnvctrl and libvdpau installed
 Neofetch tells me I have a "RTX 206" instead of 2060 for some reason
 I'm honestly not sure what to do here, how do I fix this? if I need to provide any other info please let me know
    submitted by    /u/PearsArePrettyCool  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Install Free HEVC Codecs on Windows 11 (for H.265 Video)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=804013</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/804013/how-to-install-free-hevc-codecs-on-windows-11-for-h.265-video/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T17:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[High Efficiency Video Coding, usually called HEVC or H.265, is currently the standard for compressing video. Most new content is encoded using HEVC — but it isn’t included with Windows 11, and the codecs normally cost money. Here’s how to get HEVC for free.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Lewis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migliori App per Smartwatch Android Wear OS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2016/07/migliori-app-per-smartwatch-android-wear.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2016/07/migliori-app-per-smartwatch-android-wear.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T16:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sempre più persone si sono affidate a smartwatch dotati di sistema operativo Wear OS, di fatto l'unica vera alternativa agli Apple Watch per funzionalità e per supporto alle app più desiderate dagli utenti. Gli smartwatch con sistema operativo Wear OS tendono ad avere un prezzo accessibile nella maggior parte dei casi e si interfacciano bene sia con in telefoni Android (dove la compatibilità è...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fake Binance NFT Mystery Box bots steal victim's crypto wallets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fake-binance-nft-mystery-box-bots-steal-victims-crypto-wallets/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fake-binance-nft-mystery-box-bots-steal-victims-crypto-wallets/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T16:24:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new RedLine malware distribution campaign promotes fake Binance NFT mystery box bots on YouTube to lure people into infecting themselves with the information-stealing malware from GitHub repositories. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here's How Tesla Superchargers Will Work With Other EVs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117879/heres-how-tesla-superchargers-will-work-with-other-evs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117879/heres-how-tesla-superchargers-will-work-with-other-evs/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T16:16:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year, Tesla announced plans to open its fast Supercharger network to all EVs instead of only its own vehicles. The first rollout started in the Netherlands, then all EVs in Europe, and now Elon Musk is sharing details on how it’ll work in the United States.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smart DNS vs. VPNs: Which Is Better?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=794720</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/794720/smart-dns-vs-vpn/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T16:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re trying to circumvent geographical restrictions on certain websites, you have two major options. A VPN, which creates a tunnel through the internet, or a Smart DNS that can reroute specific traffic to the regional server of your choice.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sydney Butler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Copertura aree bianche: TIM, Fibercop e Open Fiber stringono un accordo sulla fibra ottica]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Copertura-aree-bianche-TIM-Fibercop-e-Open-Fiber-stringono-un-accordo-sulla-fibra-ottica_24515</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Copertura-aree-bianche-TIM-Fibercop-e-Open-Fiber-stringono-un-accordo-sulla-fibra-ottica_24515"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T15:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Era già nell'aria ma il comunicato ufficiale dei 'protagonisti' è arrivato oggi. TIM, Fibercop e Open Fiber hanno stretto un importante accordo commerciale che permetterà di accelerare la copertura in fibra ottica delle aree bianche del Paese.Come abbiamo visto nell'articolo sulle differenze tra aree bianche, grigie e nere, le aree bianche d'Italia sono quelle zone in cui nessun operatore privato aveva mai fatto investimenti per portare la copertura in banda ultralarga.L'accordo stretto tra Fibercop, azienda che si occupa dell'ammodernamento della rete di accesso secondaria e in particolare dell''ultimo miglio' (ovvero il tratto che separa l'utente dagli apparati per le telecomunicazioni installati in strada) e Open Fiber è storico.Open Fiber potrà utilizzare le infrastrutture di rete Fibercop nelle aree bianche per un controvalore superiore ai 200 milioni di euro.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can not play audio through Redmi Buds 3]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uout9l/can_not_play_audio_through_redmi_buds_3/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uout9l/can_not_play_audio_through_redmi_buds_3/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T15:53:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My redmi buds 3 connect fine in Bluetooth settings, and also appear in the available audio input and outputs. When I connect them I also hear a sound through the earphones, but other than that, all audio is played through my laptop's speakers.
 ​
 What I've already done:
 install bcm20702a1-firmwareAUR or bcm20702b0-firmwareAUR
 pacmd set-card-profile 2 a2dp_sink 
 ​
 Relevant logs:
 pulseaudio[7082]: org.freedesktop.DBus.Properties.Get /org/bluez/hci0/dev_E0_67_81_71_88_23/fd2 Volume failed: org.freedesktop.DBus.Error.InvalidArgs: No such property 'Volume' 
 ​
 May 13 20:35:27 wali-g515 bluetoothd[824]: Endpoint registered: sender=:1.203 path=/MediaEndpoint/A2DPSink/sbc_xq_453 May 13 20:35:27 wali-g515 bluetoothd[824]: Endpoint registered: sender=:1.203 path=/MediaEndpoint/A2DPSource/sbc_xq_453 May 13 20:35:27 wali-g515 bluetoothd[824]: Endpoint registered: sender=:1.203 path=/MediaEndpoint/A2DPSink/sbc_xq_512 May 13 20:35:27 wali-g515 bluetoothd[824]: Endpoint registered: sender=:1.203 path=/MediaEndpoint/A2DPSource/sbc_xq_512 May 13 20:35:27 wali-g515 bluetoothd[824]: Endpoint registered: sender=:1.203 path=/MediaEndpoint/A2DPSink/sbc_xq_552 May 13 20:35:27 wali-g515 bluetoothd[824]: Endpoint registered: sender=:1.203 path=/MediaEndpoint/A2DPSource/sbc_xq_552 May 13 20:35:45 wali-g515 bluetoothd[824]: /org/bluez/hci0/dev_E0_67_81_71_88_23/fd1: fd(42) ready May 13 20:36:13 wali-g515 bluetoothd[824]: src/profile.c:ext_io_disconnected() Unable to get io data for Hands-Free Voice gateway: getpeername: Transport endpoint is not connected (107) May 13 20:38:02 wali-g515 bluetoothd[824]: /org/bluez/hci0/dev_E0_67_81_71_88_23/fd2: fd(42) ready May 13 20:39:44 wali-g515 bluetoothd[824]: src/profile.c:ext_io_disconnected() Unable to get io data for Hands-Free Voice gateway: getpeername: Transport endpoint is not connected (107) 
    submitted by    /u/No-Rich5357  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hisense's Next Smartphone Is Almost a Kindle]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117877/hisenses-next-smartphone-is-almost-a-kindle/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117877/hisenses-next-smartphone-is-almost-a-kindle/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T15:51:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you think about new smartphones, you probably think of fancy specs like a big gorgeous display or a powerful rear camera system. But Hisense’s new E-Ink smartphone, the A9, will make you think differently about gorgeous displays.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzanne Humphries</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SonicWall ‘strongly urges’ admins to patch SSLVPN SMA1000 bugs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/sonicwall-strongly-urges-admins-to-patch-sslvpn-sma1000-bugs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/sonicwall-strongly-urges-admins-to-patch-sslvpn-sma1000-bugs/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T15:38:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SonicWall "strongly urges" customers to patch several high-risk security flaws impacting its Secure Mobile Access (SMA) 1000 Series line of products that can let attackers bypass authorization and, potentially, compromise unpatched appliances. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[9 of the Best Alternatives to Apple’s Magic Keyboard]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=334202</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15294237/best-alternatives-apple-magic-keyboard"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you need to replace your Mac’s Magic keyboard but don’t really want to pay the “Apple tax”? Or what about that hated default Butterfly keyboard that leads you to use an external keyboard instead? You’re in luck. We’ve assembled a list of some great alternatives that maintain the functionality and mimic the aesthetics of Apple’s Magic keyboard. Furthermore, we’ve organized the list from lowest to highest list price (USD) so that you can find a Magic Keyboard alternative that fits your budget. 
   

Content

Under $20: iHome Full Size Mac Keyboard
$30 All-Rounder: OMOTON Bluetooth Keyboard for Mac
$30-60: Macally Ultra-Slim USB Wired Keyboard/Macally Slim USB Wired Compact Mini Keyboard
$80: Satechi Aluminum Bluetooth Keyboard
$80 Mechanical Keyboard: Keychron K8
$100: Logitech K750 Wireless Solar Keyboard

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:Apple Magic Keyboard Review
    
Under $20: iHome Full Size Mac Keyboard
    
iHome has been making Apple-compatible peripherals for years, so... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Lynch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CCleaner velocizza Windows con la nuova funzione Ottimizzazione prestazioni]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=CCleaner-velocizza-Windows-con-la-nuova-funzione-Ottimizzazione-prestazioni_24514</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=CCleaner-velocizza-Windows-con-la-nuova-funzione-Ottimizzazione-prestazioni_24514"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T15:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Uno dei programmi storicamente più apprezzati dagli utenti di Windows era certamente CCleaner. Usiamo l'imperfetto perché, nonostante l'applicazione vantasse ottime recensioni fin dalla data di debutto della prima versione, nel lontano 2003, tra il 2018 e il 2019 qualcosa si è rotto nel rapporto con gli utenti.A metà del 2017 Avast acquisì Piriform ovvero la software house sviluppatrice di CCleaner e di altre note utilità. L'anno seguente un gruppo di criminali informatici riuscì a sostituire la versione originale dell'applicazione con una dannosa agendo sui server dell'azienda e nel 2020 destò scalpore la raccolta di dati effettuata senza il consenso degli utenti.Da allora Piriform assunse un impegno preciso e spiegò che avrebbe risolto ogni problematica in sospeso cercando di riguadagnare la fiducia degli utenti.Dopo i precedenti 'scivoloni', CCleaner è tornato un software decisamente più affidabile anche se la mancata condivisione del codice sorgente (non è un progetto open source) resta un problema per molti utenti.CCleaner 6.0 è l'ultima versione del software che Piriform ha appena iniziato a distribuire attraverso i suoi server: l'abbiamo provata e al momento non viene proposta l'installazione di alcun software aggiuntivo o potenzialmente inutile come accaduto in passato e come segnalava lo stesso Microsoft Defender.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Explains Your Android Phone’s Broken Notifications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=805157</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/805157/google-explains-your-android-phones-broken-notifications/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T15:06:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not all of the best Android phones and tablets work alike, and some devices have aggressive battery-saving software that can stop background notifications from coming through reliably. The Android team at Google I/O explained this week why that’s an ongoing issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Emoji Reactions in Google Docs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=802526</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/802526/emoji-reactions-in-google-docs/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Emoji seem to be everywhere, from communications in Slack to social media posts to emails in Outlook. So, why not Google Docs? If you want a casual interaction when collaborating on a document, start showing your reactions with emoji.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thank Goodness, the Pixel 6a Uses a New Fingerprint Sensor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117869/thank-goodness-the-pixel-6a-uses-a-new-fingerprint-sensor/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117869/thank-goodness-the-pixel-6a-uses-a-new-fingerprint-sensor/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T14:55:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After six months of complaints, updates, and weird excuses, the Pixel 6 fingerprint sensor still sucks. It’s slow and unresponsive, likely due to hardware constraints. But thank goodness—the Pixel 6a may not suffer from these problems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What does Gentoo help teach that Arch doesn't?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uot5zd/what_does_gentoo_help_teach_that_arch_doesnt/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uot5zd/what_does_gentoo_help_teach_that_arch_doesnt/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T14:36:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I started my linux journey with Ubuntu back in '08. It was wonderfully freeing. Later on down the road I started trying new distros. I didn't really give Arch a chance until around 2012 and it was quite a bit different back then. But one thing I loved was the documentation and how much it taught me about linux and maintaining the system itself. Using Ubuntu was freeing but it also felt like I didn't really get what was going on under the surface because I didn't really have a hand to play in any of it.
 So that's a really long-winded way to start this post but my main question for you all is - what could Gentoo teach me? Is there any advantage? I don't know if I would stick with it for long and it's not like I want to switch away from Arch but I'm thinking that maybe it would be able to help teach me a few things if I tried it for a while. Am I completely off-base here? Or does anybody that has tried both have any input on this? I appreciate any replies.
    submitted by    /u/dasonk  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to bypass the Microsoft Account requirement during Windows setup]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178572</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/05/13/how-to-bypass-the-microsoft-account-requirement-during-windows-setup/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T14:14:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every few years, Microsoft is making it more difficult to create a local account during setup of the Windows operating system. The company announced in February 2022 that new setups and first […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post How to bypass the Microsoft Account requirement during Windows setup appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11: cosa sono le azioni suggerite e come funzionano]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-11-cosa-sono-le-azioni-suggerite-e-come-funzionano_24513</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-11-cosa-sono-le-azioni-suggerite-e-come-funzionano_24513"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T14:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Il primo grande pacchetto di aggiornamento destinato al più recente sistema operativo Microsoft, Windows 11 22H2 verrà rilasciato con buona probabilità già entro la fine dell'estate 2022. In un altro articolo abbiamo descritto le principali novità di Windows 11 22H2.Microsoft sta però già guardando oltre e se le funzionalità di Windows 11 22H2 sono ormai 'congelate' adesso si comincia a parlare delle innovazioni che verranno introdotte in tempi successivi.In una nota pubblicata sul blog ufficiale dell'azienda, Amanda Langowski e Brandon LeBlanc hanno presentato Azioni suggerite o Suggested actions in inglese.Si tratta di una funzionalità attiva a livello di sistema che consente di riconoscere le informazioni selezionate con il cursore o il puntatore del mouse o del touchpad.Si supponga di evidenziare un numero di telefono: Windows 11 lo riconoscerà e permetterà di chiamarlo usando le applicazioni supportate oppure di aggiungerlo in rubrica.

Stessa cosa per date e orari: selezionandoli il sistema operativo chiederà all'utente se aggiungere un'attività nel calendario, avviare una pianificazione con Outlook oppure con altre applicazioni compatibili.Al momento le Azioni suggerite possono essere provate solo dagli utenti statunitensi iscritti al canale Dev del programma Windows Insider di Windows 11.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[L'App che asciuga gli altoparlanti del telefono ed espelle l'acqua con i suoni]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/05/l-app-che-asciuga-gli-altoparlanti-del.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/05/l-app-che-asciuga-gli-altoparlanti-del.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T14:06:00.013Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Capita a tutti, soprattutto d'estate, di parlare al telefono e sudare. le piccole goccioline di sudore sulla pelle, provocate dal calore dello smartphone durante una telefonata, possono essere un problema se penetrano all'interno del piccolo foro dell'altoparlante, provocando a volte malfunzionamenti, una forte attenuazione dell'audio, rumore metallico o distorsioni, rovinando quindi la qualità...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Smart Sprinkler Controllers of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=794148</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/794148/best-smart-sprinkler-controller/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T14:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Installing smart sprinkler controllers gives you more and better control over your irrigation. You can manually or automatically set schedules and use real-time data to save time, frustration, and money on your water bills. Our in-depth guide will help you pick the best.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Nguyen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[openSUSE Tumbleweed Jumps To The Newly-Released GCC 12 Compiler]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=openSUSE-Tumbleweed-GCC-12.1</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=openSUSE-Tumbleweed-GCC-12.1"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was just last week that GCC 12.1 was released and already it's being used by the rolling-release openSUSE Tumbleweed distribution as of today's build...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Chrome updates failing on Android devices in Russia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/google-chrome-updates-failing-on-android-devices-in-russia/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/google-chrome-updates-failing-on-android-devices-in-russia/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T13:52:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A growing number of Russian Chrome users on Android report getting errors when attempting to install the latest available update of the popular web browser. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When to See the Super Flower Blood Moon Lunar Eclipse]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lifesavvy.com/128868/when-to-see-the-super-flower-blood-moon-lunar-eclipse/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lifesavvy.com/128868/when-to-see-the-super-flower-blood-moon-lunar-eclipse/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you enjoy seeing each month’s full moon, May’s lunar moment is going to have you extra excited. Not only is it the summer’s Flower Moon, but there’s also a full lunar eclipse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shea Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SSID: usare lo stesso su più router e access point è una buona idea?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=SSID-usare-lo-stesso-su-piu-router-e-access-point-e-una-buona-idea_24512</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=SSID-usare-lo-stesso-su-piu-router-e-access-point-e-una-buona-idea_24512"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T13:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quando si devono coprire con il segnale WiFi aree piuttosto vaste l'approccio migliore è certamente quello di orientarsi su sistemi mesh che consentono di spostarsi da un ambiente all'altro con i dispositivi client (notebook, convertibili, smartphone, tablet,...) senza disconnessioni rilevabili.Le WiFi mesh sono la migliore risposta alle esigenze di copertura di chi ha la necessità di creare una rete WiFi domestica o professionale.Nell'articolo citato in apertura abbiamo comunque evidenziato su quali aspetti è importante concentrare la propria attenzione e soprattutto sull'importanza del backhauling ovvero del collegamento (wireless o cablato, con cavo Ethernet) tra i nodi del sistema WiFi e il router principale.I sistemi WiFi mesh, tuttavia, sono piuttosto costosi e una delle domande più ricorrenti tra gli utenti è la seguente: è possibile usare lo stesso SSID su più router e access point, anche di diversi produttori, senza orientarsi su una soluzione mesh? Proviamo a rispondere.
SSID, cos'è e a cosa serve
 Acronimo di Service Set IDentifier, SSID è l'identificativo che viene assegnato a ciascuna rete WiFi: è un nome arbitrario che rende riconoscibile la rete e semplifica il collegamento dei client wireless.Una volta stabilita la connessione con un router o un access point che utilizza un certo SSID, il client WiFi proverà successivamente a ricollegarsi alle reti wireless note usando i parametri di accesso precedentemente impostati: ad esempio la password utilizzata a protezione della rete WiFi e l'algoritmo configurato (i.e.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Stream Every ‘Friday the 13th’ Movie in 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=802356</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/802356/stream-every-friday-the-13th-movie-online/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T13:30:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With his hockey mask and his machete, Friday the 13th‘s Jason Voorhees is one of the most recognizable villains in horror, even if his onscreen track record is uneven at best. Here’s how to stream every Friday the 13th movie.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Bell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AverMedia PW315 Webcam Review: A Great Value at an Awkward Price]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117083/avermedia-pw315-webcam-review-a-great-value-at-an-awkward-price/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117083/avermedia-pw315-webcam-review-a-great-value-at-an-awkward-price/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T13:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avermedia is best known for its capture cards, which are popular among gamers. So, I was pretty excited when the company told us about its PW315 webcam. At just $120, this is one of the cheapest webcams to offer 1080p 60FPS video, and I figured that it’d be a great value for both livestreamers and remote workers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is a Nano IPS Display?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=804492</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/804492/what-is-a-nano-ips-display/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manufacturers are always trying to improve the picture performance of monitors. As a result, we have seen several different display technologies over the years. And Nano IPS is one such technology. Here’s everything you need to know about it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gaurav Shukla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Secure Network is now available as a limited preview in Edge Canary]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178568</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/05/13/microsoft-secure-network-is-now-available-as-a-limited-preview-in-edge-canary/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T12:57:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We reported about Microsoft Secure Network a few weeks ago, when it was spotted on the company's support website. The free VPN has officially entered a limited access preview in Edge Canary. […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Microsoft Secure Network is now available as a limited preview in Edge Canary appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Differenze tra formati di file Word, Excel e PowerPoint]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2016/02/differenze-tra-formati-di-file-word.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2016/02/differenze-tra-formati-di-file-word.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T12:54:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I documenti digitali, ossia quelli creati con il computer, differiscono tra loro in base al formato di file e in base al programma utilizzato per scriverli. Quando si salva un nuovo documento di testo con un programma come Microsoft Word, si può scegliere tra diversi formati di file.

 La scelta è importante perché se questo documento sarà poi inviato a un'altra persona bisogna essere sicuri che...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ubuntu's Chromium Snap Now Allows Enabling Native Wayland Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Chromium-Snap-Wayland</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Chromium-Snap-Wayland"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T12:41:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Those using the Chromium web browser on Ubuntu by way of the Snap package, the latest build has now enabled (optional) Wayland support...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Broadcast message by systemd when suspending?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uoqqgh/broadcast_message_by_systemd_when_suspending/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uoqqgh/broadcast_message_by_systemd_when_suspending/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T12:35:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apparently a recent commit to systemd enabled wall messages and every time I suspend my system I get the following message in the terminal after waking it.
  
Broadcast message from arjab@laptop (Fri 2022-05-13 12:41:43 CEST): 
 The system is going down for suspend NOW!
  
I'm on the testing repos and I'm wondering if this is intended behavior or not? It's obviously not a real bug, but somewhat annoying nonetheless.
    submitted by    /u/Arjab  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 10 Best Stephen King Movies to Stream in 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=799139</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/799139/best-stephen-king-movies-to-stream-online/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stephen King’s vast catalog of novels and stories is nearly matched by the many movies that have been adapted from his work. From horror to drama, here are 10 of the best Stephen King movies to stream right now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Bell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is a Mesh Router Backhaul?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=802009</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/802009/what-is-a-mesh-router-backhaul/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T12:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re shopping for a new mesh router system, you may come across references to the platform’s “backhaul.” Here’s what it is and how it affects Wi-Fi performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Fitzpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All you need to know about PlayStation Plus subscription changes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178559</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/05/13/all-you-need-to-know-about-playstation-plus-subscription-changes/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T11:37:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are looking to get yourself a PlayStation Plus subscription and save a little bit of money while you are at it, check out the Eneba marketplace! This place is home […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post All you need to know about PlayStation Plus subscription changes appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sponsored Content</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ubuntu Core 22 Beta Released For IoT & Edge Devices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Ubuntu-Core-22-Beta</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Ubuntu-Core-22-Beta"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T11:33:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building off last month's Ubuntu 22.04 Long-Term Support release, Canonical today has published the beta builds of the upcoming Ubuntu Core 22...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Annoying Features You Can Disable on Samsung Phones]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=801968</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/801968/5-annoying-features-you-can-disable-on-samsung-phones/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T11:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The “everything but the kitchen sink” approach that Samsung employs is not for everyone. Some things are useful, other things are not. The good news is Samsung doesn’t force features on you. Many things can be turned off or customized.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel In-Field Scan "IFS" Poised For Linux 5.19 To Help Spot Faulty Silicon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-In-Field-Scan-IFS</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-In-Field-Scan-IFS"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T10:53:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in early March Intel engineers posted a Linux driver for new functionality called In-Field Scan used for silicon failure testing. Barring any last minute issues, that Intel IFS driver should be merged for the upcoming Linux 5.19 cycle...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Say Goodbye to Both the iPod and Pixel Headphone Jack]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=488765</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15293560/say-goodbye-ipod-pixel-headphone-jack"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T10:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For more than 20 years, the typical image of personal music included an Apple iPod and wired headphones. But that picture has slowly been changing. Now you’re more likely to see a smartphone and wireless earbuds. Apple and Google closed the coffin on two items this week to permanently change that picture. Apple announced it is discontinuing the iPod, and Google announced its new Pixel 6A smartphone will not have a headphone jack.
   
Also read:Did Google Mean to Add a Pixel 6 Feature to Older Phones?
    
Goodbye iPod
    
The iPod has gone through many iterations over the years, but we all know that first one was the coolest. Until that was released in 2001, we thought the Walkman was the epitome in personal music.
    
Image Source: Apple
  ... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QNAP presenta il NAS TS-435XeU: connettività 2,5GbE/10GbE e cache SSD M.2 NVMe]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=QNAP-presenta-il-NAS-TS-435XeU-connettivita-25GbE-10GbE-e-cache-SSD-M2-NVMe_24511</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=QNAP-presenta-il-NAS-TS-435XeU-connettivita-25GbE-10GbE-e-cache-SSD-M2-NVMe_24511"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T09:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alle aziende alla ricerca di NAS di tipo professionale QNAP presenta da oggi il nuovo TS-435XeU, un modello a 4 vani che si mette in evidenza per il fattore di forma (rack a profondità ridotta), per il processore utilizzato - un quad-core Marvell OCTEON TX2 CN9131 a 2,2 GHz - e per le specifiche in termini di connettività.Il sistema assicura un ottimo bilanciamento tra costi e prestazioni offrendo due porte 10 GbE e due porte 2,5 GbE, slot SSD M.2 PCIe Gen 3 NVMe e massima scalabilità per quanto riguarda lo storage grazie al supporto di funzioni avanzate per il mondo business e le esigenze multimediali.

Le porte 10GbE e 2,5GbE integrate aiutano a semplificare i flussi di lavoro in caso di trasferimento di grandi quantità di dati, facilitano il backup e ripristino ad alta velocità, lo streaming multimediale; consentono inoltre di attivare il trunking di porta e il bilanciamento del carico per prestazioni e affidabilità aumentate.Il TS-435XeU dispone di quattro alloggiamenti per unità SATA da 3,5' e 4 GB di memoria DDR4 di serie (espandibili fino a 32 GB).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Valve Developer Starts Poking At Open-Source "RADV" Driver Support For GFX11/RDNA3]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=RADV-GFX11-Starts</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=RADV-GFX11-Starts"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T09:35:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prominent Mesa Radeon Vulkan "RADV" driver contributor Samuel Pitoiset of Valve's open-source driver team has begun working on GFX11 support for this driver ahead of AMD RDNA3 graphics cards launching later this year...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FFmpeg Lands AVIF Muxer For This Image Format Based On AV1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=FFmpeg-AVIF-Muxing</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=FFmpeg-AVIF-Muxing"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T09:30:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The widely-used FFmpeg multimedia library this morning merged AVIF muxing support for this image format based on the AV1 royalty-free video codec technology...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Realme 9 4G e 5G: smartphone con importanti differenze e un rapporto qualità-prezzo convincente]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Realme-9-4G-e-5G-smartphone-con-importanti-differenze-e-un-rapporto-qualita-prezzo-convincente_24510</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Realme-9-4G-e-5G-smartphone-con-importanti-differenze-e-un-rapporto-qualita-prezzo-convincente_24510"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T09:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arrivano in Italia due dispositivi che sorprendono per rapporto qualità-prezzo: si tratta dei nuovi smartphone Realme 9 5G e Realme 9 4G. Basti pensare che essi coniugano l'utilizzo di un sensore fotografico principale da ben 108 Megapixel, l'eventuale supporto per la connessione alle reti mobili 5G con un prezzo che non arriva a 300 euro.Nonostante i due Realme 9 siano 'varianti' del medesimo dispositivo, le differenze tra i modelli 4G e 5G sono notevoli se si esaminano le specifiche tecniche: ciò si riflette sul prezzo finale. È curioso, ad esempio, che alla fine è il Realme 9 4G a vantare i componenti hardware più potenti montando ad esempio un sensore Samsung HM6 da 108 Megapixel, un obiettivo ultra grandangolare, un display da 6,4 pollici Super AMOLED (FHD+ 2.400 x 1.080 pixel 90 Hz) e un SoC Snapdragon 680 accompagnato da 64 o 128 GB di storage interno. Lo smartphone ha uno spessore di 7,99 mm e 178 grammi di peso.

Viceversa, il Realme 9 5G - pur compatibile con le reti mobili di quinta generazione - ha qualche caratteristica in meno.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NetworkManager 1.38 Released For Improving Linux Network Management]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=NetworkManager-1.38-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=NetworkManager-1.38-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T09:17:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NetworkManager 1.38 is now available for this widely-used software on the Linux desktop (and elsewhere) for managing wired and wireless network interfaces...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch Linux Temporarily Steps Back From WirePlumber After Snafu]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Arch-Linux-WirePlumber-Snafu</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Arch-Linux-WirePlumber-Snafu"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T09:14:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier this week Arch Linux set the WirePlumber package to replace PipeWire-Media-Session. WirePlumber is the modern, feature-rich session manager for PipeWire and much better off than the reference PipeWire-Media-Session manager that is effectively unmaintained. But Arch Linux developers are now calling this premature and have reverted the change...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Resize root partition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uonlqc/resize_root_partition/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uonlqc/resize_root_partition/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T09:09:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is it possible to resize my root which is already full? I'm trying using GParted and it is refusing.
    submitted by    /u/mpokie  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch audio not working until I switch the audio profile]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uomjwe/arch_audio_not_working_until_i_switch_the_audio/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uomjwe/arch_audio_not_working_until_i_switch_the_audio/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T07:48:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I updated my system with the yay command and then the sound stopped to work. After trying a few things I realized that it starts working again when I switch the sound profile. If I stop playing some sound it stops working again.
 For example after logging in I can click on the soundbar and hear a sound but when I open up YouTube it stops working. I then switch the sound profile and can watch the YouTube video. If I stop the video for too long it stops working again.
 Do you have any idea what might cause these issues?
    submitted by    /u/Neotricx  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Realtà aumentata: Google presenta gli occhiali che fanno da traduttore]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Realta-aumentata-Google-presenta-gli-occhiali-che-fanno-da-traduttore_24509</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Realta-aumentata-Google-presenta-gli-occhiali-che-fanno-da-traduttore_24509"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T07:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[È indubbio che gli occhiali Google Glass siano stati uno dei più grandi fallimenti della storia dell'azienda. Un prodotto caricato di enormi aspettative che però non ha mai raggiunto il mercato di massa. E forse non tanto perché non vi fosse interesse ma perché i Google Glass sono rimasti un dispositivo piuttosto costoso, riservato soltanto al mercato professionale e delle imprese.In occasione della Google I/O 2022 l'azienda di Mountain View ha confermato che l'idea di realizzare occhiali smart basati sulla realtà aumentata non è tramontata.I portavoce di Google hanno mostrato un breve video che descrive un prototipo di occhiali in grado di abbattere le barriere linguistiche e consentire la traduzione in tempo reale. In altre parole chi indossa i nuovi occhiali Google può leggere la trascrizione istantanea del parlato tradotta nella propria lingua mentre sta guardando negli occhi il suo interlocutore.

Come si vede nell'immagine, il software degli occhiali Google rileva automaticamente che l'altra persona sta parlando in inglese quindi traduce le sue parole nella lingua conosciuta da chi indossa il dispositivo smart.Come si vede, almeno allo stato attuale, non si tratta affatto di una nuova versione dei Google Glass.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CCleaner 6.0 launches with new Performance Optimizer tool]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178552</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/05/13/ccleaner-6-0-released-featuring-new-performance-optimizer-tool/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T04:44:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Piriform released CCleaner 6.0, a new major milestone for the system optimizer, this week to the public. The new version is available as a feature-limited free version and a professional version. CCleaner […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post CCleaner 6.0 launches with new Performance Optimizer tool appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Besides the memes, why are you really using Arch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uoj93j/besides_the_memes_why_are_you_really_using_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uoj93j/besides_the_memes_why_are_you_really_using_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T04:03:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my time as linux enthusiast, I stumbled across many Arch users. But only a few could hive me a real answer why they’re using Arch. So why do you use it?
    submitted by    /u/NokuHD  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[`xdg-open` has been complaining because it tries to run`kde-config`, which isn't installed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uogwpv/xdgopen_has_been_complaining_because_it_tries_to/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uogwpv/xdgopen_has_been_complaining_because_it_tries_to/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T01:52:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[/usr/bin/xdg-open: line 501: test: : integer expression expected /usr/bin/xdg-open: line 502: test: : integer expression expected /usr/bin/xdg-open: line 503: test: : integer expression expected 
 and those lines are the three tests in
 kfmclient_fix_exit_code() { version=`LC_ALL=C.UTF-8 kde-config --version 2>/dev/null | grep '^KDE'` major=`echo $version | sed 's/KDE.*: \([0-9]\).*/\1/'` minor=`echo $version | sed 's/KDE.*: [0-9]*\.\([0-9]\).*/\1/'` release=`echo $version | sed 's/KDE.*: [0-9]*\.[0-9]*\.\([0-9]\).*/\1/'` test "$major" -gt 3 && return $1 test "$minor" -gt 5 && return $1 test "$release" -gt 4 && return $1 return 0 } 
 . . . and (a) I can't find the kde-config command or anything like it anywhere and (b) xdg-open doesn't source anything I can see.
 So I'm getting the impression I'm missing something idiotic but, well, so be it.
 Is this just some command that's gone now and I should just hack up a substitute? It looks as if ln -s /usr/bin/kdeinit5 ~/bin/kde-config does the trick but that feels unclean.
    submitted by    /u/jthill  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How can I find out my laptop charging rate?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uofcpb/how_can_i_find_out_my_laptop_charging_rate/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uofcpb/how_can_i_find_out_my_laptop_charging_rate/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T00:27:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have a 100w GaN charger and want to know if it is actually charging at 100w
    submitted by    /u/theguysk21  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[15 Safe Websites for Downloading Windows Software]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=152689</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/3459316/websites-download-windows-software"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows has tons of free software, and of course, there are so many websites where you can download it. The challenge is that a lot of these freeware download sites, each claiming to be the best, routinely saddle the software with custom installers, adware, crapware, and bloatware. 
    
However, there are still quite a few reliable software download websites which don’t complicate the core installer with crapware. The following updated list comprises an exhaustive collection of sites where you can download Windows software, minus the bad stuff.
   

Content

Our Criteria to Assess a Source's Safety for Software Downloads
1. Microsoft.com
2. Microsoft Store 
3. Developer's Website 
4. SourceForge
5. AlternativeTo
6. GitHub
7. Steam
8. Epic Games
9. Filepuma
10. Ninite
11. Softpedia
12. DownloadCrew
13. FileHorse
14. Chocolatey
15. DeviantArt
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Install Unsigned Drivers in Windows
  ... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sayak Boral</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Need to restart `pulseaudio` every time I open browser to play video]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uoec8a/need_to_restart_pulseaudio_every_time_i_open/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uoec8a/need_to_restart_pulseaudio_every_time_i_open/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T23:33:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This happened after an update and a reboot. Basically, I need to restart pulseaudio everytime I want to play a video on a browser or hear audio in general.
  systemctl restart --user pulseaudio  Even if you already restarted pulseaudio, the problem happens again when opening another YouTube tab or closing/reopening browser.
    submitted by    /u/MISTREAPERf  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AUR is down?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uodmbb/aur_is_down/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uodmbb/aur_is_down/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T22:57:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Can't seem to access the AUR right now. Is this happening to anyone else?
    submitted by    /u/Prizefighter-Mercury  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come risolvere le problematiche relative all’audio quando lavorate da remoto]]></title>
        <id>3570|20220513000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/audio-30/come-risolvere-problematiche-relative-allaudio-quando-lavorate-remoto-3570"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Una delle principali problematiche, per l’utente che lavora da casa su sistemi aziendali, è quella relativa all’audio delle telefonate, fatte o ricevute, con i clienti. Audio mancante, gracchiante, incompleto, il microfono che non funziona, sono tra i principali difetti. Vediamo come cercare di risolvere questi problemi, perché, almeno in alcuni casi le soluzioni sono molto semplici.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tried to use the new Install script but it failed and I'm not really sure what happened?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uocepw/tried_to_use_the_new_install_script_but_it_failed/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uocepw/tried_to_use_the_new_install_script_but_it_failed/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T21:59:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Could someone please explain what exactly is causing this to fail?
 To me it looks like it is looking for the drive at /dev/sda instead of /dev/nvme0n1 but im not 100% sure.
 Hardware model detected: Eluktronics Inc. MAX-15; UEFI mode: True Processor model detected: Intel(R) Core(TM) i7-10870H CPU @ 2.20GHz Memory statistics: 15473192 available out of 16210456 total installed Could not detect virtual system: ['/usr/bin/systemd-detect-virt'] exited with abnormal exit code [256]: b'none\r\n' System is not running in a VM: ['/usr/bin/systemd-detect-virt'] exited with abnormal exit code [256]: b'none\r\n' Virtualization detected: None; is VM: None Graphics devices detected: dict_keys(['Intel Corporation CometLake-H GT2 [UHD Graphics] (rev 05)', 'NVIDIA Corporation TU104BM [GeForce RTX 2070 SUP…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iranian hackers exposed in a highly targeted espionage campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/iranian-hackers-exposed-in-a-highly-targeted-espionage-campaign/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/iranian-hackers-exposed-in-a-highly-targeted-espionage-campaign/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T21:30:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat analysts have spotted a novel attack attributed to the Iranian hacking group known as APT34 group or Oilrig, who targeted a Jordanian diplomat with custom-crafted tools. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 of the Best VPN Apps for iPhone and Android]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=473562</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15291293/best-mobile-vpn-apps"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly everyone uses the internet daily at this point, there’s almost no way around it. Between cybercriminals, phishing emails, and targeted ads, though, many people are looking for ways to protect themselves while they use the internet. This is where VPN apps come in handy, since they can help protect your browsing habits and data on virtually any device.
   

Content

What Is a VPN?
What About Mobile VPNs?
The Benefits of Having VPN Apps on Your Mobile Device
1. NordVPN
2. Surfshark
3. ExpressVPN
4. Datacappy
5. CyberGhost
6. Windscribe
7. ProtonVPN
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Spot a Facebook Phishing Email and Similar Scams
    
What Is a VPN?
    
A virtual private network, or VPN for short, is essentially a service that protects your online privacy. These virtual networks create a sort of encrypted tunnel... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Megan Glosson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ukrainian imprisoned for selling access to thousands of PCs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ukrainian-imprisoned-for-selling-access-to-thousands-of-pcs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ukrainian-imprisoned-for-selling-access-to-thousands-of-pcs/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T21:10:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Glib Oleksandr Ivanov-Tolpintsev, a 28-year-old from Ukraine, was sentenced today to 4 years in prison for stealing thousands of login credentials per week and selling them on a dark web marketplace. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaFX install help]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uob9ly/javafx_install_help/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uob9ly/javafx_install_help/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T21:09:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am studying a BSc at University of the people, and the unit I'm working on now works with JavaFX. However, I'm having trouble getting JavaFX to work at all, and as you can tell it's quite important I get it to work, otherwise I can't get my work done.
 Any guide or general information of what I'm doing wrong will really help. I'm fairly new at using Linux so treat me like a beginner.
 If this will help I get get these errors when I run Main.java from a new javafx project:
 ​
 Graphics Device initialization failed for : es2, sw
 Error initializing QuantumRenderer: no suitable pipeline found
 java.lang.RuntimeException: java.lang.RuntimeException: Error initializing QuantumRenderer: no suitable pipeline found
 at [javafx.graphics](https://javafx.graphics)@18.0.1/com.sun.javafx.tk.quantum.Q…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Install Free HEVC Codecs on Windows 10 (for H.265 Video)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=680690</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/680690/how-to-install-free-hevc-codecs-on-windows-10-for-h.265-video/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 10 supports video files encoded with High-Efficiency Video Coding (HEVC), also known as H.265 video. However, Microsoft charges for its official codecs and doesn’t include them in Windows 10. You can get them for free without busting out the credit card and spending $0.99.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Initial Performance Of NVIDIA's R515 Open-Source Linux GPU Kernel Driver]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31119</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31119"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As outlined in yesterday's extensive article about NVIDIA's new open-source Linux kernel GPU driver, currently for consumer GeForce RTX GPUs the driver is considered of "alpha quality" while NVIDIA's initial focus has been on data center GPU support. In any event with having lots of Turing/Ampere GPUs around, I've been trying out this new open-source Linux kernel driver on the consumer GPUs. In particular, I've been curious about the performance of using this open-source kernel driver relative to the default, existing closed-source kernel driver. Here are some early benchmarks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia Releases Open-Source Linux GPU Drivers, With a Catch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=805004</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/805004/nvidia-releases-open-source-linux-gpu-drivers-with-a-catch/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T20:32:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gaming on Linux has always been a bit more complicated than on Windows (or game consoles), and one reason for that is Nvidia’s poor driver support on Linux. That’s now changing, though it’s unclear how much the situation will improve.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Subscription Boxes for Gardeners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/13463/the-best-subscription-boxes-for-gardeners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/13463/the-best-subscription-boxes-for-gardeners/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gardening is a satisfying hobby for so many reasons—your outdoor space looks great, you’ve helped cultivate new life, and you even get some crops or flowers in return. We’ve checked out the best subscription boxes for gardeners so that your green finger endeavors are even more successful.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Allen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Any clue why my programs are using English instead of default language?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uoa0b7/any_clue_why_my_programs_are_using_english/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uoa0b7/any_clue_why_my_programs_are_using_english/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T20:16:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since some days ago... I have been experiencing something really weird. 
 All my programs run in English, unless I manually override their specific configuration. 
 I have tried locale command, and everything looks good. LC_ALL is empty which I have read it is the way, as it should only be used for specific cases where you want to quickly override all languages for a specific task. 
 locale -a also seems to output the expected, and my KDE Plasma also has the proper configuration in the language section of their settings. 
 Here is my system data. 
  Operating System: Arch Linux KDE Plasma Version: 5.24.5 KDE Frameworks Version: 5.93.0 Qt Version: 5.15.3 Kernel Version: 5.17.6-zen1-1-zen (64-bit) Graphics Platform: Wayland 
 Examples of programs that have switched to English: - Dolphin - Kate - FreeTube - Gnome Boxes - GIMP
 Examplees of programas that use the correct language: - The Plasma settings are half in my language, half not. Weird. - locale seems to speak in my language too.
    submitted by    /u/anotheruser123123  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Just made my first package on the AUR, rofi-checklist-git!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uo9yi8/just_made_my_first_package_on_the_aur/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uo9yi8/just_made_my_first_package_on_the_aur/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T20:13:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was surprised how easy it was to get stuff on the AUR. I made a small little shell script for rofi that works as a checklist, if anyone wants to check it out (GitHub, AUR). It's not much, but I find it useful and I hope somebody else does too. I'm pretty new to bash scripting so they script itself is kind of messy and bodged together, but it works. That's all, just wanted to share.
    submitted by    /u/ElnuDev  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Clear Your Computer’s CMOS to Reset BIOS Settings]]></title>
        <id>http://www.howtogeek.com/?p=131623</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/131623/how-to-clear-your-computers-cmos-to-reset-bios-settings/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your computer stores low-level settings like the system time and hardware settings in its CMOS. These settings are configured in the BIOS or UEFI setup menu. If you’re experiencing a hardware compatibility issue or another problem, you may want to try clearing the CMOS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Undone replacement of pipewire-media-session with wireplumber]]></title>
        <id>tag:archlinux.org,2022-05-12:/news/undone-replacement-of-pipewire-media-session-with-wireplumber/</id>
        <link href="https://archlinux.org/news/undone-replacement-of-pipewire-media-session-with-wireplumber/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T19:48:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two days ago the wireplumber package was made to replace pipewire-media-session as the latter session manager for PipeWire is considered dead upstream and will see no more releases. Unfortunately, this step was premature.
Our pipewire audio packages (pipewire-alsa, pipewire-jack and pipewire-pulse) ship configuration that prompt media-session to activate PipeWire's audio features. When these packages are not installed and the configuration is missing, PipeWire can be used for screen recording without interfering with ALSA or PulseAudio.
WirePlumber disregards this mechanism and always configures PipeWire to grab audio devices, meaning users of PulseAudio or bare ALSA experience broken audio.
The replacement has been reverted while we attempt to look for a better solution switching to WirePlumber. If you are currently not using PipeWire for audio and wireplumber got installed on your system, please reinstall pipewire-media-session and reboot to restore audio functionality.
pacman -Syu pipewire-media-session]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jan Alexander Steffens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will fire jail propagate to subprocesses?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uo9dnr/will_fire_jail_propagate_to_subprocesses/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uo9dnr/will_fire_jail_propagate_to_subprocesses/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T19:46:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anyone know if I run a bash script that executes other commands like a Python script or another shell script if the options I passed to firejail will propagate to the subprocesses?
 E.g.
 firejail --net=none launcher.sh 
 Where launcher.sh might run a couple of python scripts and a shell script?
    submitted by    /u/krisclarkdev  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[cron isn't removing files at startup]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uo97o4/cron_isnt_removing_files_at_startup/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uo97o4/cron_isnt_removing_files_at_startup/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T19:39:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On some computers I administer, I would like to have the Desktop cleared for the student user at reboot. I've tried doing this with cron, but it isn't working and I can't figure out why. Here is what I've tried:
 $ crontab -e @reboot /usr/bin/rm -rf /home/student/Desktop/* 
 I've tried that as the 'student' user as well as on root and the files remain after reboot. I've also tried it with just 'rm' instead of the full path. No dice. Any ideas why it isn't working?
    submitted by    /u/LorenWard  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open 3D Engine 22.05 Released With New Features]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=O3DE-22.04-Open-3D-Engine</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=O3DE-22.04-Open-3D-Engine"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T19:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In addition to a new development release of Godot 4.0 out today, the other high profile open-source 3D game engine is Open 3D Engine (O3DE) that started last year from Amazon's Lumberyard Engine and now under the Linux Foundation's Open 3D Foundation. Out today is O3DE 22.05 for this high profile free software 3D game engine...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save $70 on an Apple Watch Series 7]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=467477</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15103583/apple-watch-series-7"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may be looking forward to all the great fitness you’ll be doing in the great weather this summer. Get some help with that by buying an Apple Watch Series 7. It’s now available for $70 off (its lowest ever!) in certain colors with a 41mm sport band and GPS.
    
The Watch features the Always-On Retina display for almost 20% more screen real estate than the previous model, which makes it easier to see your messages, fitness counter, health information, etc. This information is under the most crack-resistant front crystal yet for an Apple Watch. It also sports IP6X dust resistance and is swim-proof to boot.
    
This particular version of the Apple Watch Series 7 is non-cellular, meaning you will have to remain connected to your iPhone for you to take calls, use the health and fitness features, or do anything Internet-related while using the Watch.
    

    
You can check your heart rhythm with the ECG app anytime and anywhere and get high and low heart rate and irregular heart... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eternity malware kit offers stealer, miner, worm, ransomware tools]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/eternity-malware-kit-offers-stealer-miner-worm-ransomware-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/eternity-malware-kit-offers-stealer-miner-worm-ransomware-tools/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T19:18:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors have launched the 'Eternity Project,' a new malware-as-a-service where threat actors can purchase a malware toolkit that can be customized with different modules depending on the attack being conducted. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fix “Network Blocking Encrypted DNS Traffic” on iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=785617</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/785617/how-to-fix-network-blocking-encrypted-dns-traffic-on-iphone/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T19:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your iPhone can encrypt DNS traffic so that the names of websites and servers you access cannot be seen by third parties. Occasionally your iPhone may display a warning that encrypted DNS traffic is being blocked. Learn what it means and how to resolve it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pixel Watch Is Google’s Long-Awaited Apple Watch Competitor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=804871</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/804871/pixel-watch-is-googles-long-awaited-apple-watch-competitor/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T18:35:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google held its yearly Google I/O event on Wednesday, and among the sea of new software and hardware announcements, we got our first look at the long-awaited Pixel Watch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[virtualbox-host-dkms error when compiling kernel modules (solved)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uo7jrl/virtualboxhostdkms_error_when_compiling_kernel/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uo7jrl/virtualboxhostdkms_error_when_compiling_kernel/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T18:23:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I did a pacman -Syu today and Virtualbox stopped working. I narrowed down the issue to the kernel modules not compiling. When installing virtualbox-host-dkms I get the error Error! Bad return status for module build on kernel: $kernelname. It also spits out "exit: 10".
 The solution was to downgrade gcc from 12.1 to 11.2. I navigated to /var/cache/pacman/pkg and ran sudo pacman -U gcc-11.2.0-4-x86_64.pkg.tar.zst gcc-libs-11.2.0-4-x86_64.pkg.tar.zst lib32-gcc-libs-11.2.0-4-x86_64.pkg.tar.zst and then the kernel modules compiled properly.
 Just putting this out there because googling the issue didn't result in much useful info, so maybe newer users will come across this if they experience this issue
    submitted by    /u/pinephreak  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zyxel fixes firewall flaws that could lead to hacked networks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/zyxel-fixes-firewall-flaws-that-could-lead-to-hacked-networks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/zyxel-fixes-firewall-flaws-that-could-lead-to-hacked-networks/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T18:13:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat analysts who discovered a vulnerability affecting multiple Zyxel products report that the network equipment company fixed it via a silent update pushed out two weeks ago. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zyxel silently fixes critical RCE vulnerability in firewall products]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/zyxel-silently-fixes-critical-rce-vulnerability-in-firewall-products/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/zyxel-silently-fixes-critical-rce-vulnerability-in-firewall-products/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T18:13:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat analysts who discovered a vulnerability affecting multiple Zyxel products report that the network equipment company fixed it via a silent update pushed out two weeks ago. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s Pixel Buds Pro Will Have Incredible Battery Life]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=804964</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/804964/googles-pixel-buds-pro-will-have-incredible-battery-life/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T18:02:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has released a few pairs of wireless earbuds at this point, and the company revealed the a new pair on Wednesday during the Google I/O main keynote. The Pixel Buds Pro aims to be one of the best wireless earbuds ever, and that might just be true.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Is My Microphone Quiet in Windows 11? 5 Fixes to Try]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=802204</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/802204/why-is-my-microphone-quiet-in-windows-11-5-fixes-to-try/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s happened to all of us. You’re in a video call, and someone says “you sound quiet.” There are a surprising number of things that could be causing this in Windows 11. Let’s figure out what’s going on.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rivian R1T Electric Truck Recalled Over Dangerous Child Safety Issue]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117766/rivian-r1t-electric-truck-recalled-over-dangerous-child-safety-issue/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117766/rivian-r1t-electric-truck-recalled-over-dangerous-child-safety-issue/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T17:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, Rivian issued its first recall on the popular new R1T electric truck over a critical safety issue affecting over 500 vehicles. According to the NHTSA, defective airbag sensors may not deactivate when a child is in the passenger seat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOOGEE S98 Smartphone Review: Rugged and Innovative]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=482006</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15291028/doogee-s98-smartphone"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T17:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With so many Android devices on the market, sometimes it’s hard to find the best option for your needs. For those with active lifestyles that need a durable phone with innovative features, the DOOGEE S98 could be the perfect solution. With a brand philosophy of “Our spirit is to have the courage to keep challenging and exploring,” you’d expect an impressive device. I recently had the pleasure of seeing just how well the DOOGEE S98 smartphone lives up to the brand’s promises.
    
This is a sponsored article and was made possible by DOOGEE. The actual contents and opinions are the sole views of the author who maintains editorial independence even when a post is sponsored.
    
Overview of Features
    
Straight away, the DOOGEE S98 has an incredible feature set, along with accessories, that you won’t find on most major smartphones. Even when you lift it for the first time, you can tell it’s designed to be more durable and rugged than the competition.
    
The phone has a 6.3 in. LCD FHD+ waterdrop screen. The 1080 x 2340 resolution screen is heavily protected from drops... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Crystal Crowder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sony's WH-1000XM5 Arrive With a Refined Design at a Higher Price]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117753/sonys-wh-1000xm5-arrive-with-a-refined-design-at-a-higher-price/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117753/sonys-wh-1000xm5-arrive-with-a-refined-design-at-a-higher-price/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T17:09:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After several recent leaks, Sony unveiled its new premium WH-1000XM5 headphones with an all-new refined design and countless upgrades. While everything is a little better than the previous generation, they cost $399, a $50 price increase over the 1000XM4s.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BPFdoor: Stealthy Linux malware bypasses firewalls for remote access]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/bpfdoor-stealthy-linux-malware-bypasses-firewalls-for-remote-access/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/bpfdoor-stealthy-linux-malware-bypasses-firewalls-for-remote-access/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T17:07:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recently discovered backdoor malware called BPFdoor has been stealthily targeting Linux and Solaris systems without being noticed for more than five years. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Ilascu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s a POAP? How Memories Are Being Transformed in Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=800246</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/800246/whats-a-poap-how-memories-are-being-transformed-in-web3/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[POAPs are used to mark participation or attendance at an event. Just like you might save ticket stubs from concerts or movies, buy pins at a sporting event or festival, or collect matches from restaurants or hotels, a POAP is a digital version of that same notion, satiating our desire to collect items that mark our experiences throughout life.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Colin Brightfield</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come condividere lo stesso abbonamento Netflix per pagare meno]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2016/01/si-puo-dividere-il-prezzo-di-netflix.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2016/01/si-puo-dividere-il-prezzo-di-netflix.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T16:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix è il miglior servizio per vedere in streaming film e serie TV, vista anche l'elevata qualità audio e video offerta dai contenuti, in particolare se attiviamo l'abbonamento più costoso (che sblocca il 4K con HDR, una qualità impensabile per un flusso in streaming via Internet).

 I costi dell'abbonamento di Netflix vanno da 7,99 € a 17,99 € al mese, in base alla qualità che vogliamo...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[two dams can be found on my login screen but I don’t know how to delete them, where could they be?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uo59r0/two_dams_can_be_found_on_my_login_screen_but_i/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uo59r0/two_dams_can_be_found_on_my_login_screen_but_i/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T16:39:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/9934d  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD's Xilinx Posts New Linux DRM Display Driver]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Xilinx-2022-DRM-Driver</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Xilinx-2022-DRM-Driver"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T16:19:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AMD-owned Xilinx posted a new patch series today implementing a new DRM display driver for supporting their soft MIPI DSI Tx subsystem IP...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LEGO Optimus Prime Is Ready to Roll Out]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117736/lego-optimus-prime-is-ready-to-roll-out/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117736/lego-optimus-prime-is-ready-to-roll-out/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T16:17:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Move over Batmobile; LEGO just announced its best 80s nostalgia set yet: Optimus Prime. And if just the name of the set isn’t enough to make you instantly pull out $169.99 to buy it, you should know this set actually transforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Hendrickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Android TV 13 Will Upgrade Picture-in-Picture Mode]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=804506</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/804506/android-tv-13-will-upgrade-picture-in-picture-mode/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T16:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Android TV powers many different smart TVs, cable boxes, and some of the best streaming devices, and a customized version called Google TV has appeared on some devices. Google has now shared more information about the next major update, Android TV 13.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There's Now a Wordle Game for Food Lovers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lifesavvy.com/128798/theres-now-a-wordle-game-for-food-lovers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lifesavvy.com/128798/theres-now-a-wordle-game-for-food-lovers/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T16:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By now, you’ve likely played Wordle at least once. The Hangman-esque game took the internet by storm earlier this year, and now there are all kinds of iterations, including one for foodies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shea Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is the Line Under the Battery on the iPhone Lock Screen?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=802975</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/802975/what-is-the-line-under-the-battery-on-the-iphone-lock-screen/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T16:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The iPhone has a pretty simple and intuitive interface, but there are still some things that appear with no explanation. One such thing is the line under the cell signal, Wi-Fi, and battery icons on the lock screen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We take a closer look at Suggested Actions in Windows 11, and show you how to disable it]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178538</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/05/12/we-take-a-closer-look-at-suggested-actions-in-windows-11-and-show-you-how-to-disable-it/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T15:52:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft released Windows 11 Insider Preview Build 25115 to the Dev Channel. It introduced a new feature called Suggested Actions. Microsoft showcased it with two screenshots. We take a closer look at […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post We take a closer look at Suggested Actions in Windows 11, and show you how to disable it appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ghacks Deals: The Jumbo 2022 Javascript Bundle]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178549</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/05/12/ghacks-deals-the-jumbo-2022-javascript-bundle/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T15:50:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript is one of the most popular programming languages; if you want to get started with the language or finetune your skills, you may find the Jumbo 2022 JavaScript Bundle perfectly suited […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Ghacks Deals: The Jumbo 2022 Javascript Bundle appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smart Lock Google: cos'è e come funziona]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Smart-Lock-Google-cos-e-e-come-funziona_24508</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Smart-Lock-Google-cos-e-e-come-funziona_24508"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T15:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ogni dispositivo mobile è una vera e propria miniera di dati personali e informazioni riservate. Ciò che custodisce va mantenuto protetto nei confronti di terzi sia evitando l'installazione di app che possono trasferire dati personali a soggetti sconosciuti, sia impostando lo sblocco del dispositivo mediante impronta digitale, un PIN o una password complessi.La sequenza grafica viene comunemente utilizzata per proteggere il dispositivo ma è necessario sceglierne una articolata e assicurarsi che qualcuno, nelle vicinanze, non la lista di fatto memorizzando.Una delle funzioni meno conosciute di Android, nonostante sia stata introdotta già ai tempi della release 5.0 Lollipop (2014), è Smart Lock: essa permette di mantenere lo smartphone sbloccato quando si ha il telefono con sé, se ci si trova a casa o in un altro luogo affidabile ('Luoghi attendibili'), se nelle immediate vicinanze ci fosse un proprio dispositivo Bluetooth (uno smartwatch, una smart band, un PC,...).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Future Rivian EV Pre-Orders Will No Longer Guarantee a Price]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117735/future-rivian-ev-pre-orders-will-no-longer-guarantee-a-price/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117735/future-rivian-ev-pre-orders-will-no-longer-guarantee-a-price/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T15:43:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in March, Rivian announced large price increases for its popular R1T and R1S electric truck and SUV, affecting all orders. However, it quickly rolled back that decision after backlash and honored the original pre-order price for early buyers. And while that still stands, upcoming orders will lose the price guarantee.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox crashing on system restart]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uo3rj9/firefox_crashing_on_system_restart/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uo3rj9/firefox_crashing_on_system_restart/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T15:31:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey!
 Over the last few days I am running into a new issue with Firefox that I have no idea how to debug. When I boot up the computer, Firefox would usually restore the windows and tabs from the last session. But in the last few days, I am running into a new issue where Firefox doesn't open properly when it tries to restore the windows from the previous session. Here is a screenshot of what it looks like. The black window on the left is supposedly Firefox, but it's not responsive at all. The black is also from the KDE login splash screen (you can kind of see the logo). When I close that window from the task bar and reopen Firefox, it doesn't open any previous tabs, even pinned tabs. Another weird thing is that it logs me out of some sites, such as Reddit, which is weird and leads me to think some local data is getting wiped. This whole issue only happens sometimes, but more often than not and has only started in the last few days. I am guessing it started after a recent update.
 Any pointers on how I can dig into this further to figure out what's causing it?
 I am running KDE Plasma (X11), NVIDIA 3070 TI with nvidia driver package.
    submitted by    /u/Probotect0r  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Beginner’s Guide to Git]]></title>
        <id>http://maketecheasier.com/?p=13394</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/14185817/beginners-guide-to-git"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T15:25:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git is a wonderful program. It is a version control utility that allows you to seamlessly manage a file’s edit history. While this might seem simple and unimpressive, Git’s strength lies in the fact that you can extend this history to entire groups of files and directories.
    
This means that it is possible to use Git to track every change in every file for every directory. This is highly useful if you are doing a project where you want to have a rolling snapshot of everything that you are doing.
   

Content

What is Git?
Installing Git
Using Git for a Local Project
Using Git for Online Projects
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Determine Whether a Website Is Legit and Safe to Use
    
What is Git?
    
At its... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramces Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up Appointment Schedules in Google Calendar]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=800079</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/800079/google-calendar-appointment-schedules/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T15:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you have a business or service where you want to allow clients and customers to book appointments with you, take a look at the Appointment Schedules feature in Google Calendar.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Drive Will "Delete" Your Duplicate Files]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117729/google-drive-will-delete-your-duplicate-files/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117729/google-drive-will-delete-your-duplicate-files/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T14:56:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an effort to streamline Google Drive and help optimize your storage space, Google is rolling out a feature that is sure to be divisive among its users. Soon, it will replace all of your files and folders stored in multiple locations with shortcuts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzanne Humphries</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Steam Deck Update Includes the Feature You Asked For]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117726/new-steam-deck-update-includes-the-feature-you-asked-for/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117726/new-steam-deck-update-includes-the-feature-you-asked-for/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T14:51:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After the last Steam Deck update unlocked system-wide performance settings, gamers asked for the option to save these settings to individual games. And Valve listened—today’s update introduces per-game performance settings that you can quickly program through the Quick Access menu.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s Pixel Tablet Arrives in 2023 to Battle the iPad]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=804749</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/804749/googles-pixel-tablet-arrives-in-2023-to-battle-the-ipad/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T14:47:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s interest in Android tablets has gone up and down over the years (mostly down), but at Google I/O on Wednesday, the company revealed there will be a Pixel-branded tablet sometime in 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why does Debian use so much more memory than Arch?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uo2lyk/why_does_debian_use_so_much_more_memory_than_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uo2lyk/why_does_debian_use_so_much_more_memory_than_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T14:39:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been experimenting with putting together a desktop environment my brother can run on his crappy old laptop (2G ram single core). The first one I built on a base Arch install and the second on a Debian server install. I used the same packages, or if I couldn't find an exact match I was careful to install packages with the same memory footprint. I also disabled all the services that Debian was using and Arch was not. The result was the Arch system idles at 230 MB of ram and Debian idles at 445 MB. It may not seem like much, but with 2 gigs of ram it can make a difference. The Arch system is a lot more responsive, things happen like right freaking now while the Debian system is quite a bit more sluggish. Why is that?
    submitted by    /u/pressman57  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Arch Linux paradox noone seems to talk about]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uo2lms/the_arch_linux_paradox_noone_seems_to_talk_about/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uo2lms/the_arch_linux_paradox_noone_seems_to_talk_about/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T14:39:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The paradox that says
 "You will never complete the installation of Arch Linux"
 I started installing Arch linux about 3yrs ago and I got it to a point of working in about 45mins(much of that has to do with internet speed). Yet, every time I have to do something unique, I have to install more packages in the system to make it more complete. What I believed to be a complete installation of Arch Linux 3yrs ago, now I realise is very incomplete.
 And the fact that there are always new things coming. What wasnt possible in linux then is now being possible thanks to many people writing and improving free software to do real work. Means more puzzle pieces you stumble upon to make your system more complete, means there is always more steps to do.
 I think its better related to with the big bang, that thing which initialized the universe. We have a date when it started but not when big bang end. Why? Because it is still going on. Big Bang will end only when the universe ends. Same thing with Arch Linux. Your Arch Linux installation will be complete only after the death of technology.
    submitted by    /u/cy_narrator  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tutti i metodi per sospendere correttamente Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/05/se-dobbiamo-allontanarci-dalla.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/05/se-dobbiamo-allontanarci-dalla.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T14:36:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Se dobbiamo allontanarci dalla postazione PC per la pausa pranzo o solo per pochi minuti conviene metterlo in modalità sospensione, così da risparmiare energia o, nel caso dei computer portatili, aumentare la durata della batteria. La modalità sospensione consente di riprendere rapidamente da dove eravamo rimasti senza spegnere completamente il computer: avremo tutti i nostri file e programmi...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NVIDIA has open-sourced its Linux GPU kernel drivers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/linux/nvidia-has-open-sourced-its-linux-gpu-kernel-drivers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/linux/nvidia-has-open-sourced-its-linux-gpu-kernel-drivers/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T14:31:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NVIDIA has published the source code of its kernel modules for the R515 driver, using a dual licensing model that combines the GPL and MIT licenses, making the modules legally re-distributable. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cannot write password on lock screen after putting laptop to sleep]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uo2f1n/cannot_write_password_on_lock_screen_after/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uo2f1n/cannot_write_password_on_lock_screen_after/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T14:30:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have a problem with getting past lock screen after putting laptop to sleep. When I wake it up password field is write protected ( basically i can't type anything in it ), and it's not keyboard fault because when click CapsLock it notifies me about clicking it, and also i can get to tty. My display manager is Lightdm with gtk greeter and my DE is xfce4. Also I think that this started happening after I installed deepin DE for fun and then removed it. If anyone knew how I could tell me how I could fix it I would be grateful.
    submitted by    /u/Kuba_CXD  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kovol Sprint 120W Desktop Charger Review: Compact and Speedy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117285/kovol-sprint-120w-desktop-charger-review/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117285/kovol-sprint-120w-desktop-charger-review/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T14:24:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you start buying new smartphones, gaming handhelds, and tablets, you will eventually realize that there aren’t enough USB ports to go around when you need them. The Kovol Sprint 120W Desktop Charger is worth investing in to keep all of your devices juiced up and ready to roll at the same time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arnold Carreiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>