<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-05-29T02:06:04.054Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A nice way to share a disk between users?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzz4cp/a_nice_way_to_share_a_disk_between_users/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzz4cp/a_nice_way_to_share_a_disk_between_users/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T23:46:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello,
 I've 2 disks on my PC:
  
1 SSD for /root and /home (ext4)
 1 HDD for backups (etx4)
 1 HDD for data and storage (NTFS) (Its legacy from when i had dual boot with windows. Wanting to reformat as ext4 or XFS).
  
And i also have 2 active users on the PC, me and my wife.
 Is there a fancy way to have que Storage HDD mounted as, let's say /home/shared? with full read/write access to both users if i formated as ext4 or XFS?
 Nowadays, being NTFS both users has full access to all files inside. But if I reformated as XFS or ext4 won't permissions, user and group create conflicts between files from one user and another? I need both users to have full permissions on all disks contents.
 PS: Also, for storage like documents, music, videos, etc in that storage disk should i use XFS, ext4? or its the same any of them?
    submitted by    /u/thalskarth_  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PulseAudio 16.0 Released With A Variety Of Improvements]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=PulseAudio-16.0</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=PulseAudio-16.0"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T23:25:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While PipeWire continues gaining traction for fulfilling the audio management roles long handled by PulseAudio, the PulseAudio project itself continues progressing and successfully evolving its mature code-base. Out this weekend is PulseAudio 16.0...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 Tools for Designing Amazing Social Media Graphics]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=447212</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15040022/design-apps-social-media-graphics"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Social media has become a key part of the marketing strategy for most companies and influencers. However, not everyone has the graphic design chops to make amazing social media graphics on their own. Luckily, there are several great online tools that can help you design graphics for your social media accounts, and many of these tools offer free versions.
   

Content

1. Desygner
2. Canva
3. Piktochart
4. PicMonkey
5. Snappa
6. QuotesCover
7. Adobe Creative Cloud Express
8. Pablo
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:6 of the Best Photo-Editing Apps for iOS
    
1. Desygner
    
Price: Free, subscription starts at $9.95
    
Desygner (Web | Android | iOS) is one of the more elegant tools for creating eye-catching social media images with relatively little effort (though if you want to dive into more detail and spend... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Megan Glosson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Turn Off Auto Brightness on Windows 10 or 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=772783</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/772783/how-to-turn-off-auto-brightness-on-windows-10-or-11/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re tired of your Windows 10 or 11 PC’s screen automatically getting brighter or dimmer, it’s easy to turn off. All it takes is a quick trip to Settings. Here’s how to do it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Software RAID drive missing in 5.18]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzvx1i/software_raid_drive_missing_in_518/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzvx1i/software_raid_drive_missing_in_518/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T20:53:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[5.18 just dropped and it isn't booting right for me. I narrowed it down to a mirrored array in my fstab that I use as a non-boot drive. It loads fine if I downgrade to 5.17. Not sure what the issue is but if I boot 5.18 with it commented out of fstab I find that /proc/mdstat doesn't even exist and I have manually load the module. Even if I do, an mdadm --detail --scan never finds it.
 So far I have tried the following:
  
Adding/removing mdadm and mdadm_udev from my HOOKS in mkinitcpio (neither were needed in the past as it's a non-boot drive)
 Adding/removing mdmon to BINARIES in mkinitcpio (again, never needed in the past)
  
Heads up for anyone running a RAID and any thoughts as to what the issue might be?
    submitted by    /u/SecretAgentKen  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will a clean install of Arch proper help with instability issues I'm having with a derivative?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzv682/will_a_clean_install_of_arch_proper_help_with/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzv682/will_a_clean_install_of_arch_proper_help_with/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T20:11:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am not asking for support for my current not-quite-Arch setup, I'm asking how much a clean install of Arch proper is going to help with general stability.
 I've been using an Arch derivative (EndeavourOS) for about a year now on my main PC, and I'm finding I'm really struggling with stability. This was the first Linux distro I really learned (aside from a brief stint with Kubuntu), so there's been a lot of experimentation, mistakes, and reconfiguration done that I've lost track of. There's a lot I really love about using an Arch-based distro, and I'm wondering if a clean install of Arch proper might help without having to look to another distro family.
 My main issue with this system is stability. It's really not good. Something minor breaks twice a week. Something major breaks twice a m…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What We're Watching: 'Primitive Technology' Gets Back to Basics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118935/what-were-watching-primitive-technology-gets-back-to-basics/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118935/what-were-watching-primitive-technology-gets-back-to-basics/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T20:04:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What if all of our modern technology was somehow rendered useless tomorrow? Most of us are dependent on electricity, supermarkets, clothing stores, and other modern conveniences, but YouTube’s Primitive Technology channel shows us how we can survive (at least in a basic way) without all of that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzanne Humphries</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 Mac Shortcuts Actions You’ll Actually Use]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=764636</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/764636/mac-shortcuts-actions-youll-actually-use/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple added the Shortcuts app to macOS Monterey in 2021, making it easy to build workflows using visual coding blocks just like you can on iPhone and iPad. While the feature still lacks the power of Automator or AppleScript, it’s still pretty useful.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft: The new Windows 11 features from Build 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-the-new-windows-11-features-from-build-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-the-new-windows-11-features-from-build-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T19:53:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During the Build 2022 developer conference, Microsoft announced a number of new features for Windows 11, including an improved Windows Subsystem for Android (WSA) and more. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mayank Parmar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wifi card gone after arch install.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzu9l3/wifi_card_gone_after_arch_install/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzu9l3/wifi_card_gone_after_arch_install/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T19:23:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After installing using archinstall for a test. My wlan0 wifi card is gone, it was there in the live iso. Help would be appreciated
    submitted by    /u/Alecccs  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Restart a MacBook Air]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=807319</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/807319/how-to-restart-a-macbook-air/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T19:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re having trouble with your MacBook Air, it’s easy to restart. A restart will completely reboot and reload the macOS operating system, clearing the system’s working memory for a fresh start. None of your data will be affected. Here are several ways to do it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[the annoying beep bug: is systemctl susped hardcoded in plasma?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uztp75/the_annoying_beep_bug_is_systemctl_susped/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uztp75/the_annoying_beep_bug_is_systemctl_susped/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T18:54:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was trying to bypass the annoying problem of the bell ringing when the PC goes into suspension. The best way would be to add --no-wall to the systemctl call but I can't find any configuration file that allows to change the command (neither in powerdevil nor in solid), while for sddm it exists... any ideas?
    submitted by    /u/guiodic76  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[with kernel 5.18.0-arch1-1's drop today, FreeSync is now enabled by default.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzt58j/with_kernel_5180arch11s_drop_today_freesync_is/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzt58j/with_kernel_5180arch11s_drop_today_freesync_is/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T18:25:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I just tested this as in the past, I've always had to have Option "VariableRefresh" "true" in my .conf file (bspwm on X11). I just removed that line after updated and found that it is, in fact, enabled by default.
    submitted by    /u/peak-shidder  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Freesync, amdgpu and linux 5.18]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzsz51/freesync_amdgpu_and_linux_518/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzsz51/freesync_amdgpu_and_linux_518/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T18:16:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The changenotes say that Freesync would be enabled by default in Linux 5.18. I thought this meant that you didn't have to set VariableRefresh in X11 amdgpu.conf file? It doesn't seem to be the case on my system. Am I mis-understanding what that change is referring to?
 EDIT:
  
FreeSync Video Mode is enabled by default in 5.18, not FreeSync as a whole.
  
Thanks!
    submitted by    /u/Xyklone  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Uniswap With MetaMask on iPhone or Android]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=802099</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/802099/how-to-use-uniswap-with-the-metamask-app-on-iphone-or-android/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T18:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using Uniswap with your MetaMask wallet is one of the easiest ways to “swap” your favorite Ethereum-based tokens in a matter of minutes. Here’s how to do it on your iPhone or Android phone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>RJ Fulton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Maps' Street View Can Now Take Your Phone Back In Time]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118977/google-maps-street-view-can-now-take-your-phone-back-in-time/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118977/google-maps-street-view-can-now-take-your-phone-back-in-time/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T18:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Can you believe it’s been 15 years since Google Street view launched? To celebrate the anniversary, Google will now let you travel back in time when using Street View in the Google Maps app. All you need to do is tap a location in Street View, select “see more dates,” and enjoy the feeling of growing old.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cannot launch VirtualBox, results in NS_ERROR_SOCKET_FAIL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzsg5u/cannot_launch_virtualbox_results_in_ns_error/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzsg5u/cannot_launch_virtualbox_results_in_ns_error/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T17:49:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, so I am trying to run virtualbox (not a VM, just the base app) and I am getting this error: NS_ERROR_SOCKET_FAIL
 I have tried everything i could, researched about this error in other forums/subreddits, still no anwser. Also deleted everything in /tmp/ folder... Here's an screenshot: https://ibb.co/qsDW7P7
 ​
 Does anyone got the same issue or is it just me? If so, can someone help me?
    submitted by    /u/DominiCzech  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[pls help, so weird]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzsc2g/pls_help_so_weird/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzsc2g/pls_help_so_weird/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T17:43:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ey guys, yesterday I left my computer on to watch a movie. After I was tired so went to sleep, but before I was going to shut down but the os wasn't responding so I pressed the button 5 sec and went to sleep. Today, no login screen was showing and I tried a few things. 
 nomodeset and the other 2 didn't do anything Ctrl alt f1 to f3 let me login but didn't accept any command Runlevel3 gave me root console, but no command works, it doesn't go past the 1st line. 
 Also, sometimes changing from f2 to f1 the login screen appears but after login just stays black and after awhile asks for login again
 What can I do? 
 https://imgur.com/a/h41ry64
    submitted by    /u/Asdrubalpraias  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Minecraft Launcher Won't Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzrrpx/minecraft_launcher_wont_launch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzrrpx/minecraft_launcher_wont_launch/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T17:14:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm new to Arch. I have a small amount of experience with Ubuntu, but other than that, I'm still trying to figure things out. 
 I was trying to install minecraft, but when I run the launcher from both terminal and desktop, nothing happens. 
 I got the launcher from https://aur.archlinux.org/packages/minecraft-launcher. I found multiple articles and videos that instructed me to run makepkg, and then run the package. I did all that, and now I'm lost as to why it isn't running. 
 Terminal seems to recognize 'minecraft-launcher' as a command, as it doesn't throw any errors, but when I run 'ps -au | grep minecraft', the only process running is my command. When I run it from the desktop, I get the spinning cursor (which I imagine means it's doing something), but then it just disappears and nothing happens.
 If someone could point me in the right direction that would be greatly appreciated.
 Thank you.
    submitted by    /u/SignificantCredit529  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I don't have muhc money to donate to Arch. So i decided to seed the Arch Iso 24/7 on my server!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzrqp3/i_dont_have_muhc_money_to_donate_to_arch_so_i/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzrqp3/i_dont_have_muhc_money_to_donate_to_arch_so_i/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T17:13:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you for making such a minimalistic Distro!
    submitted by    /u/SchwarzeFlagge  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When to Replace Your Old Monitor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=796494</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/796494/when-to-replace-your-monitor/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While it’s easy to get attached to tech you’ve used for years, a run-down monitor with poor image quality and hardware issues keeps you from experiencing the best in productivity and entertainment. Here’s how to know it’s time to upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Nguyen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rivian Releases 'Soft Sand Mode' Update Just in Time For Summer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119409/rivian-releases-soft-sand-mode-update-just-in-time-for-summer/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119409/rivian-releases-soft-sand-mode-update-just-in-time-for-summer/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T16:34:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You now have one more reason to be excited if you’re the proud owner of the Rivian R1T electric truck or are waiting for the new R1S all-electric SUV. Rivian has finally released its “soft sand” driving mode software update.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Archinstall hard drives doesn't show any.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzql0q/archinstall_hard_drives_doesnt_show_any/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzql0q/archinstall_hard_drives_doesnt_show_any/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T16:15:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It juat gives me an error: I/O error, dev sr0, sector 24512 op 0x0:(READ) flags 0x80700 phys_seg 1 prio class 0
    submitted by    /u/Eetu13  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Install Google Assistant on Samsung Galaxy Smartwatches]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=684233</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/684233/how-to-install-google-assistant-on-samsung-galaxy-smartwatches/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung Galaxy smartwatches are a great option for people with Android phones, but some of them don’t have Google Assistant. We’ll show you how to get Assistant up and running on your Samsung wearable with Wear OS or Tizen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Connect Your PS4/PS5 to a Laptop or Mac]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=post-ideas&amp;p=354429</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/13730542/connect-ps4-to-laptop-mac"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T15:25:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you have your PlayStation next to a monitor or TV, it’s convenient to hook up your console to your setup for quick and easy gaming. However, if you own something like a Mac or a laptop, you may need to do a little more legwork to play games on your screen. Let’s take a look at how you can connect PS4 or PS5 to your laptop or Mac.
   

Content

The Problem With Using a PlayStation's HDMI Cable on a Laptop or Mac
How to Play PS4/PS5 Games on a Laptop or Mac
How to Turn Off PS4/PS5 Controller
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Check for Controller Deadzones in Windows
    
The Problem With Using a PlayStation’s HDMI Cable on a Laptop or Mac
    
If you use a traditional computer and monitor setup that uses HDMI connections, plugging in a... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miguel Leiva-Gomez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ASUS Reveals an Unnecessarily Cool 500Hz Gaming Monitor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119131/asus-reveals-an-unnecessarily-cool-500hz-gaming-monitor/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119131/asus-reveals-an-unnecessarily-cool-500hz-gaming-monitor/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T15:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone knows that a higher refresh rate makes you a better gamer. That’s why ASUS and NVIDIA teamed up to build the ROG Swift 500Hz gaming monitor, something that will “benefit every game and every gamer.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clop ransomware gang is back, hits 21 victims in a single month]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/clop-ransomware-gang-is-back-hits-21-victims-in-a-single-month/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/clop-ransomware-gang-is-back-hits-21-victims-in-a-single-month/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After effectively shutting down their entire operation for several months, between November and February, the Clop ransomware is now back according to NCC Group researchers. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Edit a PDF in Google Docs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=805821</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/805821/edit-pdf-in-google-docs/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T15:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Google Docs’ editing tools, you can edit your PDF to add and remove text, images, charts, and more. It then gives you the resulting file back as a PDF. We’ll show you how to use this service for PDF editing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Store is getting a much needed boost (and ads)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178832</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/05/28/microsoft-store-is-getting-a-much-needed-boost-and-ads/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T14:54:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During Build 2022, Microsoft highlighted some of the improvements that it plans to roll out to the virtual Microsoft Store. The Store, which the company introduced in Windows 8 and refined in […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Microsoft Store is getting a much needed boost (and ads) appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch random freeze but audio keeps playing.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzoiuf/arch_random_freeze_but_audio_keeps_playing/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzoiuf/arch_random_freeze_but_audio_keeps_playing/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T14:31:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Problem:
 Arch randomly freezes after a while (1 hour or so of use). Temps are stable (CPU around 35c, GPU around 60c). When it freezes, my music keeps playing. next song also queues up and continues. However, my mouse stops moving. I cannot use numlock/cap (the light doesn't go on or off), and the mouse randomly starts moving after a while but then when i am moving it stops after few seconds. I am unable to click anything or do anything. It is as if the whole PC is frozen and the only thing thats working is audio. Only solution if i hard reset my PC, which obviously i do not like to do.
 ​
 Attempt:
 While scouting the net, i found something about Nvidia and PowerMizer. Mine was set to Auto/Adaptive. However, i saw something about putting it in Maximum Performance mode. I believe this to be the fix.
 ​
 Issue:
 My issue is, going to nvidia-settings and putting it on Maximum Performance does not stick. As soon as i reboot, its back to auto. Is there a way to make the setting stick even after a reboot?
 ​
 PC Info:
 CPU: I7 8700K
 RAM: 16GB
 GPU: RTX 2070 Super
 OS + Kernal: Arch Linux - 5.17.9-arch1-1
 DE/WM: KDE Plasma 5
 ​
 Thank you to all in advance for the help <3
 ​
 ​
 EDIT: Possible solution? Not quite sure yet. Will report back later. PC has been on for 1 hour now without a freeze.
 What i did: On KDE autostart, i added the following line: nvidia-settings -a "[gpu:0]/GpuPowerMizerMode=1"
 After rebooting, going to nvidia-settings seems to have made it stick. Thank you all for the help! I will report back here in a few hours in case nothing happens (or if something happens)
    submitted by    /u/fatalrein  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using multiple different repositories (testing and/or ALHP)?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzo3tn/using_multiple_different_repositories_testing/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzo3tn/using_multiple_different_repositories_testing/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T14:09:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I used to use the testing repositories and now switched to using the ALHP repos. And I was wondering if it's generally advised to use only one of the two, or whether it's fine, to have both in my pacman.conf.
 The idea behind it is that if one package is maybe not included in one repo pacman would then retrieve the package from the next best repo, considering all repos are in a correct order in the config file. Or does this introduce incompatibilities?
 Or doesn't it even matter, because all packages in the ALHP repos are also in the testing repos, so packages are always retrieved from the ALHP repos and never from the testing repos?
 For example I only had AHLP and default repos (core, extra, community, multilib) active and my system up-to-date and when I also activated the testing repos (kde-unstable, testing, community-testing, multilib-testing) I get updates for a few packages.
    submitted by    /u/Arjab  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How can I use iGPU on Arch (VM/Passthru)?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzo2nk/how_can_i_use_igpu_on_arch_vmpassthru/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzo2nk/how_can_i_use_igpu_on_arch_vmpassthru/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T14:07:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arch Host Win10 Guest
 So I've managed to get PCI passthrough working for my dGPU by creating libvirt hooks that toggle me out of X before and after launching/destroying VM. This is, however, less than ideal as I wanted to use my iGPU to keep the Arch session running. No matter what I tried, it seems I am unable to use my UHD 630 (running i915) to be seen as the primary GPU for the host. I can pass through the iGPU no problem, but I cannot seem to get Arch to latch to it and reserve the dGPU for passthrough.
 dGPU is AMD. MB is MSI Gaming Pro Z390. Starting to think it's impossible simply because my firmware forces me to boot using AMD card (cannot boot with just "IGD" if card is installed).
    submitted by    /u/profile_this  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[how to remove grub in legacy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uznznl/how_to_remove_grub_in_legacy/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uznznl/how_to_remove_grub_in_legacy/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T14:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have arch and windows7 dual boot with grub on bare metal. I want to unistall grub from my device but grub doesn't have a specific partition in bios devices so when I uninstall a linux distro grub shows me errors. I want to experiment more with arch and install grub on my usb stick but I can't uninstall grub
    submitted by    /u/MoodFew956  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Windows Subsystem for Linux malware steals browser auth cookies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-windows-subsystem-for-linux-malware-steals-browser-auth-cookies/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-windows-subsystem-for-linux-malware-steals-browser-auth-cookies/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T14:01:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers are showing an increased interest in the Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSL) as an attack surface as they build new malware, the more advanced samples being suitable for espionage and downloading additional malicious modules. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Ilascu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best 4K TVs of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=754502</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/754502/best-4k-tv/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[4K TVs are more affordable now than ever before, but which model should you buy? Whether you want a set for gaming, movie watching, or just a good all-rounder, we have some recommendations to eliminate the guesswork.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Butts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are iPads Waterproof?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=806352</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/806352/are-ipads-waterproof/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T13:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sure, you’ve heard a lot about iPhones being water resistant, but what about iPads? Can you dunk them in the drink without any damage? Let’s take a look—and see what you can do about it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Do the Different Vinyl Condition Grades Mean?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/116413/what-do-the-different-vinyl-condition-grades-mean/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/116413/what-do-the-different-vinyl-condition-grades-mean/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T13:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ve probably heard the term “mint condition” when talking about comic books or baseball cards, but it can also apply to vinyl records. There are other condition grades you might stumble upon while buying used vinyl, and it’s worth learning what each grade means.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzanne Humphries</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gcc-12 include errors in cmake, CUDA project]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzm62x/gcc12_include_errors_in_cmake_cuda_project/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzm62x/gcc12_include_errors_in_cmake_cuda_project/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T12:19:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi,
 Latest Cuda (11.6) is not well compatible with gcc-12, which is now default in Arch Linux. I got errors when building cmake project, while trying to include GRPC and other libraries, which works in .cpp gcc, but not in .cu file.
 I figured out, that this is related to gcc-12. I installed gcc-11 from official repo, but compiling with cmake still points to */usr/include/c++/12.1.0/* but not to */usr/lib/gcc/x86_64-pc-linux-gnu/11.3.0/include/*I am using vscode, I changed my kit to gcc-11, but that doesn't effect on building .cu files with cmake, while it effects only building .cpp files.
 Where could problem be? What workaround could be made?
 Thanks in advance
 [build] /usr/include/c++/12.1.0/bits/stl_map.h:593:29: error: parameter packs not expanded with ‘...’: 
 it is related to this https://github.com/open-mmlab/mmcv/issues/1967
    submitted by    /u/KestM  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can You Still Stream With a VPN in 2022?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=802194</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/802194/can-you-still-stream-netflix-or-other-services-with-a-vpn/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T12:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Virtual private networks let you access different regions’ streaming libraries. Unsurprisingly, Netflix, Hulu, and other streaming services aren’t too enthusiastic about VPN users unlocking all this extra content and have put up countermeasures. How effective are they, though?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fergus O'Sullivan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome 103 Beta Adds Local Font Access, Deflate-Raw Compression Format]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Chrome-103-Beta</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Chrome-103-Beta"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following this week's release of Chrome 102, Google has promoted Chrome 103 to beta for their cross-platform web browser...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Numerous "MM" Improvements Land In Linux 5.19]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-MM</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-MM"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Andrew Morton with his recent shift to a Git-based workflow rather than maintaining long patch series has sent in all of the memory management "mm" changes for the Linux 5.19 merge window...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come trovare i canali HD sul Digitale terrestre]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2018/01/digitale-terrestre-come-trovare-i.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2018/01/digitale-terrestre-come-trovare-i.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T11:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Il digitale terrestre ha rivoluzionato il modo di vedere i canali TV, con una qualità del segnale decisamente migliore rispetto al segnale analogico, un numero davvero infinito di canali e minore interferenza.

 Dal passaggio definitivo al digitale terrestre sono passati anni, ma molti utenti non riescono ancora a capire come funzionano correttamente i canali, dove trovare i canali che si vedono...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stop Putting Your Phone in Rice]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=804442</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/804442/stop-putting-your-phone-in-rice/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T11:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For nearly as long as smartphones have existed, people have been putting them in rice after dropping them in water. This often-repeated “trick” to save a water-logged phone has gone too far. Allow us to explain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[20 Design Tools for Startups on Budget]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/?p=26472</id>
        <link href="https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/design-tools-for-startup/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T10:01:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the beginning, there was you, and your laptop. As entrepreneurs, we've all been there: nurturing a larger-than-life vision of what our app/product]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victor Balasa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel oneVPL 2022.1 Brings Support For Arc A Series, Rocky Linux, Better Multi-GPU]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-oneVPL-2022.1</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-oneVPL-2022.1"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While for years Intel has traditionally devoted all their video acceleration attention on Linux to VA-API (and the Media SDK albeit less popular with Linux enthusiasts), with the modern oneAPI world for Intel hardware their oneVPL library is quickly becoming a viable contender and a primary focus for their open-source video accelerator efforts. On Friday the oneVPL 2022.1 release was made available...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FAT32 File Creation/Birth Time Reporting Finally Comes To Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=FAT-File-Creation-Birth-5.19</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=FAT-File-Creation-Birth-5.19"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T09:21:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Finally for FAT file-systems with the in-development Linux 5.19 kernel is support via the statx() system call for reporting a file's birth/creation time...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KDE Developers Land More Bug Fixes Ahead Of Plasma 5.25]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=KDE-Plasma-5.25-More-Fixes</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=KDE-Plasma-5.25-More-Fixes"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T09:03:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ahead of next month's big Plasma 5.25 release, KDE developers are wrapping up May with more bug fixes for polishing up this open-source desktop...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eclipse IDE for Java]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzja6f/eclipse_ide_for_java/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzja6f/eclipse_ide_for_java/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T08:49:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey, I am trying to install the Eclipse package and get "error: target not found: eclipse-java".
 The community mirrorlist is enabled in the config file and I have also made a system update, still nothing.
 I have also tried to install the tar.gz file from the official website but after extracting I can't see a makefile to compile the application.
 Preferably I'd install it from the AUR, thanks for any answers!
    submitted by    /u/KeksMember  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CXL Support Continues To Be Refined In Linux 5.19 Ahead Of Next-Gen Servers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-CXL</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-CXL"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T08:43:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intel has been working heavily on getting the Compute Express Link (CXL) subsystem in place so that when next-generation servers appear with this new high-speed interconnect industry standard, open-source operating systems will be ready...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WifiDiagnosticsView: diagnose wireless connectivity issues on Windows PCs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178824</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/05/28/wifidiagnosticsview-diagnose-wireless-connectivity-issues-on-windows-pcs/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T07:09:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WifiDiagnosticsView is a portable program for Microsoft Windows devices that provides users with wireless connectivity information. Created by Nirsoft, it has the same traits as other Nirsoft applications, including that it is […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post WifiDiagnosticsView: diagnose wireless connectivity issues on Windows PCs appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fix Google Play Store Not Working on Chromebook]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=474144</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15334827/fix-google-play-store-not-working-chromebook"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T05:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the help of the Google Play Store you can download Android apps on your Chromebook. You don’t need to use any workaround to use Google Play Store as it is officially available from Google. However, many users often experience issues with the Play Store on Chromebook. For instance, users can’t download apps from the Google Play Store app or the Play Store randomly stops functioning. Some even get error codes 7, 8, or downloading pending, etc., while using the Store. If you are experiencing a similar issue with the Play Store, try the following solutions to fix this problem on your Chromebook.
   

Content

1. Check Compatibility With Your Chromebook
2. Restart Your Chromebook
3. Check Internet Connection
4. Enable Play Store on Your Chromebook
5. Sign Out of Guest Accounts
6. Create a New User Profile
7. Clear Cache for Google Play Store
8. Run Chromebook Diagnostics
9. Check Date and Time
10. Uninstall Third-Party Apps or Extensions
11. Update Chrome OS
12. Update Play Store on Chromebook
13. Remove Google Play Store
14. Factory Reset Chromebook
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mehvish Mushtaq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Move Arch hard drive from one pc to another]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzgiiw/move_arch_hard_drive_from_one_pc_to_another/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzgiiw/move_arch_hard_drive_from_one_pc_to_another/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T05:22:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I just installed Arch on an old hp elitedesk with a brand new ssd in it. Only to realize it only has a display port and no hdmi port. 
 I think I may have an hdmi to dp cable in the shed. I'm going to look tomorrow. But if I don't, I have a different micro pc I could use. I have no gui installed on this. I'm just going to use tty with it for now. Could I pull the drive out of the hp and put it in the other micro pc and not have to worry about reinstalling Arch or should I just move that drive and reinstall Arch on that unit?
 EDIT: I did find the hdmi to dp cable so that's one less hoop I need to jump through today.
 Thanks for all the pointers guys. I appreciate it.
    submitted by    /u/Phydoux  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating PKGBUILD for Rust Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzgb36/creating_pkgbuild_for_rust_applications/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzgb36/creating_pkgbuild_for_rust_applications/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T05:08:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi!
 I am new to arch linux packages, and I want to add my package built with Rust (which contains a CLI command and a service) to AUR. I saw different posts and youtube videos but it seems confusing. 
 So, can you all give a sample of the PKGBUILD for my usage or list down important links that can lead my the way.
    submitted by    /u/0xsapphir3  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[System76 fan going berserk + nonresponsive when suspended]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzdpgx/system76_fan_going_berserk_nonresponsive_when/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzdpgx/system76_fan_going_berserk_nonresponsive_when/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T02:22:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm really at a loss for this issue.
 I'm running Arch on a System76 Lemur Pro. This issue started about a month ago.
 Sometimes, when I close the laptop, shortly after closing it, the fan goes on full blast like a helicopter trying to take off. I open the computer, and it's nonresponsive to input - touchpad or keyboard - and the screen is black. The only way to make it stop is to force power down. If I just ignore it, it will continue until it runs out of battery. It seems to be happening with increasing frequency, or maybe I'm just closing my computer more often nowadays.
 It doesn't matter which apps I do or don't have open.
 Here is the end of the output of journalctl -xb -1 | tail after this happened yesterday. I closed the computer at 14:36:05.
 $ journalctl -xb -1 | tail Hint: You are currently not seeing messages from other users and the system. Users in groups 'adm', 'systemd-journal', 'wheel' can see all messages. Pass -q to turn off this notice. May 27 14:09:18 lemur2 /usr/lib/gdm-x-session[46304]: [{"success":true}] May 27 14:09:24 lemur2 /usr/lib/gdm-x-session[46306]: [{"success":true}] May 27 14:09:26 lemur2 /usr/lib/gdm-x-session[46307]: [{"success":true}] May 27 14:36:05 lemur2 wireplumber[2649]: 0x56127c06d3f8: error 24 May 27 14:36:05 lemur2 obexd[2877]: disconnected: Transport got disconnected May 27 14:36:05 lemur2 /usr/lib/gdm-x-session[2670]: (II) event26 - Bose QuietComfort 35 (AVRCP): device removed May 27 14:36:05 lemur2 /usr/lib/gdm-x-session[2670]: (II) config/udev: removing device Bose QuietComfort 35 (AVRCP) May 27 14:36:05 lemur2 /usr/lib/gdm-x-session[2670]: (**) Option "fd" "57" May 27 14:36:05 lemur2 /usr/lib/gdm-x-session[2670]: (II) UnloadModule: "libinput" May 27 14:36:05 lemur2 /usr/lib/gdm-x-session[2670]: (II) systemd-logind: releasing fd for 13:90 
 I would appreciate any advice.
    submitted by    /u/epoxyfoxy  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Turn Your Raspberry Pi into a Video Conferencing Station]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=369436</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15334663/turn-raspberry-pi-video-conferencing-station"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Post-lockdown, with working and schooling from home as a matter of routine, more people are turning toward video conferencing as a way to keep in touch and get things done. Tools like Google Meet, Skype and Zoom mean we can keep in touch with people outside the confines of our home, across cities, time zones, and even countries, making the world smaller and allowing for remote collaboration. If you’re looking for another great Raspberry Pi project, I urge you to try this one. This tutorial shows you how to turn your Raspberry PI into a video conferencing station.
   

Content

Gathering Supplies
Setting Up Your Pi
Zoom
Google Meet
Skype
Jitsi
Hardware Essentials
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:9 of the Best Video Call Apps for Mobile Users
    
Gathering Supplies
    
Here’s what you will need:
   ... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phil South</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Yogurt that Wasn't, book I]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzbm6l/the_yogurt_that_wasnt_book_i/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzbm6l/the_yogurt_that_wasnt_book_i/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T00:19:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve been trying to learn more about using and manipulating Linux since getting a Steam Deck. So before trying this I had practically no knowledge of Linux usage except what sudo meant. My first challenge to myself was to get GBStudio v.3.0.3 to run on the deck so I can create on the go. 
 From the itch.io link, I can get an Ubuntu/Debian package, or a Fedora/Red Hat package. I went with the .deb package because I saw more info online for it.
 I decided the easiest way to do all this was with AUR (Arch User Repository). And then using YAY (Yet Another Yogurt). Which is a Pacman wrapper and AUR helper.
 This would supposedly allow me to wrap the .deb package into something more palatable for the Steam Deck to install.
 Starting by allowing the Decks read only to be written. I’m iffy on that…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[FAILED] Failed to start Load Kernel Modules on boot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzbf26/failed_failed_to_start_load_kernel_modules_on_boot/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzbf26/failed_failed_to_start_load_kernel_modules_on_boot/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T00:09:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Then it boots into my system but with the wrong resolution, no network drivers (is that what they're called?), and a lot of stuff not working
 Initially, it also gave me a lot of mounting errors on boot even though my fstab seemed perfectly fine. Still, I deleted it and generated a new one with genfstab, and then it started. This is where I'm at. (Initially, I think it failed to mount /boot and also said something about dependencies failing for the local file system)
 I'm not exactly sure what I did that might've caused all of this. My uptime was ~5 days, so there are a lot of things that I could've done
 From a chroot, I've tried reinstalling the kernel and downgrading it, neither of which helped
    submitted by    /u/Merulox  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EasyTether]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzauwt/easytether/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzauwt/easytether/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T23:38:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, i can't configure Easy tether on Arch Linux How can i configure it? configure the network interface tap-easytether somehow (on each successful connection attempt)
    submitted by    /u/CandidateJunior5743  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mesa's Lavapipe Now Officially Vulkan 1.2 Conformant]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Lavapipe-Vulkan-1.2-Conformant</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Lavapipe-Vulkan-1.2-Conformant"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T23:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lavapipe as Mesa's software/CPU-based Vulkan implementation akin to LLVMpipe for OpenGL is now officially Vulkan 1.2 conformant...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[trouble installing opera browser]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uza2hu/trouble_installing_opera_browser/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uza2hu/trouble_installing_opera_browser/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T22:57:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to solve this:
  sudo pacman -S opera resolving dependencies... looking for conflicting packages... Packages (1) opera-87.0.4390.25-1 Total Download Size: 83.81 MiB Total Installed Size: 239.99 MiB :: Proceed with installation? [Y/n] :: Retrieving packages... opera-87.0.4390.25-1-x86_64.pkg.tar.zst failed to download error: failed retrieving file 'opera-87.0.4390.25-1-x86_64.pkg.tar.zst' from mirror.telepoint.bg : The requested URL returned error: 404 error: failed retrieving file 'opera-87.0.4390.25-1-x86_64.pkg.tar.zst' from mirror.telepoint.bg : The requested URL returned error: 404 error: failed retrieving file 'opera-87.0.4390.25-1-x86_64.pkg.tar.zst' from archlinux.thaller.ws : The requested URL returned error: 404 error: failed retrieving file 'opera-87.0.4390.25-1-x86_64.pkg.tar.zst' from mirror.telepoint.bg : Protocol "rsync" not supported or disabled in libcurl warning: too many errors from mirror.telepoint.bg, skipping for the remainder of this transaction error: failed retrieving file 'opera-87.0.4390.25-1-x86_64.pkg.tar.zst' from archlinux.thaller.ws : Protocol "rsync" not supported or disabled in libcurl warning: failed to retrieve some files error: failed to commit transaction (download library error) Errors occurred, no packages were upgraded. 
    submitted by    /u/buzzwallard  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[zram worth using with 32gb ram?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uz9grt/zram_worth_using_with_32gb_ram/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uz9grt/zram_worth_using_with_32gb_ram/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T22:26:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello community. I have 32gb of ram and rarely use all of it. I'm using btrfs and have no swap set up since I never thought I needed it. My question is this: in my environment where I rarely use all my ram, should I still set up zram/zswap/swap? And if so, which one should I be using? Thanks everyone!
    submitted by    /u/Fxzzi  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What do you use for bluetooth?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uz9dfc/what_do_you_use_for_bluetooth/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uz9dfc/what_do_you_use_for_bluetooth/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T22:21:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[do you use blueman, bluedevil, bluetoothctl, other
 why do you use them and what advantages do they have over other ones?
 ​
 (also idk if this is the right flair so if its wrong i can change it)
    submitted by    /u/Kiing_Watermelon  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[clamAV scan seems to stop]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uz97d6/clamav_scan_seems_to_stop/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uz97d6/clamav_scan_seems_to_stop/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T22:13:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone.
 I've setup the clamAV into a server according to this tutorial . And I'm scanning from the "peripheral" devices using the clamdscan command. 
 It seems though that something is not going right.
 Although it scans and finds a test file as malicious after a while it stops giving me back these outputs:
 In the client side:
 clamdscan /home /home/orbitz/test-doc-see-as-virus-by-clamav.txt: Win.Test.EICAR_HDB-1 FOUND ERROR: Can't send to clamd: Broken pipe LibClamAV Error: File tree walk aborted. LibClamAV Error: File tree walk aborted. LibClamAV Error: File tree walk aborted. LibClamAV Error: File tree walk aborted. LibClamAV Error: File tree walk aborted. LibClamAV Error: File tree walk aborted. LibClamAV Error: File tree walk aborted. LibClamAV Error: File tree walk aborted.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Questa settimana su TLI (28 maggio 2022)]]></title>
        <id>3591|20220528000001</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/newsletter-turbolab.it-1349/questa-settimana-tli-28-maggio-2022-3591"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T22:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Non hai tempo di leggerci tutti i giorni? nessun problema! ecco a te il riepilogo di quanto proposto da TurboLab.it nel corso della settimana in conclusione.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 Ways to Stop Windows Updates]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=487484</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15334464/stop-windows-updates"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows updates bring crucial stability and security improvements to your OS. But they can also be a nuisance. Not only do they disrupt your work by requiring a restart, they can also negatively affect user experience. Case in point, Microsoft has released numerous updates with bugs in recent years.
    
Luckily, you can stop or pause Windows updates with a few tweaks to your system, as will be described below.
   

Content

1. Pause Windows Updates in Settings
2. Use the Registry Editor
3. Delay Windows Update Restart Times
4. Use Windows Services
5. Try the Windows Update Blocker Utility
6. Group Policy
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Use SetupDiag to Fix Windows Update Problems
    
1. Pause Windows Updates in Settings
    
If you want to pause Windows updates for some time (up to a few weeks),... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Kanyoro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[find what bothers pc fan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uz874h/find_what_bothers_pc_fan/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uz874h/find_what_bothers_pc_fan/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T21:23:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, is there any program to find what makes my fan turns a lot when it happens ?
    submitted by    /u/Spare_Prize1148  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Connect AirPods to a Windows 11 PC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=763250</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/763250/how-to-connect-airpods-to-a-windows-11-pc/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Although Apple’s AirPods are designed to work with other Apple products, you can also connect them to your Windows 11 PC. All you need to do is turn on Bluetooth on your PC and enable Pairing Mode on your AirPods.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marshall Gunnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chromebooks Can Now Warn You About Bad USB Type-C Cables]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=808292</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/808292/chromebooks-can-now-warn-you-about-bad-usb-type-c-cables/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T20:40:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[USB Type-C is the one connector to rule them all, but that can become a problem when you’re not sure if a certain cable can handle all USB features. Thankfully, Chromebooks now have a partial solution for that issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FBI warns of hackers selling credentials for U.S. college networks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fbi-warns-of-hackers-selling-credentials-for-us-college-networks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fbi-warns-of-hackers-selling-credentials-for-us-college-networks/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T20:26:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybercriminals are offering to sell for thousands of U.S. dollars network access credentials for higher education institutions based in the United States. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Ilascu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Trim and Cut Videos on Your Android Device]]></title>
        <id>http://www.howtogeek.com/?p=201843</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/201843/how-to-trim-and-cut-videos-on-your-android-device/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A smartphone in your pocket all the time makes it easy to record impressive videos. Historically, editing those videos on your Android phone hasn’t been as easy, but that’s not the case anymore. We’ll show you how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save $99 on a 2021 Apple iPad Pro 11″]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=493597</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15334376/2021-apple-ipad-pro-11"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year Apple made its intentions with the iPad very clear when it added the M1 chip to the iPad Pro lineup. These tablets now have the power of a laptop. You can get a 2021 Apple iPad Pro 11″ with the M1 chip for $99 off.
    
The device features an 11″ Liquid Retina display. It includes 600 nits peak brightness, ProMotion, True Tone, and P3 wide color. It’s the perfect option for content with very bright high contrast media, such as HDR photos and videos.
    
The M1 chip allows you to both view and create amazing graphics. You’ll experience a battery that will last all day. Multitask through work, your home life, and even games that make you feel like they’re being played on a console. Connect pro accessories to the tablet, such as monitors and external drives, through the Thunderbolt port.
    

    
The new ultra-wide front-facing camera features Center Stage so that you’ll always be the center of attention in video conferencing or just FaceTiming with the... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can You Unsend in iMessage?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=807265</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/807265/can-you-unsend-in-imessage/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T19:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[iMessage on the iPhone feels like an instant messaging app, but it doesn’t quite have all the same features. What if you accidentally send a message to someone? Can you undo it? The answer is a little complicated.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I need help (i‘m an idiot)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uz5370/i_need_help_im_an_idiot/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uz5370/i_need_help_im_an_idiot/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T18:53:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I installed arch without ANY packages preinstalled. After installing some applications I rebooted my system and I forgot to install something like network-manager or other networking tools. Now I don’t have network access anymore. (My disk is encrypted and I don’t know how to chroot into it to fix this) 
 Long story short: I don’t have any Networking packages installed and can’t connect anymore 
 How do I fix this?
    submitted by    /u/crimewaffle  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chromebooks Get a New “Cursive” App for Handwritten Notes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=808256</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/808256/chromebooks-get-a-new-cursive-app-for-handwritten-notes/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T18:51:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has been testing its new ‘Cursive’ notetaking application on select Chromebooks, and now it’s officially available on any Chromebook that supports stylus input.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub: Attackers stole login details of 100K npm user accounts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/github-attackers-stole-login-details-of-100k-npm-user-accounts/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/github-attackers-stole-login-details-of-100k-npm-user-accounts/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T18:40:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub revealed today that an attacker stole the login details of roughly 100,000 npm accounts during a mid-April security breach with the help of stolen OAuth app tokens issued to Heroku and Travis-CI. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Flatpak removed as a dependency of gnome-control-centre]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uz4s95/flatpak_removed_as_a_dependency_of/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uz4s95/flatpak_removed_as_a_dependency_of/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T18:39:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Be sure to run pacman -Qtdq | pacman -Rns -
    submitted by    /u/luca1416  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LG's New OLED Gaming Monitor Looks Stonking Ridiculous]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119383/lgs-new-oled-gaming-monitor-looks-stonking-ridiculous/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119383/lgs-new-oled-gaming-monitor-looks-stonking-ridiculous/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T18:32:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you think of OLED PC monitors, you might not think of LG, even though the company makes some of the most outstanding OLED TVs. However, LG just unveiled its latest gaming monitors, including an enormous 4K OLED monitor with an impressive slew of features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzanne Humphries</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KDE and GNOME not playing well together -- both run at once, affecting GNOME functionality.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uz4ety/kde_and_gnome_not_playing_well_together_both_run/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uz4ety/kde_and_gnome_not_playing_well_together_both_run/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T18:21:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi Everyone, Sorry if this isn't exactly the right spot, but I just need some pointers more than a concrete solution. I've got both KDE 5.24 and GNOME 42 installed on my Arch system, largely because of GNOME's more mature Wayland implementation. All arch packages are up to date, systemd is version 251, and I'm using the latest ZEN kernel, 5.17.9.
 These DE's seem to play poorly together, with GNOME the more affected party. Perhaps notably, my login/startup is SDDM, not GDM, since I had installed KDE first.
 In both
 opening a terminal gives the message:
 discover_other_daemon: 1% 
 which I think is the clue that things are duplicated.
 On GNOME: The KDE wallet system always opens at startup, and the akonadi server processes all run in the background. Further, the KDE demon runs in the background; if I log out or shutdown, it warns me that I will also log out... myself, but that's presumably my username "logged in" on a KDE session.
 Theming on GNOME seems to be seriously impacted, in that only my legacy app theme -- the one I can set in KDE, fwiw -- respected, whereas all other GTK apps, including all those that are part of GNOME itself, completely ignoring my theming, darkmode preferences, etc. Changing config files doesn't seem to do anything, nor does completely deleting them, even.
 Any Ideas about what to try? I think if I can find a way to make KDE services and daemons only launch if a KDE desktop session is started by me would probably solve all the troubles, though I don't know what troubles that might cause for KDE.
    submitted by    /u/Watership_of_a_Down  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Possible to grab package descriptions with pacman?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uz4dog/possible_to_grab_package_descriptions_with_pacman/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uz4dog/possible_to_grab_package_descriptions_with_pacman/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T18:19:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm trying to learn more about Arch Linux and packages. Is there a way to grab the description from the pacman repos for all of my installed packages? I already did verbose for pacman but that just makes it into a list and shows the version before and after update.
 Example, today there was an update for knewstuff. I had no idea what the hell that was. Looking on the pacman repo it says "Support for downloading application assets from the network".
 https://archlinux.org/packages/?sort=&q=knewstuff&maintainer=&flagged=
 Basically I want to make a spreadsheet with all of my installed packages and the pacman description beside each package so I can continue learning.
 Thanks fellow Archers.
    submitted by    /u/linux_masterrace  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Change the Time on Windows 10]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=804604</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/804604/how-to-change-the-time-on-windows-10/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft’s Windows 10 operating system allows you to adjust your clock manually as well as automatically using a Settings option. We’ll show you how to do just that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to stop pip and VS Code asking for keyring?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uz3y0u/how_to_stop_pip_and_vs_code_asking_for_keyring/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uz3y0u/how_to_stop_pip_and_vs_code_asking_for_keyring/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T17:59:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since some time, when I run pip list and open VS Code, they both ask for the keyring to be opened (in my case, KeePass XC). pip sometimes blocks and I have to kill KeePass, relaunch it and relaunch pip. VS Code, when I close the KeePass window asking for the password to open the database, re-opens it a few times, until it is satisfied and proceeds as nothing happened. How can I stop this?
    submitted by    /u/CousinOfThor  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung Shows off Its Next-Gen 200MP Phone Camera Sensor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119378/samsung-shows-off-its-next-gen-200mp-phone-camera-sensor/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119378/samsung-shows-off-its-next-gen-200mp-phone-camera-sensor/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T17:48:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung first started teasing its insane new 200-megapixel camera system back in 2021, and now it looks like the sensor is almost ready for primetime. This week, the company gave us our first glance at what will likely power the camera in its upcoming Galaxy S23 Ultra.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mouse lagging only on one third of the screen]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uz3n01/mouse_lagging_only_on_one_third_of_the_screen/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uz3n01/mouse_lagging_only_on_one_third_of_the_screen/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T17:44:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi,
 I'm having a weird issue with my new notebook(i7-11370H, RTX 3050), my mouse is lagging only on the top third of the screen. I found a post with the exactly same issue, but no solution(link).
 I'm currently using the modesetting driver, no xf86-video packages are installed and my nvidia card is blacklisted in modprobe.
 P.S. The screen have a resolution of 2880x1800 90Hz, 14".
 Someone had this issue before?
    submitted by    /u/matfurla79  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ford Starts Shipping the F-150 Lightning Electric Truck]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=808234</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/808234/ford-starts-shipping-the-f-150-lightning-electric-truck/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T17:38:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ford revealed its F-150 Lightning electric truck last year, serving as another sign that legacy auto companies are shifting to electric vehicles. Now the truck has finally started shipping to buyers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improvements For Wacom Driver, AMD SFH, ThinkPoint Keyboard II Land In Linux 5.19]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-HID</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-HID"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T17:33:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The HID subsystem changes were merged this week into the Linux 5.19 kernel...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Impostazioni Google Android, quali sono le più importanti]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Impostazioni-Google-Android-quali-sono-le-piu-importanti_14508</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Impostazioni-Google-Android-quali-sono-le-piu-importanti_14508"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T17:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quando si acquista un dispositivo Android è bene essere consapevoli della presenza di alcune impostazioni Google che non soltanto ne regolano il funzionamento ma consentono anche di specificare come devono essere utilizzati i dati dell'utente.Le impostazioni Google su Android sono accessibili in maniera differente a seconda della versione del sistema operativo installato e delle eventuali personalizzazioni applicate dai singoli produttori dei dispositivi.
Impostazioni Google: come accedervi sui dispositivi Android
 In tutte le versioni di Android antecedenti alla 6.0 (Marshmallow), le impostazioni Google si presentavano sotto forma di un'icona raffigurante un ingranaggio mescolata tra le tante presenti nella lista delle app installate.Nelle successive versioni del sistema operativo e nelle…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft finds severe bugs in Android apps from large mobile providers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-finds-severe-bugs-in-android-apps-from-large-mobile-providers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-finds-severe-bugs-in-android-apps-from-large-mobile-providers/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T17:06:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft security researchers have found high severity vulnerabilities in a framework used by Android apps from multiple large international mobile service providers. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chromebooks Will Now Call Out Your Bad USB-C Cable]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119369/chromebooks-will-now-call-out-your-bad-usb-c-cable/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119369/chromebooks-will-now-call-out-your-bad-usb-c-cable/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T17:05:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week Google released its latest Chrome OS 102 update and inside is a neat new feature that will alert users if they’re using bad or incompatible USB-C cables. And while that sounds like a small change, it’s more useful than you probably think.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When to Replace Your Old USB Flash Drive]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=797300</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/797300/when-to-replace-your-old-usb-flash-drive/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T17:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Still using an outdated USB flash drive to store your files? Why not upgrade to a newer, bigger, and faster stick that will last you for years to come? Here’s why you might want to replace your old USB stick.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Nguyen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Stream Live News for Free]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119253/how-to-stream-live-news-for-free/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119253/how-to-stream-live-news-for-free/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T16:34:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Live news is often the only thing keeping families from abandoning cable TV. But you don’t need to pay for live news. Most major news networks broadcast for free through streaming services, apps, and websites. And in some cases, you can even stream local news to your devices!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[BTRFS] Where to pacstrap; /mnt or /mnt/root?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uz24ln/btrfs_where_to_pacstrap_mnt_or_mntroot/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uz24ln/btrfs_where_to_pacstrap_mnt_or_mntroot/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T16:33:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If I'm installing Arch on a BTRFS partition and need to reinstall down the road, what pacstrap command would I use to allow me to reinstall while leaving the home subvolume intact? pacstrap /mnt OR pacstrap /mnt/root?
    submitted by    /u/kantoking0206  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Is Testing a Snore and Cough Detection Feature for Android]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119356/google-is-testing-a-snore-and-cough-detection-feature-for-android/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119356/google-is-testing-a-snore-and-cough-detection-feature-for-android/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T16:30:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google unveiled an update last December that allowed Pixel phones to track your heart rate and respiration using the device’s camera, accelerometer, and microphone. The company seems to be furthering that effort with a cough and snore detection feature on Android.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzanne Humphries</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Walmart Announces Same-Day Drone Delivery in Six States]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119361/walmart-announces-same-day-drone-delivery-in-six-states/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119361/walmart-announces-same-day-drone-delivery-in-six-states/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T16:28:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the last year, Walmart has been working hard on a new drone delivery system, and it’s available in select cities. However, this week we learned that Walmart would officially expand its same-day drone delivery service to six states, serving nearly 4 million customers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11: adesivi sul desktop, come attivarli]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-11-adesivi-sul-desktop-come-attivarli_24576</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-11-adesivi-sul-desktop-come-attivarli_24576"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T16:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Proseguendo sulla filosofia che aveva portato alla nascita di Windows 10, il sistema operativo più aggiornato di Microsoft si arricchisce continuamente di nuove caratteristiche. Abbiamo visto quelle che debutteranno con il rilascio di Windows 11 22H2 in attesa che Microsoft prenda in esame cosa va cambiato in Windows 11 secondo gli utenti.Con la pubblicazione delle più recenti versioni di anteprima di Windows 11 è emerso che il feature update 22H2 introdurrà anche qualche funzione non propriamente indispensabile e delle quali molti utenti forse farebbero a meno.Il sistema operativo Microsoft sta in parte diventando più 'giocoso', forse con l'obiettivo di intercettare un'utenza ancora più ampia.
Cosa sono gli adesivi per il desktop di Windows 11
 Con Windows 11 22H2 debutteranno anche gli adesivi o sticker per il desktop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come sapere dove si trova una persona]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2018/03/come-sapere-dove-si-trova-una-persona.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2018/03/come-sapere-dove-si-trova-una-persona.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T16:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sapere dove si trova una persona è possibile oggi grazie agli smartphone e la funzione di condivisione della posizione messa a disposizione da numerose applicazioni anche molto popolari.

 Certamente è sempre necessario il consenso di chi viene cercato, altrimenti non è possibile seguire una persona solo per spiarla o per vedere cosa fa o che luoghi frequenta (non possiamo utilizzarle per...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung Pay vs. Google Pay: What’s the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=807107</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/807107/samsung-pay-vs.-google-pay-whats-the-difference/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T16:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the Android world, there are two mobile payment platforms to choose from—Samsung Pay and Google Pay. They have a lot in common, but there are some big differences as well. Let’s find out which one you should use.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft to force better security defaults for all Azure AD tenants]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-to-force-better-security-defaults-for-all-azure-ad-tenants/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-to-force-better-security-defaults-for-all-azure-ad-tenants/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T15:59:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has announced that it will force enable stricter secure default settings known as 'security defaults' on all existing Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) tenants starting in late June 2022. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GPU Fan Control With Wayland]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uz192t/gpu_fan_control_with_wayland/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uz192t/gpu_fan_control_with_wayland/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T15:54:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I switched to Wayland from X11 on gnome because I was having stuttery window movement with two different refresh rate screens. This is fixed on Wayland but it seems like there is no way for me to adjust GPU fan speed. I think my GPU has a broken fan controller or something because it makes a grinding noise over and over when starting up and at certain speeds (no clue how hard this would be to fix). so I usually set the fans to a higher speed.
 I saw a post here with someone using green with envy in a separate/parallel TTY. If I launch it the gui does actually launch into Wayland but it is still unable to control the fans. 
 Would appreciate any help.
    submitted by    /u/Red_Loa  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Processori Intel Core Raptor Lake di 13esima generazione e i Sapphire Rapids presentati forse già a ottobre]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Processori-Intel-Core-Raptor-Lake-di-13esima-generazione-e-i-Sapphire-Rapids-presentati-forse-gia-a-ottobre_24575</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Processori-Intel-Core-Raptor-Lake-di-13esima-generazione-e-i-Sapphire-Rapids-presentati-forse-gia-a-ottobre_24575"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T15:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[L'ultima parte dell'anno si preannuncia molto impegnativa per Intel che potrebbe presentare sia i processori Raptor Lake, i Core di tredicesima generazione, sia i Sapphire Rapids con l'obiettivo, in questo caso, di recuperare il terreno perso in campo professionale, HEDT (High-End Desktop) e server dopo l'avanzata degli AMD EPYC.I modelli più prestazionali degli Intel Core Raptor Lake potrebbero essere presentati a ottobre prossimo insieme con il chipset Z790.La società guidata da Pat Gelsinger starebbe lavorando per incentivare l'arrivo sul mercato di nuove schede madri della serie 700: quelle con chipset H770 e B760 verrebbero rese disponibili il prossimo anno.Un programma simile è stato adottato per la gamma Intel Core di dodicesima generazione: molto probabile che le CPU della serie K saranno tra le prime a essere presentate.Per quanto riguarda i Sapphire Rapids non è dato sapere quale nome commerciale assumeranno ma in linea di principio dovrebbero essere processori appartenenti alla gamma Xeon e potrebbero sfidare i Threadripper PRO della rivale AMD.Nella nostra guida al miglior processore Intel e AMD ci siamo ampiamente soffermati sulle differenze tra le CPU proposte dalle due aziende per i vari segmenti di mercato.AMD è già pronta con la sua offerta Ryzen 7000 presentata in occasione del Computex 2022: l'avvio delle vendite, insieme con le motherboard compatibili, potrebbe avvenire già a fine agosto.Non è esclusa una presentazione estiva, a luglio, per massimizzare gli sforzi e giocare d'anticipo rispetto a Intel e ai suoi Core di tredicesima generazione..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 of the Best Linux Distros for Windows Users]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=164130</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/4523644/best-linux-distro-for-windows-users"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T15:25:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re new to Linux or are switching to Linux from Windows, you’ll want an operating system that is GUI-focused like Windows. There are many different distributions of Linux, and some aim to replicate the look and feel of Windows. This helps during the transition from Windows, since you don’t have to fight with an unfamiliar interface. With Linux boasting improved hardware support, long term stability, and a more comprehensive range of software applications, there is no better time to try it!
    
In this roundup, we introduce you to the best Linux distributions for Windows users looking to switch to Linux.
   

Content

1. Kubuntu
2. Linux Mint
3. Robolinux
4. Solus
5. Zorin OS
6. ChaletOS
7. Elementary OS
8. Linux Lite
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:5 Useful Emacs Packages for Better Productivity
    
1. Kubuntu
    
We have to admit... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Crystal Crowder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some issues on window decorator of some apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uz0m3r/some_issues_on_window_decorator_of_some_apps/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uz0m3r/some_issues_on_window_decorator_of_some_apps/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T15:24:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey guys, I have some issues on Gnome 42. Some apps has this window bar issue. I was been using Arch with KDE, then I've remove the metapackage 'plasma-desktop' and install 'gnome' package. Some lib or something is missing here?
    submitted by    /u/bloodring_racer  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ford Begins Customer Delivery of the F-150 Lightning Electric Truck]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119358/ford-begins-customer-delivery-of-the-f-150-lightning-electric-truck/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119358/ford-begins-customer-delivery-of-the-f-150-lightning-electric-truck/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T15:23:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Almost exactly one year after announcing the all-new F-150 Lightning electric truck, Ford finally shipped its first vehicle to retail customers. Production started last month, and on May 26th, the first customer picked up his truck at Richardson Ford in the town of Standish, Michigan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mailspring icon badge doesn't work]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uz0d9g/mailspring_icon_badge_doesnt_work/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uz0d9g/mailspring_icon_badge_doesnt_work/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T15:12:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Libunity is installed already but badges for apps like mailspring, slack, discord doesn't show the counter badge. My system is arch + kde. Any help would be greatly appreciated.
    submitted by    /u/shawnk723  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Do Freelance Clients Actually Care About?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/?p=19250</id>
        <link href="https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/what-design-clients-want/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T15:01:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot of freelance designers find themselves stuck in the same place, year after year, serving the same types of clients despite their desire to move on]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Addison Duvall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Bionic Reading, and How Do You Use It?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=807981</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/807981/what-is-bionic-reading-and-how-do-you-use-it/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T15:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s no mystery that some fonts are easier to read than others. “Bionic Reading” is a tool that’s more than just font, and it could improve your reading speed and comprehension. Here’s what you need to know.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come tagliare, dividere e unire video su Android]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/05/come-tagliare-dividere-e-unire-video-su.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/05/come-tagliare-dividere-e-unire-video-su.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T15:00:00.006Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sui dispositivi Android può capitare di imbattersi in video troppo lunghi da condividere in chat o su un social network, spesso frutto di riprese che abbiamo effettuato con la fotocamera posteriore. Questi video possono essere tagliati e resi molto più comodi da condividere con alcune semplici app per l'editing video, senza dover utilizzare il PC per il classico video editing con programmi come...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Giochi Google nascosti: come e dove trovarli]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Giochi-Google-nascosti-come-e-dove-trovarli_24574</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Giochi-Google-nascosti-come-e-dove-trovarli_24574"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gli easter eggs (uova di Pasqua) sono funzionalità non documentate che i programmatori nascondono nei loro software. Possono essere segretamente aggiunte all'interno dei videogiochi, nei programmi per PC, nelle applicazioni per i dispositivi mobili ma anche nelle applicazioni Web. Si presentano come ingegnosi messaggi, piccoli giochi, presentazioni, citazioni goliardiche.Nei prodotti dell'azienda di Mountain View sono presenti tanti giochi Google nascosti: alcuni di essi vengono inseriti come parte integrante dei doodle ovvero i loghi animati che vengono pubblicati nella pagina del motore di ricerca durante occasioni speciali ed eventi.I doodle interattivi avviano un gioco o comunque richiedono all'utente qualche tipo di intervento: talvolta vengono mostrati brevi video, a volte si ha a che fare con dei veri e propri videogiochi, altre volte con delle avventure grafiche.Qualche esempio? Il gioco dei nani da giardino, il gioco di Halloween che può essere addirittura utilizzato per organizzare partite in multiplayer, il gioco del basket, il gioco del calcio Google, quello più recente dedicato ai Giochi Olimpici 2020-2021.Sono solo alcuni esempi nei quali è impossibile imbattersi scorrendo l'archivio dei doodle.
Dove trovare i giochi Google nascosti nel motore di ricerca
 Il motore di ricerca Google consente di accedere direttamente ad un ampio ventaglio di giochi pronti per l'uso.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do you want some Stickers on your Windows desktop?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178818</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/05/27/do-you-want-some-stickers-on-your-windows-desktop/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T14:32:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft is working on integrating support for placing stickers on the Windows 11 desktop. Users who run a recent Windows 11 version 22H2 Insider build can enable the functionality to test it […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Do you want some Stickers on your Windows desktop? appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Drive Now Has Keyboard Shortcuts for Copy and Paste (in 2022)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=808153</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/808153/google-drive-now-has-keyboard-shortcuts-for-copy-and-paste-in-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T14:30:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web apps often lack the keyboard shortcuts you might expect in desktop application, and to that point, Google Drive is just now adding support for common desktop shortcuts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Should I always use --batchinstall with yay?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uyz6zt/should_i_always_use_batchinstall_with_yay/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uyz6zt/should_i_always_use_batchinstall_with_yay/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T14:16:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I found out about the --batchinstall option to yay 
  
When building and installing AUR packages instead of installing each package after building, queue each package for install. Then once either all packages are built or a package in the build queue is needed as a dependency to build another package, install all the packages in the install queue.
  
It solves some issues I get when trying to do zfs upgrades so I wanted to add it to my yay config file so it always does a batch install. Is there any problem that come could up if I always use it? It seems like a good option but it's not the default so there could be some downside to it so is there a time you wouldn't want to add --batchinstall?
    submitted by    /u/Status-Floor3119  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>