<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-06-02T01:59:57.089Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Need help debugging a curl/SSL/Plexamp issue]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2we0d/need_help_debugging_a_curlsslplexamp_issue/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2we0d/need_help_debugging_a_curlsslplexamp_issue/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T00:44:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At some point in May, the Plexamp Appimage stopped working entirely. Checking Plexamp's logs, it says:
 [Javascript] INFO - Auth: Requesting PIN. [0x0513ba40] DEBUG - Networking: Create request 2: (POST https://plex.tv/api/v2/pins?strong=true). [0xf61fb640] DEBUG - Networking: Completed request 2: (POST https://plex.tv/api/v2/pins?strong=true) with code -59 (have 0 bytes) in 146 ms. [Javascript] ERROR - Auth: Could not get PIN HTTP status -59 
 cURL's manual states code 59 means it cannot use the selected SSL cipher (whatever that may be). 
 The Plexamp Appimage doesn't seem to be at fault as it hadn't been updated before it broke and it works without issue on an xUbuntu 21.10 machine I have. Additionally, although I'm running Arch, I grabbed the latest Manjaro daily build as well as a build from April and threw them into a VM for testing. Plexamp had no issues with the build from April but the daily build exhibited the same behavior as Arch, cURL code -59.
 Worth noting the Flatpak version of Plexamp works as expected, but Plexamp by default doesn't have a titlebar and I only had success force enabling it with the Appimage version.
 Tried downgrading OpenSSL and cURL but had no luck. I'm not sure where to go from here, especially since I thought Appimages contained all the required dependencies and wouldn't rely on system packages. Any suggestions would be appreciated.
    submitted by    /u/CarelessSpark  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch Linux Hits Top Linux Spot Over Ubuntu In May's Steam Survey]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Steam-Survey-May-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Steam-Survey-May-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T00:40:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Steam Survey results are in for May 2022 and while it shows Linux slightly down on a percentage basis, it shows a new top-spot for the most popular Linux distribution unseating Ubuntu LTS...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Is Activity Status Not Showing on Instagram?]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=489573</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15344575/activity-status-not-showing-instagram"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just like on Facebook, it’s possible to view when someone was last active on Instagram. The feature was introduced back in 2018 and proved quite popular with users on the network. However, as you might have noticed yourself, sometimes a user’s “Activity Status” can be hidden or unavailable. This post examine all the reasons you can’t see when someone was last active on Instagram and offers a few tips to fix it.
   

Content

How to Tell When Someone Was Last Active on Instagram
1. They Are Not Following You
2. They Don’t Have Activity Status Turned On
3. You Don’t Have the Activity Status Enabled
4. You’ve Never Sent Them a Direct Message
5. The 25 Conversations Rule
6. You’ve Been Restricted
7. You’ve Been Blocked
What to Do If You Can’t See “Activity Status” on Instagram
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Rearrange Photos in an... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexandra Arici</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mesa 22.1.1 Released With Many Open-Source Graphics Driver Fixes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Mesa-22.1.1-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Mesa-22.1.1-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T23:58:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last month marked the debut of Mesa 22.1 as the newest quarterly release to this open-source Linux graphics driver stack. For those that prefer waiting until the first point release before upgrading, today is the day with Mesa 22.1.1 now available...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Windows Search zero-day added to Microsoft protocol nightmare]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-windows-search-zero-day-added-to-microsoft-protocol-nightmare/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-windows-search-zero-day-added-to-microsoft-protocol-nightmare/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T22:06:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new Windows Search zero-day vulnerability can be used to automatically open a search window containing remotely-hosted malware executables simply by launching a Word document. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use S Pen Like a Pro on Samsung Galaxy Phones]]></title>
        <id>http://maketecheasier.com/?p=63743</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15344400/tips-and-tricks-to-using-the-s-pen-stylus"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[S Pen can be incredible useful accessory for your Samsung Galaxy phone or tablet. Whether you’re using the S Pen as a remote control, copying text, taking handwritten notes, or creating GIFs, the stylus can significantly enhance your experience while using your device. This post aims to help you get most of the S Pen on Samsung Galaxy phones and tablets.
   

Content

1. Open Air Command Menu in Multiple Ways
2. Scroll Using S Pen
3. Preview Image or Videos
4. Read Notifications and Messages
5. Select and Copy Text
6. Select Multiple Items Using S Pen
7. Take Notes on Lock Screen
8. Pin Notes to Always-on Display
9. Create a Note When You Remove S Pen
10. Take Notes on Any Screen
11. Write on Screenshot
12. Annotate a PDF
13. Write Using S Pen in Any App
14. Take Advantage of Smart Select
15. Extract Text
16. Create GIFs Using S Pen
17. Use S Pen to Translate Text
18. Listen to Text
19. Use the Glance Tool
20. Magnify Text Using S Pen
21. Search for Similar Images
22. Launch Camera Quickly
23. Use S Pen as... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mehvish Mushtaq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Import Data From a PDF to Microsoft Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=770474</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/770474/how-to-import-data-from-a-pdf-to-microsoft-excel/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you have a PDF document such as a bank statement or financial report, you may want to pull this information into Microsoft Excel. With a built-in feature, you can easily import and automatically convert a PDF to Excel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8bitdo controller issues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2r6tv/8bitdo_controller_issues/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2r6tv/8bitdo_controller_issues/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T20:55:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey I just bought an 8bitdo pro 2 wired gamepad, and I cannot get steam, or retroArch to detect it. when I do "Lsusb" it shows up, but nothing detects it, I've been looking online for solutions but I havent found anything. Thanks!
    submitted by    /u/Tetlus  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Is Raising Prices on Ring Protect Basic Subscriptions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=808929</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/808929/amazon-is-raising-prices-on-ring-protect-basic-subscriptions/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T20:49:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon-owned Ring sells some of the most popular video doorbells, and the Ring Protect Basic subscription offers video storage in the cloud and other features. Now prices for the subscription are going up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Glitchy/Corrupt Desktop after the last update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2qyj6/glitchycorrupt_desktop_after_the_last_update/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2qyj6/glitchycorrupt_desktop_after_the_last_update/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T20:45:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi. After I updated my arch installation today and restarted, I started to get a very strange glitching effect on my desktop. It happens at random but consistent places, like my panel and on application previews. The glitch is not visible on screenshots. I've tried reinstalling the Nvidia drivers, but that didn't help. Dmesg and the journal report no problem. Iv'e also reset my Xorg config, but that also didn't help. It's also not related to gnome extentions.
 https://imgur.com/a/sMbY24R
 The problem is not hardware related, as it is completely fine in console and bios.
 I'm running GNOME 42.1 on X11 with nvidia proprietary drivers 515.43.04. 
 Edit: Forgot to mention OpenGL applications are also broken with the message:
  
X Error of failed request: BadWindow (invalid Window parameter) 
 Major opcode of failed request: 156 (NV-GLX) 
 Minor opcode of failed request: 4 () 
 Resource id in failed request: 0x3800002 
 Serial number of failed request: 45 
 Current serial number in output stream: 45
  
​
    submitted by    /u/IndependentCrow-448  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MESA-LOADER - Problem to run flatpak app]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2qrjf/mesaloader_problem_to_run_flatpak_app/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2qrjf/mesaloader_problem_to_run_flatpak_app/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T20:36:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am getting this error when I try to run Frog, an Flatpak app.
 ​
 ​
 $ flatpak run com.github.tenderowl.frog
 libEGL warning: MESA-LOADER: failed to retrieve device information
 ​
 libEGL warning: DRI2: could not open /dev/dri/card0 (Arquivo ou diretório inexistente)
 libGL error: MESA-LOADER: failed to retrieve device information
 Cache downloaded codes: ['eng']
 No provider of glGetShaderiv found. Requires one of:
 Desktop OpenGL 2.0
 OpenGL ES 2.0
 ​
 Someone can help me to fix it?
 ​
    submitted by    /u/anderson_szr  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former OpenSea head of product charged with NFT insider trading]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/former-opensea-head-of-product-charged-with-nft-insider-trading/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/former-opensea-head-of-product-charged-with-nft-insider-trading/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T20:21:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nathaniel Chastain, a former product manager at OpenSea, the largest online non-fungible token (NFT) marketplace, has been arrested and charged by the U.S. Department of Justice (DOJ) with NFT insider trading. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Google Pixel Watch Won't Outlast Your Fitbit's Battery]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119790/the-google-pixel-watch-wont-outlast-your-fitbits-battery/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119790/the-google-pixel-watch-wont-outlast-your-fitbits-battery/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T20:10:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People are really overestimating the Pixel Watch’s capabilities, likely because it’s backed by several years of rumors and hype. And while we don’t really know all of the Pixel Watch’s specs, it probably doesn’t have a crazy battery life. Yeah, I’m making an educated guess, but it’s backed by a recent 9to5Google report.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stop Closing Apps on Your Android Phone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=771413</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/771413/stop-closing-apps-on-your-android-phone/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since its birth, Android has had to deal with one big misconception. Some phone makers have even helped perpetuate this myth. The truth is you do not need to kill Android apps. In fact, closing apps can make things worse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Where should I report this Bug?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2prmx/where_should_i_report_this_bug/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2prmx/where_should_i_report_this_bug/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T19:54:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Title says it all: I've found a bug and im unsure where to report it.
 When in install gdm, gnome-terminal, gnome-themes-extra and gnome-control-center, restart into gnome and open the control center, i cannot change any settings...
 I managed a few installes where I install the packages one by one and everything works fine. Maybe it's a gnome issue, maybe it's only on arch, where should i go to report this?
    submitted by    /u/Zacki_404  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Is Mixing up Its Video Chat Apps Again]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=808900</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/808900/google-is-mixing-up-its-video-chat-apps-again/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T19:45:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google currently has two apps for video and audio calls, Meet and Duo, but soon the company will combine them into a new Google Meet application.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iwd can't see my home Wi-Fi network.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2payc/iwd_cant_see_my_home_wifi_network/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2payc/iwd_cant_see_my_home_wifi_network/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T19:35:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My internet was working fine, connecting automatically through iwd and whatnot.
 Then, out of nowhere, my AP stopped showing when I scan and get-networks, other SSIDs do show, but my home one doesn't. 
 I can, by the way, connect to it through my phone, a laptop, and other phones in the house, just not my Linux client.
 Being able to see other SSIDs means that the problem isn't iwd, nor is it my Wi-Fi dongle, but my router/modem/ap, but I'm not sure, because it works fine with every other device.
    submitted by    /u/BraveWinner  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save 33% on a YOREPEK Travel Backpack, Extra Large, with USB Port]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=494272</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15344260/yorepek-travel-backpack"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re planning on taking your laptop and other devices with you during your summer plans, you’ll want the YOREPEK Travel Backpack. This extra-large bag has a USB port, fits a 17″ laptop, and is TSA approved. Buy it now for 33% off, and if you do it soon enough, Prime members can still get it delivered today.
    
Inside the 18″ x 13.5″ x 6.5″ large capacity bag, there are three spacious sections, with one of them roomy enough for a 17″ laptop. Another one will fit your daily needs, such as a change of clothes, portable charger, etc. The front section has small pockets to hold pens, a stylus, and cords, with a special spot for your keys as well so that these items are always at hand. There are also two side mesh pockets for water bottles and similar items.
    

    
The YOREPEK Travel Backpack is TSA approved and can be fully unfolded 90 to 180 degrees, which allows it to pass through security quickly while still keeping everything... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Command to show usage of apps?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2oyng/command_to_show_usage_of_apps/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2oyng/command_to_show_usage_of_apps/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T19:19:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi,
 Is there a command/application to show the frequence/usage of installed programms?
 Something like, "spent 20h in firefox"
 Thanks in advance
    submitted by    /u/len1315  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GM's 2023 Chevy Bolt EV Gets a Massive Price Cut]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119782/gms-2023-chevy-bolt-ev-gets-a-massive-price-cut/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119782/gms-2023-chevy-bolt-ev-gets-a-massive-price-cut/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T19:16:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These days EV manufacturers like Tesla and Rivian are raising the prices of vehicles at an alarming rate, but GM decided to do the complete opposite. The already affordable Chevy Bolt EV and EUV just received a massive price cut for the 2023 models.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Which Smart TV Should You Buy: Roku, Fire, or Google]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119734/which-smart-tv-should-you-buy-roku-fire-or-google/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119734/which-smart-tv-should-you-buy-roku-fire-or-google/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T19:15:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When talking about TVs, we tend to only focus on specs and pricing. But a smart TV’s operating system is also quite important. For most people, this operating system is the springboard for streaming content, discovering new shows, or even controlling a smart home. But with so many options to choose from, which smart TV OS is best?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hundreds of Elasticsearch databases targeted in ransom attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hundreds-of-elasticsearch-databases-targeted-in-ransom-attacks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hundreds-of-elasticsearch-databases-targeted-in-ransom-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T19:13:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A campaign targeting poorly secured Elasticsearch databases has deleted their contents and dropped ransom notes on 450 instances, demanding a payment of $620 to give them back their indexes, totaling a demand of $279,000. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Yield Farming in DeFi?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=804073</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/804073/what-is-yield-farming-in-defi/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T19:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi promises to eliminate the need for banks almost entirely. Known as yield farmers, holders of a cryptocurrency can earn yields by serving the same role that banks traditionally did. Here’s how it works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>RJ Fulton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IO_uring Continues Advancing In 2022 With New Features For Pushing Linux I/O]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=KR2022-IO_uring</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=KR2022-IO_uring"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Kernel Recipes 2022 conference kicked off today in Paris, France. Kicking off the event was Linux block subsystem maintainer and lead IO_uring developer Jens Axboe to talk about all of the recent and ongoing work around this major advancement to Linux I/O in recent years...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[keeping user accounts in sync across multiple btrfs root subvolumes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2odm9/keeping_user_accounts_in_sync_across_multiple/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2odm9/keeping_user_accounts_in_sync_across_multiple/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T18:54:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m looking for advice on how to keep the user accounts in sync across multiple btrfs subvolumes on the same ssd—usernames, passwords, etc. I’ve read about LDAP configuration, but since this would all be local, I was wondering if LDAP was the right way forward.
 My use case is I have a “recovery” subvolume for “ / “that I leave unaltered, and a “system” subvolume for “ / “ that’s for regular use. However, changes to the user on one are not reflected in the other.
    submitted by    /u/wohnonono  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This issue has bested me]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2ocdl/this_issue_has_bested_me/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2ocdl/this_issue_has_bested_me/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T18:52:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I bought a clone wireless x360 controller and I couldn't get my laptop to see it as a wireless x360 controller. Usb_modeswitch didn't work no matter what I did. Xpad, xpadneo, xow, xone were tested and none of those worked too. The computer thinks it's a goddamn nintendo switch pro controller through the dongle but it's seen as a generic x360 controller when connected with the cable. I am completely stumped it's been at least painful 1.5 months trying to fix this. I had it working as it should on Ubuntu and Linux Mint. But I can't make it work on arch.
 Edit: thank you, you beautiful bastards, I tried what worked on mint live boot and it works on arch now
    submitted by    /u/crippl3r  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FBI seizes domains used to sell stolen data, DDoS services]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fbi-seizes-domains-used-to-sell-stolen-data-ddos-services/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fbi-seizes-domains-used-to-sell-stolen-data-ddos-services/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T18:46:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) and the U.S. Department of Justice announced today the seizure of three domains used by cybercriminals to sell personal info stolen in data breaches and to provide DDoS attack services. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[systemd-udev throwing a ton of errors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2ntww/systemdudev_throwing_a_ton_of_errors/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2ntww/systemdudev_throwing_a_ton_of_errors/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T18:30:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm running archlinux with nvidia drivers. When I look at journalctl, I find that systemd-udev is throwing a ton of errors. Can someone please help me debug this. I can use my system just fine. There is no noticeable impact of these errors, but I would still like to clear these out if I can.
 ​
 # uname -a Linux acerarch 5.17.9-arch1-1 #1 SMP PREEMPT Wed, 18 May 2022 17:30:11 +0000 x86_64 GNU/Linux # pacman -Qs local/cuda 11.6.2-1 NVIDIA's GPU programming toolkit local/cuda-tools 11.6.2-1 NVIDIA's GPU programming toolkit (extra tools: nvvp, nsight, samples) local/egl-wayland 2:1.1.9+r3+g582b2d3-1 EGLStream-based Wayland external platform local/libvdpau 1.5-1 Nvidia VDPAU library local/libxnvctrl 515.43.04-1 NVIDIA NV-CONTROL X extension local/nvidia 515.43.04-7 NVIDIA drivers for linux local/nvidia-lts 1:515.43.04-8 NVIDIA drivers for linux-lts local/nvidia-prime 1.0-4 NVIDIA Prime Render Offload configuration and utilities local/nvidia-settings 515.43.04-1 Tool for configuring the NVIDIA graphics driver local/nvidia-utils 515.43.04-2 NVIDIA drivers utilities local/opencl-nvidia 515.43.04-2 OpenCL implemention for NVIDIA # journalctl -p 3 -xb Output link below since it was too big for this post. # systemctl --failed UNIT LOAD ACTIVE SUB DESCRIPTION 0 loaded units listed. 
 Journalctl output at https://pastebin.com/RSTfujfS
 My machine is an Acer Predator Helios 300 laptop. Also I am using auto-cpufreq. Also, I'm dual booting archlinux with Windows 11.
    submitted by    /u/pr0_Disappointment  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[how to make sure kde plasma splash screen runs for a specific number of seconds before desktop starts up]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2nrj9/how_to_make_sure_kde_plasma_splash_screen_runs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2nrj9/how_to_make_sure_kde_plasma_splash_screen_runs/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T18:27:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is there any way to configure my start up via sddm in such a way that the splash screen animation gets completed atleast by setting some user defined time intervals. Currently I am unable to see what goes on in the splash screen as the desktop loads really fast. It's a not super important factor but I would love to know if it's possible in some way.
    submitted by    /u/Kknsr  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Etcher now needs sudo privileges?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2nfkl/etcher_now_needs_sudo_privileges/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2nfkl/etcher_now_needs_sudo_privileges/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T18:13:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've written many iso USB sticks (I do the Arch Linux one every month just so I have a up to date USB stick handy). Well, last month and this month I have been unable to write to USB sticks without becoming sudo. Did something change with etcher or is it something in Arch? I'm not sure. I'm thinking it's something with etcher. I installed imagewriter just to try that one out but nope, I have to run that as sudo too. 
 Did something change with user permissions or something? I know I had no issues in April when I mad 4 USB sticks for friends who wanted to try Arch (They love it BTW). I'm confused as to what happened. 
 Why am I no longer able to write iso files to USB sticks without becoming sudo?
    submitted by    /u/Phydoux  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unable to edit /etc/locale.gen]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2n9zc/unable_to_edit_etclocalegen/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2n9zc/unable_to_edit_etclocalegen/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T18:06:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, I am following the arch installation guide: https://wiki.archlinux.org/title/Installation_guide and I am at the step where I need to edit the locale.gen file. I have chroot'ed into the new system and used pacman -S vim and it says it installed correctly however when I try use vim to edit locale.gen I get the error: 
 vim: error while loading shared libraries: libperl.so: cannot open object file: no such file or directory
    submitted by    /u/Glum_Ad7879  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Twitter Circle, and Should You Use It?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=808813</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/808813/what-is-twitter-circle-and-should-you-use-it/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T18:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter makes it easy to blast your thoughts out for everyone to see. However, you may not always want all your followers to see every single tweet. That’s where a feature called “Twitter Circle” comes in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Launches New Silicon Design Portal For Open-Source Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Google-Open-Silicon-Portal</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Google-Open-Silicon-Portal"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has been helping small open-source projects get started in chip fabrication with Google covering the costs and partnering with SkyWater Technology using their open-source process design kit (PDK). While the chip manufacturing is done on a 130nm process (SKY130), this effort has proven to be a big success for open-source hardware projects with limited funding and Google today announced a new silicon design portal...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch Linux STM32 SDK & IDE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2mxnx/arch_linux_stm32_sdk_ide/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2mxnx/arch_linux_stm32_sdk_ide/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T17:53:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone, is there an SDK and IDE for STM32 development for Linux. Currently now I use arm-none-eabi GCC toolchain and openocd for firmware upload. Is there any thing like SDK? It would be good but if there isn't any, I would write my one via documentation
    submitted by    /u/nikolaytihonov  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Surface Laptop Go 2 Is Microsoft’s New Budget Windows 11 PC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=808888</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/808888/surface-laptop-go-2-is-microsofts-new-budget-windows-11-pc/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T17:22:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The original Surface Laptop Go was one of the best laptops for students and anyone else not interested in dropping $1,000 or more on a PC. Now the laptop has received a much-needed upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US govt: Paying Karakurt extortion ransoms won’t stop data leaks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-govt-paying-karakurt-extortion-ransoms-won-t-stop-data-leaks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-govt-paying-karakurt-extortion-ransoms-won-t-stop-data-leaks/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T17:09:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several U.S. federal agencies warned organizations today against paying ransom demands made by the Karakurt gang since that will not prevent their stolen data from being sold to others.  [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTG Deals: Get Our Favorite Earbuds for Just $28, Plus More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=808883</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/808883/htg-deals-get-our-favorite-earbuds-for-just-28-plus-more/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T17:09:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the first day of June! To kick off the new month, we’ve assembled an awesome array of deals for your buying pleasure. Enjoy savings on Apple Watch Series 7, Microsoft Surface Duo 2, an Amazon eero 6 mesh Wi-Fi 6 router, our Editor’s Choice UGREEN HiTune T3 Earbuds, and one of our favorite Amazon Fire TV televisions of 2022. Continue on for details!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zach Laidlaw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Buick Teases Stunning Wildcat EV Concept As it Shifts to Electric]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119740/buick-teases-stunning-wildcat-ev-concept-as-it-shifts-to-electric/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119740/buick-teases-stunning-wildcat-ev-concept-as-it-shifts-to-electric/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T17:09:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Buick, the well-known American automaker owned by General Motors, just unveiled its Wildcat EV concept to help tease its all-electric future. The stunning Fastback coupe certainly doesn’t look like an old person’s car, something many think of when hearing the Buick name.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Upgrade to latest Nextcloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2lr83/upgrade_to_latest_nextcloud/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2lr83/upgrade_to_latest_nextcloud/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T17:02:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone. I've been running an old version of Nextcloud (20.x.x) because it wouldn't work with php8. So I stuck my head in the sand and now I've come up for air and noticed that the dependencies for nextcloud 23 in the repositories has php8. I've currently have this line in my pacman.conf:
 IgnorePkg = nextcloud php php-apache php-apcu php-cgi php-dblib php-igbinary php-imagick php-imap php-intl php-memcached perl
 If I remove this line am I going to mess up everything?
    submitted by    /u/PhantomNomad  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up Voice Access on Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=806979</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/806979/how-to-set-up-voice-access-on-windows-11/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Voice controls are everywhere now. They’re ubiquitous in TVs, smartphones, and cars, and they’re increasingly common in household appliances. Windows 11 also includes the ability to control your computer with your voice. All you need is a microphone and some practice. Here’s how to set up Windows Speech Recognition.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Lewis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lampada LED smart da soffitto con ventilatore integrato: si comanda via Bluetooth]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Lampada-LED-smart-da-soffitto-con-ventilatore-integrato-si-comanda-via-Bluetooth_24594</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Lampada-LED-smart-da-soffitto-con-ventilatore-integrato-si-comanda-via-Bluetooth_24594"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T16:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Il mercato offre un numero sempre crescente di dispositivi per la smart home che possono essere gestiti a distanza utilizzando lo smartphone o i comandi vocali.La lampada LED smart da soffitto con ventilatore è in offerta fino al prossimo 30 giugno a soli 69,99 euro con spedizione dai magazzini europei.Si tratta di un oggetto circolare installabile a soffitto, di diametro pari a 54 cm e spessore di circa 18 cm, che permette di illuminare l'ambiente grazie alla lampada LED integrata e alla possibilità di scegliere tra tre diverse temperature di colore: 3000K, 4500K e 6000K. In questo modo si può ottenere una luce calda, un bianco neutro o oppure una luce più fredda.

Tutti i parametri sono regolabili mediante l'app su smartphone: la connessione con la lampada smart avviene infatti via Bluetooth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RuneScape phishing steals accounts and in-game item bank PINs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/runescape-phishing-steals-accounts-and-in-game-item-bank-pins/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/runescape-phishing-steals-accounts-and-in-game-item-bank-pins/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T16:39:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered a new RuneScape-themed phishing campaign, and it stands out among the various operations for being exceptionally well-crafted. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft's Affordable Surface Laptop Go 2 Promises Repairability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119714/microsofts-affordable-surface-laptop-go-2-promises-repairability/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119714/microsofts-affordable-surface-laptop-go-2-promises-repairability/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T16:21:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The original Surface Laptop Go launched in 2020 as a sort of Chromebook competitor. And while it looked really pretty for a $550 device, the pricing was actually a bit awkward. Now, Microsoft is back with the $600 Surface Laptop Go 2, a repairable laptop with specs that more appropriately match the MSRP.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel Makes Another Exciting Software Acquisition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-Acquires-Codeplay</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-Acquires-Codeplay"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T16:12:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in February Intel announced it was acquiring Linutronix as the folks maintaining real-time Linux (PREEMPT_RT) and other prominent Linux contributions. Today Intel announced another exciting software acquisition for bolstering their open ecosystem...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google TV Arrives on iPhone to Help You Find Your Next Show]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=808826</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/808826/google-tv-arrives-on-iphone-to-help-you-find-your-next-show/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T16:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google TV is the new(ish) brand for all of Google’s entertainment offerings, but the old ‘Google Play Movies & TV’ name was sticking around on the iPhone and iPad. At long last, Apple devices can use the newer Google TV app.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Switching Between iPhone and Android Is Easier Than You Think]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=805224</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/805224/switching-between-iphone-and-android-isnt-a-big-deal/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T16:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[iPhone vs. Android is one of the biggest rivalries in the tech world. Switching between the platforms is not something people take lightly. I recently made the switch, and you know what? It’s really not that big of a deal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Mac App Is Great for People With Short Attention Spans]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=798968</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/798968/working-from-home-boost-your-productivity-with-setapp-for-mac/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T15:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Working from home has become wildly popular over the past few years, but it has also introduced us to challenges we hadn’t considered. Pets, projects around the house, random distractions on the internet — all serve to deter focus and hamper productivity. Can a suite of work-focused apps help you get back on track? We’ll discuss how to stay productive while working from home with Setapp, a popular subscription service with more than 200 incredible apps for Mac.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sponsored</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows MSDT zero-day vulnerability gets free unofficial patch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/windows-msdt-zero-day-vulnerability-gets-free-unofficial-patch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/windows-msdt-zero-day-vulnerability-gets-free-unofficial-patch/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T15:31:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A free unofficial patch is now available to block ongoing attacks against Windows systems that target a critical zero-day vulnerability known as 'Follina.' [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung Galaxy Z Fold 4 Leak Teases Huge Camera Upgrades]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119712/samsung-galaxy-z-fold-4-leak-teases-huge-camera-upgrades/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119712/samsung-galaxy-z-fold-4-leak-teases-huge-camera-upgrades/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T15:29:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we draw closer to a release date for Samsung’s next foldable phone, the Galaxy Z Fold 4, we’re getting new rumors about the device. And while we know plenty about it already, the latest Galaxy Z Fold 4 leaks suggest some huge camera upgrades—both inside and out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Beginner’s Guide to Using Cron in Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=276787</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/10892137/beginner-guide-use-cron-linux"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T15:25:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cron is a simple UNIX utility that manages and schedules the execution of commands in your computer. It was first developed in 1987 by Paul Vixie and it has since become an invaluable tool in Linux-based operating systems for both administrators and users alike.
    
Nowadays, there are a number of cron implementations and rewrites that you can easily install in your Linux system. Despite the differences, these programs all share the same Vixie Cron lineage.
    
As such, this article aims to provide a basic overview of how the original Vixie cron works, its syntax, and how you can use it to schedule tasks in your Linux system.
   

Content

How Does Cron Work?
Crontab: The Heart of Cron
System Crontabs
Reviewing cron activity
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Easily Create Cron jobs in Linux with... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramces Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xbox Steals PlayStation's Best Trophy Feature]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119703/xbox-steals-playstations-best-trophy-feature/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119703/xbox-steals-playstations-best-trophy-feature/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T15:06:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gamers get hyped! Microsoft just revealed a long-awaited (and highly demanded) achievement feature for its Xbox consoles in its June 2022 update, and we’re certain gamers of all varieties, especially achievement hunters, will be incredibly excited about it!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzanne Humphries</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make a Bubble Chart in Microsoft Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=804965</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/804965/bubble-chart-excel/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T15:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you want to display three data series on a type of scatter plot, then a bubble chart is the ideal choice. We’ll show you how to organize your data and create a bubble chart in Microsoft Excel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix's Anti-Account Sharing Test Is Confusing Customers and Employees]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119694/netflixs-anti-account-sharing-test-is-confusing-customers-and-employees/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119694/netflixs-anti-account-sharing-test-is-confusing-customers-and-employees/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T14:50:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix wants to crack down on password sharing. And to prepare for this unpopular new policy, it’s running an anti-account sharing “pilot program” in Chile, Costa Rica, and Peru. But the test is going about as well as you’d expect. Neither customers nor employees seem to understand what’s going on.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Murena One, smartphone Android senza i servizi Google. Un valore aggiunto per gli ideatori del progetto]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Murena-One-smartphone-Android-senza-i-servizi-Google-Un-valore-aggiunto-per-gli-ideatori-del-progetto_24593</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Murena-One-smartphone-Android-senza-i-servizi-Google-Un-valore-aggiunto-per-gli-ideatori-del-progetto_24593"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T14:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Huawei è l'azienda che forse più di tutti ha investito sulla creazione di un ecosistema alternativo a quello di Google: con HMS Core l'azienda ha proposto una valida alternativa lasciando comunque agli sviluppatori la facoltà di creare applicazioni Android compatibili anche con i servizi dell'azienda di Mountain View.L'ideatore della nota distribuzione Mandrake Linux, Gaël Duval, ha presentato il suo Murena One, uno smartphone che vuole distinguersi per l'impegno sul piano della tutela della privacy e dei dati degli utenti.Duval racconta di aver sviluppato il sistema operativo sul quale si basa Murena One stanco del duopolio Android-iOS e della massiccia raccolta di dati che viene posta in essere.Non aspettatevi però di trovare Linux all'interno di Murena One: lo smartphone poggia il suo funzionamento su un fork di Android chiamato /e/ che abbina buona parte del codice sorgente del progetto Google AOSP (Android Open Source Project) con quello di LineageOS, una delle ROM più apprezzate.

Nel sistema /e/ la maggior parte dei servizi Google (non tutti) vengono sostituiti con delle implementazioni open source totalmente svincolate dal lavoro dell'azienda di Mountain View.Ci sono ad esempio librerie e app che forniscono servizi di mappe, geolocalizzazione, messaggistica, uno store basato sul repository non ufficiale Clean APK e così via.Gli utenti possono ovviamente installare la maggior parte delle app di Google e le migliaia di quelle esistenti per Android.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[App per il Rooting di quasi tutti gli smartphone Android (Samsung, Xiaomi e altri)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2014/03/root-are-quasi-tutti-gli-smartphone.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2014/03/root-are-quasi-tutti-gli-smartphone.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T14:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Il Root di Android è la procedura di sblocco dei permessi del sistema operativo per usarlo come amministratore. Usare come amministratore uno smartphone o un tablet Android significa poterlo usare come un vero computer, senza limitazioni. Questo permette di personalizzare il sistema a proprio piacimento, di installare le app che sfruttano il root e installare una Custom ROM, ossia cambiare...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anker 757 PowerHouse Battery Review: Crazy Fast and Powerful]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118973/anker-757-powerhouse-battery-review-crazy-fast-and-powerful/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118973/anker-757-powerhouse-battery-review-crazy-fast-and-powerful/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T14:24:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you go on outdoor adventures and camping trips or live somewhere with frequent power outages, having a way to recharge all your gadgets is essential. And while Anker is a well-known brand for charging accessories, its new massive 757 PowerHouse portable power station is another beast entirely.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best USB Flash Drives of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=795657</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/795657/best-usb-flash-drive/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T14:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shopping for a new flash drive? There are tons out there. They may all look the same at a glance, but they’re not. We’ve highlighted some of the best USB flash drives you can buy today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Max Buondonno</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What to Know About the Strawberry Recall]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lifesavvy.com/131281/what-to-know-about-the-strawberry-recall/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lifesavvy.com/131281/what-to-know-about-the-strawberry-recall/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T14:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You probably read about the recent Jif peanut butter recall, but unfortunately, another one is now dominating the news. Here’s what you might want to check in your pantry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shea Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple WWDC 2022: How to Watch and What to Expect]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=808733</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/808733/apple-wwdc-2022-how-to-watch-and-what-to-expect/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T13:56:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple holds a Worldwide Developers Conference (WWDC) every year, and WWDC 2022 is quickly approaching. Here’s how to watch it, and what Apple might reveal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[can I force password prompt using popup for GPG?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2hkwg/can_i_force_password_prompt_using_popup_for_gpg/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2hkwg/can_i_force_password_prompt_using_popup_for_gpg/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T13:55:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[on my laptop using BSPWM everytime I have to enter my GPG passphrase there's this little popup thing asking me for my password
 on my desktop running kde plasma I got this curses interface instead. 
 how do I make it so that GPG asks for password using popup prompt like on my laptop? since I sign my git commits, this makes me unable to commit my changes using fugitive plugin in neovim, I have to exit neovim, commit my changes, then open neovim again, which is very inconvenient
 I'm using the exact same dotfiles, so I doubt it has anything to do with this (shell config, env variables and all that)
    submitted by    /u/shkspr_  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chiavi crittografiche RSA deboli recuperate con un algoritmo di 380 anni fa]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Chiavi-crittografiche-RSA-deboli-recuperate-con-un-algoritmo-di-380-anni-fa_24592</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Chiavi-crittografiche-RSA-deboli-recuperate-con-un-algoritmo-di-380-anni-fa_24592"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T13:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gli algoritmi crittografici sono essenziali per proteggere i dati scambiati attraverso un mezzo di comunicazione intrinsecamente insicuro qual è la rete Internet.La crittografia asimmetrica in particolare permette a due soggetti o due entità di comunicare a distanza in modo sicuro senza bisogno di essersi prima scambiati reciprocamente 'un segreto' (come può essere una password di decodifica dei dati).Gli sviluppatori, quando realizzano un software o implementano qualunque funzione in hardware che deve gestire dati riservati, sono soliti ricorrere all'utilizzo di algoritmi crittografici oggi considerati affidabili e robusti.In un altro articolo abbiamo visto quanto è davvero sicuro un algoritmo crittografico come RSA e abbiamo chiarito qual è il ruolo dell'operazione di fattorizzazione qua…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FluBot Android malware operation shutdown by law enforcement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/flubot-android-malware-operation-shutdown-by-law-enforcement/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/flubot-android-malware-operation-shutdown-by-law-enforcement/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T13:31:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Europol has announced the takedown of the FluBot operation, one of the largest and fastest-growing Android malware operations in existence. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Edge 102 fixes 31 security issues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178887</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/01/microsoft-edge-102-fixes-31-security-issues/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T13:23:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft released a new stable version of the company's Edge web browser on May 31, 2022. Microsoft Edge 102 is a security update first and foremost, that addresses 31 different security issues […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Microsoft Edge 102 fixes 31 security issues appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weird problems starting VirtualBox after boot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2gr46/weird_problems_starting_virtualbox_after_boot/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2gr46/weird_problems_starting_virtualbox_after_boot/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T13:13:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi r/archlinux
 I'm having a peculiar problem regarding VirtualBox.
 Every time i reboot and try to open VirtualBox from the Application Menu I'm faced with this error:
 https://imgur.com/a/XO6JHbS
 However when i run VirtualBox in the terminal, the program opens:
 https://imgur.com/a/a1MrSVm
 And after running it once in the terminal, I can then use the Application Menu/Dock to open VirtualBox.
 When looking in the /tmp i get the following output, where USER is my username.
 ~ ➜ ls -a /tmp ... drwx------ - USER 1 Jun 15:02  .vbox-USER-ipc ... 
 Hope someone knows or can explain the problem, because I'm quite curious to why it happens.
    submitted by    /u/Az0n  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SideWinder hackers plant fake Android VPN app in Google Play Store]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/sidewinder-hackers-plant-fake-android-vpn-app-in-google-play-store/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/sidewinder-hackers-plant-fake-android-vpn-app-in-google-play-store/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T13:10:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Phishing campaigns attributed to an advanced threat actor called SideWinder involved a fake VPN app for Android devices published on Google Play Store along with a custom tool that filters victims for better targeting. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Ilascu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Should You Abandon Low-Paying Clients (And Jobs)?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/?p=17131</id>
        <link href="https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/forsaking-low-paying-jobs/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T13:01:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the outset of my freelancing career, I would always fall into a dilemma while quoting my price for freelancing jobs. It was difficult because, on the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajiv Sighamony</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Month in Tech History: June]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118870/this-month-in-tech-history-june/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118870/this-month-in-tech-history-june/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T13:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The history of technology in June sees the birth of corporate giants, iconic products, and gaming legends. From Sonic the Hedgehog and Tetris to Atari and IBM, it all starts in June. Read below for the details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Chadwick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 DIY Outdoor Glass-Cleaning Solutions for Sparkling Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lifesavvy.com/130513/3-diy-outdoor-glass-cleaning-solutions-for-sparkling-windows/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lifesavvy.com/130513/3-diy-outdoor-glass-cleaning-solutions-for-sparkling-windows/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T13:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cleaning your windows on the outside doesn’t have to be a smelly, frustrating chore. Armed with these DIY washing solutions, every window in your home will soon be sparkling clean, and you won’t even have to touch (or smell) any harsh chemicals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amanda Prahl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Where to Stream the ‘Jurassic Park’ Franchise in 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=807194</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/807194/where-to-stream-jurassic-park/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting with one blockbuster movie about genetically engineered dinosaurs in the modern world, Jurassic Park has become one of the most lucrative pop-culture properties of the last three decades. Here’s how to stream the Jurassic Park franchise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Bell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come cambiare velocemente account in Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/06/come-cambiare-velocemente-account-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/06/come-cambiare-velocemente-account-in.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T12:32:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sui PC che dispongono di più account utente possiamo passare da un account all'altro senza dover riavviare o spegnere il computer, visto che Windows fornisce varie scorciatoie per cambiare al volo utente attivo. Conoscere questo tipo di scorciatoie si rileverà molto utile quando abbiamo vari account di test sul computer in uso o quando utilizziamo un computer condiviso e necessitiamo di...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trouble with running dbus command from a systemd service]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2flzb/trouble_with_running_dbus_command_from_a_systemd/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2flzb/trouble_with_running_dbus_command_from_a_systemd/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T12:14:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So im trying to run a bash script which is running a dbus command to change my desktop wallpaper, now the script runs perfectly when executed but when I try to run it as a systemd service (with a timer) I get;
 " Could not connect to D-Bus server: org.freedesktop.DBus.Error.NotSupported: Us>ct to D-Bus server: org.freedesktop.DBus.Error.NotSupported using X11 for dbus-daemon autolaunch was disabled at compile time, set your DBUS_SESSION_BUS_ADDRESS instead "
 Im pretty new to this so if I need to provide anything else just let me know, Thanks for any help in advance!
    submitted by    /u/mitchmatch99  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s Why GeForce NOW Is the Best Cloud Gaming Service]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=808081</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/808081/heres-why-geforce-now-is-the-best-cloud-gaming-service/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T12:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud gaming platforms have surged over the last several years, bringing out contenders like Xbox Cloud Gaming, Google Stadia, and Amazon Luna. But one of them reigns above the rest. Here are five reasons why NVIDIA’s GeForce NOW  is the best cloud gaming option available, bar none.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zach Laidlaw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ransomware attacks need less than four days to encrypt systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ransomware-attacks-need-less-than-four-days-to-encrypt-systems/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ransomware-attacks-need-less-than-four-days-to-encrypt-systems/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T11:32:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The duration of ransomware attacks in 2021 averaged 92.5 hours, measured from initial network access to payload deployment. In 2020, ransomware actors spent an average of 230 hours to complete their attacks and 1637.6 hours in 2019. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Long Does It Really Take to Blow Through a 1TB Data Cap?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=803656</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/803656/how-long-does-it-really-take-to-blow-through-a-1tb-data-cap/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T11:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your ISP has a data cap. You’re worried about using so much data you blow through it. So what exactly does that look like, and are you really at risk of doing so?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Fitzpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WhatsApp: come ti rubo l'account e tutti i messaggi con l'inoltro delle chiamate]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=WhatsApp-come-ti-rubo-l-account-e-tutti-i-messaggi-con-l-inoltro-delle-chiamate_24591</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=WhatsApp-come-ti-rubo-l-account-e-tutti-i-messaggi-con-l-inoltro-delle-chiamate_24591"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T10:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sebbene l'espediente sia in sé piuttosto semplice, è difficile che gli utenti più esperti cadano nella trappola. Purtuttavia riteniamo importante parlare di un trucco svelato da Rahul Sasi, fondatore e CEO di CloudSEK, che viene già utilizzato per rubare account WhatsApp sottraendo anche il contenuto delle chat, degli allegati e la lista dei contatti altrui.Sasi ha spiegato che utilizzando un po’ di ingegneria sociale, un aggressore può invitare la vittima a chiamare un numero di telefono che inizia con * o #. Ricordiamo che con questi due simboli si possono invocare i codici MMI (Man Machine Interface): si tratta di 'scorciatoie' che, sotto forma di numeri brevi, possono essere inviate all'operatore di telecomunicazioni mobile per attivare o disattivare servizi oppure per consultarne lo stato.Ogni operatore utilizza dei codici MMI che permettono di attivare la deviazione delle chiamate quando l'utenza in uso fosse irraggiungibile oppure risultasse occupata in altra conversazione.Se l'utente, magari poco pratico con l'uso dei codici MMI, effettuasse una chiamata usando il numero fornito dal malintenzionato, questi potrebbe di fatto attivare un inoltro di tutte le chiamate in arrivo verso una numerazione che non è più sotto il suo controllo.L'utente interessato a mettere le mani sui dati WhatsApp altrui può usare codici come **67* o *405* seguiti da un numero telefonico da lui gestito per indurre la vittima a richiedere la deviazione delle chiamate verso tale numerazione.A questo punto il criminale dovrebbe semplicemente richiedere l'attivazione di WhatsApp sul nuovo numero e attivare l'autenticazione a due fattori in modo che il legittimo proprietario dell'account non possa più accedervi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Upgrading Ubuntu 22.04's Kernel & Mesa For Better AMD RDNA2 Performance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31165</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31165"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T10:38:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While Ubuntu 22.04 LTS was just released over one month ago, it is shipping on the Linux 5.15 kernel that was already two stable series behind at release time but chosen as the default due to its long-term support status. Ubuntu 22.04 also shipped with Mesa 22.0 as the latest stable version albeit the open-source OpenGL/Vulkan graphics drivers are quick to advance. So if you've been thinking about upgrading Mesa or the Linux kernel on your Ubuntu 22.04 system for better Linux gaming performance, here are some benchmarks looking at such performance impact for AMD RDNA2 / Radeon RX 6000 series graphics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GoodWill Ransomware Requires Victims to Do Good Deeds]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=494198</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15343062/goodwill-ransomware-good-deeds"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T10:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve heard of white hat hackers who are on the good side of the issue: ethical hacking that identifies vulnerabilities to help others not be victims. But the GoodWill ransomware is a different type of ethical – it requires its victims to do good deeds to get their data back.
   
Also read:How to Enable Ransomware Protection in Windows
    
Identifying GoodWill Ransomware
    
Threat analysis company CloudSEK identified the GoodWill ransomware this March. Victims don’t need to worry about losing money to these hackers, though. Instead of demanding a cash ransom, the hackers require victims do good deeds if they ever want to see their data again.
    
You may be asking how the hackers will know the good deeds have been carried out. Victims are required to record them in pictures, audio, and/or video, then post the proof to social media.
    
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 Website-Building Tips and Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/?p=47201</id>
        <link href="https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/think-you-know-best-page-and-website-building-tools/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T10:01:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web designers have relied on the advantages website and page building tools offer. They save them time and money and make it easier for them to achieve]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Dagli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Govee RGBIC Neon Rope Lights Review: Your Lights, Your Way]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=802169</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/802169/govee-rgbic-neon-rope-lights-review-your-lights-your-way/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T10:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Govee’s Neon Rope Light is the simple to set up, sure to spice up your room solution to a lacking atmosphere. Countless effects, quality construction, and unparalleled customizability make the Neon Rope Light perfect for movie nights, gaming setups, and holiday get-togethers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcus Mears III</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram’s blogging platform abused in phishing attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/telegram-s-blogging-platform-abused-in-phishing-attacks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/telegram-s-blogging-platform-abused-in-phishing-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram's anonymous blogging platform, Telegraph, is being actively exploited by phishing actors who take advantage of the platform's lax policies to set up interim landing pages that lead to the theft of account credentials. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Velocizzare Windows 11 e ottimizzare il sistema]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Velocizzare-Windows-11-e-ottimizzare-il-sistema_24016</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Velocizzare-Windows-11-e-ottimizzare-il-sistema_24016"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Come avevamo già visto nel caso di Windows 10, anche Windows 11 viene installato utilizzando una serie di impostazioni che potrebbero non soddisfare l'utente, essere considerate inutili o addirittura fastidiose.In un altro articolo abbiamo spiegato come eseguire un'installazione personalizzata di Windows 11 in modalità unattended ovvero non presidiata: l'installazione di Windows 11 diventa più veloce ed è possibile richiedere una serie di modifiche che permettono di ottimizzare e velocizzare il sistema operativo.Abbiamo anche visto come far installare da solo Windows 11 con i programmi più utili personalizzando il contenuto del file ISO ufficiale.Se nel caso di un'installazione unattended di Windows la procedura di setup non pone alcuna domanda all'utente ed è possibile applicare tutte le …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TIL over time your Arch system might start accumulating unused packages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2dcgp/til_over_time_your_arch_system_might_start/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2dcgp/til_over_time_your_arch_system_might_start/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T09:57:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been running this same Arch installation since 2013 (head -n1 /var/log/pacman.log) and I only recently learned that Arch doesn't by default have a function like the apt autoremove function ("The following packages were automatically installed and are no longer required: ..."). 
 So your system can over time accumulate packages that you don't need. Even though pacman keeps track of this information, it doesn't show it by default.
 This can happen because of 
  
using pacman -R instead of pacman -Rs to remove packages (dependencies stay installed)
 makedeps stay installed after building AUR packages
 packages removing dependencies in newer versions (without you noticing)
  
You can remove them by doing pacman -Qtdq | pacman -Rns - but check the list carefully first since some of those packages you might actually want to keep, especially if your installation is very old.
 I've added all this info to the Pacman tips: Removing unused packages section of the Wiki. 
 I've also created pacman-log-orphans-hook[AUR] which logs the list of unused packages whenever pacman runs.
    submitted by    /u/tehdog  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[F2FS Enhancements Land In Linux 5.19]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-F2FS</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-F2FS"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T09:27:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New feature code for the Flash-Friendly File-System (F2FS) has landed for the in-development Linux 5.19 kernel...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cancellare i messaggi inviati per errore in Whatsapp, per tutti]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2017/10/elimina-messaggi-per-tutti-in-whatsapp.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2017/10/elimina-messaggi-per-tutti-in-whatsapp.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T09:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Su WhatsApp possiamo sempre cancellare i messaggi inviati per tutti in modo che nessuno possa più vederli. Si tratta, in pratica, della funzione per annullare l'invio di un messaggio in modo tale che possa essere ritirato ed eliminato prima che possa essere letto.

 Se, quindi, fino a oggi, nel caso di un messaggio inviato per errore a qualcuno o in un gruppo, di cui ci si pente subito dopo o...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to remove Windows Spotlight's "Learn about this picture icon" from your desktop in Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178881</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/01/how-to-remove-windows-spotlights-learn-about-this-picture-icon-from-your-desktop-in-windows-11/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T08:58:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The KB5014019 update for Windows 11 was released last week with a bunch of fixes for known issues. The Cumulative Preview patch also brought something else, it introduces the Spotlight Desktop feature […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post How to remove Windows Spotlight's "Learn about this picture icon" from your desktop in Windows 11 appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ARM: Qualcomm parla di un consorzio per acquistare l'azienda e mantenerla neutrale]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=ARM-Qualcomm-parla-di-un-consorzio-per-acquistare-l-azienda-e-mantenerla-neutrale_24590</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=ARM-Qualcomm-parla-di-un-consorzio-per-acquistare-l-azienda-e-mantenerla-neutrale_24590"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T08:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[La concreta ipotesi di acquisizione di ARM da parte di NVidia era malvista da una buona parte dell'industria: non è certo un segreto. Esattamente un anno fa Qualcomm si dichiarò pronta a formare una cordata per rilevare ARM se NVidia non fosse riuscita a chiudere l'operazione.Adesso che NVidia ha dovuto accantonare il progetto di acquisizione di ARM, soprattutto in forza delle crescenti pressioni esercitate dalle Autorità competenti in materia di antitrust, arriva la notizia che Qualcomm potrebbe effettivamente attivarsi per creare una piattaforma comune tra i big dell'industria volta all'acquisizione di ARM.D'altra parte nubi nere sull'accordo NVidia-ARM (del valore di 40 miliardi di dollari) si erano addensate già a dicembre 2021 quando la FTC parlò dell'eventuale intesa come di una minaccia concreta sul piano della concorrenza: NVidia si sarebbe di fatto trovata in una situazione di monopolio totale tenendo per sé le redini della parte più ampia del mercato dei chip per i dispositivi mobili e mettendo una seria ipoteca sullo sviluppo delle soluzioni per il mercato professionale, server e data center.A suo tempo parlammo delle possibili conseguenze di un accordo NVidia-ARM.Riferendosi ad ARM, il CEO di Qualcomm Cristiano Amon ha descritto la società britannica come 'una risorsa molto importante che sarà essenziale per lo sviluppo del settore'.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[nvidia-smi not showing applications launched with prime-run]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2c6r6/nvidiasmi_not_showing_applications_launched_with/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2c6r6/nvidiasmi_not_showing_applications_launched_with/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T08:32:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have set up nvidia drivers on my laptop with hybrid graphics. I use gnome with wayland.
 When I try to run any application with prime-run, it launches but nvidia-smi does not show the application as listed.
 Only glxgears works. nvidia-smi lists glxgears as an application using the gpu.
 I was trying to run a game with wine. It works but nvidia-smi does not show anything.
 Am I doing something wrong? Is there any other way to check if an application is run by the discrete gpu?
    submitted by    /u/abrattic  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[flameshot crashes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2c5v7/flameshot_crashes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2c5v7/flameshot_crashes/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T08:30:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently installed arch linux and ran into a problem related to flameshot. When I press print screen for the first time, flameshot takes a screenshot, but when I try to take it again, it freezes tightly, and then crashes. In other distributions everything works fine for example in manjaro and linux mint.
    submitted by    /u/sp595s  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genode OS 22.05 Adds WireGuard VPN Support, Linux Device Driver Updates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Genode-OS-22.05</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Genode-OS-22.05"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For ending out the month of May the Genode open-source operating system framework developers published a new feature release of their software as they advance both the framework itself and the Sculpt OS general purpose operating system...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vivaldi 5.3 arrives with editable toolbars]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178874</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/01/vivaldi-5-3-arrives-with-editable-toolbars/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T07:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vivaldi Technologies released Vivaldi 5.3, a new version of the company's web browser, to the public on June 1st, 2022. The new version of Vivaldi introduces support for the full customization of […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Vivaldi 5.3 arrives with editable toolbars appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vivaldi Browser Pushes Customization With Editable Toolbars]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=808665</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/808665/vivaldi-browser-pushes-customization-with-editable-toolbars/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T07:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vivaldi is one of the most popular alternative web browsers, aimed at people who want a feature-packed experience. Now the browser is rolling out the ability to fully customize its toolbars.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RISC-V With Linux 5.19 Allows Running RV32 32-bit Binaries On RV64, Adds Svpbmt]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-RISC-V</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-RISC-V"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Tuesday the RISC-V architecture changes were merged into the in-development Linux 5.19 kernel with several new features in tow...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux 5.19 Adds Support For XSAVEC When Running As A VM Guest]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-XSAVEC-Support</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-XSAVEC-Support"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Various hypervisors expose support for the XSAVEC instruction as an XSAVE with compaction as an efficiency optimization. However, the Linux kernel doesn't currently make use of XSAVEC as an alternative to XSAVES (supervisor mode) but that is now changing with Linux 5.19...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Arch Linux as a Virtual Machine host]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v24qqm/using_arch_linux_as_a_virtual_machine_host/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v24qqm/using_arch_linux_as_a_virtual_machine_host/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T00:52:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently tried to install in VirtualBox another linux distribution using my Arch linux as a host. I followed the steps in Arch Wiki and I installed the virtualbox-host-modules-arch package. However, when I start the machine I am stuck at "Starting Virtual Machine ...(2/2) 20%". Has anyone else encountered that specific problem?
 Edit: I am using Linux for 2 years (Arch for about 6 months) and it is my main OS, so I would not characterize myself a begginer with linux.
 Edit2: I retried with Ubuntu and I have the same problem
    submitted by    /u/Grand_Unique  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 Ways to Fix Apple Watch Not Unlocking Mac Issue]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=485644</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15341693/fix-apple-watch-not-unlocking-mac-issue"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Auto Unlock is one of the many “Apple Continuity” features. It automatically unlocks a Mac when wearing an Apple Watch without requiring to type in the password. When it works properly, the feature is magical.
    
Apple has a complex system in place to make Auto Unlock possible, but unfortunately it can sometimes malfunction. If you’ve been experiencing issues yourself, here’s what you can do if your Apple Watch won’t unlock your Mac.
   

Content

Apple Watch Auto Unlock Requirements
1. Disable Auto Unlock and Enable It Again
2. Reset Bluetooth and Wi-Fi Connection
3. Turn Off Automatic Login
4. Turn Off Internet Sharing and Screen Sharing
5. Update Mac and Apple Watch
6. Unpair Apple Watch and Pair Again
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Unlock iPhone and Mac with an Apple Watch
    
Apple Watch Auto Unlock... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ratnesh Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mutter build failing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v245nv/mutter_build_failing/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v245nv/mutter_build_failing/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T00:21:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, I'm trying to build the latest release of mutter from the repositories, but it is failing.
 Steps:
 $ asp update mutter $ asp checkout mutter $ cd mutter/repos/extra-x86_64 $ extra-x86_64-build 
 The failures happen at the check() step. Some excerpts of the check log:
 78/114 mutter:core+mutter/backend / monitor-unit FAIL 0.60s exit status 1 ... (EE) failed to read Wayland events: Connection reset by peer (mutter-test-client:16390): Gtk-WARNING **: 21:10:25.356: cannot open display: :512 Traceback (most recent call last): File "/build/mutter/src/mutter/src/tests/meta-dbus-runner.py", line 184, in <module> test_case.wrap_call(rest[1:]) File "/build/mutter/src/mutter/src/tests/meta-dbus-runner.py", line 171, in wrap_call self.assertEqual(p.wait(), 0) File "/usr/lib/python3.10/unittest/case.py", line 845, in assertEqual assertion_func(first, second, msg=msg) File "/usr/lib/python3.10/unittest/case.py", line 838, in _baseAssertEqual raise self.failureException(msg) AssertionError: -5 != 0 ... (Ends on a summary with 23 failed tests) 
 All tests seem to fail with the same issue "cannot open display". I used to build the previous versions of mutter and this error never happened before. Can someone please help me investigate this?
 OS configuration is Gnome/Wayland and KDE/Wayland (different machines).
  
Edit: I tried building an older version and it also failed. Strange, though, since at least the builds on my Gnome machine were going just fine.
    submitted by    /u/parcimonic  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2022.06.01]]></title>
        <id>tag:archlinux.org,2022-06-01:/releng/releases/2022.06.01/</id>
        <link href="https://archlinux.org/releng/releases/2022.06.01/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux: Releases</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers steal WhatsApp accounts using call forwarding trick]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-steal-whatsapp-accounts-using-call-forwarding-trick/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-steal-whatsapp-accounts-using-call-forwarding-trick/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T23:10:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's a trick that allows attackers to hijack a victim's WhatsApp account and gain access to personal messages and contact list. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Ilascu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NVIDIA's Open-Source Kernel Driver, Graviton3 & Fedora 36 Made For An Exciting May]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=May-2022-Highlights</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=May-2022-Highlights"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Word of NVIDIA working on an open-source kernel driver with hopes of eventually being mainlined and being of better quality than Nouveau topped the Linux news for the past month. Plus the introduction of Amazon's new Graviton3 processors, the debut of Fedora 36 and SteamOS 3.2 among other distribution updates, and Linux 5.19 development getting underway all made for an interesting month of May...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 14 Best Local Co-op Games for Nintendo Switch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/18742/the-ten-best-local-co-op-games-for-nintendo-switch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/18742/the-ten-best-local-co-op-games-for-nintendo-switch/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T22:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Switch’s dock and KitKat controllers make it perfect for multiplayer games. But if you’re looking for something without intense competition, a cooperative local multiplayer game is what you need. Here are the best ones on the console.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Crider</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How do i change the language used by pacman ?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v21gyy/how_do_i_change_the_language_used_by_pacman/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v21gyy/how_do_i_change_the_language_used_by_pacman/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T22:07:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey
 So my problem isn't actually that hard to solve but i couldn't manage to find a solution for it, i just wanna make pacman use English as the language used to display information about packages, updates ,etc .... while not making it the language used by KDE itself, as I've set KDE to use French as the display language so pacman followed that setting and now i'm stuck unable to understand a single infromation displayed by pacman as I'm used to have it in English. I do know that changing KDE language back to English can solve the problem but that's not what I really want.
 I know that there's a way to control pacman as it does have a config file stored somewhere but i'm not pretty sure how i can achieve it.
 Any help will be appreciated, thanks in advance !
    submitted by    /u/1_7xr  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows MSDT zero-day now exploited by Chinese APT hackers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/windows-msdt-zero-day-now-exploited-by-chinese-apt-hackers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/windows-msdt-zero-day-now-exploited-by-chinese-apt-hackers/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T22:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese-linked threat actors are now actively exploiting a Microsoft Office zero-day vulnerability (known as 'Follina') to execute malicious code remotely on Windows systems. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ClamAV: antivirus open-source, "on demand" e con protezione residente, per il nostro Linux Mint]]></title>
        <id>3572|20220601000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/antivirus-antimalware-2421/clamav-antivirus-open-source-on-demand-protezione-residente-linux-mint-3572"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Questo articolo, a differenza di molti altri (i più!) solitamente proposti ai nostri lettori, invece di essere una monolitica, completa guida per un determinato argomento o per la risoluzione di qualche problema informatico, deve considerarsi come una sorta di "esperimento sociale", da condurre con i volenterosi che vorranno addentrarsi nelle funzionalità di uno dei più affermati (e potenti) antivirus, attualmente disponibili e open source, per ambiente Linux: ClamAV.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can't find a way to make caps lock act like escape]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v20tji/cant_find_a_way_to_make_caps_lock_act_like_escape/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v20tji/cant_find_a_way_to_make_caps_lock_act_like_escape/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T21:37:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I read the documentation on the arch wiki. And I tried editing the 00-keyboard.conf by adding the option "caps:escape" but it didn't work. I then tried looking into the vconsole.conf file but couldn't find a way to add an option. I don't know what to do anymore, does anybody know what I could do ?
    submitted by    /u/douhan_wicht  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[11 Common ADB Commands You Should Know]]></title>
        <id>http://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=96680</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/12842997/common-adb-commands"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Android Debug Bridge (ADB) is a command-line tool to interact with your Android device from your computer. ADB commands enable you to perform a wide range of tasks, including some that would be difficult or even impossible to achieve without ADB. In this article we cover the essential ADB commands that every Android user should know.
   

Content

How Do I Set Up ADB?
1. Show Connected Devices
2. Reboot Your Device
3. Reboot into Recovery
4. Reboot into Bootloader Mode
5. Reboot into Fastboot
6. Send File to Your Device
7. Get Files from Your Device
8. Install an App on Your Device
9. Remount the System
10. Sideload System Updates
11. Create and Restore a Backup
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Install Windows from Android
    
Enable Developer Options on Android
    
Before your computer will recognize your Android device to use ADB commands,... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Crystal Crowder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ten Gadgets To Take The Stress Out Of Long Flights]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/4120/ten-gadgets-to-take-the-stress-out-of-long-flights/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/4120/ten-gadgets-to-take-the-stress-out-of-long-flights/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T21:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Air travel can be…less than pleasant. Doubly so if you have to deal with the American TSA. But some thoughtful selection and packing in your carry-on can make it more bearable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Crider</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accidentally created a big /home/ and small /. How do I repartition without losing data?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2069y/accidentally_created_a_big_home_and_small_how_do/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2069y/accidentally_created_a_big_home_and_small_how_do/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T21:08:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm currently backing up /home/, so even if things go south I can afford it. I must've not paid attention somewhere when installing, but apparently I allocated most of my drive space to my /home directory, so now my root is out of space. I don't use a separate partition for home, I like to just have a root partition. What's the best course of action here? Would booting from a live usb allow me to resize the partitions?
    submitted by    /u/Gisbitus  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Find Your Lost Windows or Office Product Keys]]></title>
        <id>http://www.howtogeek.com/?p=206329</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/206329/how-to-find-your-lost-windows-or-office-product-keys/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re planning on doing a reinstall of Windows but can’t find your product key, you’re in luck because it’s stored in the Windows Registry. It’s just not easy to find, and it’s impossible to read without some help. Luckily, we’re here to help.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lowell Heddings</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[disable sleep while playing music]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v1z5ia/disable_sleep_while_playing_music/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v1z5ia/disable_sleep_while_playing_music/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T20:21:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[i use arch linux kde and each time i’m using spotify i’m encountering the same behaviour. after some minutes the computer goes to sleep. is there a way (any script maybe) i could use to not let the system sleep when spotify is on?
    submitted by    /u/reggaetis  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do EVs Really Require Less Maintenance?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119554/do-evs-really-require-less-maintenance/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119554/do-evs-really-require-less-maintenance/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T20:20:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re like many others considering an electric vehicle for your next car, you probably have a lot of questions. Owning an EV has several benefits, like saving money and avoiding the gas pump, but electric vehicles also require far less maintenance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Over 3.6 million MySQL servers found exposed on the Internet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/over-36-million-mysql-servers-found-exposed-on-the-internet/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/over-36-million-mysql-servers-found-exposed-on-the-internet/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T20:02:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[​Over 3.6 million MySQL servers are publicly exposed on the Internet and responding to queries, making them an attractive target to hackers and extortionists. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stop Closing Apps on Your iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=773871</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/773871/stop-closing-apps-on-your-iphone/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you constantly close apps on your iPhone while attempting to speed things up or save battery life, you’re doing the opposite and making your iPhone perform worse. Here’s why.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What pager does `man` use in the archiso?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v1yk58/what_pager_does_man_use_in_the_archiso/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v1yk58/what_pager_does_man_use_in_the_archiso/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T19:55:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I like the keybinds and the color scheme
 I dont think its less, more, most, or vim
    submitted by    /u/dominic_l  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dual-boot arch help]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v1yjo8/dualboot_arch_help/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v1yjo8/dualboot_arch_help/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T19:55:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey! An Arch newbie here. I want to dual boot arch linux with my windows 11 in my laptop in such a way that the boot managers are separate, and I can boot into the OSes by changing the boot priority. Is this possible? If yes, then any possible tips/guides? Thank you :)
    submitted by    /u/rumble_ftw  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FBI warns of Ukrainian charities impersonated to steal donations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fbi-warns-of-ukrainian-charities-impersonated-to-steal-donations/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fbi-warns-of-ukrainian-charities-impersonated-to-steal-donations/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T19:43:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scammers are claiming to be collecting donations to help Ukrainian refugees and war victims while impersonating legitimate Ukrainian humanitarian aid organizations, according to the Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI). [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get an Amazon Fire TV 65″ Omni Series for Under $500]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=462563</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15067477/amazon-fire-tv-75-omni"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the times this summer when you just want to relax inside, check out this deal on the Amazon Fire TV 65″ Omni. You can get it for 40% off. You’ll enjoy Dolby Vision, 4K, your favorite streaming entertainment, and the Alexa virtual assistant.
    
Sit back in your most comfortable chair or sofa and watch your favorite TV shows and movies in 4K Ultra HD. The true-to-life quality delivers brilliant colors, making you feel like you’re in the theater with Dolby Vision HDR 10, HLG, and Dolby Digital Plus.
    

    
With Alexa, you have the ability to change the channel, adjust the volume, or find a show that you’re dying to see, all hands-free. The virtual assistant works with built-in microphones to execute all your commands. New Alexa skills, features, and smartphone capabilities are always being added. Note that you can disconnect the microphones electronically anytime you want.
    
You’ll enjoy all your entertainment on the Amazon Fire TV 65″ Omni. Stream more than 1 million movies and TV episodes,... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up Touch ID on an iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=805085</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/805085/how-to-set-up-touch-id-on-an-iphone/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T19:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some iPhone models include a biometric security feature called Touch ID that lets you verify your identity with your fingerprint. This saves time because you don’t need to enter passcodes and passwords as often. Here’s how to set it up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LVFS Has Served More Than 52 Million Firmware Files To Linux Users]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=LVFS-Fwupd-52-Million</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=LVFS-Fwupd-52-Million"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was just March of last year that the Linux Vendor Firmware Service (LVFS) served up a total of 25 million firmware downloads to Linux users for updating their system firmware and peripheral devices supporting Fwupd. Just over one year later it has successfully served more than 52 million downloads!..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I solved the annoying bell on suspend bug]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v1xfje/how_i_solved_the_annoying_bell_on_suspend_bug/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v1xfje/how_i_solved_the_annoying_bell_on_suspend_bug/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T18:57:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[i) create a script
 sudo nano /usr/lib/systemd/scripts/no_bell
 add
 #!/bin/bash
 busctl set-property org.freedesktop.login1 /org/freedesktop/login1 org.freedesktop.login1.Manager EnableWallMessages b false
 exit 0
 PLEASE NOTE THAT THE COMMAND AT SECOND ROW (busctl etc) MUST STAY ON ONE ROW
 ii) make it executable
 sudo chmod a+x /usr/lib/systemd/scripts/no_bell
 iii) create the systemd service:
 sudo nano /usr/lib/systemd/system/no_bell.service
 add
 [Unit]
 Description=Disable bell 
 [Service]
 Type=oneshot
 ExecStart=/usr/lib/systemd/scripts/no_bell
 RemainAfterExit=yes 
 [Install]
 WantedBy=multi-user.target 
 iv) "make it so!"
 sudo systemctl daemon-reload
 sudo systemctl --now enable no_bell.service
 I tested this procedure on my system but I'm not responsible of any damage/loss of data/inability to boot the system/etc. The usual disclaimers apply.
    submitted by    /u/guiodic76  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[mouse flickering on second monitor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v1wi0k/mouse_flickering_on_second_monitor/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v1wi0k/mouse_flickering_on_second_monitor/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T18:15:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[so i just recently installed arch and i noticed this happening on my second monitor when every i am pressing any keyboard button or if i am hovering over a link or a video and i don't know where to even look for the problem that's my xrandr config that i use:
 xrandr --output eDP-1 --mode 2560x1600 --pos 0x0 --scale 0.5x0.5 --rotate normal --rate 120 --output DisplayPort-1 --off --output DisplayPort-2 --off --output DisplayPort-3 --off --output DisplayPort-4 --off --output DisplayPort-5 --off --output DisplayPort-6 --off --output DisplayPort-7 --off --output DisplayPort-8 --off --output eDP-1-0 --off --output DisplayPort-1-0 --off --output HDMI-A-1-0 --primary --mode 3440x1440 --pos 1280x0 --rotate normal --rate 99.992 
 ​
 my graphics card is amd integrated and external for extra information the second display uses the external gpu and i have installed all the drivers
 yay -S xf86-video-ati mesa-vdpau vulkan-radeon amdvl vulkan-amdgpu-pro amdgpu-pro-libgl libgl mesa 
 ​
 i also have these two
 /etc/X11/xorg.conf.d/20-radeon.conf Section "Device" Identifier "Radeon" Driver "radeon" Option "AccelMethod" "glamor" Option "DRI" "3" 
 edit: also everything works fine on the main monitor which is my laptop screen which probably uses the integrated graphics
    submitted by    /u/Akira-Arch  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When to Replace Your Old Computer or Laptop]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=797303</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/797303/when-to-replace-your-old-computer-or-laptop/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T18:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We all have an old computer or laptop laying around that we just can’t let go. Unfortunately, there comes a time when it’s better to upgrade to something faster and more secure. Here’s when to replace your old device.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Nguyen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My TTY shows on both of my monitors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v1w3p6/my_tty_shows_on_both_of_my_monitors/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v1w3p6/my_tty_shows_on_both_of_my_monitors/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T17:57:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do i make it so it only display on my main monitor?
    submitted by    /u/baliraptorr  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gnome buggy after installing next to kde]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v1w395/gnome_buggy_after_installing_next_to_kde/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v1w395/gnome_buggy_after_installing_next_to_kde/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T17:56:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I got an interesting problem. When I first installed gnome on my arch laptop, everything worked fine. Swiping gesture, on screen keyboard showing when I tapped on my touchscreen. But then, I wanted to install KDE parallel to gnome. KDE works fine. But now, swiping with my finger doesn't always work. Especially from the left corner to the middle to show the activities. Also, the on screen keyboard doesn't deploy anymore when I tap with my finger on a textfield. Even when I uninstall arch, these problems persist. Any ideas how to fix this?
    submitted by    /u/Relon928  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Costa Rica’s public health agency hit by Hive ransomware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/costa-rica-s-public-health-agency-hit-by-hive-ransomware/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/costa-rica-s-public-health-agency-hit-by-hive-ransomware/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T17:34:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All computer systems on the network of Costa Rica's public health service (known as Costa Rican Social Security Fund or CCCS) are now offline following a Hive ransomware attack that hit them this morning. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Gamevice Controller Turns Your iPad Into an Awesome Cloud Gaming Machine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119551/this-gamevice-controller-turns-your-ipad-into-an-awesome-cloud-gaming-machine/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119551/this-gamevice-controller-turns-your-ipad-into-an-awesome-cloud-gaming-machine/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T17:31:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you want a comically large portable game console? Well, if you own an iPad, you’re already halfway there. Gamevice just launched its iPad controller, an accessory that attaches to the sides of your iPad and is certified for Xbox Cloud Gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GIMP Keyboard Shortcuts Cheatsheet]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=cheatsheet&amp;p=440606</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15340997/gimp-keyboard-shortcuts"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T17:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GIMP (GNU Image Manipulation Program) is an open-source photo editor which is available on Windows, Mac or Linux, that boasts a huge number of features and functions that rival Photoshop. Unlike Adobe’s offering, however, GIMP is totally free to install and use, which certainly helps boost its appeal. Like you’d expect, GIMP has a large number of default keyboard shortcuts that can speed up your workflow considerably. We’ve aggregated them into a single post, so you can quickly view them at a glance.
   
   
  
Download this Cheatsheet
 Enter your email below to receive this PDF cheatsheet in your Inbox.
     
  
  
   
                   #cheatsheet-box{border:1px solid #ddd;background-color:#d9edf7;}    ... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexandra Arici</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hard disk, SSD SATA e NVMe: quali unità sono installate]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Hard-disk-SSD-SATA-e-NVMe-quali-unita-sono-installate_24589</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Hard-disk-SSD-SATA-e-NVMe-quali-unita-sono-installate_24589"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T17:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chi utilizza da tempo un PC sa riconoscere benissimo quando la macchina utilizza almeno un hard disk. I dischi fissi tradizionali utilizzano infatti più piatti in rapida rotazione: su ciascuno di essi 'volano' a una distanza di pochi nanometri le testine che si occupano della lettura e della scrittura dei dati.Quando un hard disk che era rimasto inutilizzato si avvia per cominciare un'attività di lettura o scrittura, esso entra nella fase di spin-up: i piatti vengono accelerati per essere messi in rotazione fino a raggiungere la velocità di rotazione operativa. È immediato riconoscere il rumore di un hard disk che sta effettuando lo spin-up.Nell'articolo su come riparare gli hard disk abbiamo presentato anche i rumori che vengono generalmente prodotti dalle unità che hanno qualche problema hardware.Le unità SSD essendo basate esclusivamente su memorie flash non hanno parti in movimento e non fanno rumore: in un altro articolo abbiamo visto le principali differenze tra hard disk e SSD.Nel caso di un PC desktop aprendo il case è piuttosto semplice riconoscere quali sono hard disk e quali unità SSD.Gli SSD meno performanti utilizzando la stessa interfaccia SATA (nel caso di SATA III in grado di trasferire fino a 6 Gbps) degli hard disk; le unità SSD più moderne e performanti utilizzando il bus PCI Express ormai giunto alla versione 5.0 (PCIe 5.0) in una continua escalation in termini di banda e prestazioni.Come visto nell'articolo dedicato agli SSD PCIe NVMe quelli basati su interfaccia PCIe 3.0 possono trasferire dati fino a 3.500 MB/s e 3.300 MB/s in lettura e scrittura; fino a 7.000 MB/s e 5.000 MB/s rispettivamente in lettura e scrittura con PCIe 4.0 usando schede madri con chipset e processori compatibili.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Pixel 7 Pops Up on eBay Months Ahead of Its Release]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119544/google-pixel-7-pops-up-on-ebay-months-ahead-of-its-release/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119544/google-pixel-7-pops-up-on-ebay-months-ahead-of-its-release/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T17:08:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s no secret that Google has struggled to keep leaks of its upcoming products under control, which is likely why it revealed the Pixel 7 and Pixel 7 Pro so early in May. Now, we’re seeing even more, thanks to a prototype Pixel 7 listed on eBay.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fallback to browser search when using command button]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v1uw6m/fallback_to_browser_search_when_using_command/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v1uw6m/fallback_to_browser_search_when_using_command/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T17:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi,
 Software engineer here. One thing I've always wanted in my arch distro is the ability to run a search on my browser (brave) as an option when typing into the command menu.
 Current workflow:
  
Hit command button
 List of apps pop up (using KDE)
 Start typing
 Filtered list of apps pop up
 Select app
 If nothing found, nothing appears.
  
What I would like;
  
Hit command button
 List of apps pop up (using KDE)
 Start typing
 Filtered list of apps pop up + option to "search with brave" 
 Select app or hit search 
 If nothing found, search with brave appears.
  
Wondering if any apps already exist with this functionality OR if someone can point me to the right place to write my own.
    submitted by    /u/jzia93  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What to Do When You See “AirTag Found Moving With You”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=806202</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/806202/what-to-do-when-you-see-airtag-found-moving-with-you/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T17:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you received a message that an AirTag, pair of AirPods, or unknown accessory is moving with you? Here’s what to do, how to contact the owner, and how to disable the AirTag if you suspect something isn’t right.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Is Shutting Down “Money in Excel” (and More)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=808679</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/808679/microsoft-is-shutting-down-money-in-excel-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T16:58:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft introduced ‘Money in Excel’ back in 2020, which allowed people to connect their financial data to Excel sheets. Now the functionality is being discontinued, alongside a few other Microsoft 365 features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel Announces Rialto Bridge As Ponte Vecchio Successor, Talks Up Falcon Shores & DAOS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31158</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31158"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intel is using ISC 2022 this week in Hamburg, Germany to provide an update on their Super Compute Group road-map and the efforts they are pursuing both in hardware and software for a sustainable, open HPC ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come sincronizzare iPhone col PC, senza iCloud e senza Mac]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2016/10/configurare-iphone-se-non-hai-un-mac-e.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2016/10/configurare-iphone-se-non-hai-un-mac-e.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T16:28:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Il cloud fornito da Apple su iPhone si integra alla perfezione con macOS e con le applicazioni della Apple generando un'esperienza di continuità: tutte le nostre attività possono essere iniziate da una parte e terminate sul Mac o so un altro dispositivo Apple.
Abbiamo così applicazioni come quella delle Note che si sincronizza su Mac, iCloud per mantenere file personali e fotografie, la rubrica...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NVIDIA Proprietary drivers on Wayland]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v1u48k/nvidia_proprietary_drivers_on_wayland/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v1u48k/nvidia_proprietary_drivers_on_wayland/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T16:25:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I know NVIDIA drivers are not really great on Wayland, but I still wanted to try out my (albeit shitty) Pascal MX250 dGPU in my laptop.
 I followed instructions here, here and here.
 But when I rebooted, GDM did not give me an option to use Wayland.
 P.S. I also blacklisted nouveau BTW.
 Am I doing something wrong?
    submitted by    /u/abrattic  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Marketing our privacy products while preserving privacy]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.mozilla.org/?p=69067</id>
        <link href="https://blog.mozilla.org/en/products/mozilla-vpn/marketing-our-privacy-products-while-preserving-privacy/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T16:22:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When we launched Mozilla VPN, a fast and easy-to-use VPN, it was in a market crowded by companies making promises about privacy and security and we believed our reputation for building products that help you keep your information safe would make our product stand-out. To date, tens of thousands of people have signed up to […]
The post Marketing our privacy products while preserving privacy  appeared first on The Mozilla Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jenifer Boscacci</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Is About to Kill Your Cloud Cam (And Offer a Replacement)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119536/amazon-is-about-to-kill-your-cloud-cam-and-offer-a-replacement/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119536/amazon-is-about-to-kill-your-cloud-cam-and-offer-a-replacement/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T16:18:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since its launch in 2017, the Amazon Cloud Cam has only grown more and more obscure. It was quickly superseded by Ring and Blink, and on December 2nd of 2022, the Cloud Cam will die. Thankfully, Amazon will offer you a replacement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Robot Vacuum OS Could Become the Center of Next-Gen Smart Homes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119534/this-robot-vacuum-os-could-become-the-center-of-next-gen-smart-homes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119534/this-robot-vacuum-os-could-become-the-center-of-next-gen-smart-homes/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T16:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two years ago, iRobot unveiled its AI-powered Genius Home Intelligence platform that’d help the company’s Roomba vacuums know where and when to clean. Now iRobot just revealed a powerful new software platform for its vacuum cleaners: iRobot OS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzanne Humphries</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NVIDIA 515.48.07 Linux Driver Released As Stable With Open Kernel Driver Option]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=NVIDIA-515.48.07</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=NVIDIA-515.48.07"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T16:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following the NVIDIA R515 Linux driver beta from earlier this month that was published alongside NVIDIA's open kernel driver announcement, today the NVIDIA 515.48.07 Linux driver has been released as the first R515 stable release...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make the Android Home Screen Look Like an iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=806640</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/806640/how-to-make-the-android-home-screen-look-like-iphone/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T16:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The most noticeable difference between the iPhone and Android is the home screen. While Android home screens can look wildly unique, the iconic iOS home screen is very distinct. We’ll show you how to get that look on Android.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeLorean Alpha5 EV Revealed with Gull-Wing Doors and 300-Mile Range]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119515/delorean-alpha5-ev-revealed-with-gull-wing-doors-and-300-mile-range/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119515/delorean-alpha5-ev-revealed-with-gull-wing-doors-and-300-mile-range/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T15:49:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After several months of teasing a new electric vehicle, the DeLorean Motor Company has officially unveiled its first EV, the DeLorean Alpha5. It’s an exciting new luxury sportscar coupe with impressive specs to match the stylish design.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New XLoader botnet uses probability theory to hide its servers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-xloader-botnet-uses-probability-theory-to-hide-its-servers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-xloader-botnet-uses-probability-theory-to-hide-its-servers/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T15:45:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat analysts have spotted a new version of the XLoader botnet malware that uses probability theory to hide its command and control servers, making it difficult to disrupt the malware's operation. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leaving the Android 13 Beta May Brick Your Pixel Phone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119510/leaving-the-android-13-beta-may-brick-your-pixel-phone/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119510/leaving-the-android-13-beta-may-brick-your-pixel-phone/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T15:38:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You should never install an unstable beta OS on your main smartphone. And if you’re wondering why that’s the case, take a stroll through the Android Beta forum on Reddit. A shocking number of users report that their Pixel phone “bricked” after trying to downgrade from the buggy Android 13 Beta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[laggy nvidia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v1ssr8/laggy_nvidia/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v1ssr8/laggy_nvidia/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T15:25:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[when i switch to nvidia from optimus manager everything becomes laggy it looks like it is running on less fps ,i also checked in the display settings and it looks the same whether i keep it on 144hz or 60hz. I looks so smooooooooooooth on integrated im sad someone help me
 ​
 ​
 EDIT : It's still crazy smooth when im in game , i using xfce btw
 EDIT2: Fixed, spammed the display settings (60 hz/120hz/144hz) few times and it worked
    submitted by    /u/Character-Figure8004  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Change Margins on Google Docs]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=post-ideas&amp;p=473512</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15340729/change-margins-google-docs"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Docs has become the go-to word processor for many individuals and businesses because of the versatility and sharing capabilities it offers. Unfortunately, some tasks like changing margin settings, can be difficult to figure out at first. Luckily, this guide can help you learn the various ways to adjust document margins in Google Docs without searching for the right setting for hours.
   

Content

Use the Ruler to Adjust Margins in Google Docs
Use Page Setup to Set Custom Margins
How to Set 1-Inch Margins in Google Docs
How to Fix Default Margins in Google Docs 
How to Change Google Doc Margins on Mobile 
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Efficiently Share or Send Google Docs via Email
    
Use the Ruler to Adjust Margins in Google Docs
    
The easiest way to adjust margins in Google... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Megan Glosson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Touchpad tap to click doesn't work]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v1sdem/touchpad_tap_to_click_doesnt_work/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v1sdem/touchpad_tap_to_click_doesnt_work/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T15:05:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am trying to use Cutefish DE. The settings has an option for tap to click but that turns off on its own. Tap to click works fine on GNOME/KDE. I have both xf86-input-synaptics and xf86-input-libinput installed
    submitted by    /u/saikrishnav333  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[9 Project & Task Management Tools for Project Managers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/?p=26331</id>
        <link href="https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/project-task-management-tools/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T15:01:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you find it difficult to manage your team and projects or find difficulty in keeping them at top productivity levels, then a project management tool is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh KS</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Currency Exchange Rates in Microsoft Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=804797</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/804797/currency-exchange-rates-excel/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T15:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you use Microsoft Excel for financial data where exchange rates are part of what you need, check out the Currencies data type. This gives you various exchange details that you can include in your spreadsheet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare è un intermediario: l'azienda non è responsabile dell'uso dei suoi servizi]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Cloudflare-e-un-intermediario-l-azienda-non-e-responsabile-dell-uso-dei-suoi-servizi_24588</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Cloudflare-e-un-intermediario-l-azienda-non-e-responsabile-dell-uso-dei-suoi-servizi_24588"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T14:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare è un'azienda statunitense i cui servizi sono utilizzati da milioni di siti Web in tutto il mondo. Oltre a mettere a disposizione dei clienti CDN e servizi DNS per la risoluzione dei nomi a dominio, Cloudflare offre strumenti per velocizzare le pagine Web riducendo significativamente il carico di lavoro dei server Web grazie a sistemi di caching intelligenti. Per proteggere le applicazioni da varie tipologie di attacchi informatici, Cloudflare ha presentato anche un suo Web Application Firewall, disponibile in versione gratuita. La platea di siti Web cui Cloudflare si rivolge è quindi universale.La società di produzione cinematografica italiana Medusa Film aveva accusato Cloudflare di non verificare in che modo i suoi servizi venissero utilizzati.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[arch won't boot unless external drive is connected.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v1rv2u/arch_wont_boot_unless_external_drive_is_connected/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v1rv2u/arch_wont_boot_unless_external_drive_is_connected/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T14:43:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[i'm sure i probably changed a flag some where, but this morning i had my external drive unplugged and arch wouldn't boot. plugged it back in and it booted fine. i don't have arch installed on that at all. is there a way to make it so i don't need the external drive plugged in to boot into this install? i'm sure when i was messing with plex media server, i messed something up.
    submitted by    /u/KageOG  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Petition to add GitHub Sponsors as a way to donate to Arch Linux project]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v1rlnh/petition_to_add_github_sponsors_as_a_way_to/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v1rlnh/petition_to_add_github_sponsors_as_a_way_to/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T14:30:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the title says, is there any possibilities for Arch devs to start GitHub Sponsors?
 Background: here in Japan it's impossible to donate via PayPal(it doesn't accept donations from Japan), and using credit card is generally comes with concern of potential risk.
 GitHub Sponsors lets me donate OSS projects periodically, and easily. It's also widely used rn(afaik). 
 So could I ask Arch Linux project for opportunity of starting GitHub Sponsors? Thanks.
    submitted by    /u/motorailgun  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chromebooks Might Get Google Pixel-Style Adaptive Charging]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=808551</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/808551/chromebooks-might-get-google-pixel-style-adaptive-charging/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T14:30:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many phones and tablets have some version of adaptive charging or optimized charging, which limits the maximum charge to improve battery health. Now that functionality might be coming to some of the best Chromebooks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Usare la tavoletta grafica per firmare documenti e PDF]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/05/usare-la-tavoletta-grafica-per-firmare.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/05/usare-la-tavoletta-grafica-per-firmare.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T14:28:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In ufficio si ricevono sempre più spesso documenti digitali su cui è necessario apporre la firma elettronica e non sempre è possibile utilizzare il mouse o il touchpad del computer per disegnare con precisione la propria firma, a meno di non voler disegnare uno scarabocchio! Senza dover scomodare le firme digitali (che sfruttano tutt'altro meccanismo per l'autenticazione) possiamo attrezzare la...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monoprice Harmony Capsule 200 Bluetooth Speaker Review: A Middled Budget Buy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118678/monoprice-harmony-capsule-200-bluetooth-speaker-review/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118678/monoprice-harmony-capsule-200-bluetooth-speaker-review/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T14:24:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Monoprice Harmony Capsule 200 is a decent budget speaker with a sturdy body suitable for indoor and outdoor environments. But while this speaker is certainly well-built and accessible, it lacks the sound quality necessary to be worth the price tag. Consider picking this one up on sale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chazz Mair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aligning Your Password Policy enforcement with NIST Guidelines]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/aligning-your-password-policy-enforcement-with-nist-guidelines/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/aligning-your-password-policy-enforcement-with-nist-guidelines/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T14:06:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Although most organizations are not required by law to comply with NIST standards, it is usually in an organization's best interest to follow NIST's cybersecurity standards. This is especially true for NIST's password guidelines. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sponsored by Specops</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Android Phones of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=734936</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/734936/best-android-phones/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the great things about Android phones is how many models there are to choose from. That can also be overwhelming, as it can be hard to choose the right one for your loved one this holiday season. We’re here to help!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GNOME's Mutter Moving Closer To Pure Wayland-Only Build Option]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=GNOME-Mutter-Prep-X11-Free</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=GNOME-Mutter-Prep-X11-Free"/>
        <updated>2022-05-31T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GNOME's Mutter compositor has been going through some code restructuring and preparations for being able to build it without any X11 dependencies at all, for those wanting a legacy-free/X11-free GNOME desktop experience that would also forego any XWayland support...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>