<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-05-30T01:58:45.637Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Just installed arch - installation and first impressions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0mlqr/just_installed_arch_installation_and_first/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0mlqr/just_installed_arch_installation_and_first/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T23:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been a Debian user for a long time, and just tried arch for the first time. I'm still happy with Debian but I got gifted an old laptop and wanted to try something different on it. Also I had trouble getting android studio and flutter to work on Debian (although others seem to have no problem) and I thought it would be nice to have a Linux system that could run newer programs and systems without issue. 
 I've been loyal to Debian because I love the stability, being able to sit down to a system that just always works and not having to do too much maintenance. Which is probably not good for switching Arch, but I figured why not, since so many seem to enjoy it. Some people say Arch breaks and needs maintenance, others say it's very stable and they only update it once every few weeks. I'm …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel Media Driver Adding Vulkan Video Acceleration Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-Media-Driver-Vulkan</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-Media-Driver-Vulkan"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T22:55:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While Intel has long supported GPU-based video decode acceleration on Linux using the Video Acceleration API (VA-API) and more recently via oneVPL under their oneAPI umbrella, with their Intel Media Driver stack they have begun offering support for video decoding using the cross-platform video acceleration extensions to the Vulkan API...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apparently I don't have space on a 1TB drive despite having done nothing...]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0loeq/apparently_i_dont_have_space_on_a_1tb_drive/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0loeq/apparently_i_dont_have_space_on_a_1tb_drive/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T22:10:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just installed arch, and now my main partition is apparently full, sans 400mb. This makes no goddamn sense.The closest thing ive got is that when I was partitioning this SSD, the logs for the size of what was going to be swap (didnt keep the swap) stayed when I made /dev/sda2 the root partition (which gnome disks lists as its actual size). Can't install or do shit with the system reading stuff like this.Any ideas on how to fix this? 
 SOLVED: Ran [ resize2fs -f /dev/sda2 ] as root, it resized the ext4 filesystem on sda2 to fill the partition.
    submitted by    /u/CrazyIronMyth  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come togliere gli elementi in evidenza dalla barra di ricerca di Windows 10]]></title>
        <id>3588|20220530000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/windows-10/come-togliere-elementi-evidenza-barra-ricerca-windows-10-3588"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chi utilizza le versioni più aggiornate di Windows 10, potrebbe aver visto comparire nella sua barra di ricerca delle strane icone e cliccandoci sopra ci sono delle informazioni aggiuntive, che cambiano sempre, e usano Bing per essere visualizzate.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PC suddenly reboots during VM configuration in KVM/QEMU]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0lfyb/pc_suddenly_reboots_during_vm_configuration_in/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0lfyb/pc_suddenly_reboots_during_vm_configuration_in/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T21:58:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm following this guide to passthrough my GPU to VM, but when I get to the part where I pass the SSD, my host system freezes for a second and reboots. For reference, I'm running the zen-kernel on Gnome.
 Specs: i7-8700, 2x16GB RAM, 512GB SATA, 1TB NVMe.
    submitted by    /u/AlpinDale  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethernet doesnt work after done installing and dhcpcd command doesnt work]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0l6bu/ethernet_doesnt_work_after_done_installing_and/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0l6bu/ethernet_doesnt_work_after_done_installing_and/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T21:45:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My ethernet isnt working, i just finished installing and i already took the installation usb off, tried the dhcpcd things and it didnt work because it results in not found.
    submitted by    /u/allmynamesweretaken1  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Encrypted system doesn't boot up when remotely unlocking]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0l2bn/encrypted_system_doesnt_boot_up_when_remotely/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0l2bn/encrypted_system_doesnt_boot_up_when_remotely/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T21:39:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently updated my system after a few weeks of not updating and rebooted. I get this message when I enter the decryption key into tinyssh.
  ~ > ssh root@10.0.10.3 Enter passphrase for /dev/sda1: cryptsetup(209): Function not implemented cryptsetup: no process found Connection to 10.0.10.3 closed. 
 I can still ping the server, but then I end up not being able to SSH into the system and it seemingly hangs endlessly.
 Whereas usually I encounter on a successful bootup:
  ~ > ssh root@10.0.10.3 Enter passphrase for /dev/sda1: Connection to 10.0.10.3 closed. 
 I can still manually decrypt the LUKS container, mount the LVM volume, and interact with files if I boot into a microSD card instead of trying a remote unlock. I'm using the LVM on LUKS setup described on the Arch Wiki. fsck reports clean drives as well. What could be going on?
    submitted by    /u/nasdack  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add Dark Mode to Google Chrome]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=330529</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15336440/add-dark-mode-google-chrome"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Chrome is by far the world’s most popular web browser. But with that, users have grown to have certain expectations. One of those is a dark mode. The idea of dark mode is that it makes the screen easier on your eyes in a low- or no-light setting. Of course, there are still some questions about the extent to which dark themes are really better for your eyes, but it’s certainly useful in certain circumstances.
    
There are a few different ways to enable dark mode in Chrome, though weirdly it’s not quite as simple and obvious as it should be. Here’s how to do it.
   

Content

Enable Chrome Dark Mode in Desktop
Enable Chrome Dark Mode in Flags
Enable Chrome Dark Mode on iOS
Enable Chrome Dark Mode on Android
Use Third-Party Dark Mode Extension

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}    
Enable Chrome Dark Mode in Desktop
    
Whether you’re using Windows or macOS, the simplest – though not most effective – way of enabling dark mode in Google Chrome is to do it through your desktop.... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Zak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is the Best VPN Protocol? OpenVPN vs. WireGuard vs. SSTP and More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=770807</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/770807/what-is-the-best-vpn-protocol-openvpn-vs-wireguard-vs-sstp-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are multiple VPN protocols, and which protocol a VPN uses has a big influence on how it functions. Some protocols are a lot better than others. Thankfully, finding the best VPN protocol is easy as there are only a few candidates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fergus O'Sullivan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[i8kutils is broken]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0jmy0/i8kutils_is_broken/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0jmy0/i8kutils_is_broken/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T20:26:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I noticed my fan wasn't running at the right speed after updating the kernel. i8kfan was giving can't open /proc/i8k: No such file or directory. According to the kernel documentation, for /proc/i8k to exist, the kernel must be compiled with the CONFIG_I8K. And, here's the diff for the 5.18 kernel. CONFIG_IK8 has gone. Why? Is there a fix? Is i8kutils just dead?
    submitted by    /u/-LeopardShark-  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Barnes & Noble Releases an eReader with Actual Freaking Buttons]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119393/barnes-and-noble-releases-an-ereader-with-actual-freaking-buttons/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119393/barnes-and-noble-releases-an-ereader-with-actual-freaking-buttons/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T20:04:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bookseller giant Barnes & Noble just released its newest Nook eReader, the Nook GlowLight 4e, and it’s looking to be an excellent competitor for Amazon’s Kindle eReaders. It’s an exciting entry into the often slow-moving world of eReaders, and packs some highly-desired features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzanne Humphries</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to See Your Android Phone’s Processor and Speed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=773050</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/773050/how-to-see-your-android-phones-processor-and-speed/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some people like to know what’s powering the device in their pocket, others simply forgot the specs. Whatever the case may be, we’ll show you how to see the processor in your Android phone—and how fast it is.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cross compiling Gentoo from Arch for Raspberry Pi.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0iokh/cross_compiling_gentoo_from_arch_for_raspberry_pi/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0iokh/cross_compiling_gentoo_from_arch_for_raspberry_pi/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T19:39:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been trying to get a Gentoo system up, and running; but, have been running into issues getting it to boot properly. Previously, I installed Raspbian on the Pi, created a partition for Gentoo, and tried to build and bootstrap from there. For some reason the kernel is not able to load the Gentoo root partition.
 So, I think it would be faster and easier to just build a kernel from my Arch machine for the Pi. My Gentoo machine won't be up for a couple of weeks, and I'd like to get this working sooner. So, how can I compile the Raspberry Pi kernel from Arch? How should I go about configuring QEMU?
    submitted by    /u/Zara629  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best cheap laptops for running archlinux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0i9km/best_cheap_laptops_for_running_archlinux/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0i9km/best_cheap_laptops_for_running_archlinux/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T19:19:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, I'm a guy from Argentina and computers here are expensive af, could you guys suggest good laptops for running arch as main OS? 
 EDIT: I use DWM and no other heavy programs
 Thank you in advance
    submitted by    /u/Outzide_  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Restart a MacBook Pro]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=807426</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/807426/how-to-restart-a-macbook-pro/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T19:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re troubleshooting minor issues with a MacBook Pro, it can help to restart (reboot) your computer. This will reload macOS and give you a fresh start without affecting any of your documents or data. Here’s how to do it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wifi driver does not work after 5.18 update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0guah/wifi_driver_does_not_work_after_518_update/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0guah/wifi_driver_does_not_work_after_518_update/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T18:08:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[rtw88_8821ce does not work well at all so i had to install rtl8821ce-dkms-git from aur repository. but the dkms fails to build in the new update and i'm stuck with rtw88_8821ce. 
 i reverted back to linux-5.17.7 and rtl8821ce is working fine. Just wondering if anyone else bumped into the same issue.
    submitted by    /u/Ashik80  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How You Can Get Banned as a Twitch Viewer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=803608</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/803608/how-you-can-get-banned-as-a-twitch-viewer/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T18:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Love watching and chatting with your favorite streamers on Twitch? Well, if you’re not careful, you may receive a temporary or permanent ban from a streamer’s channel. Here’s what it takes to get banned as a viewer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Nguyen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla's Latest App Update Now Shows Recalls for Your Vehicle]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119396/teslas-latest-app-update-now-shows-recalls-for-your-vehicle/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119396/teslas-latest-app-update-now-shows-recalls-for-your-vehicle/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla is continuously updating its vehicles with changes or new features, and the same applies to the mobile app. The company recently updated its mobile app (Android/iOS) to version 4.9, and it now shows all recalls for the connected vehicle.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[PKGBUILD] How do I make Pacman stop asking for providers and instead just use the one specified in the PKGBUILD]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0gnop/pkgbuild_how_do_i_make_pacman_stop_asking_for/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0gnop/pkgbuild_how_do_i_make_pacman_stop_asking_for/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T17:59:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OK, so I've just created a gaming meta-package. One of its dependencies is lib32-pipewire-jack, because my system will use Pipewire. However, when I try and install it Pacman still asks me:
 :: There are 2 providers available for lib32-jack: :: Repository multilib 1) lib32-jack2 2) lib32-pipewire-jack Enter a number (default=1): 
 It's a problem, because one can easily hit enter by accident and install lib32-jack2 instead. (Well actually you can't because Pacman throws an error saying lib32-jack2 and lib32-pipewire-jack are in conflict). How can I force my package to install lib32-pipewire-jack instead of asking for a lib32-jack provider?
    submitted by    /u/dankcuddlybear-v2-0  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can I Use an arch .config to Compile a Xubuntu 22.04 Kernel?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0fjm0/can_i_use_an_arch_config_to_compile_a_xubuntu/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0fjm0/can_i_use_an_arch_config_to_compile_a_xubuntu/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T17:04:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have a Pocket 3 N6000, which has no sound in any linux unless patched by this:
 https://github.com/thesofproject/linux/issues/3393
 My various attempts at compiling have failed for fewer and fewer reasons that I can grasp, and I don't know arch at all.
 But this arch .config: https://aur.archlinux.org/cgit/aur.git/tree/config?h=linux-p3-patch
 apparently works. Can I use that .config in xubuntu?
 Many thanks for any help, Jake
    submitted by    /u/jakfish  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fix “Page Fault in Nonpaged Area” on Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=807269</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/807269/how-to-fix-page-fault-in-nonpaged-area-on-windows/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some Blue Screens of Death (BSODs) are difficult or impossible to diagnose and fix, whereas others are pretty straightforward. Luckily, a Page Fault BSOD is often fixable. Here are some things you can try.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Lewis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EnemyBot malware adds exploits for critical VMware, F5 BIG-IP flaws]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/enemybot-malware-adds-exploits-for-critical-vmware-f5-big-ip-flaws/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/enemybot-malware-adds-exploits-for-critical-vmware-f5-big-ip-flaws/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T16:39:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EnemyBot, a botnet based on code from multiple malware pieces, is expanding its reach by quickly adding exploits for recently disclosed critical vulnerabilities in web servers, content management systems, IoT, and Android devices. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch Linux's Archinstall 2.5 Released With FIDO2 Support, Other Improvements]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Arch-Linux-Archinstall-2.5</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Arch-Linux-Archinstall-2.5"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T16:10:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just in time for Arch Linux's June 2022 monthly ISO refresh, Archinstall 2.5 was released today as the newest version of this text-based Arch Linux installer...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Manage Notification Grouping on iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=805354</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/805354/how-to-manage-notification-grouping-on-iphone/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T16:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[iPhone notifications can be a bit overwhelming at times. Notification Grouping is a feature that aims to help you clean things up. We’ll show you how to use it to bring some more organization to your iPhone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[11 Strategies to Find Great Deals and Save Money]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=442945</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/14960580/deal-strategy-save-money"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deal, sale, special offer, buy now, all of these phrases are words that are meant to grab our attention and click the “Buy” button. Between Amazon, Walmart+ and retail shops all around us, it’s easy to impulse buy as soon as you think something is a good deal. The reality is quite different after a few minutes of research. This article will help you out and tell you if something really is a great deal. Read on to learn whether you should jump on a low price or keep waiting.
   

Content

1. Integrate Cashback into Your Browser
2. Never Pay Full Price
3. Use a Price Comparison Tool
4. Look for Coupons First
5. Save Money with Discounted Gift Cards
6. Add Items to Your Shopping Cart and Wait
7. Follow Discount Sites/Deal-Hunters
8. Wait for Specific Times to Buy
9. Check for Veteran, Education, and Other Discounts
10. Search a Deal Website First
11. Using the Right Credit Cards
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Tee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Volkswagen's ID. Buzz Meets the 'Obi-Wan' Cast In a New Promo Video]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118969/volkswagens-id-buzz-meets-the-obi-wan-cast-in-a-new-promo-video/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118969/volkswagens-id-buzz-meets-the-obi-wan-cast-in-a-new-promo-video/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T15:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Volkswagen is joining the force with the first advertisement for its ID. Buzz EV. The short video features characters from Obi-Wan Kenobi, a new Star Wars prequel series from Disney+. Oh, and Ewan McGregor is now the brand ambassador for Volkswagen, so there’ll probably be more tie-in ads in the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mobile trojan detections rise as malware distribution level declines]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/mobile-trojan-detections-rise-as-malware-distribution-level-declines/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/mobile-trojan-detections-rise-as-malware-distribution-level-declines/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T15:15:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kaspersky's quarterly report on mobile malware distribution records a downward trend that started at the end of 2020, detecting one-third of the malicious installations reported in Q1 2021, and about 85% of those counted in Q4 2021. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Does “LTE” Mean on a Phone?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=805712</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/805712/what-does-lte-mean-on-my-phone/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T15:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Curious about the LTE symbol on your smartphone? It’s one of the many wireless standards that allow you to communicate on the go. But what does LTE mean, and how is it different from 5G?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gaurav Shukla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Confronto VPN: qual è la più veloce e la più sicura?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/05/confronto-vpn-qual-e-la-piu-veloce-e-la.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/05/confronto-vpn-qual-e-la-piu-veloce-e-la.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T14:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scegliere una VPN al giorno d'oggi è davvero molto difficile: ci sono così tanti servizi in commercio e spesso troviamo scritte e valori che non comprendiamo appieno, affidandoci quindi solo al prezzo di vendita e a pochi altri dettagli. Una VPN va scelta invece con molta cura, visto che su di essa passeranno le informazioni sulla nostra connessione e su quello che facciamo sul PC quando...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Yorker imprisoned for role in carding group behind $568M damages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-yorker-imprisoned-for-role-in-carding-group-behind-568m-damages/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-yorker-imprisoned-for-role-in-carding-group-behind-568m-damages/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Telusma, a 37-year-old man from New York, was sentenced to four years in prison for selling and using stolen and compromised credit cards on the Infraud carding portal operated by the transnational cybercrime organization with the same name. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Mice of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=732167</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/732167/the-best-mice-for-gaming-productivity-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smooth browsing, productivity shortcuts right at your fingertips, and the accuracy needed to land the perfect shot. An average computer mouse can’t do these things, but with our recommendations, your new mouse can do all of that and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Henges</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anyone having issues with nvidia?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0bp0x/anyone_having_issues_with_nvidia/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0bp0x/anyone_having_issues_with_nvidia/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T13:55:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My arch install broke after an update. Sddm refused to start, could not find display pipe.
 Made a fresh install and the same thing happend again, any broken package?
    submitted by    /u/Titoli1  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Need help Installing Arch with Systemd-boot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0bizx/need_help_installing_arch_with_systemdboot/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0bizx/need_help_installing_arch_with_systemdboot/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T13:46:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the past couple days, I've been trying to install Arch in a VM (Virt-Manager) with Systemd-boot as the bootloader with no success.
 I've successfully installed with GRUB as the bootloader but I wanted to try my hand with Systemd-boot since it comes with systemd. So I know the general steps to install Arch. That's not the problem. My problem is the bootloader part. Despite taking the steps outlined n the wiki (mount esp to /boot --> run bootctl install --> create loader.conf, arch.conf, and arch-fallback.conf --> exit chroot --> reboot), I always end up back at the EFI shell. 
 Am I missing a step or something? I've ensured that /dev/vda1 is an EFI partition, formatted to Fat32, mounted to /boot, ran bootctl sucessfully with no errors, created the necessary files. I've confirmed that initramfs-linux, initramfs-linux-fallback, and vmlinuz-linux files are where they need to be (/boot). When I reboot I get to a screen where the only option is "Return to firmware interface." 
 What I am doing wrong? Help me, Arch Gods!!!!
 UPDATE : HOLY CRAP I GOT IT!!!!
    submitted by    /u/kantoking0206  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Problem with changing the keyboard language]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0bh6u/problem_with_changing_the_keyboard_language/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v0bh6u/problem_with_changing_the_keyboard_language/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T13:43:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When playing Minecraft there is a problem with changing the keyboard language. When I change the layout the screen starts blinking, and then you get to the desktop, but I can not do anything there, everything lags, and the extensions behave strangely. This can only be fixed with alt+tab or a reboot. This is most likely caused by a window that pops up when I change the language as I use GNOME. How do I fix it?
    submitted by    /u/Reged1tFox  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything You Need for an Ergonomic Office]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/116918/everything-you-need-to-know-for-an-ergonomic-office/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/116918/everything-you-need-to-know-for-an-ergonomic-office/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T13:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s more to an ergonomic office than comfy chairs and wrist-friendly keyboards. Our mental health and stress levels are part of our cognitive ergonomic environment, too. Create a healthy work environment at home with ergonomic furniture and accessories that help reduce pain and increase focus.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melissa Nicholson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Choose an Ethernet Cable]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=795666</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/795666/how-to-choose-an-ethernet-cable/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Choosing an Ethernet cable is for the most part relatively straightforward. However, there are some things to keep in mind if you want to get the most out of your internet and local network connection.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[port 22: Connection refused]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v09u1s/port_22_connection_refused/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v09u1s/port_22_connection_refused/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T12:08:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone
 i'm having a porblem conncting to my home server on a local network and i keep getting this error
  
ssh: connect to host 192.168.178.54 port 22: Connection refused
  
i will add some info and hoping it might me helpful
 ● sshd.service - OpenSSH Daemon
 Loaded: loaded (/usr/lib/systemd/system/sshd.service; enabled; vendor preset: disabled)
 Active: active (running) since Sun 2022-05-29 13:34:49 CEST; 15min ago
 Main PID: 1912 (sshd)
 Tasks: 1 (limit: 19013)
 Memory: 1.6M
 CPU: 3ms
 CGroup: /system.slice/sshd.service
 └─1912 "sshd: /usr/bin/sshd -D [listener] 0 of 10-100 startups" 
 The result when using nmap:
 nmap -p 22 192.168.178.54
 Starting Nmap 7.92 ( https://nmap.org ) at 2022-05-29 13:58 CEST
 Nmap scan report for 192.168.178.54
 Host is up (0.00059s latency). 
 PORT S…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Ways to Game on a Low (or Zero) Budget]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=801931</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/801931/ways-to-game-on-a-budget/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T12:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you believe what you see on social media, you may think of multi-thousand-dollar, bright RGB gaming-room setups as the only “real” gaming. Save your money, and use these tips to enjoy gaming for its own sake, without the frill.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sydney Butler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Trims Hyper-V Boot Time By Minutes For Big Azure VMs With Linux 5.19]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Microsoft-Hyper-V-Linux-5.19</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Microsoft-Hyper-V-Linux-5.19"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T12:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Microsoft-contributed fix as part of their Hyper-V updates for the Linux 5.19 kernel can shave minutes off their Azure VM boot times when launching a virtual machine with numerous GPUs...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux 5.19 Allows EFI Accessing VM Secrets For Confidential Computing / AMD SEV]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-EFI-Secrets-CoCo</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-EFI-Secrets-CoCo"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T11:45:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The EFI changes for the Linux 5.19 kernel bring a few interesting changes, including the ability to access secrets injected into the boot image via Confidential Computing "CoCo" hypervisors...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No WiFi on 5.15.43-1 lts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v09dys/no_wifi_on_515431_lts/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v09dys/no_wifi_on_515431_lts/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T11:40:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WiFi stopped working after updating to 5.15.43-1 lts . Rolled back to 5.15.41-1 lts to fix the issue.
 I have an acer aspire 7 having Intel Wi-Fi 6 AX200 . 
 iwlwifi modules are loaded and ax200 is shown as detected, dmesg doesn't show any errors too. But iwd doesn't detect wlan0.
 EDIT: WiFi mysteriously started working again on 5.15.43-1, no idea what caused it.
    submitted by    /u/derangedPenguin47  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is a “Bump” On the Internet?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=765515</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/765515/what-is-a-bump-on-the-internet/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T11:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bumping can be one of the most annoying practices on the internet. If you’ve ever seen someone spam “bump” on a post for seemingly no reason, here’s why, and what they’re trying to communicate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vann Vicente</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Framework Laptop Gets ChromeOS EC Driver Support In Linux 5.19]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=ChromeOS-EC-Framework-Laptop</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=ChromeOS-EC-Framework-Laptop"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T10:18:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Chrome platform updates for Linux 5.19 bring various fixes as well as a new ChromeOS ACPI device driver, but for the most part is relatively basic. One notable addition though is the Framework Laptop now having support by cros_ec_lpcs with that modular Linux laptop making use of Google's ChromeOS embedded controller...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Distrobox 1.3 Released For Quickly & Easily Firing Up Different Distros On Your System]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Distrobox-1.3-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Distrobox-1.3-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T09:39:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new version of Distrobox was released today, the open-source system that allows quickly and easily launching different distributions from your terminal via Podman or Docker. Distrobox has been a popular option for augmenting the package selection/versions available on your system or as well for firing up faster versions of software...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dedicated AMD gpu refuses to work]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v07njo/dedicated_amd_gpu_refuses_to_work/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v07njo/dedicated_amd_gpu_refuses_to_work/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T09:33:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For a long time I have been trying to game using dedicated amd gpu but it just does now work.
 I have tried both amdgpu and radeon
 I have disabled dynamic power management for amdgpu and radeon
 If I use DRI_PRIME=1 glmark2, it stops at the first frame itself
 If I use DRI_PRIME=1 glxgears, it works, till a size of window after which it freezes, radeontop shows 100 % usage.
 Also I should have 4gb of VRAM, in windows it is a shared memory between both iGPU and dGPU, but radeontop shows 2gb of VRAM
 I dont want to go through the efforts of using propietary drivers by downgrading my xorg
 What do i do ?
    submitted by    /u/shelra  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XFS With Linux 5.19 Brings "Lots Of New Code"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-XFS</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-XFS"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T09:22:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The XFS file-system updates for the Linux 5.19 merge window are on the heavier side with this pull being described as "a big update with lots of new code" abound for this summer 2022 kernel release...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[nvme SSD boot time slowed down with linux 5.18]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v06w8h/nvme_ssd_boot_time_slowed_down_with_linux_518/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v06w8h/nvme_ssd_boot_time_slowed_down_with_linux_518/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T08:34:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After upgrading to linux-5.18 (stock kernel), nvme SSD boot time is slowed down by approximately 3 seconds compared to linux-5.17 . This happened to multiple arch installations I have.
 linux-5.18:
 793ms (kernel) + 3.851s (initrd) 
 linux-5.17:
 689ms (kernel) + 911ms (initrd) 
 The slowdown occurs when mounting the root file system.
 [* ] A start job is running for /dev/disk/bu-uuid/a62288aa-6fab-42fc-921c-59e9838b73ee (3s / 1min 30s) 
    submitted by    /u/rekaerst  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brave partners with Guardian to bring a paid VPN and Firewall to its browser]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178837</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/05/29/brave-partners-with-guardian-to-bring-a-paid-vpn-and-firewall-to-its-browser/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T08:13:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brave Software, maker of the Brave web browser for desktop and mobile operating systems, is integrating firewall and VPN functionality into its web browser. Brave 1.39 for Android includes the new functionality, […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Brave partners with Guardian to bring a paid VPN and Firewall to its browser appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PC no longer recognizes my WiFi Adapters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v02b8k/pc_no_longer_recognizes_my_wifi_adapters/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v02b8k/pc_no_longer_recognizes_my_wifi_adapters/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T03:02:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was having issues connecting to my WiFi before, but I would just repeatedly try to connect and it would work eventually. This time though, when I booted my PC, my WiFi adapter is no longer recognized by the PC. Currently I'm using USB tethering with my android phone, but anyways here's what nmcli outputs:
 nmcli device
 DEVICE TYPE STATE CONNECTION 
 enp3s0f0u1 ethernet connected Wired connection 2 
 enp9s0 ethernet unavailable -- 
 lo loopback unmanaged --
 ​
 If I recall correctly, the WiFi adapter was called wlan0, but it's no longer here. so every time I try to connect to the WiFi with nmcli I just get "Error: No Wi-Fi device found." 
 This is the WiFi adapter I'm using:
 Bus 001 Device 008: ID 0bda:c811 Realtek Semiconductor Corp. 802.11ac NIC
 I installed the corresponding WiFi drivers from the AUR a while ago when I first installed Arch:
 https://aur.archlinux.org/packages/rtl8821cu-dkms-git
 ​
 I don't think that the driver's the problem, so I can't think of a reason why the WIFI adapter would suddenly stop being recognized.
    submitted by    /u/Prizefighter-Mercury  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Failed to Load kernel modules - No boot after linux 5.18 update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v01ra7/failed_to_load_kernel_modules_no_boot_after_linux/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v01ra7/failed_to_load_kernel_modules_no_boot_after_linux/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-29T02:27:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey there!
 ​
 I updated all packages on arch, during then, kernel got updated to 5.18. After that, the system no longer loads. All I get is the dmesg buffer on the screen. When the dmesg buffer scrolls through, I noticed one message that said [FAILED] Load kernel modules. Later I chrooted into the arch install, and downgraded the linux to 5.17.9, and it works properly. Any ideas on how to fix the error?
 ​
 Thanks! 
 EDIT: Issue solved
 https://www.reddit.com/r/linux/comments/uzxvko/psa_if_you_get_kernel_panics_after_upgrading
 ​
 If u have a recent intel CPU, along with Nvidia GPU, set command line parameters of the kernel - 'ibt=off' 
 ​
    submitted by    /u/SuperSecureHuman  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A nice way to share a disk between users?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzz4cp/a_nice_way_to_share_a_disk_between_users/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzz4cp/a_nice_way_to_share_a_disk_between_users/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T23:46:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello,
 I've 2 disks on my PC:
  
1 SSD for /root and /home (ext4)
 1 HDD for backups (etx4)
 1 HDD for data and storage (NTFS) (Its legacy from when i had dual boot with windows. Wanting to reformat as ext4 or XFS).
  
And i also have 2 active users on the PC, me and my wife.
 Is there a fancy way to have que Storage HDD mounted as, let's say /home/shared? with full read/write access to both users if i formated as ext4 or XFS?
 Nowadays, being NTFS both users has full access to all files inside. But if I reformated as XFS or ext4 won't permissions, user and group create conflicts between files from one user and another? I need both users to have full permissions on all disks contents.
 PS: Also, for storage like documents, music, videos, etc in that storage disk should i use XFS, ext4? or its the same any of them?
    submitted by    /u/thalskarth_  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PulseAudio 16.0 Released With A Variety Of Improvements]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=PulseAudio-16.0</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=PulseAudio-16.0"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T23:25:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While PipeWire continues gaining traction for fulfilling the audio management roles long handled by PulseAudio, the PulseAudio project itself continues progressing and successfully evolving its mature code-base. Out this weekend is PulseAudio 16.0...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 Tools for Designing Amazing Social Media Graphics]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=447212</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15040022/design-apps-social-media-graphics"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Social media has become a key part of the marketing strategy for most companies and influencers. However, not everyone has the graphic design chops to make amazing social media graphics on their own. Luckily, there are several great online tools that can help you design graphics for your social media accounts, and many of these tools offer free versions.
   

Content

1. Desygner
2. Canva
3. Piktochart
4. PicMonkey
5. Snappa
6. QuotesCover
7. Adobe Creative Cloud Express
8. Pablo
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:6 of the Best Photo-Editing Apps for iOS
    
1. Desygner
    
Price: Free, subscription starts at $9.95
    
Desygner (Web | Android | iOS) is one of the more elegant tools for creating eye-catching social media images with relatively little effort (though if you want to dive into more detail and spend... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Megan Glosson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Turn Off Auto Brightness on Windows 10 or 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=772783</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/772783/how-to-turn-off-auto-brightness-on-windows-10-or-11/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re tired of your Windows 10 or 11 PC’s screen automatically getting brighter or dimmer, it’s easy to turn off. All it takes is a quick trip to Settings. Here’s how to do it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Software RAID drive missing in 5.18]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzvx1i/software_raid_drive_missing_in_518/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzvx1i/software_raid_drive_missing_in_518/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T20:53:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[5.18 just dropped and it isn't booting right for me. I narrowed it down to a mirrored array in my fstab that I use as a non-boot drive. It loads fine if I downgrade to 5.17. Not sure what the issue is but if I boot 5.18 with it commented out of fstab I find that /proc/mdstat doesn't even exist and I have manually load the module. Even if I do, an mdadm --detail --scan never finds it.
 So far I have tried the following:
  
Adding/removing mdadm and mdadm_udev from my HOOKS in mkinitcpio (neither were needed in the past as it's a non-boot drive)
 Adding/removing mdmon to BINARIES in mkinitcpio (again, never needed in the past)
  
Heads up for anyone running a RAID and any thoughts as to what the issue might be?
    submitted by    /u/SecretAgentKen  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will a clean install of Arch proper help with instability issues I'm having with a derivative?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzv682/will_a_clean_install_of_arch_proper_help_with/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzv682/will_a_clean_install_of_arch_proper_help_with/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T20:11:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am not asking for support for my current not-quite-Arch setup, I'm asking how much a clean install of Arch proper is going to help with general stability.
 I've been using an Arch derivative (EndeavourOS) for about a year now on my main PC, and I'm finding I'm really struggling with stability. This was the first Linux distro I really learned (aside from a brief stint with Kubuntu), so there's been a lot of experimentation, mistakes, and reconfiguration done that I've lost track of. There's a lot I really love about using an Arch-based distro, and I'm wondering if a clean install of Arch proper might help without having to look to another distro family.
 My main issue with this system is stability. It's really not good. Something minor breaks twice a week. Something major breaks twice a m…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What We're Watching: 'Primitive Technology' Gets Back to Basics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118935/what-were-watching-primitive-technology-gets-back-to-basics/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118935/what-were-watching-primitive-technology-gets-back-to-basics/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T20:04:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What if all of our modern technology was somehow rendered useless tomorrow? Most of us are dependent on electricity, supermarkets, clothing stores, and other modern conveniences, but YouTube’s Primitive Technology channel shows us how we can survive (at least in a basic way) without all of that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzanne Humphries</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 Mac Shortcuts Actions You’ll Actually Use]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=764636</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/764636/mac-shortcuts-actions-youll-actually-use/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple added the Shortcuts app to macOS Monterey in 2021, making it easy to build workflows using visual coding blocks just like you can on iPhone and iPad. While the feature still lacks the power of Automator or AppleScript, it’s still pretty useful.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft: The new Windows 11 features from Build 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-the-new-windows-11-features-from-build-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-the-new-windows-11-features-from-build-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T19:53:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During the Build 2022 developer conference, Microsoft announced a number of new features for Windows 11, including an improved Windows Subsystem for Android (WSA) and more. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mayank Parmar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wifi card gone after arch install.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzu9l3/wifi_card_gone_after_arch_install/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzu9l3/wifi_card_gone_after_arch_install/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T19:23:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After installing using archinstall for a test. My wlan0 wifi card is gone, it was there in the live iso. Help would be appreciated
    submitted by    /u/Alecccs  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Restart a MacBook Air]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=807319</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/807319/how-to-restart-a-macbook-air/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T19:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re having trouble with your MacBook Air, it’s easy to restart. A restart will completely reboot and reload the macOS operating system, clearing the system’s working memory for a fresh start. None of your data will be affected. Here are several ways to do it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[the annoying beep bug: is systemctl susped hardcoded in plasma?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uztp75/the_annoying_beep_bug_is_systemctl_susped/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uztp75/the_annoying_beep_bug_is_systemctl_susped/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T18:54:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was trying to bypass the annoying problem of the bell ringing when the PC goes into suspension. The best way would be to add --no-wall to the systemctl call but I can't find any configuration file that allows to change the command (neither in powerdevil nor in solid), while for sddm it exists... any ideas?
    submitted by    /u/guiodic76  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[with kernel 5.18.0-arch1-1's drop today, FreeSync is now enabled by default.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzt58j/with_kernel_5180arch11s_drop_today_freesync_is/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzt58j/with_kernel_5180arch11s_drop_today_freesync_is/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T18:25:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I just tested this as in the past, I've always had to have Option "VariableRefresh" "true" in my .conf file (bspwm on X11). I just removed that line after updated and found that it is, in fact, enabled by default.
    submitted by    /u/peak-shidder  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Freesync, amdgpu and linux 5.18]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzsz51/freesync_amdgpu_and_linux_518/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzsz51/freesync_amdgpu_and_linux_518/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T18:16:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The changenotes say that Freesync would be enabled by default in Linux 5.18. I thought this meant that you didn't have to set VariableRefresh in X11 amdgpu.conf file? It doesn't seem to be the case on my system. Am I mis-understanding what that change is referring to?
 EDIT:
  
FreeSync Video Mode is enabled by default in 5.18, not FreeSync as a whole.
  
Thanks!
    submitted by    /u/Xyklone  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Uniswap With MetaMask on iPhone or Android]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=802099</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/802099/how-to-use-uniswap-with-the-metamask-app-on-iphone-or-android/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T18:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using Uniswap with your MetaMask wallet is one of the easiest ways to “swap” your favorite Ethereum-based tokens in a matter of minutes. Here’s how to do it on your iPhone or Android phone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>RJ Fulton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Maps' Street View Can Now Take Your Phone Back In Time]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118977/google-maps-street-view-can-now-take-your-phone-back-in-time/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118977/google-maps-street-view-can-now-take-your-phone-back-in-time/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T18:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Can you believe it’s been 15 years since Google Street view launched? To celebrate the anniversary, Google will now let you travel back in time when using Street View in the Google Maps app. All you need to do is tap a location in Street View, select “see more dates,” and enjoy the feeling of growing old.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cannot launch VirtualBox, results in NS_ERROR_SOCKET_FAIL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzsg5u/cannot_launch_virtualbox_results_in_ns_error/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzsg5u/cannot_launch_virtualbox_results_in_ns_error/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T17:49:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, so I am trying to run virtualbox (not a VM, just the base app) and I am getting this error: NS_ERROR_SOCKET_FAIL
 I have tried everything i could, researched about this error in other forums/subreddits, still no anwser. Also deleted everything in /tmp/ folder... Here's an screenshot: https://ibb.co/qsDW7P7
 ​
 Does anyone got the same issue or is it just me? If so, can someone help me?
    submitted by    /u/DominiCzech  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[pls help, so weird]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzsc2g/pls_help_so_weird/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzsc2g/pls_help_so_weird/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T17:43:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ey guys, yesterday I left my computer on to watch a movie. After I was tired so went to sleep, but before I was going to shut down but the os wasn't responding so I pressed the button 5 sec and went to sleep. Today, no login screen was showing and I tried a few things. 
 nomodeset and the other 2 didn't do anything Ctrl alt f1 to f3 let me login but didn't accept any command Runlevel3 gave me root console, but no command works, it doesn't go past the 1st line. 
 Also, sometimes changing from f2 to f1 the login screen appears but after login just stays black and after awhile asks for login again
 What can I do? 
 https://imgur.com/a/h41ry64
    submitted by    /u/Asdrubalpraias  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Minecraft Launcher Won't Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzrrpx/minecraft_launcher_wont_launch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzrrpx/minecraft_launcher_wont_launch/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T17:14:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm new to Arch. I have a small amount of experience with Ubuntu, but other than that, I'm still trying to figure things out. 
 I was trying to install minecraft, but when I run the launcher from both terminal and desktop, nothing happens. 
 I got the launcher from https://aur.archlinux.org/packages/minecraft-launcher. I found multiple articles and videos that instructed me to run makepkg, and then run the package. I did all that, and now I'm lost as to why it isn't running. 
 Terminal seems to recognize 'minecraft-launcher' as a command, as it doesn't throw any errors, but when I run 'ps -au | grep minecraft', the only process running is my command. When I run it from the desktop, I get the spinning cursor (which I imagine means it's doing something), but then it just disappears and nothing happens.
 If someone could point me in the right direction that would be greatly appreciated.
 Thank you.
    submitted by    /u/SignificantCredit529  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I don't have muhc money to donate to Arch. So i decided to seed the Arch Iso 24/7 on my server!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzrqp3/i_dont_have_muhc_money_to_donate_to_arch_so_i/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzrqp3/i_dont_have_muhc_money_to_donate_to_arch_so_i/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T17:13:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you for making such a minimalistic Distro!
    submitted by    /u/SchwarzeFlagge  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When to Replace Your Old Monitor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=796494</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/796494/when-to-replace-your-monitor/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While it’s easy to get attached to tech you’ve used for years, a run-down monitor with poor image quality and hardware issues keeps you from experiencing the best in productivity and entertainment. Here’s how to know it’s time to upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Nguyen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rivian Releases 'Soft Sand Mode' Update Just in Time For Summer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119409/rivian-releases-soft-sand-mode-update-just-in-time-for-summer/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119409/rivian-releases-soft-sand-mode-update-just-in-time-for-summer/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T16:34:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You now have one more reason to be excited if you’re the proud owner of the Rivian R1T electric truck or are waiting for the new R1S all-electric SUV. Rivian has finally released its “soft sand” driving mode software update.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Archinstall hard drives doesn't show any.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzql0q/archinstall_hard_drives_doesnt_show_any/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzql0q/archinstall_hard_drives_doesnt_show_any/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T16:15:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It juat gives me an error: I/O error, dev sr0, sector 24512 op 0x0:(READ) flags 0x80700 phys_seg 1 prio class 0
    submitted by    /u/Eetu13  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Install Google Assistant on Samsung Galaxy Smartwatches]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=684233</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/684233/how-to-install-google-assistant-on-samsung-galaxy-smartwatches/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung Galaxy smartwatches are a great option for people with Android phones, but some of them don’t have Google Assistant. We’ll show you how to get Assistant up and running on your Samsung wearable with Wear OS or Tizen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Connect Your PS4/PS5 to a Laptop or Mac]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=post-ideas&amp;p=354429</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/13730542/connect-ps4-to-laptop-mac"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T15:25:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you have your PlayStation next to a monitor or TV, it’s convenient to hook up your console to your setup for quick and easy gaming. However, if you own something like a Mac or a laptop, you may need to do a little more legwork to play games on your screen. Let’s take a look at how you can connect PS4 or PS5 to your laptop or Mac.
   

Content

The Problem With Using a PlayStation's HDMI Cable on a Laptop or Mac
How to Play PS4/PS5 Games on a Laptop or Mac
How to Turn Off PS4/PS5 Controller
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Check for Controller Deadzones in Windows
    
The Problem With Using a PlayStation’s HDMI Cable on a Laptop or Mac
    
If you use a traditional computer and monitor setup that uses HDMI connections, plugging in a... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miguel Leiva-Gomez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ASUS Reveals an Unnecessarily Cool 500Hz Gaming Monitor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119131/asus-reveals-an-unnecessarily-cool-500hz-gaming-monitor/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119131/asus-reveals-an-unnecessarily-cool-500hz-gaming-monitor/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T15:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone knows that a higher refresh rate makes you a better gamer. That’s why ASUS and NVIDIA teamed up to build the ROG Swift 500Hz gaming monitor, something that will “benefit every game and every gamer.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clop ransomware gang is back, hits 21 victims in a single month]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/clop-ransomware-gang-is-back-hits-21-victims-in-a-single-month/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/clop-ransomware-gang-is-back-hits-21-victims-in-a-single-month/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After effectively shutting down their entire operation for several months, between November and February, the Clop ransomware is now back according to NCC Group researchers. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Edit a PDF in Google Docs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=805821</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/805821/edit-pdf-in-google-docs/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T15:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Google Docs’ editing tools, you can edit your PDF to add and remove text, images, charts, and more. It then gives you the resulting file back as a PDF. We’ll show you how to use this service for PDF editing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Store is getting a much needed boost (and ads)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178832</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/05/28/microsoft-store-is-getting-a-much-needed-boost-and-ads/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T14:54:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During Build 2022, Microsoft highlighted some of the improvements that it plans to roll out to the virtual Microsoft Store. The Store, which the company introduced in Windows 8 and refined in […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Microsoft Store is getting a much needed boost (and ads) appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch random freeze but audio keeps playing.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzoiuf/arch_random_freeze_but_audio_keeps_playing/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzoiuf/arch_random_freeze_but_audio_keeps_playing/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T14:31:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Problem:
 Arch randomly freezes after a while (1 hour or so of use). Temps are stable (CPU around 35c, GPU around 60c). When it freezes, my music keeps playing. next song also queues up and continues. However, my mouse stops moving. I cannot use numlock/cap (the light doesn't go on or off), and the mouse randomly starts moving after a while but then when i am moving it stops after few seconds. I am unable to click anything or do anything. It is as if the whole PC is frozen and the only thing thats working is audio. Only solution if i hard reset my PC, which obviously i do not like to do.
 ​
 Attempt:
 While scouting the net, i found something about Nvidia and PowerMizer. Mine was set to Auto/Adaptive. However, i saw something about putting it in Maximum Performance mode. I believe this to be the fix.
 ​
 Issue:
 My issue is, going to nvidia-settings and putting it on Maximum Performance does not stick. As soon as i reboot, its back to auto. Is there a way to make the setting stick even after a reboot?
 ​
 PC Info:
 CPU: I7 8700K
 RAM: 16GB
 GPU: RTX 2070 Super
 OS + Kernal: Arch Linux - 5.17.9-arch1-1
 DE/WM: KDE Plasma 5
 ​
 Thank you to all in advance for the help <3
 ​
 ​
 EDIT: Possible solution? Not quite sure yet. Will report back later. PC has been on for 1 hour now without a freeze.
 What i did: On KDE autostart, i added the following line: nvidia-settings -a "[gpu:0]/GpuPowerMizerMode=1"
 After rebooting, going to nvidia-settings seems to have made it stick. Thank you all for the help! I will report back here in a few hours in case nothing happens (or if something happens)
    submitted by    /u/fatalrein  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using multiple different repositories (testing and/or ALHP)?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzo3tn/using_multiple_different_repositories_testing/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzo3tn/using_multiple_different_repositories_testing/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T14:09:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I used to use the testing repositories and now switched to using the ALHP repos. And I was wondering if it's generally advised to use only one of the two, or whether it's fine, to have both in my pacman.conf.
 The idea behind it is that if one package is maybe not included in one repo pacman would then retrieve the package from the next best repo, considering all repos are in a correct order in the config file. Or does this introduce incompatibilities?
 Or doesn't it even matter, because all packages in the ALHP repos are also in the testing repos, so packages are always retrieved from the ALHP repos and never from the testing repos?
 For example I only had AHLP and default repos (core, extra, community, multilib) active and my system up-to-date and when I also activated the testing repos (kde-unstable, testing, community-testing, multilib-testing) I get updates for a few packages.
    submitted by    /u/Arjab  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How can I use iGPU on Arch (VM/Passthru)?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzo2nk/how_can_i_use_igpu_on_arch_vmpassthru/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uzo2nk/how_can_i_use_igpu_on_arch_vmpassthru/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T14:07:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arch Host Win10 Guest
 So I've managed to get PCI passthrough working for my dGPU by creating libvirt hooks that toggle me out of X before and after launching/destroying VM. This is, however, less than ideal as I wanted to use my iGPU to keep the Arch session running. No matter what I tried, it seems I am unable to use my UHD 630 (running i915) to be seen as the primary GPU for the host. I can pass through the iGPU no problem, but I cannot seem to get Arch to latch to it and reserve the dGPU for passthrough.
 dGPU is AMD. MB is MSI Gaming Pro Z390. Starting to think it's impossible simply because my firmware forces me to boot using AMD card (cannot boot with just "IGD" if card is installed).
    submitted by    /u/profile_this  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[how to remove grub in legacy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uznznl/how_to_remove_grub_in_legacy/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uznznl/how_to_remove_grub_in_legacy/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T14:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have arch and windows7 dual boot with grub on bare metal. I want to unistall grub from my device but grub doesn't have a specific partition in bios devices so when I uninstall a linux distro grub shows me errors. I want to experiment more with arch and install grub on my usb stick but I can't uninstall grub
    submitted by    /u/MoodFew956  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Windows Subsystem for Linux malware steals browser auth cookies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-windows-subsystem-for-linux-malware-steals-browser-auth-cookies/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-windows-subsystem-for-linux-malware-steals-browser-auth-cookies/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T14:01:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers are showing an increased interest in the Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSL) as an attack surface as they build new malware, the more advanced samples being suitable for espionage and downloading additional malicious modules. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Ilascu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best 4K TVs of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=754502</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/754502/best-4k-tv/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[4K TVs are more affordable now than ever before, but which model should you buy? Whether you want a set for gaming, movie watching, or just a good all-rounder, we have some recommendations to eliminate the guesswork.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Butts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>