<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-06-29T02:10:33.094Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are they doing over at protonvpn?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vn2h6v/what_are_they_doing_over_at_protonvpn/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vn2h6v/what_are_they_doing_over_at_protonvpn/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T00:41:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's like someone is actively trying to make conflicts here. Whenever I try to upgrade my system: python-protonvpn-nm-lib and protonvpn-cli are in conflict. Trying to remove either before the other doesn't work because removing protonvpn-cli breaks dependency 'protonvpn-cli' required by protonvpn and removing python-protonvpn-nm-lib breaks dependency 'python-protonvpn-nm-lib' required by protonvpn-cli.
 I'm not really looking for a solution, will probably just uninstall everything and possibly lose config. Just wanted to point out we have some sadists on the AUR.
    submitted by    /u/algebra4life  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[libldap_r-2.4.so.2 and liblber-2.4.so.2 missinh]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vn28lf/libldap_r24so2_and_liblber24so2_missinh/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vn28lf/libldap_r24so2_and_liblber24so2_missinh/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T00:29:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I overwritten some libraries and now a lot of my systems doesn't work! I already fixed the other libraries that where missing but i'm not able to find this two... I know that they are both part of openldap but reinstalling the pkg doesn't seem to help. N.B. I need to fix the system true chroot because main system pacman doesn't work without those libraries. Any help is really really welcome
    submitted by    /u/Error916  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emacs Keyboard Shortcuts]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=485185</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15399061/emacs-keyboard-shortcuts"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Emacs is a fully-featured text editor that is both powerful and extensible out of the box, without needing to install any additional packages to make it work. With Emacs, you can easily manipulate text and files by executing Lisp commands. These commands, in turn, are then bound to a series of simple keybindings which allows you to focus on what you need to do.
   
   
  
Download this Cheatsheet
 Enter your email below to receive this PDF cheatsheet in your Inbox.
     
  
  
   
                   #cheatsheet-box{border:1px solid #ddd;background-color:#d9edf7;}                 @media(min-width:576px){#cheatsheet-box{grid-template-columns:200px 1fr;}}    ... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramces Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Compiling software inside arch-nspawn chroot (without PKGBUILD)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vn21rf/compiling_software_inside_archnspawn_chroot/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vn21rf/compiling_software_inside_archnspawn_chroot/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T00:19:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm trying to compile this application for rendering Lego models and instructions, and encountering difficulties because the maintainer's build script was written for cloud-based CI services. Consequently, the PKGBUILD that is included in the repository will not work properly. I'm in the process of figuring out exactly what the scripts do so I can make a PKGBUILD that does work, but in the meantime I'd like to be able to be able to build it in a semi-isolated environment. 
 The Arch developer tools do include scripts that allow packages to be compiled within a clean chroot, but how can I spawn a chroot for building software that doesn't conform to the usual packaging standards?
    submitted by    /u/zoqaeski  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple M2 Enablement For Linux Begins With Good Progress]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Apple-M2-Linux-Starts</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Apple-M2-Linux-Starts"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T23:45:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hector Martin who has been leading the Asahi Linux effort for bringing up Linux on Apple Silicon recently received his new 2022 MacBook Pro 13-inch to begin porting Linux to Apple's new M2 SoC. While only started this week, he's already making significant progress. Fortunately, much of the existing M1-written Linux code can work for the M2 but some new drivers will need to be written before the new M2 Macs are fully usable on Linux...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thunderbird 102 Released With Big Improvements To This Leading Open-Source Mail Client]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Thunderbird-102-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Thunderbird-102-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T23:38:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After what has felt like years of neglect and little progress in advancing this open-source mail/communications client, Thunderbird 102 is out today with some shiny new features and a lot of UI refinements...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 10 KB5014666 update brings new printing features, bug fixes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-10-kb5014666-update-brings-new-printing-features-bug-fixes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-10-kb5014666-update-brings-new-printing-features-bug-fixes/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T22:37:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has released the optional KB5014666 Preview cumulative update for Windows 10 20H2, Windows 10 21H1, and Windows 10 21H2. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[502 http code with yay]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmzigm/502_http_code_with_yay/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmzigm/502_http_code_with_yay/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T22:17:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am trying to download libxft-bgra-git. When I do yay -S libxft-bgra-git. I get this error:
 [liam@Zeus ~]$ yay -S libxft-bgra-git :: Checking for conflicts... :: Checking for inner conflicts... [Aur:1] libxft-bgra-git-2.3.4.r147.42c6616-1 1 libxft-bgra-git (Installed) (Build Files Exist) ==> Packages to cleanBuild? ==> [N]one [A]ll [Ab]ort [I]nstalled [No]tInstalled or (1 2 3, 1-3, ^4) ==> N :: (1/1) Downloaded PKGBUILD: libxft-bgra-git 1 libxft-bgra-git (Installed) (Build Files Exist) ==> Diffs to show? ==> [N]one [A]ll [Ab]ort [I]nstalled [No]tInstalled or (1 2 3, 1-3, ^4) ==> N :: (1/1) Parsing SRCINFO: libxft-bgra-git ==> Making package: libxft-bgra-git 2.3.4.r147.42c6616-1 (Tue 28 Jun 2022 05:09:40 PM CDT) ==> Retrieving sources... -> Updating libxft git repo... Fetching origin remote: GitLab is not responding fatal: unable to access 'https://gitlab.freedesktop.org/xorg/lib/libxft.git/': The requested URL returned error: 502 error: could not fetch origin ==> WARNING: Failure while updating libxft git repo -> Found 1.patch ==> Validating source files with md5sums... libxft ... Skipped 1.patch ... Passed ==> Making package: libxft-bgra-git 2.3.4.r147.42c6616-1 (Tue 28 Jun 2022 05:09:41 PM CDT) ==> Checking runtime dependencies... ==> Checking buildtime dependencies... ==> Retrieving sources... -> Updating libxft git repo... 
 Can anyone help me?
    submitted by    /u/l0cky12f  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strange Wifi issue.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmzgou/strange_wifi_issue/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmzgou/strange_wifi_issue/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T22:15:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So, I've recently installed Arch Linux, and set up my Wifi using iwd/iwctl. However, after that, I installed KDE, and switched to using NetworkManager (KDE uses it by default, and it is required for accurate information in the network applet). Weirdly, my Wifi connection will randomly reset while using it, and reconnect under a different name. For example, my connection is normally "wlan0". However, it randomly disconnected me, and reconnected using "wlan1". This has happened multiple times now, and I can't find any mention of it online. What could be a possible cause of this?
    submitted by    /u/notabirb2  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Auricolari Bluetooth TWS ACEFAST T6 ENC: opinione, recensione e prova pratica]]></title>
        <id>3606|20220629000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/cuffie-9543/auricolari-bluetooth-tws-acefast-t6-enc-opinione-recensione-prova-pratica-3606"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ACEFAST è un'azienda cinese fondata nel 2020 che opera nel mercato degli accessori tech con un catalogo piuttosto ampio, che spazia dai caricatori per smartphone ai supporti per notebook, passando per gli auricolari Bluetooth. Ho avuto l'occasione di provare le nuove ACEFAST T6 ENC, cuffiette Bluetooth TWS (True Wireless Stereo) dal design coloratissimo, vendute ad un prezzo che si aggira attorno ai 50 €. Sono un buon acquisto? Vediamolo in questa recensione e prova degli auricolari Bluetooth TWS ACEFAST T6 ENC
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evilnum hackers return in new operation targeting migration orgs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/evilnum-hackers-return-in-new-operation-targeting-migration-orgs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/evilnum-hackers-return-in-new-operation-targeting-migration-orgs/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T21:49:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Evilnum hacking group is showing renewed signs of malicious activity, targeting European organizations that are involved in international migration. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to View and Manage Your TikTok Watch History]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=post-ideas&amp;p=490892</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15398873/view-manage-tiktok-watch-history"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TikTok has easily become one of the most popular social media platforms around the world. Yet, in many ways, the app is still very much in development, with new features being added constantly. One such feature is the ability to see which videos you’ve already watched, aka your TikTok Watch History. This can be an important tool for daily TikTok users, especially when you accidentally refresh your “For You” page or forget to favorite a video.
   

Content

How the TikTok Watch History Feature Works
How to Enable and View Watch History on TikTok
Clearing Your Watch History
What If I Don't Have the Watch History Feature?
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Download TikTok Videos Anywhere
    
How the TikTok Watch History Feature Works
    
TikTok launched its Watch History feature in March 2022. However, like most other features, the platform is slowly releasing it... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Megan Glosson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Firefox privacy feature strips URLs of tracking parameters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-firefox-privacy-feature-strips-urls-of-tracking-parameters/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-firefox-privacy-feature-strips-urls-of-tracking-parameters/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T21:11:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla Firefox 102 was released today with a new privacy feature that strips parameters from URLs that are used to track you around the web. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Install and Move Android Apps to the SD Card]]></title>
        <id>http://www.howtogeek.com/?p=114667</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/114667/how-to-install-android-apps-to-the-sd-card-by-default-move-almost-any-app-to-the-sd-card/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some Android phones don’t have a lot of storage, so you might run out of room for apps. If your device has an SD card slot, you can use that to expand the storage and have more room for apps. However, SD card support is more limited than it used to be.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft 365 now prevents data leaks with new session timeouts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-365-now-prevents-data-leaks-with-new-session-timeouts/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-365-now-prevents-data-leaks-with-new-session-timeouts/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T20:10:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft announced today the general availability of tenant-wide idle session timeout for Microsoft 365 web apps to protect confidential data on shared or non-company devices left unattended. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Check Your Motherboard Model Number on Your Windows PC]]></title>
        <id>http://www.howtogeek.com/?p=208420</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/208420/how-to-check-your-motherboard-model-number-on-your-windows-pc/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you need to update drivers, check hardware compatibility, or you’re just curious, it’s way easier to check your motherboard model number with these simple tricks than to crack open your case to check the board itself. Here’s how to check your motherboard model number from the comfort of your keyboard.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Fitzpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[tiling WM to use with XFCE4]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmw259/tiling_wm_to_use_with_xfce4/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmw259/tiling_wm_to_use_with_xfce4/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T19:48:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I want to use tiling wm with familiar desktop environment, what is the best option in this case? I have little to no experience with tiling wms and hardware from 2009 so I want something fast and simple that won't interfere with anything
    submitted by    /u/AkuBusshu  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[T-Mobile Is Selling Your App Activity: Here’s How to Opt Out]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=814461</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/814461/t-mobile-is-selling-your-app-activity-heres-how-to-opt-out/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T19:31:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[T-Mobile has positioned itself as a better alternative to other carriers over the past few years, but it also plays many of the same tricks as other networks, including selling user data. The network is now targeting advertisements based on app usage data, but there’s a way to opt out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get a Roku Streambar with Voice Remote for Under $100]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=387966</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/14316325/roku-streambar-streaming-media-player"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not interested in Amazon Prime but want Alexa assistance with your streaming. You can stream all of your entertainment, including movies, TV shows, music, podcasts, etc., from a Roku Streambar with Voice Remote and still have Alexa assistance. You can get a streaming media player and premium audio speaker all in one for 24% off.
    
This streaming device has an easy and quick interface with most popular channels and access to free entertainment. Stream it all in HD, 4K, and HDR with a resolution and colors that are optimized for all TVs. Everything you need to get set up is included in the box. Plug it into your TV, connect it to your home Internet, and you’re done!
   
 
   
Four internal speakers on the Roku Streambar provide Dolby Audio calibrated for full sound on your TV. Room-filling audio moves with the action in your entertainment, makes you feel like you’re in the conversations and takes you to another world through the sounds of nature. This is all thanks to advanced audio engineering in the Roku... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fix a Flickering External Screen on a Mac]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=805459</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/805459/mac-flickering-external-screen/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T19:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re using an Apple display with your MacBook or desktop Mac, things are generally flawless. However, non-Apple displays can exhibit weird behavior such as flickering, and it’s not always obvious how to fix it. There are some things you can try, though.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sydney Butler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD GPUOpen Working On A New "gpurt" Open-Source Project]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMD-GPUOpen-gpurt</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMD-GPUOpen-gpurt"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AMD's GPUOpen team quietly setup a new GitHub repository for "gpurt", presumably a new ray-tracing related software effort...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Anyone using Microsoft Edge's Collections feature?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179419</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/28/is-anyone-using-microsoft-edges-collections-feature/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T18:32:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Collections, a way to save content in Edge, is one of the features that distinguishes Microsoft Edge from Google Chrome, its main competitor. Collections work similarly to bookmarks, as the feature's main […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Is Anyone using Microsoft Edge's Collections feature? appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[help]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmu590/help/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmu590/help/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T18:28:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[the "arch-chroot /mnt" doesn't work :chroot failed to run command "/bin/bash": no such file directory . I'm trying to install on a 32 bits PC and I didn't find the solution please help me.
    submitted by    /u/archimen5024  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iwctl stuck in "Waiting for IWD to start"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmu35q/iwctl_stuck_in_waiting_for_iwd_to_start/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmu35q/iwctl_stuck_in_waiting_for_iwd_to_start/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T18:25:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Refer to title. I looked at some other posts here and the solutions there didn't work. I tried systemctl enable --now iwd but that never completes. I checked the logs with systemctl status iwd but I didn't find anything out of the ordinary except Vendor Preset is disabled. I tried looking at my /usr/lib/iwd/iwd but the whole file is in gibberish even though I have my locale set to UTF-8. I tried using leafpad to select a different encoding but every encoding there gives me gibberish. 
 All I really want to do is connect to wifi, if there is an easier way to do it please let me know
    submitted by    /u/Big_Cartographer_676  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Monitor Kubernetes Pod Logs In Real-Time With Stern]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?post_type=devops&amp;p=800723</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/devops/how-to-monitor-kubernetes-pod-logs-in-real-time-with-stern/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T18:25:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stern is an open-source tool that makes it easier to stream real-time Kubernetes logs to your terminal. You can use Stern to monitor logs from multiple containers simultaneously, giving you a combined view of activity inside Pods.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making an Arch install with the Cosmic DE so I made a Plymouth logo .]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmtt6j/making_an_arch_install_with_the_cosmic_de_so_i/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmtt6j/making_an_arch_install_with_the_cosmic_de_so_i/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T18:15:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://imgur.com/a/HHhOclJ
    submitted by    /u/P65B40  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fix: Why Isn’t Linux Detecting My Wi-Fi Adapter?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=806845</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/806845/linux-not-detecting-wi-fi-adapter/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T18:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever installed Linux on a laptop, rebooted, and found it can’t see your Wi-Fi card? It’s pretty deflating. Try these hints. One or more of them might just get it working.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKay</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The M2 MacBook Pro's Base Model Comes with a Disappointing Downgrade]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/121901/the-m2-macbook-pros-base-model-comes-with-a-disappointing-downgrade/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/121901/the-m2-macbook-pros-base-model-comes-with-a-disappointing-downgrade/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T17:57:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple’s new 13-inch MacBook Pro M2 has a lot to offer, but the entry-level model comes with a pretty disappointing downgrade. The base model with 256GB of storage has significantly slower SSD performance speeds than the previous M1 generation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ARM presenta le nuove CPU ARMv9 e le GPU con supporto per il ray-tracing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=ARM-presenta-le-nuove-CPU-ARMv9-e-le-GPU-con-supporto-per-il-ray-tracing_24718</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=ARM-presenta-le-nuove-CPU-ARMv9-e-le-GPU-con-supporto-per-il-ray-tracing_24718"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T17:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ci troviamo nel periodo durante il quale ARM è solita annunciare le novità che debutteranno da qui a un anno sotto forma di prodotti commerciali.La società britannica, che ha visto sfumare l'acquisizione da parte di NVidia e che adesso è nel mirino di una cordata di imprese capeggiata da Qualcomm, ha annunciato la nuova generazione di CPU ARMv9 basate su core Cortex-X3 e Cortex-A715. ARM ha anche annunciato un Cortex-A510 'rinnovato'.

Partendo dalla proposta più performante, il Cortex-X3 è un core focalizzato sulle prestazioni (+22% rispetto agli smartphone Android di punta basati su Cortex-X2). Secondo ARM i SoC basati su Cortex-X3 sarebbero fino al 34% più prestazionali rispetto ad esempio a un Intel Core i7 per notebook (28W).ARM fa riferimento anche a un aumento del valore IPC pari all'11% rispetto al Cortex-X2 che utilizza lo stesso processo produttivo.Non si parlato esplicitamente, in questo caso, di migliorie in fatto di efficienza energetica: l'azienda si è limitata a dire che Cortex-X3 consuma meno energia nella maggior parte dei casi rispetto al Cortex-X2.Il secondo nuovo core, Cortex-A715, raccoglie l'eredità del Cortex-A710: sarà il core 'a media potenza' in questi SoC che usano un'architettura composta da tre cluster fornendo un buon equilibrio tra potenza ed efficienza.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arm Cortex-X3 + Cortex-A715 Announced As Second-Gen Armv9 CPUs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Arm-Cortex-X3-Cortex-A715</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Arm-Cortex-X3-Cortex-A715"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T17:46:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arm today announced their second-generation Armv9 CPU designs with the Cortex-X3 and Cortex-A715. Arm also refreshed the Cortex-A510 to allow for more cores and a power reduction...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vim 9.0 Released With New Vim9 Script For 10~100x Execution Speed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Vim-9.0-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Vim-9.0-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T17:32:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vim 9.0 is out as the first major update in two years for this popular text editor. With Vim 9.0 comes the Vim9 scripting language that offers significantly better performance...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD investigates RansomHouse hack claims, theft of 450GB data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/amd-investigates-ransomhouse-hack-claims-theft-of-450gb-data/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/amd-investigates-ransomhouse-hack-claims-theft-of-450gb-data/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T17:18:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chip manufacturer AMD says they are investigating a cyberattack after threat actors claimed to have stolen 450 GB of data from the company last year. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[After system upgrade X server no longer working?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmseiy/after_system_upgrade_x_server_no_longer_working/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmseiy/after_system_upgrade_x_server_no_longer_working/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T17:17:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I did a paru -Syu but in the middle of it thought it got stuck and stupidly powered off the machine. Now X server encounters fatal errors and I'm not sure what to do. The machine still works and I was able to do another paru -Syu and complete the upgrade. However, I cannot log into the GUI since lightdm can't connect to the X server. Lightdm continously failed. I reinstalled both lightdm and xorg but still run into the issue. I installed SDDM and disabled lightdm. I enabled and started SDDM and it didn't fail but the X server still won't work.
 Here is the log, can anyone offer insight into this issue:
 [ 46200.412] X.Org X Server 1.21.1.3 X Protocol Version 11, Revision 0 [ 46200.413] Current Operating System: Linux arch-pc 5.18.7-arch1-1 #1 SMP PREEMPT_DYNAMIC Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:22:01 +…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nura's New Earbuds Combine Lossless Audio with "Personalized" Sound]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/121878/nuras-new-earbuds-combine-lossless-audio-with-personalized-sound/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/121878/nuras-new-earbuds-combine-lossless-audio-with-personalized-sound/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T17:13:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nura is often lauded for its personalized sound technology, which tests your ears to automatically find optimal EQ settings. But its latest earbuds, the NuraTrue Pro, take things to a new level—they support CD-quality lossless audio.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Force Delete a Folder on Windows 10 and 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=811409</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/811409/force-delete-folder-windows/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T17:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you having trouble deleting a folder from your Windows 10 or Windows 11 PC? If so, that may be a system folder or a folder being used by other apps. We’ll show you how to successfully delete “undeletable” folders on your computer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung's Next Phone Has a Headphone Jack and Removable Battery]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/121885/samsungs-next-phone-has-a-headphone-jack-and-removable-battery/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/121885/samsungs-next-phone-has-a-headphone-jack-and-removable-battery/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T16:32:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung recently confirmed that its next smartphone announcement is coming on July 13th, where it’ll debut the rugged Galaxy XCover 6 Pro. Now, weeks ahead of the event, we’ve received new details confirming it’ll have a large removable battery and a 3.5mm headphone jack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MITRE shares this year's list of most dangerous software bugs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/mitre-shares-this-years-list-of-most-dangerous-software-bugs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/mitre-shares-this-years-list-of-most-dangerous-software-bugs/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T16:29:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MITRE shared this year's top 25 most common and dangerous weaknesses impacting software throughout the previous two calendar years. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Risolvere errore 502 Bad Gateway se un sito non si apre]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2018/10/risolvere-errore-502-bad-gateway-se-un.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2018/10/risolvere-errore-502-bad-gateway-se-un.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T16:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ogni tanto sui siti web troviamo l'errore 502 Bad Gateway: questo è un tipo di errore che si verifica tentando di visitare un sito web ed è legato alla risposta non valida data dal server che agisce da proxy e si collega poi al server web che ospita il sito e dipende, il più delle volte, dal sito stesso.

 Rispetto però la serie di errori 404 o 403, quando compare la pagina con il 502, può darsi...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Have Secret Chats With the iPhone Notes App]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=813110</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/813110/how-to-have-secret-chats-with-the-iphone-notes-app/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T16:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are plenty of messaging apps to choose from when it comes to having private conversations on the iPhone. One that you may not have expected is the good ‘ol Apple Notes app. We’ll show you how it works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[sudo -b replacement with doas]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmq8tp/sudo_b_replacement_with_doas/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmq8tp/sudo_b_replacement_with_doas/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T15:42:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone,
 I'm trying out doas to see if it could fit in my workflow. Everything runs smoothly, apart from one command that runs openconnect.
 The current command is 
 echo $PWD | sudo -b openconnect --background -u AppleseedJ -passwd-on-stdin vpn.company.com 
 I have not been able to work this one out using a mix of doas and nohup (that's why I ended up using the -b switch of sudo back when I wrote the script). The biggest constraint is that the script is run from a terminal that is then killed.
 If anyone has any pointers, I'd be happy to read them.
 ​
 Cheers
    submitted by    /u/noah_boegli  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tradurre testi in italiano nelle app Android]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Tradurre-testi-in-italiano-nelle-app-Android_24716</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Tradurre-testi-in-italiano-nelle-app-Android_24716"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T15:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A meno di non essere poliglotti può capitare di trovarsi in difficoltà nel leggere quanto riportato nelle applicazioni Android. Tante app sono in inglese e chi non è abituato a leggere spesso testi in questa o in altre lingue può realizzare di essere un po’ arrugginito per quello che riguarda la traduzione in italiano.Per tradurre testi nelle app Android, di seguito proponiamo tre possibili soluzioni: le prime due si basano sull'utilizzo di applicazioni sviluppate da Google, la terza fa leva su un'applicazione di terze parti davvero utile e semplice da usare.
Android: tradurre testi in italiano con Google Traduttore
 L'app gratuita Google Traduttore si è da tempo arricchita di una comoda funzionalità chiamata Tocca per tradurre: essa consente di visualizzare una piccola 'bolla' sopra le altre app e di tradurre in italiano i testi presenti in qualunque app che ne consenta la selezione.Per utilizzare lo strumento basta installare il traduttore Google, fare clic sull'icona in alto a destra, scegliere Impostazioni quindi Tocca per tradurre.

A questo punto si devono attivare le opzioni Tocca per tradurre e Mostra icona floating.

L'icona di Google Translate compare sullo schermo: a questo punto si può aprire l'app Android di proprio interesse quindi selezionare il testo e scegliere Copia.

Toccando la 'bolla' del traduttore Google, si può incollare il testo copiato dall'app Android e ottenere immediatamente la traduzione in italiano.

Una volta conclusa l'operazione di traduzione, la 'bolla' di Google Translate può essere disattivata dall'area delle notifiche di Android.L'unico problema, nel caso della soluzione basata su Google Translate, è che l'app Android deve consentire la selezione del testo da tradurre.
Tradurre testi dagli screenshot delle app con Google Lens
 Una soluzione alternativa per ottenere la traduzione in italiano di un testo scritto in un'altra lingua consiste nel creare uno screenshot del contenuto dell'app Android: di solito è possibile farlo premendo Volume giù+tasto accensione.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Atari Launches Two Working 2600 Cartridges for Its 50th Anniversary]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/121866/atari-launches-two-working-2600-cartridges-for-its-50th-anniversary/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/121866/atari-launches-two-working-2600-cartridges-for-its-50th-anniversary/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T15:38:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s been 50 years since Atari sprang to life and kicked off the never-ending video game craze. And to celebrate that anniversary, we’re getting two new limited-edition Atari 2600 cartridges—Missile Command and Adventure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ford Issues F-150 Lightning Recall Over Tire Safety Issue]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/121869/ford-issues-f-150-lightning-recall-over-tire-safety-issue/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/121869/ford-issues-f-150-lightning-recall-over-tire-safety-issue/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T15:38:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to Ford, the new F-150 Lightning electric truck is facing its first recall, and the company has issued a software recall for thousands of vehicles over a tire safety software issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New ZuoRAT malware targets SOHO routers in North America, Europe]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-zuorat-malware-targets-soho-routers-in-north-america-europe/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-zuorat-malware-targets-soho-routers-in-north-america-europe/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T15:33:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A newly discovered multistage remote access trojan (RAT) dubbed ZuoRAT has been used to target remote workers via small office/home office (SOHO) routers across North America and Europe undetected since 2020. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your Roku Now Has Free Local News Channels Built-In]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=814396</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/814396/your-roku-now-has-free-local-news-channels-built-in/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T15:28:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roku streaming devices and TVs have offered free movies, TV shows, and “live” channels for a while now through the pre-installed Roku Channel. Starting today, the Roku Channel now has local news stations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Beautiful Beamer Slides with Emacs]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=477245</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15398417/create-beautiful-beamer-slides-with-emacs"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Emacs is a highly versatile program. Aside from being a text editor, it can be your email client, news reader and even your finances tracker. This is because you can easily adapt Emacs to any purpose and situation. 
    
Beamer is a LaTeX module that allows you to create presentation slides in a similar manner to creating LaTeX documents. Here we will show you how to use it to create presentations inside Emacs.
   

Content

How does Beamer work?
Using Beamer in Emacs
Creating a Basic Presentation in Emacs
Adding Bullets and Symbols to Slides
Adding Images to Slides in Emacs
Adding Tables to Slides in Emacs
Changing the Default Beamer Theme in Emacs
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:5 Hidden Features You Can Use to Improve Emacs
    
How does Beamer work?
   ... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramces Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[User specific daemons?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmpoan/user_specific_daemons/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmpoan/user_specific_daemons/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T15:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I wanted my friking mute button to work and so I installed acpid - and along with some other things configured the mute button. The issue I faced many times is that user specific utilities - notify-send/amixer need to be run with a su <user> -c prefix. I am wondering if this is the actuall way to do it? How does a program know what user I am - for example alsamixer?
    submitted by    /u/Narrow_Farmer_6018  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Time-Saving Google Docs Features You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=810442</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/810442/time-saving-google-docs-features/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T15:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you have a dozen tasks to do before lunchtime, any shortcut to speed things up is welcome. Here are several time-saving features for Google Docs that can help make creating and editing documents go quicker.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New in Mozilla Thunderbird 102]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=814358</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/814358/whats-new-in-mozilla-thunderbird-102/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T14:48:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla Thunderbird is having a resurgence right now, armed with an expanded team of developers and a plan to take over the email world (including Android). The first of several planned updates, Thunderbird 102, is about to start rolling out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FBI: Stolen PII and deepfakes used to apply for remote tech jobs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fbi-stolen-pii-and-deepfakes-used-to-apply-for-remote-tech-jobs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fbi-stolen-pii-and-deepfakes-used-to-apply-for-remote-tech-jobs/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T14:41:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) warns of an increase in complaints that cybercriminals are using Americans' stolen Personally Identifiable Information (PII) and deepfakes to apply for remote work positions. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Miglior processore Intel del momento]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/06/miglior-processore-intel-del-momento.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/06/miglior-processore-intel-del-momento.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T14:41:00.006Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I processori Intel sono senza ombra di dubbio i più potenti e i più richiesti sulle configurazioni PC domestici e per l'utilizzo sui computer da ufficio, ma pochissimi utenti sono in grado di capire se il processore Intel che si trovano davanti è un modello di nuova generazione o un modello vecchio, venduto magari a prezzo di saldo proprio perché uscito fuori supporto. Questo errore deve essere...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roku Now Offers Free Local Channels]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/121861/roku-now-offers-free-local-channels/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/121861/roku-now-offers-free-local-channels/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T14:39:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ever-expanding Roku Channel is about to gain eight local news stations, courtesy of NBCUniversal. These stations provide news coverage in “major U.S. markets” like NYC and LA, though they will be available to all Roku users regardless of their location.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Quickly Switch Kubernetes Contexts With Kubectx and Kubens]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?post_type=devops&amp;p=800736</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/devops/how-to-quickly-switch-kubernetes-contexts-with-kubectx-and-kubens/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T14:24:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kubectx and Kubens are two tools which accelerate your Kubernetes management experience. They address some of the shortcomings of Kubectl by making it quicker and more convenient to switch between cluster environments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Editing file content with pacman hook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmogni/editing_file_content_with_pacman_hook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmogni/editing_file_content_with_pacman_hook/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T14:23:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi,
 I'm trying to create simple pacman hook to clear file contents, for now I have: 
 [Trigger] Operation = Install Operation = Upgrade Operation = Remove Type = Package Target = * [Action] Description = Clear update list file When = PostTransaction Exec = /bin/bash -c '> /tmp/packages_to_update.txt' 
 After system update I get that /tmp/packages_to_update.txt can't be accessed.
 I read that pacman hooks is run by current user, and /tmp should be accessible by anyone. Am I missing something?
    submitted by    /u/silverweaver  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trying to Rust-ify my system as much as possible. Is installing a new shell and a new terminal easy?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmoeph/trying_to_rustify_my_system_as_much_as_possible/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmoeph/trying_to_rustify_my_system_as_much_as_possible/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T14:20:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is it literally just "install mynewshell" "uninstall bash".
 "install alacritty" "uninstall xfce terminal"
 Someone mentioned that "coreutils" has been rewritten in Rust, but "coreutils" is a scary word and "uninstall coreutils" sounds like "bye bye system and all my data".
 Thanks for your help!
    submitted by    /u/Remarkable-River-300  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[App coding: quali le migliori per imparare a sviluppare]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=App-coding-quali-le-migliori-per-imparare-a-sviluppare_24715</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=App-coding-quali-le-migliori-per-imparare-a-sviluppare_24715"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T14:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Un tempo imparare i rudimenti della programmazione era quasi indispensabile. Per sfruttare il potenziale di un elaboratore informatico e adattarne il funzionamento alle proprie necessità era necessario scrivere codice.Come racconta Steve Wozniak, cofondatore di un tempo, i sistemi di maggior successo di una volta erano così attraenti perché sollecitavano subito l'interesse dell'utente che era portato a sviluppare i suoi programmi con la possibilità di comunicare direttamente con l'hardware.Oggi sono disponibili strumenti e servizi che vengono incontro ad ogni possibile esigenza: essi solevano gli utenti dalla necessità di scrivere codice. Esistono anche nuovi strumenti basati sull'intelligenza artificiale che permettono di generare codice funzionante nei vari linguaggi di programmazione scrivendo semplicemente il nome di una funzione o descrivendo ciò che si vuole ottenere: GitHub Copilot e Amazon CodeWhisperer.Non c'è nulla di male: questi strumenti aiutano a concludere più velocemente lo sviluppo di un progetto dispensando il programmatore dallo scrivere codice di base o comunque che si ripete di frequente nei vari progetti.Sviluppare è un'attività stimolante che richiede una dose di logica e di creatività.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking Down the Zola Hack and Why Password Reuse is so Dangerous]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/breaking-down-the-zola-hack-and-why-password-reuse-is-so-dangerous/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/breaking-down-the-zola-hack-and-why-password-reuse-is-so-dangerous/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T14:02:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In May of 2022, the wedding planning and registry site Zola suffered a major security breach due to a credential stuffing attack. due to password reuse. Here's what happened and what could have been done to prevent the attack. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sponsored by Specops</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Portable Chargers of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=770220</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/770220/best-portable-charger/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The best portable chargers and battery packs keep extra juice handy for your electronic devices when you do not have nearby access to a wall or power outlet. They can power all kinds of devices, including phones, tablets, and laptops. Here are our top picks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Prince</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LightDM failing because the X server process keeps exiting?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmnpal/lightdm_failing_because_the_x_server_process/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmnpal/lightdm_failing_because_the_x_server_process/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T13:48:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, I did something dumb, I powered my machine off in the middle of a paru -Syu because I thought it was stuck. and now when I boot up I get this error:
 [FAILED] Failed to start: Light Display Manager 
 The rest of the machine works just fine and I have full access via SSH. I was able to SSH in and redo the system upgrade and it has since been completed but it seems that when lightdm tries to start it launches X server and then the X server exits with error code 1:
 lightdm.log here:
 [+0.00s] DEBUG: Logging to /var/log/lightdm/lightdm.log [+0.00s] DEBUG: Starting Light Display Manager 1.30.0, UID=0 PID=46095 [+0.00s] DEBUG: Loading configuration dirs from /usr/share/lightdm/lightdm.conf.d [+0.00s] DEBUG: Loading configuration dirs from /usr/local/share/lightdm/lightdm.conf.d [+0.00s] DEB…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Raccoon Stealer is back with a new version to steal your passwords]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/raccoon-stealer-is-back-with-a-new-version-to-steal-your-passwords/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/raccoon-stealer-is-back-with-a-new-version-to-steal-your-passwords/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T13:39:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Raccoon Stealer malware is back with a second major version circulating on cybercrime forums, offering hackers elevated password-stealing functionality and upgraded operational capacity. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows Defender is reportedly affecting the performance of Intel CPUs, but there's a fix]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179401</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/28/windows-defender-performance-of-intel-cpus/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T13:38:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kevin Glynn, the developer of popular tools like ThrottleStop and RealTemp has discovered a bug in Windows Defender that was causing it to consume more system resources than was required. He has […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Windows Defender is reportedly affecting the performance of Intel CPUs, but there's a fix appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NVIDIA 515.57 Linux Driver Released With Fixes, NvFBC Improvements]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=NVIDIA-515.57-Linux-Driver</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=NVIDIA-515.57-Linux-Driver"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T13:20:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In addition to announcing the GeForce GTX 1630 budget card today (expect our Linux review soon), NVIDIA published 515.57 as their newest stable NVIDIA Linux driver release...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fedora 37 Gets A Batch Of New Features Approved]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Fedora-37-More-Features</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Fedora-37-More-Features"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T13:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Fedora Engineering and Steering Committee (FESCo) has approved a fresh batch of features for the next Fedora Linux distribution release...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mesa's RADV Radeon Vulkan Driver Continues Outperforming AMDVLK For RDNA2 Linux Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31245</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31245"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T13:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With last week seeing AMDVLK 2022.Q2.3 released as an update to AMD's official open-source Vulkan Linux driver and it noting performance improvements, it was time for some fresh benchmarks of that driver up against Mesa's alternative "RADV" Vulkan driver. Here are some fresh benchmarks with an AMD RDNA2 GPU for seeing how RADV continues competing -- and usually outperforming -- AMD's own official open-source driver.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malicious Messenger chatbots used to steal Facebook accounts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/malicious-messenger-chatbots-used-to-steal-facebook-accounts/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/malicious-messenger-chatbots-used-to-steal-facebook-accounts/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new phishing attack is using Facebook Messenger chatbots to impersonate the company's support team and steal credentials used to manage Facebook pages. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Whole Home Audio: Wired or Wireless?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=807110</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/807110/whole-home-audio-wired-or-wireless/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The idea of music floating through every room in your home seems fantastic, but getting there isn’t always easy. Choosing between a wired or wireless multi-room audio setup can be tricky, but we’re here to help.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kris Wouk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Velotric Discover 1 E-Bike Review: An Affordable, Comfortable Cruiser]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/121536/velotric-discover-1-e-bike-review-an-affordable-comfortable-cruiser/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/121536/velotric-discover-1-e-bike-review-an-affordable-comfortable-cruiser/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The electric bike market is getting more crowded and expensive by the day, which can be intimidating for a first-time buyer or someone looking for a good deal. So, when Velotric debuted the Discover 1 e-bike promising a premium commuter bike that’s affordable and fun for anyone, I had to take a look.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[La Truffa dello Storno]]></title>
        <id>3614|20220628144844</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/sicurezza-13/truffa-storno-3614"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T12:48:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vari istituti di credito stanno mettendo in guardia i propri clienti in merito alla nuova "truffa dello storno", l'ennesima trovata truffaldina finalizzata ad aspirare soldi dai conti correnti dei malcapitati. Vediamo di cosa si tratta
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GCC 10.4 Released With 200+ Bug Fixes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=GCC-10.4-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=GCC-10.4-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T12:38:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For those not yet on the GCC 11 or GCC 12 stable series, GCC 10.4 is out today as the latest in that older stable series...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ghacks Deals: The Learn to Code Full Stack Developer Certification Bundle]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179409</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/28/ghacks-deals-the-learn-to-code-full-stack-developer-certification-bundle/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T12:29:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Learn to Code Full Stack Developer Certification Bundle includes nine different eLearning courses that teach you programming languages and skills, such as C#, .NET Core, Microsoft SQL Server, HTML and PHP […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Ghacks Deals: The Learn to Code Full Stack Developer Certification Bundle appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ricerca una persona e le sue foto su Facebook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2014/05/come-fare-una-ricerca-su-facebook-di.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2014/05/come-fare-una-ricerca-su-facebook-di.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T12:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Facebook fornisce numerose funzioni di ricerca nascoste, che possiamo utilizzare per arrivare a trovare una persona in base ai post, ai tag e ai luoghi che ha aggiunto su Facebook, oltre a poter trovate le foto in cui è taggato.

 In questo modo possiamo cercare post pubblici o trovare cosa hanno scritto gli amici in un modo simile a come si farebbe su Google ma senza usare un servizio esterno,...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 10 Best Netflix Original Movies in 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=813418</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/813418/best-netflix-original-movies/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T12:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting with a single original production in 2015, Netflix has become a powerhouse of original filmmaking, on par with any major studio. From dramas to comedies to action and more, here are the best original movies to stream on Netflix.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Bell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[After archinstall's auto partitioning, i can only set my hdd as steam library and not my nvme ssd.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vml249/after_archinstalls_auto_partitioning_i_can_only/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vml249/after_archinstalls_auto_partitioning_i_can_only/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T11:32:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[First of all, totally new to Linux. 
 I have a 500gb nvme drive and a 1Tb hd. With archinstall, i chose both of them and set full wipe and automatic partitions using btrfs.
 It set the nvme as root and the hd for the home directory. If it has different partitions, I'm not sure where to find them, but it seems to be using the whole thing for the "/" directories. Because of this i can't write on that directory. 
 Am i just being dumb? Is there anything i can do except reinstall and change the partitions?
    submitted by    /u/designingfailure  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 Essential VPN Features You Should Be Using]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=807474</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/807474/6-essential-vpn-features-you-should-be-using/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T11:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re using a VPN or planning to sign up to one, there are a few easily overlooked features that will help you make the most of your new virtual private network. Let’s take a look at six of them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fergus O'Sullivan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How can I improve my Windows laptop's battery life? [Ask ZDNet]]]></title>
        <id>9048595a-9925-482a-ba80-4fcaedcfb69f</id>
        <link href="https://www.zdnet.com/article/how-can-i-improve-my-windows-laptops-battery-life-ask-zdnet/#ftag=RSSbaffb68"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T11:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Got a tech question? Ed Bott and ZDNet's squad of editors and experts probably have the answer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest topics for ZDNet in Windows</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Over 900,000 Kubernetes instances found exposed online]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/over-900-000-kubernetes-instances-found-exposed-online/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/over-900-000-kubernetes-instances-found-exposed-online/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T10:39:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over 900,000 misconfigured Kubernetes clusters were found exposed on the Internet to potentially malicious scans, some even vulnerable to data-exposing cyberattacks. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Valorant Players: Riot Games Will Be Listening to Your Chats]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=500644</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15397865/riot-games-listening-to-valorant-chats"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T10:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Does the chat room in your gaming sessions get to be a free-for-all? One gaming company wants to put an end to that. Riot Games announced that starting in July, it will be listening in on the voice chats between Valorant players.
   
Also read:How to Make Your Windows Gaming Laptop Play Longer on Battery
    
Riot Games’ Announcement
    
Riot Games has a plan in place to stop abusive comments in the online chats during Valorant gameplay. It’s something it laid the groundwork for more than a year ago.
    
The game-maker made a change to its Privacy Policy and Terms of Service in April 2021. It allows Riot Games to “record and evaluate in-game voice communications when a report for that type of behavior is submitted.”
   
 Image source: Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Defender può rallentare i sistemi basati su processore Intel Core]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Microsoft-Defender-puo-rallentare-i-sistemi-basati-su-processore-Intel-Core_24714</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Microsoft-Defender-puo-rallentare-i-sistemi-basati-su-processore-Intel-Core_24714"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T10:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Per sua stessa natura un software antimalware non può non occupare risorse macchina, ad esempio processore e memoria. Il modulo di protezione che lavora in background deve infatti controllare in tempo reale le attività che vengono svolte sul sistema neutralizzando eventuali minacce.Microsoft Defender, la soluzione per la sicurezza integrata in Windows, si è evoluta molto dalle origini fino ad oggi, al punto che nel 2020 ha ottenuto il punteggio più alto nelle verifiche condotte da AV-Test. A dimostrazione che gli sforzi non sono stati vani.Dietro un'interfaccia molto semplice che in Windows 10 e 11 viene proposta come parte integrante della finestra Sicurezza di Windows, Microsoft Defender nasconde decine di funzionalità evolute che possono essere gestite con un programma gratuito come DefenderUI.Dicevamo che un antimalware ha sempre un certo impatto sulle prestazioni complessive del sistema: l'importante è che le risorse siano impegnate solo quando serve e in modo intelligente in modo da non affossare le performance del PC come accadeva con alcuni storici antivirus in passato.Non sono infrequenti casi in cui Microsoft Defender occupa stabilmente il processore per completare l'analisi del sistema: in caso di problemi è possibile applicare un semplice intervento che permette di limitare l'uso della CPU da parte di Defender.In questi giorni è emerso però un problema che sembra interessare tanti sistemi basati su CPU Intel (quelli equipaggiati con un processore AMD sono immuni alla problematica): Microsoft Defender occupa sempre un minimo quantitativo della CPU, anche quando non ce n'è effettivamente bisogno.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel Brews Linux Change For More Efficient Idle CPU Searching Under Heavy System Load]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.20-SIS_UTIL-Sched-Core</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.20-SIS_UTIL-Sched-Core"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T09:22:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A "sched/fair" scheduler change queued this morning into TIP's sched/core for Linux 5.20 aims to enhance the efficiency when searching for an idle CPU under heavy system load. The change led by Intel should improve the kernel's efficiency when the system is overloaded but as with most low-level tuning does run the risk of regressions...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mesa's Lima Gallium3D Driver Lands 4x MSAA Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Lima-4x-MSAA-Mesa-22.2</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Lima-4x-MSAA-Mesa-22.2"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T08:59:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A decade after Luc Verhaegen started the Lima driver effort for reverse-engineering Arm Mali graphics, developers continue occasionally working on improvements to this Gallium3D driver for older generations of Mali hardware. The most recent feature work is finally enabling 4x MSAA support...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11: Rufus permette di installarlo senza account Microsoft saltando tutte le domande]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-11-Rufus-permette-di-installarlo-senza-account-Microsoft-saltando-tutte-le-domande_24713</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-11-Rufus-permette-di-installarlo-senza-account-Microsoft-saltando-tutte-le-domande_24713"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T08:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Con il lancio di Windows 11 Microsoft ha reso più severi i requisiti per l'installazione del sistema operativo. Esistono comunque dei semplici strumenti per installare Windows 11 su un PC non compatibile.Microsoft stessa ha confermato che Windows 11 si può installare anche sui sistemi incompatibili chiarendo però che in futuro tali macchine potrebbero non ricevere più gli aggiornamenti attraverso Windows Update. Per ora non è successo e Windows Update continua a funzionare regolarmente anche sui sistemi che sulla carta non dovrebbero essere supportati.Rufus è un'applicazione open source che consente di creare supporti USB avviabili.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Atari: il fondatore Nolan Bushnell celebra il 50esimo compleanno dell'azienda]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Atari-il-fondatore-Nolan-Bushnell-celebra-il-50esimo-compleanno-dell-azienda_24712</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Atari-il-fondatore-Nolan-Bushnell-celebra-il-50esimo-compleanno-dell-azienda_24712"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T08:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Era il 27 giugno 1972 quando a Sunnyvale, in California, Nolan Bushnell e Ted Dabney fondarono Atari, un'azienda il cui nome resta scolpita nella memoria di chiunque sia nato tra gli anni '60 e '80.Atari, il cui nome deriva da un verbo giapponese che ha il significato di 'colpire il bersaglio', era sinonimo di innovazione e di rivoluzione nel campo dell'hardware per il settore videoludico.La console più riuscita destinata agli appassionati di videogiochi fu Atari 2600 (1977): non era la prima in assoluto ma seppe guadagnarsi un successo sconfinato.A differenza di altre proposte dell'epoca, Atari 2600 utilizzava cartucce intercambiabili per memorizzare i giochi, un formato che la rese incredibilmente popolare e che è rimasto apprezzato per anni.Grazie al successo dell'Atari 2600, il marchio di Bushnell e Dabney è riuscito a raggiungere la vetta: fino al lancio del NES (Nintendo Entertainment System) nel 1983, il nome Atari era legato alla soluzione migliore per il gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boot stuck at "manage install and generate color profiles..."]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmgfwu/boot_stuck_at_manage_install_and_generate_color/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmgfwu/boot_stuck_at_manage_install_and_generate_color/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T06:32:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This happened after I tried switching to bumblebee Nvidia drivers using nvidia-inst -b. I also don't have a USB key right now and tty don't open using Ctrl+alt+f keys ... Am I screwed?
    submitted by    /u/Dafeader  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox 102: new ESR base and improved security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179390</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/28/firefox-102/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T05:29:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox 102 and Firefox 102 ESR will be released later today. The new version of Mozilla's Firefox web browser improves security, picture-in-picture mode, and is the new base for the Extended Support […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Firefox 102: new ESR base and improved security appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is the 'resume=' kernel parameter necessary?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmaydz/is_the_resume_kernel_parameter_necessary/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmaydz/is_the_resume_kernel_parameter_necessary/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T01:26:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In arch wiki the following kernel parameter for boot loader is typically listed,
 root=PARTUUID=X resume=PARTUUID=Y rw initrd=\initramfs-linux.img
 and the resume= pointing to a swap partition is used for hibernation. I do have a swap partition, but do not have the resume= parameter, and the machine hibernates/resumes just fine. (However waking up from hibernation takes a looooong time, 10-20s with 16G mem.)
 So is the resume= necessary? Without this parameter, does hibernation by default still saves memory snapshot (roughly speaking) to the swap partition when available?
    submitted by    /u/notnullnone  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How can I enable NVIDIA graphics? Followed the wiki and screenfetch still shows Intel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmaexa/how_can_i_enable_nvidia_graphics_followed_the/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vmaexa/how_can_i_enable_nvidia_graphics_followed_the/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T00:59:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://wiki.archlinux.org/title/NVIDIA_Optimus#Use_NVIDIA_graphics_only
 I copied over that configuration blurb into where it said to. Since I'm using the LightDM welcome screen screen locker, I also copied over that blurb.
 I have the nvidia package installed.
 I rebooted, but nothing happened. Screenfetch still shows Intel graphics.
 What's wrong?
    submitted by    /u/Remarkable-River-300  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Facebook Pictures Not Loading? Here Are the Fixes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=post-ideas&amp;p=362094</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/13900599/fix-facebook-pictures-not-loading"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Facebook has become ubiquitous in today’s world. It’s something you expect to always be there working, ready to service your need to snoop on people from your distant past and get involved in whatever strange Facebook groups you’re part of. If pictures are not loading on Facebook, then that defeats a big point of the social site’s appeal. For this reason, we’ve put together a list of reasons your Facebook pictures might not be loading and what you can do about it.
   

Content

1. Check Facebook Server Status
2. Allow Sites to Show Images in Browser
3. Clear Browser Cache
4. Troubleshoot Internet Problems
5. Change DNS Settings
6. Reset Network Configurations
7. Disable Ad Blocker
8. Clear Facebook Cache (Android/iOS)
9. Disable Data Saver (Android)
10. Open Facebook in Your Mobile Browser (Android & iOS)
11. Try Facebook Lite (Android)
12. Reinstall the App
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexandra Arici</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Having issues with USB input devices not being registered by the system.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vm8fbd/having_issues_with_usb_input_devices_not_being/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vm8fbd/having_issues_with_usb_input_devices_not_being/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T23:21:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(A) yes this is in relation to my Steam Deck, I did ask on that Sub and got nothing ... My gut says this is an OS setting issue, not a Steam issue. (B) I haven't used a Linux desktop in over a Decade & a lot has changed, but I am trying to learn. (C) I tried googling this & my issues seems to be unique.
 I can't get my Steam Deck to recognize any USB wired input devices. Bluetooth works fine, but directly connecting a USB device (either through a dock or directly plugging in a single device with a USB-C to USB-C cable). Display out works when connecting a Dock, all devices I plug in directly will light up and start charging from the Deck, but no input devices are detected by the system.
 I have tried two different Docks, two sets of KB+M (my gaming ones off my main PC and a generic Dell Set), an 8BitDo SN30 game pad, and a Rii i8 mini KB+trackpad.
 None of them will show up when connected through USB, but both my Gaming mouse from corsair & the SN30 worked fine when connect through Bluetooth. The only things I have done with Desktop mode is try out Heroic Game Launcher and Lutris, install flat seal, and install ProtonUp-QT ... All done through the discovery application.
 The over all symptoms of this make me think that some kind of permission for USB PnP detection got turned off, but I don't know enough about Linux to start guessing at where to find those: any suggestions for how to fix this?
    submitted by    /u/Xijit  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[qusetion, how do you remove the bottom panel from xfce?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vm828t/qusetion_how_do_you_remove_the_bottom_panel_from/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vm828t/qusetion_how_do_you_remove_the_bottom_panel_from/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T23:03:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[i searched everything and didnt find the solution
 https://imgur.com/a/ekCAAuK
    submitted by    /u/angryteapod  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel Begins Publishing Habana Labs Gaudi2 Linux Driver Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-Gaudi2-Linux-Driver</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-Gaudi2-Linux-Driver"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T22:36:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last month for their Vision conference, Intel announced the Habana Labs Gaudi2 accelerator. Gaudi2 is the second-generation offering from Intel-owned Habana Labs for training and inference.  The open-source Linux kernel driver support for Gaudi2 is now getting underway along with accompanying open-source user-space software stack support...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git 2.37 Released With Sparse Index Feature Now Ready For Widespread Use]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Git-2.37-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Git-2.37-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T22:19:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git 2.37 is out today as the latest feature update to this widely-used, distributed revision control system...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Screen Capture (XSHM)" is no longer there is OBS Studio]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vm6u7u/screen_capture_xshm_is_no_longer_there_is_obs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vm6u7u/screen_capture_xshm_is_no_longer_there_is_obs/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T22:10:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have absolutely no idea how OBS Studio works, but yeah, the option that I use for screen capture on Arch Linux (Screen Capture (XSHM)) is no longer there.
 It started with OBS saying something like it "doesn't exist" (sorry, I didn't take a screenshot nor do I fully remember what it exactly said) and for further investigation, upon removing it, there is now no option altogether.
 After this happening, I also notice Gnome's screen recording utility also isn't working now either. All videos save as a 0 second video.
 Is this a dependency issue? Is anybody else having this issue? Please help!
    submitted by    /u/jaamivstheworld  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come controllare un PC da remoto: guida a Iperius Remote 4 (desktop remoto e assistenza)]]></title>
        <id>1360|20220628000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/controllo-remoto-270/come-controllare-pc-remoto-guida-iperius-remote-4-desktop-remoto-assistenza-1360"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Il lavoro remoto è ormai una prassi consolidata per molti di noi, con tutte le comodità e tutte le problematiche che questo comporta. Fra le criticità introdotte dal lavorare lontano da colleghi e attrezzature aziendali, figura sicuramente la necessità di collegarsi ai computer remoti, magari per interagire con la propria postazione fissa in sede o fornire assistenza ad un altro lavoratore geograficamente lontano da noi. In questa situazione, ci viene in aiuto Iperius Remote 4: una soluzione integrata che risponde a tutte le necessità di controllo e assistenza remoti. Vediamo dunque come utilizzarlo in questa nostra guida a Iperius Remote 4
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fix Mobile Data Not Working on Android]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=165018</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/4557633/fix-cellular-data-not-working-on-android"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cellular data, mobile data, whatever you want to call it, is one of those things that only becomes a life necessity once you acquire your first smartphone. It’s only when you lose connectivity that you realize you don’t know how to get anywhere without Google Maps, don’t have anything to read without Flipboard, and don’t know how to communicate with people through any medium other than WhatsApp.
    
When mobile data stops working on Android, it’s world-shattering, in other words. Here are some tips on how to get it back.
   

Content

1. Reset Your APNs
2. Set APN Protocol to iPv4/IPv6
3. Enter Your APN Settings Manually
4. Wipe Cache Partition from Recovery
5. Reset Your Phone’s Network Connection
6. Enable the Right Network Mode
7. Reset Networks
8. Remove and Reinsert Your SIM Card
9. Do You Have a Mobile Data Limit?
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Crystal Crowder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Play Adobe Flash SWF Files Outside Your Web Browser]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=438141</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/438141/how-to-play-adobe-flash-swf-files-outside-your-web-browser/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web browsers have dropped support for Flash, but what if you have an SWF file to open? Never fear: Adobe offered a hidden Flash Player download for Windows, Mac, and Linux that is still available from the Wayback Machine. You can open an SWF file outside your browser.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Is the Apple TV 4K so Expensive?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/121779/why-is-the-apple-tv-4k-so-expensive/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/121779/why-is-the-apple-tv-4k-so-expensive/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T20:43:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a world of $50 streaming sticks, the $180 Apple TV 4K looks like an outrageous purchase. But even the biggest Android nerds swoon over Apple TV 4K when they see it in person. Its high price comes with premium features, and for some people, it’s the best streaming device available today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to boot into Arch while keeping secure boot on?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vm52ka/how_to_boot_into_arch_while_keeping_secure_boot_on/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vm52ka/how_to_boot_into_arch_while_keeping_secure_boot_on/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T20:28:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I need secure boot to be on to be able to play Valorant on Windows, but turning it on doesn't let me boot into the Arch Linux installation at all. It says 
  
Secure boot violation: Invalid signature detected
  
I can't even install Arch without disabling it
    submitted by    /u/kushal10  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can't get IPv6 global address]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vm4zba/cant_get_ipv6_global_address/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vm4zba/cant_get_ipv6_global_address/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T20:24:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, I have set up my router so that I can get IPv6 addresses by RA. All of my devices (android and a rpi running dietpi) can obtain an address. Only my Arch Linux desktop is unable to (I use systemd-networkd, but also tried different network managers). Would be great if someone could help me troubleshoot. :)
 Many thanks in advance
    submitted by    /u/Sparki2002  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Microsoft 365?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=669400</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/669400/what-is-microsoft-365/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re familiar with Office 365, you already know what Microsoft 365 is. It’s a subscription plan that costs $100 per year of up to six people or $70 per year for one person. Microsoft hasn’t raised the price.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bank of the West found debit card-stealing skimmers on ATMs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/bank-of-the-west-found-debit-card-stealing-skimmers-on-atms/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/bank-of-the-west-found-debit-card-stealing-skimmers-on-atms/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T19:44:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bank of the West is warning customers that their debit card numbers and PINs have been stolen by skimmers installed on several of the bank's ATMs. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web-Based Apps Are About to Get Better on Windows 10]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=814204</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/814204/web-based-apps-are-about-to-get-better-on-windows-10/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T19:31:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many desktop applications, like Discord and Spotify, are based on web technologies and usually eat up system resources than proper native apps. Microsoft has been working on an alternative to the Electron framework that most web-based apps use, and now it’s rolling out on Windows 10.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can't download hyprland-git]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vm3mp2/cant_download_hyprlandgit/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vm3mp2/cant_download_hyprlandgit/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T19:25:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey guys,
 ​
 I am trying to install hyprland but the PKGBUILD file is not being downloaded. Also shows "error: target not found" for all dependencies. 
 Anyone else having this issue?
 ​
 Thanks!
    submitted by    /u/DecafDicaprio  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save $250 on a Lenovo Flex 5 Ideapad with Windows 11 Home]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=470048</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15123260/lenovo-flex-5-ideapad"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you still looking for an affordable device that will allow you to run Windows 11? This is a great way to jump in. You can get a Lenovo Flex 5 Ideapad with Windows 11 Home built in, along with AMD Radeon graphics, AMD Ryzen 5 5500U, and Alexa.
    
The Ryzen mobile processor provides the power for the Ideapad. It also includes Radeon graphics, 16GB DDR4 RAM, and 256GB NVMe SSD storage. A narrow bezel on all four sides gives you more viewing area and more area to work on the 14″ IPS FHD 1920 x 1080 display. Added to that is Wi-Fi 6, Bluetooth 5, two USB-A ports, one USB-C port with PD, HDMI, a 4-in-1 card reader, and an audio jack.
   
 
   
If you’re the creative type, the Lenovo Flex 5 Ideapad is designed for you. It will keep your creativity flowing wherever you happen to be. It even includes a Lenovo Digital Pen to jot down and expand all of your ideas.
    
The 360º hinge allows you... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Personal Tasks Directly in Google Chat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=811566</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/811566/create-personal-tasks-in-google-chat/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T19:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many times, projects and goals develop out of emails or messaging discussions. If you’re using Google Chat, you can turn a message turn into a task. Then access it like your other Google Tasks or in Google Calendar.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Android malware ‘Revive’ impersonates BBVA bank’s 2FA app]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/android-malware-revive-impersonates-bbva-bank-s-2fa-app/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/android-malware-revive-impersonates-bbva-bank-s-2fa-app/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T18:30:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new Android banking malware named Revive has been discovered that impersonates a 2FA application required to log into BBVA bank accounts in Spain. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GCC-Rust Feedback Sought - Possibly Aiming For Upstream In GCC 13]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=GCC-Rust-Upstream-Talk-Thread</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=GCC-Rust-Upstream-Talk-Thread"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T18:10:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Rust-GCC front-end that allows Rust code to be compiled with the GNU Compiler Collection (GCC) could possibly be upstreamed for next year's GCC 13 compiler release but not necessarily complete at that stage. In any case, it's good seeing progress on Rust-GCC as an alternative to Rust's official LLVM-based compiler...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Send Mobile Push Notifications With PHP and Firebase]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?post_type=devops&amp;p=800731</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/devops/how-to-send-mobile-push-notifications-with-php-and-firebase/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T18:07:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s Firebase Cloud Messaging (FCM) service is a free and convenient way to distribute push notifications to mobile devices. It works with iOS, Android, and web targets, abstracting away the differences between platforms. You send your payload once to Firebase’s API and get real-time delivery to all your users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US, Brazil seize 272 websites used to illegally download music]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-brazil-seize-272-websites-used-to-illegally-download-music/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-brazil-seize-272-websites-used-to-illegally-download-music/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T18:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The domains of six websites that streamed and provided illegal downloads of copyrighted music were seized by U.S. Homeland Security Investigations (HSI) and the Department of Justice. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Access the Boot Menu in Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809906</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809906/how-to-access-the-boot-menu-in-windows-11/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T18:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Advanced Options Menu, sometimes called the Boot Menu, contains tools and configuration options you can use to troubleshoot or repair your PC. Here’s how to use it on Windows 11.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Lewis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mercedes-Benz Tested an EV With a 747-Mile Range]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=814221</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/814221/mercedes-benz-tested-an-ev-with-a-747-mile-range/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T17:49:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Driving range is a critical issue for electric cars, especially since charging stations still aren’t as common as gas stations. Thankfully, the maximum range on EVs is continuing to improve, as proven by a recent test from Mercedes-Benz.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux "RADV" Radeon Driver Gets A Big Speed-Up For 16-bit FidelityFX Super Resolution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=RADV-Faster-16-bit-FSR</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=RADV-Faster-16-bit-FSR"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T17:30:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Merged today to Mesa 22.2 was a four month old merge request for the open-source Radeon Vulkan driver "RADV" that significantly improves the 16-bit FidelityFX Super Resolution (FSR) performance...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SKG V7 Smartwatch Review]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=496767</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15396925/skg-v7-smartwatch"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T17:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smartwatches can be helpful yet also really expensive. If you think you don’t have the funds to put out for a smartwatch, there are some budget models that may do all the necessary functions. This review covers the SKG V7 Smartwatch to see if it covers both of those metrics: budget and necessary functions.
    
This is a sponsored article and was made possible by SKG. The actual contents and opinions are the sole views of the author who maintains editorial independence, even when a post is sponsored.
    
Setting Up the SKG V7 Smartwatch
    
To prove that the SKG V7 Smartwatch includes what’s necessary, it ships with only three items:
   
 
   
Smartwatch
Charging cord
Quick start guide
   
 
   
Before setting up the smartwatch, you need to charge it to 100%. The charging cord fits into a standard USB-A charging brick and magnetically attaches to the back of the... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Hack Apple CarPlay Onto Any Tesla Now]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/121775/you-can-hack-apple-carplay-onto-any-tesla-now/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/121775/you-can-hack-apple-carplay-onto-any-tesla-now/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T17:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier this year, Polish developer Michał Gapiński released a clever hack allowing Android Auto or Apple’s CarPlay to run on select Tesla vehicles. And while the initial version was only a beta, the latest release has new features and works on any Tesla model.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Type an Em Dash on Windows or Mac]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=811997</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/811997/how-to-type-an-em-dash-on-windows-or-mac/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T17:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’d like to type a long dash—called an em dash—on a Windows PC or Mac, you need to take some extra steps because it’s not on your keyboard. Here’s how to get an em dash.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can't delete @.snapshots subvolume (BTRFS)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vm07ae/cant_delete_snapshots_subvolume_btrfs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vm07ae/cant_delete_snapshots_subvolume_btrfs/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T16:58:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Heya! Loving BTRFS so far. Decided to do a new install with the archinstall script and use the default BTRFS subvolume layout. I'm trying to delete my @.snapshots subvolume in order to create a @snaphots subvol due to my OCD. 
 I've tried changing the permissions from RO to RW, deleting the default mount point at /.snapshots and re-mounting the subvol at /mnt/snapshots to no avail. 
 I'm running sudo btrfs subvolume delete /mnt/snapshots/@.snapshots with the error "ERROR: Could not statfs: No such file or directory"
 If I try a different syntax with sudo btrfs subvolume delete /mnt/snapshots/ /@.snapshots I end up getting back
 "Delete subvolume (no-commit): '/mnt/snapshots'
 ERROR: Could not destroy subvolume/snapshot: Invalid argument"
 Any help would be much appreciated.
 Cheers!
    submitted by    /u/Outsideyourboxes  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft will fix Windows RRAS, VPN issues for all users in July]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-will-fix-windows-rras-vpn-issues-for-all-users-in-july/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-will-fix-windows-rras-vpn-issues-for-all-users-in-july/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has finally confirmed Internet connectivity issues affecting servers with Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) enabled after installing Windows updates released as part of this month's Patch Tuesday. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Phishing più furbo con il componente WebView2 di Edge: rischio furti d'identità]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Phishing-piu-furbo-con-il-componente-WebView2-di-Edge-rischio-furti-d-identita_24711</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Phishing-piu-furbo-con-il-componente-WebView2-di-Edge-rischio-furti-d-identita_24711"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WebView2 è un controllo di Microsoft Edge che permette agli sviluppatori di integrare le principali tecnologie per il Web, come ad esempio HTML, CSS e JavaScript, all'interno di applicazioni native.Con WebView2 il programmatore può creare un eseguibile in grado di comunicare con le applicazioni Web in modo simile a quanto fa un browser.Un ricercatore indipendente ha dimostrato che è possibile utilizzare applicazioni basate su WebView2 per sottrarre dati personali come le credenziali di accesso ai principali servizi online e superare i meccanismi di autenticazione a due fattori.Il ricercatore spiega di aver trovato il modo per iniettare codice JavaScript al fine di registrare tutti i tasti premuti dall'utente (keylogger).WebView2 fornisce anche funzionalità integrate per estrarre il contenu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vice Society claims ransomware attack on Med. University of Innsbruck]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/vice-society-claims-ransomware-attack-on-med-university-of-innsbruck/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/vice-society-claims-ransomware-attack-on-med-university-of-innsbruck/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T16:31:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Vice Society ransomware gang has claimed responsibility for last week's cyberattack against the Medical University of Innsbruck, which caused severe IT service disruption and the alleged theft of data. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come stampare da Android su qualsiasi stampante]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2013/06/come-stampare-da-android-su-qualsiasi.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2013/06/come-stampare-da-android-su-qualsiasi.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T16:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Con i moderni smartphone ed i tablet è possibile stampare qualsiasi documento senza bisogno di trasferirlo ogni volta sul PC: questa comodità è sfruttabile in particolare in ufficio, dove potrebbe sicuramente esserci la necessità di stampare improvvisamente un foglio di calcolo o un documento appena ricevuto via email.

 Quando si utilizza un telefono Android abbiamo diversi metodi per aggiungere...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Earth.fm Streams Relaxing Nature Sounds from Around the World]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/121765/earth-fm-streams-relaxing-nature-sounds-from-around-the-world/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/121765/earth-fm-streams-relaxing-nature-sounds-from-around-the-world/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T16:17:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s nothing more relaxing than the sound of nature, especially when you’re stuck at a desk all day. And that’s what makes Earth.fm so interesting—it’s a website that lets you stream the “natural soundscapes” of several locations across the globe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Cheapest Way to Get iMessage on Android (and Windows)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=810209</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/810209/the-cheapest-way-to-get-imessage-on-android-and-windows/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[iMessage on Android—the white whale of many smartphone users. We’ve shown you how to use iMessage on Android and Windows, but there’s a pretty big barrier to entry. Let’s find the cheapest way to do it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recording Academy’s VP of D.E.I. Ryan Butler Tells Us What Brings Him Joy Online]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.mozilla.org/?p=69351</id>
        <link href="https://blog.mozilla.org/en/internet-culture/recording-academys-vp-of-d-e-i-ryan-butler-tells-us-what-brings-him-joy-online/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here at Mozilla, we are the first to admit the internet isn’t perfect, but we are also quick to point out that the internet is pretty darn magical. The internet opens up doors and opportunities, allows for people to connect with others, and lets everyone find where they belong — their corners of the internet. […]
The post Recording Academy’s VP of D.E.I. Ryan Butler Tells Us What Brings Him Joy Online appeared first on The Mozilla Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Damiano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung's Wackiest Monitor Could Go On Sale This Summer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/121759/samsungs-wackiest-monitor-could-go-on-sale-this-summer/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/121759/samsungs-wackiest-monitor-could-go-on-sale-this-summer/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T15:57:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier this year, Samsung unveiled its massive 55-inch curved gaming monitor called the Odyssey Ark. And while we haven’t heard much about it since, new reports suggest Samsung’s wild new monitor will arrive later this summer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Exchange bug abused to hack building automation systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-exchange-bug-abused-to-hack-building-automation-systems/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-exchange-bug-abused-to-hack-building-automation-systems/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T15:39:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Chinese-speaking threat actor has hacked into the building automation systems (used to control HVAC, fire, and security functions) of several Asian organizations to backdoor their networks and gain access to more secured areas in their networks. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Containerize a Legacy Application]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?post_type=devops&amp;p=800745</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/devops/how-to-containerize-a-legacy-application/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T15:36:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Containerization has transformed how new applications are developed and deployed. However many organizations retain a back catalog of older systems that necessitate a different approach. This disconnect between new and old doesn’t have to be perpetuated: you can package older systems as containers too, making it easier to continue evolving them with more modern development methods.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Plans a Slew of Ambitious Products for Late 2022 and Early 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/121756/apple-plans-a-slew-of-ambitious-products-for-late-2022-and-early-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/121756/apple-plans-a-slew-of-ambitious-products-for-late-2022-and-early-2023/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T15:31:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It seems that Apple was holding out during its June WWDC conference. As reported in Mark Gurman’s Power On newsletter, Apple will launch a “deluge” of ambitious new products in late 2022 and early 2023. These new products include a mixed reality headset, new “core” devices,’ and revamped versions of the Apple TV, Apple Watch, AirPods Pro, and HomePod.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 Ways to View Deleted Reddit Posts and Comments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=156639</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/4054948/access-deleted-comments-reddit"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reddit is home to the internet’s anonymous discussions on a variety of topics and interests. With the cloak of anonymity given by Reddit, users are free to say whatever they want, which isn’t always a good thing. 
    
When a post or comment goes against a subreddit’s rules, they’re deleted using bots or human moderators. Reddit users also have the option to delete their own posts and comments. But are those deleted items gone for ever? What if you’re curious to read a deleted post or comment on Reddit? You can, with the help of certain websites and browser extensions, which we discuss here.
   

Content

1. Unddit
2. Reveddit
3. Wayback Machine
4. Resavr
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:8 of the Best Reddit Clients for iOS and Android
    
1. Unddit
    
Unddit is... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Natalie dela Vega</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 10 Might Get a Major Update In 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=814170</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/814170/microsoft-10-might-get-a-major-update-in-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T15:24:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft is preparing to release a ’22H2′ update for Windows 11, the first major update since Windows 11 arrived last year. People still using Windows 10 might get their own 22H2 update, too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LockBit 3.0 introduces the first ransomware bug bounty program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/lockbit-30-introduces-the-first-ransomware-bug-bounty-program/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/lockbit-30-introduces-the-first-ransomware-bug-bounty-program/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T15:09:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LockBit ransomware operation has released 'LockBit 3.0,' introducing the first ransomware bug bounty program and leaking new extortion tactics and Zcash cryptocurrency payment options. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting NVIDIA dGPU recognized under a Wayland session]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlxl2d/getting_nvidia_dgpu_recognized_under_a_wayland/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlxl2d/getting_nvidia_dgpu_recognized_under_a_wayland/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T15:04:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! I wonder how to get NVIDIA dGPU recognized in GNOME/KDE Wayland session system settings. I experiences a lot of stuttering on the external monitor in Wayland and the system settings doesn't show the NVIDIA dGPU.
 Currently I have a gaming laptop with Intel + NVIDIA running on Xorg on an external monitor hooked up to the dGPU. The internal screen is currently disabled. It's buttery smooth, but when I switched to a Wayland session ( GNOME and KDE ), the inner screen is buttery smooth, but the external monitor stutters a lot.
 What I have done so far:
 Install mesa,xorg
 Install nvidia, set nvidia-drm.modeset=1 parameter, added nvidia nvidia_modeset nvidia_uvm nvidia_drm i915 into MODULES section of mkinitcpio.conf
 Run nvidia-xconfig twice, one with the external monitor disabled, one with the external monitor enabled
 I haven't touched any settings related to optimus yet.
    submitted by    /u/hydrocryo01  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Handy Microsoft Excel Features You May Have Missed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=807862</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/807862/handy-excel-features/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T15:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes when you use applications every day, new features can go unnoticed. So that you’re up to speed with useful tools for your spreadsheets, take a look at these Microsoft Excel features you may have missed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Suspending VMware virtual machines on standby, reboot and shutdown]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlx3z6/suspending_vmware_virtual_machines_on_standby/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlx3z6/suspending_vmware_virtual_machines_on_standby/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T14:43:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey,
 I'd like to suspend my VMs e.g. when the powerbutton is pressed, I restart my machine or shut it down. A Systemd service seems reasonable to do this.
 There are several old topics on this issue on Fedora mailing list e.g. but I cannot get it to work.
 https://lists.fedoraproject.org/pipermail/users/2011-December/409819.html
 It also seems this guy used Systemd in the wrong way according to many comments that you find on Google on this topic. Systemd does not wait for the script to be finished. Executing the script manually does exactly what it's intended for.
 Is there a proper way to suspend the machines?On the Arch wiki there is this section https://wiki.archlinux.org/title/VMware#Suspend_virtual_machines_before_host_suspend/hibernatebut the script doesn't get triggered on Sway e.g. when I poweroff the host although I copied it to
 /usr/lib/systemd/system-shutdown/vmware-suspend-all.sh 
 giving it +x execution permissions for any user. 
 Edit: It seems /usr/lib/systemd/system-shutdown/ is also not correct as this happens when the system already is mounted read only.
 Did you figure out how it works reliably?
    submitted by    /u/cmprmsd  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Pixel 6a Appears to Solve the Pixel 6's Biggest Problem]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/121754/the-pixel-6a-appears-to-solve-the-pixel-6s-biggest-problem/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/121754/the-pixel-6a-appears-to-solve-the-pixel-6s-biggest-problem/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T14:38:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Pixel 6 is plagued by bugs and annoyances, most notably a slow fingerprint sensor. And it seems that Google will fix this problem with the Pixel 6a. In an early review video, Malaysian YouTuber Fazli Halim shows the Pixel 6a besting the Pixel 6 in both fingerprint sensor speed and responsiveness.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come liberare spazio in Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/06/come-liberare-spazio-in-windows-11.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/06/come-liberare-spazio-in-windows-11.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T14:35:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 ha portato con sè numerose novità anche dal punto di vista dell'ottimizzazione e della manutenzione del sistema. Se fino a Windows 10 poteva ancora essere utile un programma di pulizia come CClenaer, con Windows 11 questo tipo di programmi è totalmente superfluo, visto che Microsoft ha introdotto degli efficaci strumenti di pulizia all'interno delle impostazioni. 
Nella guida che segue...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[co-dependent package update behavior]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlwujt/codependent_package_update_behavior/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vlwujt/codependent_package_update_behavior/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T14:31:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of my only dislikes of arch package management is co-dependent packages. If two packages require a specific version of each other and you update both at the same time it will always fail. As it can only update one package at a time. From an ignorant standpoint it seems ideal to combine the package install success of co-dependant packages, and try them both, failing and reverting only if any package fails.
 Is there currently a more elegant way to handle this rather than remove both packages and reinstall them?
 I know it's the AUR but my annoying example is zfs-utils/zfs-dkms. This comes up each kernel update but I'm pretty sure I've run into before with more supported packages, albeit much less frequently.
    submitted by    /u/habys  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple’s New 13-Inch MacBook Pro Has One Big Downgrade]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=814134</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/814134/apples-new-13-inch-macbook-pro-has-one-big-downgrade/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T14:13:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple revealed a new 13-inch MacBook Pro earlier this month, powered by the company’s new M2 chipset. Now that the laptop is starting to arrive on buyers’ doorsteps, at least one problem has become apparent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft: Recent Windows updates caused Edge freeze issues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-recent-windows-updates-caused-edge-freeze-issues/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-recent-windows-updates-caused-edge-freeze-issues/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T14:08:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft says it addressed a known issue that was causing all Microsoft Edge tabs running IE mode to stop responding if one of the opened sites displayed a modal dialog box after issuing a window.focus call. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>