<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-06-16T01:55:37.358Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gnome-keyring-deamon blocks Chromium/Chrome from first startup]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vdab1n/gnomekeyringdeamon_blocks_chromiumchrome_from/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vdab1n/gnomekeyringdeamon_blocks_chromiumchrome_from/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-16T01:37:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So I reinstalled Arch recently and noticed Chromium and Chrome wouldn't start after a fresh install. At first I thought it was a graphic card driver error or something to do with libva but it turns out it's Gnome Keyring that causes the issue. When I turn it off, it starts fine and I never have any issue after that even with Gnome Keyring started.
 Does anyone know how can I fix that?
 Thanks
    submitted by    /u/lalondan  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No Audio Fresh Install]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vd9ia8/no_audio_fresh_install/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vd9ia8/no_audio_fresh_install/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-16T00:55:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just installed Arch, No Audio. Settings displays only output option as "Dummy Output"
 I installed alsa-utils, pulseaudio, then tried pro-audio. Thats where im at, scared to continue without some guidance because i know im too impatient to not mess something up
 New Obi wan episode out so if someone could help with this asap that would be awesome thanks
    submitted by    /u/lardis74  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create and Use an Instagram Avatar]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=493784</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15371028/create-use-instagram-avatar"/>
        <updated>2022-06-16T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Snapchat users have been able to create cute customizable 3D avatars since 2016. What you may not know is that Instagram has a similar feature. It’s a bit hidden, so you might not have been aware of this option. This tutorial shows how you can create your own personalized avatar in Instagram and start using it immediately.
   

Content

What Are Instagram Avatars?
How to Create an Avatar with Instagram
How to Use Your Avatar on Instagram
How to Create Avatars with Bitmoji for Instagram
How to Share Your Bitmoji Avatar in Instagram
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Link or Unlink Your Instagram Account from Facebook
    
What Are Instagram Avatars?
    
Meta introduced avatars on Facebook Messenger back in 2019, and now they’ve made it Instagram as well. An avatar is your customizable persona that you can... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexandra Arici</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gnome-Terminal not working]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vd7ipv/gnometerminal_not_working/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vd7ipv/gnometerminal_not_working/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T23:15:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I installed Arch with the Gnome desktop, and I'm unable to use the terminal. When I click on the icon, the cursor spins for a minute and then stops. I've seen lots of posts and articles that all say "check your locale.conf file" or "install gnome-terminal" or some other solution that requires a terminal. The fatal flaw in all of these solutions is that the original issue is that the terminal doesn't work. I've seen stuff about CTRL+ALT+F1 or a billion other combinations but none of them seem to do anything. I'm lost as to how to proceed. Any help would be appreciated.
    submitted by    /u/SignificantCredit529  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pipewire not working on brand new install]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vd7582/pipewire_not_working_on_brand_new_install/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vd7582/pipewire_not_working_on_brand_new_install/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T22:57:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello there, I just installed Arch with archinstall (I already installed Arch previously when it didn't exist so I'm pretty sure about what I'm doing) on a brand new Acer Laptop as a minimal install (to which I told to install Pipewire), I then installed plasma and followed the archwiki for pipewire (also installed plasma-pa) so I'm pretty sure that I did everything alright but I still don't have sound.
 Note: I followed multiple fixes like nuking /etc/pipewire and reinstalling and still no sound :/
 Also, Plasma says there is no output other than a dummy one
 ​
 Does anyone have an idea ?
 ​
 Thanks
    submitted by    /u/WiredMario  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wyze Talks Upcoming Products, Matter Ecosystem Plans in AMA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=811868</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/811868/wyze-talks-upcoming-products-matter-ecosystem-plans-in-ama/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T22:34:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wyze sells some of the most popular smart home devices around, most notably the Wyze Cam series. The company hosted an Ask-Me-Anything (AMA) on Reddit earlier today, revealing a few details about the company’s upcoming plans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JShelter: difendi il tuo browser dai javascript malevoli]]></title>
        <id>3602|20220616000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/browser-455/jshelter-difendi-browser-javascript-malevoli-3602"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JShelter (precedentemente conosciuto come JavaScript Restrictor) è un estensione open source che si definisce come un "anti-malware" per browser (è disponibile per Firefox, Google Chrome e Opera) in grado di mitigare le potenziali minacce provenienti dai javascript incluso fingerprint, tracking e raccolta dati. È stata finanziata da un'importante fondazione che promuove e supporta progetti volti a sviluppare informazione aperta e accessibile, è sponsorizzata dalla Free Software Fondation, sviluppata da un dottorando dell'università di Brno con il contributo, tra gli altri, di Giorgio Maone (sviluppatore di un'altra famosissima estensione NoScript).
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[pls help with wifi on install, no wlan0]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vd5rvr/pls_help_with_wifi_on_install_no_wlan0/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vd5rvr/pls_help_with_wifi_on_install_no_wlan0/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T21:54:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[cant connect to wifi after install. installed and activated network tools, tried netcli, nmtui. Problem seems to be rooted in the fact that my wlan0 isnt identified with ip link. Im pretty sure i completed the install correctly but i guess not. i 100% have all my network tools installed and networkmanager service enabled. not sure what to do from here. please help, thx
    submitted by    /u/lardis74  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[14 Useful PowerPoint Templates to Set Up a Digital Planner]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=448305</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15370845/powerpoint-templates-for-digital-planner"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paper planners are difficult to always keep with you. Plus, once you use them, you have to throw them away. Instead, organize your life, keep track of goals, and plan your business’s growth with a PowerPoint-based digital planner. Start off with PowerPoint templates and customize them for any purpose. You’ll find templates for everything from a basic daily planner to a detailed project planner with timelines. Once you’re finished with a time period or project, load the template and create a new custom planner.
    
While these are all free digital planner templates, they’re only for personal use. You can’t sell them. If using them for public presentations, you may need to credit the creator, which will be detailed in the template or on template’s download page.
   

Content

1. Daily Planner
2. Weekly Planner
3. Monthly Planner
4. Yearly Planner
5. Bullet Journal
6. Wedding Planner
7. Lesson Planner
8. Event Planner
9. Timeline Planner
10. Student Planner
11. Meal Planner
12. Social Media Planner
13. Marketing Planner
14. Business Planner
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Crystal Crowder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adobe Lightroom vs Photoshop: Which Should You Use?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120964/adobe-lightroom-vs-photoshop-which-should-you-use/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120964/adobe-lightroom-vs-photoshop-which-should-you-use/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T21:01:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Beginner photographers often ask whether they should use Lightroom or Photoshop. And the answer is a lot simpler than you’d expect. Functionally, Lightroom and Photoshop have a lot of overlap, but they’re very different tools that excel in different situations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[12 Basic Excel Functions Everybody Should Know]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=765624</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/765624/basic-excel-functions-everybody-should-know/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Excel contains many functions that allow you to perform tasks without a calculator or extra work. But if you’re unfamiliar with formulas, it can feel intimidating. Here, we’ve listed 12 simple but useful Excel functions to get you started.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your Steam Library Is Coming to Nreal's AR Glasses]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120989/your-steam-library-is-coming-to-nreals-ar-glasses/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120989/your-steam-library-is-coming-to-nreals-ar-glasses/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T20:30:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Chinese augmented reality (AR) company Nreal announced that it’s bringing select Steam games to its popular Nreal Light and Nreal Air AR glasses. This way, users can enjoy some of their favorite Steam titles right from the couch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Audio gets unmuted after suspension.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vd3kpc/audio_gets_unmuted_after_suspension/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vd3kpc/audio_gets_unmuted_after_suspension/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T20:15:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey yall! I have a laptop that I use for school. I recently noticed an issue regarding the audio. Whenever I close the lid and open it again my audio gets unmuted. All the other things work as expected. The screen lights back up and KDE drops me on the lockscreen. Anything I gotta install or configure to stop the audiovfrom unmuting itself after opening that laptop back up?
    submitted by    /u/Trqhxrd  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Restore Recently Closed Tabs in Chrome, Firefox, Opera, Internet Explorer, and Microsoft Edge]]></title>
        <id>http://www.howtogeek.com/?p=125010</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/125010/restore-recently-closed-tabs-in-chrome-firefox-opera-internet-explorer-9-and-safari/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You accidentally closed a tab, then realized you weren’t done with that webpage. Or, you want to open that elusive webpage you visited last week, but you forgot to bookmark it. No worries, you can get your closed tabs back.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lori Kaufman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dish Says Its 5G Network Is Now Live In Over 120 Cities]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=811818</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/811818/dish-says-its-5g-network-is-now-live-in-over-120-cities/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T19:28:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dish Network (yes, the TV company) has been building its own cellular network in the United States, competing with other cell phone plans, which finally started going live in Las Vegas back in May. Now it’s supposedly available in over 120 cities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save 25% on a 2021 Apple TV 4K]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=497545</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15370760/2021-apple-tv-4k"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you like to immerse yourself in your favorite TV shows, the hottest blockbuster movies, and heart-pumping action games, a 2021 Apple TV 4K may be what you’re looking for. Get the best audio, video, and graphics in a small form that hooks up directly to your TV for under $150.
    
Stream your favorite binge-worthy TV and hit movies with a 4K High Frame Rate HDR and Dolby Vision for a crisp picture. Pair this with Dolby Atmos for sound that will make you feel like you’re in the middle of the action. An A12 Bionic chip improves that performance even more and allows you to experience the same on games and apps.
   
 
   
The Apple TV 4K experience includes all the major streaming channels: Netflix, Hulu, HBO Max, Disney+, Amazon Prime Video, and more. In addition, you’ll get original Apple TV shows. You’ll never run out of things to watch. Add AirPlay into the mix to view your photos and videos.
    
You can also play your favorite games on Apple... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to change whatever this boot menu is to GRUB2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vd2h9x/how_to_change_whatever_this_boot_menu_is_to_grub2/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vd2h9x/how_to_change_whatever_this_boot_menu_is_to_grub2/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T19:24:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a screenshot of my bootmenu
 Video of my regular startup
 Yeah idk what to do
    submitted by    /u/ingn  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Are Fan Tokens?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=803266</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/803266/what-are-fan-tokens/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T19:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fan tokens are cryptocurrencies that allow holders to vote on minor decisions related to sports clubs, earn rewards, and have a shot at unique experiences like meet and greets. They can be used by any other organization to engage a community with digital assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>RJ Fulton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AlmaLinux 9 Running Well, Performance On Par With RHEL 9.0]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31210</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31210"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T18:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Released at the end of May was AlmaLinux 9.0 as the first "community" distribution out of the gates based on Red Hat Enterprise Linux 9.0 that reached GA in mid-May. I've been running AlmaLinux 9.0 on a few Intel and AMD servers to great success. And, yes, as expected the performance matches that of upstream RHEL9.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco Secure Email bug can let attackers bypass authentication]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisco-secure-email-bug-can-let-attackers-bypass-authentication/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisco-secure-email-bug-can-let-attackers-bypass-authentication/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T18:24:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco notified customers this week to patch a critical vulnerability that could allow attackers to bypass authentication and login into the web management interface of Cisco email gateway appliances with non-default configurations. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zimbra bug allows stealing email logins with no user interaction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/zimbra-bug-allows-stealing-email-logins-with-no-user-interaction/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/zimbra-bug-allows-stealing-email-logins-with-no-user-interaction/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T18:01:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zimbra and SonarSource proceeded to the coordinated disclosure of a high-severity vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to steal cleartext credentials from Zimbra without any user interaction. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Delete a PivotTable in Microsoft Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=804256</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/804256/how-to-delete-a-pivot-table/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you don’t use a specific PivotTable in your spreadsheet anymore, you have two ways to remove the table in Excel. There’s a keyboard method as well as a ribbon menu option to delete PivotTables. Here’s how to use them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Godot 4.0 Alpha 10 Brings Temporal AA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Godot-4.0-Alpha-10</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Godot-4.0-Alpha-10"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T17:54:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The tenth alpha release of the Godot 4.0 open-source game engine is now available for testing with some interesting additions...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Excel on Windows Will Soon Import Data From Photos]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=811799</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/811799/microsoft-excel-on-windows-will-soon-import-data-from-photos/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T17:36:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many applications can already read and sort data from photos and scans of documents, using optical character recognition, and soon that functionality is coming to Excel for Windows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome, guida all'uso del browser]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Chrome-guida-all-uso-del-browser_24646</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Chrome-guida-all-uso-del-browser_24646"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T17:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Con l'abbandono del supporto di Internet Explorer da parte di Microsoft a metà giugno 2022 si è chiusa un'epoca. Quell'era in cui il browser dell'azienda di Redmond poteva vantare quote di mercato che sembravano assolutamente inarrivabili, soprattutto per via del fatto che Internet Explorer era il browser predefinito integrato in Windows.Eppure Firefox prima e Google Chrome poi hanno fatto la storia superando Internet Explorer per quote di mercato. I browser concorrenti convinsero gli utenti laddove Internet Explorer stava fallendo: aderenza agli standard per il Web, prestazioni, supporto per le estensioni e possibilità di personalizzazione.Chrome nasce nel 2008 e con il passare degli anni è cresciuto rapidamente per diffusione tanto da diventare il browser più utilizzato in assoluto al mondo.Ne esistono versioni per Windows, macOS, Linux, Android e iOS: la pagina di download di Chrome permette di scaricare la versione più adatta al sistema in uso.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beginner’s Guide to NordVPN: What You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=802769</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/802769/beginners-guide-to-nordvpn-what-you-need-to-know/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T17:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NordVPN is a popular virtual private network that promises excellent streaming capabilities and is one the best VPNs out there. However, if you’re new to VPNs and you’re not too sure how to sign up or what your first steps should be once you have, let us help you get to know your brand-new VPN and set it up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fergus O'Sullivan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTG Deals: Best Price Ever on Galaxy S22 Ultra, Apple TV 4K, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=811749</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/811749/htg-deals-best-price-ever-on-galaxy-s22-ultra-apple-tv-4k-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T17:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week’s a scorcher across much of the United States, and the blazing-hot deals we uncovered are equally spicy. Find some of the lowest prices ever on the Samsung Galaxy S22 Ultra, Apple TV 4K, and Amazon Smart Thermostat, plus enjoy a huge 20% off site-wide sale over at Satechi and more. Read on for all the details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zach Laidlaw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rivian Delays Delivery of Its R1S Electric SUV, Again]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120950/rivian-delays-delivery-of-its-r1s-electric-suv-again/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120950/rivian-delays-delivery-of-its-r1s-electric-suv-again/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T16:44:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building a new electric vehicle brand from scratch, then beating big names like Ford to market is no easy task. And while Rivian did precisely that after several delays with the exciting R1T electric truck, the new R1S all-electric SUV is facing similar struggles.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Extortion gang ransoms Shoprite, largest supermarket chain in Africa]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/extortion-gang-ransoms-shoprite-largest-supermarket-chain-in-africa/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/extortion-gang-ransoms-shoprite-largest-supermarket-chain-in-africa/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T16:28:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shoprite Holdings, Africa's largest supermarket chain that operates almost three thousand stores across twelve countries in the continent, has been hit by a ransomware attack. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here's a First Look at the Nothing Phone 1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120951/heres-a-first-look-at-the-nothing-phone-1/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120951/heres-a-first-look-at-the-nothing-phone-1/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T16:26:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To build hype ahead of the July 12th launch event, Nothing just revealed a full photo of the Phone 1. This photo confirms some leaks and rumors about the device, though notably, the Phone 1 is less transparent than we expected.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come collegare il Mac alla TV]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2021/05/come-collegare-il-mac-alla-tv.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2021/05/come-collegare-il-mac-alla-tv.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T16:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I MacBook dispongono di un display ad alta risoluzione che permette di lavorare con una qualità eccelsa con qualsiasi app e in qualsiasi scenario. Per alcune app o per alcuni servizi possiamo sempre prendere in considerazione l'uso di televisore moderno come monitor aggiuntivo o come monitor esclusivo (come nel caso del Mac mini): lavorare sui fogli Excel su diagonali superiori ai 20 pollici è...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Enable Dark Mode on a Chromebook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809903</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809903/how-to-enable-dark-mode-on-a-chromebook/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T16:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows, Mac, iPhone, and Android all have dedicated Dark and Light Modes now. Chrome OS devices do too, though it’s not as easy to find. We’ll show you how to use Dark Mode on a Chromebook.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft: Windows update to permanently disable Internet Explorer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-windows-update-to-permanently-disable-internet-explorer/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-windows-update-to-permanently-disable-internet-explorer/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T15:56:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft confirmed today that a future Windows update will permanently disable the Internet Explorer web browser on users' systems. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This LEGO Ideas Jazz Quartet Set Really Has Some Soul]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120935/this-lego-ideas-jazz-quartet-set-really-has-some-soul/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120935/this-lego-ideas-jazz-quartet-set-really-has-some-soul/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T15:47:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LEGO has unveiled its third Ideas creation so far this year, the new LEGO Ideas Jazz Quartet set. Music lovers will enjoy building the 1,600-piece set and four different Jazz band members and their instruments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GE's Alexa-Enabled Washing Machine Is Smarter Than It Sounds]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120930/ges-alexa-enabled-washing-machine-is-smarter-than-it-sounds/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120930/ges-alexa-enabled-washing-machine-is-smarter-than-it-sounds/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T15:46:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smart appliances are usually half-baked, touting features that aren’t useful or just don’t work. But GE seems to be taking this whole “smart home” thing seriously. Its new Profile Top Load 900 washer uses smart features to take the guesswork out of laundry, and its Alexa integration does more than just send notifications to your phone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Happens If You Don’t Activate Windows?]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=494238</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15370358/what-happens-if-you-dont-activate-windows"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before Windows 10, you needed to activate your operating system. You had to pay for a license if you wanted a full and smooth experience while using your computer. Windows 10 and Windows 11 handle things very differently. So what actually happens when you don’t activate a modern copy of Microsoft Windows?
   

Content

What Does Activation Even Mean?
The Activation Watermark
Personalization Options Are Disabled
Activation Reminders in the Settings App
Activation Banner Popups
Potentially Limited Updates
"Freemium" Windows Isn't Official
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Link Your Android Phone to Windows
    
What Does Activation Even Mean?
    
Activating Windows means registering your status as a paid, licensed user. When you buy a new copy of Windows, it usually comes with a license key. Alternatively, you can have a digital entitlement linked to your Microsoft account. Some computers have... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sydney Butler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the Snipping Tool on Mac]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=808421</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/808421/how-to-use-the-snipping-tool-on-mac/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T15:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Microsoft Windows Snipping Tool is a marvelous time-saving feature for anyone who needs to capture Windows screenshots. On MacBooks and desktop Macs, there’s an equivalent function called Screenshot that’s even easier to use. All you need are a few keyboard shortcuts!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sydney Butler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How do I setup secret storage]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcwdo8/how_do_i_setup_secret_storage/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcwdo8/how_do_i_setup_secret_storage/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T14:55:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm looking for resources for how to setup secret storage. I legit can't find anything for some reason.
 Edit: I installed gnome keyring and it works now.
    submitted by    /u/purplesycamore  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Cloud region italiana: cosa significa e quali sono i vantaggi]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Google-Cloud-region-italiana-cosa-significa-e-quali-sono-i-vantaggi_24645</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Google-Cloud-region-italiana-cosa-significa-e-quali-sono-i-vantaggi_24645"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T14:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oggi è una data importante per il cloud italiano. Google Cloud, in collaborazione con TIM, ha annunciato l'avvio delle attività della prima cloud region italiana.Il termine cloud region viene comunemente utilizzato dai fornitori cloud e dagli utenti per identificare il data center attraverso il quale vengono erogati i servizi. In generale, quando si mettono delle applicazioni e dei servizi a disposizione degli utenti, i server dovrebbero essere fisicamente posizionati il più vicino possibile rispetto ai client collegati. In questo modo è possibile garantire prestazioni di primo livello massimizzando la banda disponibile e riducendo la latenza.Inoltre, utilizzare data center fisicamente posizionati entro i confini dell'Unione Europea consente di mettersi in regola con gli adempimenti previsti nel Regolamento generale sulla protezione dei dati (GDPR).La nuova cloud region inaugurata questa mattina a Milano (denominata europe-west8) è la prima delle due di Google Cloud che saranno utilizzate in italia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TIFU by updating zstd without updating glibc.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcw8o2/tifu_by_updating_zstd_without_updating_glibc/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcw8o2/tifu_by_updating_zstd_without_updating_glibc/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T14:49:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[And now my computer is a brick. How can one package cause so much damage? :(
    submitted by    /u/rigelbm  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Citrix warns critical bug can let attackers reset admin passwords]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/citrix-warns-critical-bug-can-let-attackers-reset-admin-passwords/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/citrix-warns-critical-bug-can-let-attackers-reset-admin-passwords/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T14:46:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Citrix warned customers to deploy security updates that address a critical Citrix Application Delivery Management (ADM) vulnerability that can let attackers reset admin passwords. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frequent crashes/hard freezes after fresh installation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcw32g/frequent_crasheshard_freezes_after_fresh/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcw32g/frequent_crasheshard_freezes_after_fresh/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T14:42:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey y'all. I just re-installed Arch after a few months on OpenSUSE and everything is (mostly) working, however, if I'm using Arch everything will freeze up and I can't find a way to un-freeze it within 10-20 minutes of booting (as long as I'm actually using the computer). 
 I just got a new motherboard and power supply, and installed those & the rest of my old parts into a new case, so I initially thought that might've been the issue. However, I was having BSODs in Windows, too, except those all mentioned "HYPERVISOR_ERROR" and once I turned off AMD SVM those seem to have gone away... so I mean, that's still something I need to figure out but virtualization isn't a huge deal for me so I'll kick that can down the road for now. I tried to update the BIOS before turning off SVM, but that didn't stop the Windows BSODs or the Arch freezes.
 Anyways, disabling SVM hasn't helped Arch at all. The journals are all a bit different, but it seems like the freezes usually happen while I'm using Firefox. I'm pretty sure I installed all the drivers that I need, but I'm not positive. Here's a copy of sudo journalctl -b -1 after rebooting from a freeze: https://pastebin.com/CVCwvC4j.
 I'm using Gnome with an AMD 3700x and an Nvidia GTX 1080. Any advice would be super appreciated! And let me know if I should provide any other info.
    submitted by    /u/NormGreen  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is there a pacman equivalent for `apt-mark minimize-manual`?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcw0hw/is_there_a_pacman_equivalent_for_aptmark/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcw0hw/is_there_a_pacman_equivalent_for_aptmark/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T14:38:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is there a command that go through the dependency tree and mark explicitly installed packages as dependency if possible?
    submitted by    /u/notnullnone  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sennheiser Packs a 60-Hour Battery In Momentum 4 Wireless Headphones]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120927/sennheiser-packs-a-60-hour-battery-in-momentum-4-wireless-headphones/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120927/sennheiser-packs-a-60-hour-battery-in-momentum-4-wireless-headphones/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T14:33:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two years ago, Review Geek scored the Sennheiser Momentum 3 Wireless headphones a 9/10 after a detailed review. But one small detail kept us from giving the Momentum 3 Wireless a perfect score—the battery life kinda stank. Did Sennheiser take that complaint to heart? Uh, yeah.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interpol seizes $50 million, arrests 2000 social engineers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/interpol-seizes-50-million-arrests-2000-social-engineers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/interpol-seizes-50-million-arrests-2000-social-engineers/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T14:26:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An international law enforcement operation, codenamed 'First Light 2022,' has seized 50 million dollars and arrested thousands of people involved in social engineering scams worldwide. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Connessione internet se va via la luce (senza energia elettrica)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/06/connessione-internet-se-va-via-la-luce.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/06/connessione-internet-se-va-via-la-luce.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T14:22:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tra gli scenari peggiori in cui possiamo imbatterci quando lavoriamo al PC spicca sicuramente l'assenza di energia elettrica, dovuta la maggior parte delle volte ad un blackout della rete elettrica a livello locale, regionale o nazionale. Rispetto a qualche anno fa possiamo ancora continuare a lavorare al PC anche durante i blackout, ma dobbiamo essere attrezzati in anticipo  per poter reggere i...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not starting, but everything is ok?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcvne5/not_starting_but_everything_is_ok/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcvne5/not_starting_but_everything_is_ok/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T14:21:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Just installed arch but when it boot’s om the ‘ok screen’, it find’s everything but dont take me further to the shell?
 Just stopped at mounting boot
 The ‘cursor’ on the buttom don’t blink’s just disappeared and can open a shell via alt + f1/f2?
 Please help
    submitted by    /u/Yha_Boiii  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web admin interfaces]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcveyh/web_admin_interfaces/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcveyh/web_admin_interfaces/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T14:10:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My home network currently has an old router running an OpenWRT router, an old server running an Open Media Vault NAS, and an old gaming computer running an Arch LAMP server. I want to add an MQTT server for home automation. None of these machines really do very much and I am pretty sure everything could run on a Raspberry Pi or an x86 SBC and save me a bunch of electricity, space, and noise.
 While I can configure everything from the CLI, I really like using the OpenWRT web interface LuCI and the Open Media Vault web interface when I need to deal with things from my phone or tablet. I know I can run OMV as a service on Debian, but would prefer to stick with Arch if I am going to move everything to a single machine.
 Looking at https://wiki.archlinux.org/title/Category:Web_admin_interfaces it looks like my choices for web interfaces are webmin and cockpit. Am I/the wiki missing an alternative? Is one obviously better than the other for my application or is it like vim/emacs? Is there a good online comparison of the two interfaces?
    submitted by    /u/AppointmentNearby161  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[InQuest Labs: Man + Machine vs Business Email Compromise (BEC)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/inquest-labs-man-plus-machine-vs-business-email-compromise-bec/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/inquest-labs-man-plus-machine-vs-business-email-compromise-bec/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Attackers only have to be right once while defenders need to be right 100% of the time. To help combat this asymmetric disadvantage, InQuest provides an open research portal that combines crowdsourced efforts with machine learning to combat the likes of Bumblebee and other BEC related threats. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sponsored by InQuest</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Cell Phone Plans of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=800503</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/800503/best-cell-phone-plan/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T14:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today’s cell phone market is flooded with multiple carriers, dozens of plans, and exorbitant monthly costs. We’re here to help. From unlimited data and family plans to prepaid options and more, here are the best cell phone plans available in 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Bitner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to easily switch from Chrome to Firefox]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.mozilla.org/?p=69205</id>
        <link href="https://blog.mozilla.org/en/products/firefox/how-to-switch-from-chrome-to-firefox/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T13:47:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s never been a better time to switch from Chrome to Firefox, if we do say so ourselves.  Some of the internet’s most popular ad blockers, such as uBlock Origin — tools that save our digital sanity from video ads that auto-play, banners that take up half the screen and pop-up windows with infuriatingly tiny […]
The post How to easily switch from Chrome to Firefox appeared first on The Mozilla Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kristina Bravo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is there AUR for `󰅂 flutter doctor`'s Linux x64 Dart SDK from Flutter engine?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcut58/is_there_aur_for_flutter_doctors_linux_x64_dart/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcut58/is_there_aur_for_flutter_doctors_linux_x64_dart/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T13:41:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[flutter doctor downloads "Linux x64 Dart SDK from Flutter engine"?
 It downloads each time I reinstall Flutter which I do when something has been broken.
    submitted by    /u/mishab_mizzunet  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I migliori programmi e app per gestire criptovalute]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/06/i-migliori-programmi-e-app-per-gestire.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/06/i-migliori-programmi-e-app-per-gestire.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T13:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Negli ultimi anni le criptovalute hanno assunto un ruolo sempre più importante nell'economia mondiale, diventando a tutti gli effetti un nuovo strumento con cui speculare a livello finanziario, sia direttamente (minando e/o vendendo la criptovaluta quando essa aumenta di valore) sia indirettamente (scommettendo sulla salita o sulla discesa del valore della criptovaluta).  
La criptovaluta più...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Happened to Celsius, the Crypto Lender?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=811412</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/811412/what-happened-to-celsius-the-crypto-lender/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T13:30:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto market has been rattled again in June 2022 due to a groundbreaking announcement made by crypto platform Celsius. The company announced it would no longer allow users to withdraw, swap, or transfer account balances.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>RJ Fulton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gozney Roccbox Pizza Oven Review: Restaurant-Quality in a Portable Package]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lifesavvy.com/131867/gozney-roccbox-pizza-oven-review/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lifesavvy.com/131867/gozney-roccbox-pizza-oven-review/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T13:30:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want delicious homemade pizza fresh from a pizza oven right in your own backyard? The Gozney Roccbox is a portable pizza oven powerhouse perfect for patio pizzas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Fitzpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Akamai Warns Of "Panchan" Linux Botnet That Leverages Golang Concurrency, Systemd]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Akamai-Security-Panchan</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Akamai-Security-Panchan"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T13:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Akamai Security Research today is lifting the public embargo on "Panchan", a new peer-to-peer botnet they are warning customers about that has been breaching Linux servers since March...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fwupd 1.7.8 To Further Improve Firmware Updating On Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Fwupd-1.7.8-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Fwupd-1.7.8-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T13:17:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fwupd 1.7.8 was released this morning as the newest version of this open-source utility built around the Linux Vendor Firmware Service (LVFS) for easy and practical updating of system and component firmware under Linux...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shelly Plug US Review: A Small, Smart Investment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120775/shelly-plug-us-review/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120775/shelly-plug-us-review/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T13:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can integrate any electrical appliance with an On/Off switch into your Amazon Alexa or Google Assistant ecosystem—all it takes is the Shelly Plug US. Plug it into the wall, connect your lamp, curling iron, or TV, and gain access to power controls right from your smartphone or smart speaker.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcus Mears III</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Does an Electric Car’s Battery Degrade?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=806181</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/806181/why-do-electric-car-batteries-degrade/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T13:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The large battery packs used in electric vehicles (EVs) are sturdier than the battery in your laptop, but they will degrade over time like any other lithium-ion battery. Here we’ll look at what causes the battery in an EV to degrade, and why.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Bogna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New peer-to-peer botnet infects Linux servers with cryptominers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-peer-to-peer-botnet-infects-linux-servers-with-cryptominers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-peer-to-peer-botnet-infects-linux-servers-with-cryptominers/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new peer-to-peer botnet named Panchan appeared in the wild around March 2022,  targeting Linux servers in the education sector to mine cryptocurrency. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LibreOffice 7.4 Beta Now Available With Performance Improvements, WebP Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=LibreOffice-7.4-Beta</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=LibreOffice-7.4-Beta"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T12:58:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Out today is the beta release of LibreOffice 7.4 as the newest feature release in development for this cross-platform, open-source office suite...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Docker Build Args to Configure Image Builds]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?post_type=devops&amp;p=800750</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/devops/how-to-use-docker-build-args-to-configure-image-builds/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T12:48:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Docker’s “build args” mechanism lets you define environment variables that can be referenced in your Dockerfile during image builds. Unlike regular ENV instructions, build args are not present inside the final output image. They’re for cases where you want to configure the build process instead of created containers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Docker Build Args to Configure Image Builds]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?post_type=devops&amp;p=800750</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/devops/how-to-use-docker-build-args-to-configure-image-builds/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T12:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Docker’s “build args” mechanism lets you define environment variables that can be referenced in your Dockerfile during image builds. Unlike regular ENV instructions, build args are not present inside the final output image. They’re for cases where you want to configure the build process instead of created containers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Choose the Git Workflow & Branching Model That’s Right for Your Team]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?post_type=devops&amp;p=800755</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/devops/how-to-choose-the-git-workflow-branching-model-thats-right-for-your-team/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T12:47:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git is a version control system at the heart of almost all software development—it’s used to store and track changes to the code you write. When working in teams, having an easy-to-follow workflow that works for your business is crucial to fast development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Heddings</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Choose the Git Workflow & Branching Model That’s Right for Your Team]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?post_type=devops&amp;p=800755</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/devops/how-to-choose-the-git-workflow-branching-model-thats-right-for-your-team/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T12:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git is a version control system at the heart of almost all software development—it’s used to store and track changes to the code you write. When working in teams, having an easy-to-follow workflow that works for your business is crucial to fast development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Heddings</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ubuntu Core 22 Released For IoT & Embedded Devices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Ubuntu-Core-22</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Ubuntu-Core-22"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T12:37:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Canonical has officially released Ubuntu Core 22 as its fully containerized version of Ubuntu 22.04 LTS that is optimized for IoT and edge computing use-cases...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft: June Windows Server updates may cause backup issues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-june-windows-server-updates-may-cause-backup-issues/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-june-windows-server-updates-may-cause-backup-issues/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T12:34:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft says that some applications might fail to backup data using Volume Shadow Copy Service (VSS) after applying the June 2022 Patch Tuesday Windows updates. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Which Mobile Carriers Have Truly Unlimited Plans in the U.S?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=804072</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/804072/which-mobile-carriers-have-truly-unlimited-plans-in-the-u.s/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T12:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most mobile data plans that are advertised as “unlimited” are not really unlimited. There are little things that limit how much data you can realistically use. Do any carriers offer truly unlimited plans? Not as many as you might think.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XFMEXPRESS: cos'è e come funziona lo storage esterno flash NAND PCIe 4.0]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=XFMEXPRESS-cos-e-e-come-funziona-lo-storage-esterno-flash-NAND-PCIe-40_24644</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=XFMEXPRESS-cos-e-e-come-funziona-lo-storage-esterno-flash-NAND-PCIe-40_24644"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T11:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Un nuovo standard si aggiunge a quelli già disponibili per lo storage dei dati: se ad esempio UFS 4 è stato sviluppato con il preciso scopo di migliorare le prestazioni delle memorie interne dei dispositivi portatili, XFMEXPRESS porta le performance dello storage rimovibile a un altro livello.Kioxia (ex Toshiba) ha presentato la sua prima scheda compatibile XFMEXPRESS, uno standard approvato dal JEDEC, organismo di standardizzazione dei semiconduttori della Electronic Industries Alliance.La principale novità del prodotto firmato Kioxia risiede nell'utilizzo dell'interfaccia PCIe 4.0 con l'obiettivo di portare le prestazioni delle unità esterne a livelli mai visti prima. Tanto che i portavoce di Kioxia si spingono a sostenere che lo storage esterno XFMEXPRESS sarà una valida alternativa alle unità SSD.

Tra le caratteristiche di primo piano anche il fattore di forma: con dimensioni pari a 14 x 18 x 1,4 mm, la memoria esterna XFMEXPRESS presentata da Kioxia consente di non sacrificare spazio sui dispositivi che per loro natura già devono essere ultracompatti.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will VPNs Be Forced to Log Your Traffic?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809641</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809641/will-vpns-be-forced-to-log-your-traffic/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T11:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The heat is on, and VPNs are feeling the pressure. More and more governments are cracking down on online anonymity on the one hand, while Hollywood is doing whatever it takes to crack down on piracy. As a result, something unthinkable may become a reality: VPNs that are forced to log traffic. Is this fear realistic, or is it just a knee-jerk panic reaction?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fergus O'Sullivan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I need your opinion :)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcrezd/i_need_your_opinion/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcrezd/i_need_your_opinion/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T10:29:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Okey I'm fairly new to arch, and I'm already knowing that keeping your system organized is the most important thing ever. 
 Now there are two things I don't know how u guys do.
 1: How do you keep track of not used packages and folders? Example: let's try to setup a tftp server ahhh openssh install that doesn't work some demon packages a to make openssh work. And now I dont use it but what did I install two weeks ago what I don't use?
 2: Making the system more robust? I saw some people talk about multiple kernels and better ways to install packages? I installed Nvidia with Wayland KDE and the system doesn't boot anymore (reading In the wiki: Nvidia and Wayland doesn't work because of a security feature) but if I install all packages at once I never find the trouble making package that causes the bootcrash? How do u arch users do that?
 Thanks in advance
    submitted by    /u/Pure_Pasifist  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Teams to Add Fun to Meetings with Casual Games]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=497441</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15369871/microsoft-teams-meetings-with-casual-games"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T10:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now that much of our business is conducted through videoconferencing, we could use a few ways to spice it up. Thankfully, Microsoft understands that, as it continues its plans to make video conferencing less boring and more useful. Sources say the next change will be integrating Casual Games into Microsoft Teams. After all, Solitaire could improve anything.
   
Also read:How to Turn Your Raspberry Pi into a Video Conferencing Station
    
Games in Teams Meetings
    
Videoconferencing has been a big part of conducting business for quite some time. But the pandemic caused us all to use Microsoft Teams, Skype, Zoom, etc., in ways we hadn’t imagined. These are now tools we use for work, at home, and even at school.
    
The increased competition between the video conferencing platforms is causing them to make changes to be more enticing. Let’s face it: it can be boring to sit through meeting after meeting,... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mesa 22.2 Adds Option To Enable Compute Engine For Intel Arc Graphics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Mesa-INTEL_COMPUTE_CLASS</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Mesa-INTEL_COMPUTE_CLASS"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T10:19:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the in-development Linux 5.19 kernel there is compute engine support for DG2/Alchemist graphics now exposed to user-space. Besides the Intel OpenCL Runtime / oneAPI Level Zero preparing to make use of that compute engine support, patches merged today to Mesa 22.2 also allow enabling the DG2-class Arc Graphics compute support within the OpenGL/Vulkan drivers...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PrivacyTests reveals how your web browser does privacy-wise]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179185</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/15/privacytests-reveals-how-your-web-browser-does-privacy-wise/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T10:12:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All web browsers support some privacy features, some more than others, but none protect users 100% against all privacy threats; that is the quintessence of the tests that PrivacyTests runs regularly. PrivacyTests […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post PrivacyTests reveals how your web browser does privacy-wise appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photoshop e Illustrator in versione Web: cosa permettono di fare]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Photoshop-e-Illustrator-in-versione-Web-cosa-permettono-di-fare_23701</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Photoshop-e-Illustrator-in-versione-Web-cosa-permettono-di-fare_23701"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T10:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adobe ha annunciato a ottobre 2021 tutta una serie di novità per Photoshop e Illustrator nelle versioni per sistemi desktop ed Apple iPad.Una delle innovazioni di maggior rilevanza consiste nell'arrivo di Photoshop e Illustrator in versione Web.L'idea non era quella di replicare in tutto e per tutto le funzionalità dei due programmi in versione desktop ma permettere ai collaboratori di aprire e visualizzare un lavoro da browser per fornire commenti e riscontri, proprio come si può fare con Google Documenti od Office Online.Attualmente è possibile memorizzare un progetto realizzato con Photoshop o Illustrator sul cloud di Adobe (Creative Cloud) e permettere a chiunque di aprirlo da remoto: è però necessario usare le applicazioni desktop o l'app per iPad.Con la versione Web di Photoshop e Illustrator i colleghi possono rivedere e aggiungere commenti direttamente nel browser senza dover scaricare applicazioni o avere un abbonamento a Creative Cloud.Adobe osserva che il miglior risultato si ottiene quando si dà voce agli altri nel processo creativo.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Time-Saving Apps For Freelance Workers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/?p=33959</id>
        <link href="https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/time-tracking-invoicing-apps/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T10:01:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A regular employee is paid on the basis of the working hours set by company but freelancers are mostly paid according to the time they spend on the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Dagli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CleanMyMac X Review: One Click for a Tidy Mac]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809850</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809850/cleanmymac-x-review/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T10:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MacPaw’s CleanMyMac X is a one-stop-shop app that keeps your Mac spick-and-span even if you’re not keen on getting under the software hood yourself. The user-friendly UI makes its host of features a breeze to utilize when you need to and easy to hide away when you don’t. Here’s what you should know.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcus Mears III</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dasharo 1.0 Open-Source Firmware Released For MSI Alder Lake Motherboard]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Dasharo-1.0-Z690-A-Port</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Dasharo-1.0-Z690-A-Port"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier this year the folks at firmware consulting firm 3mdeb announced a open-source Coreboot port to a retail Intel Alder Lake motherboard. It's very exciting since outside of Chromebooks, IHV reference boards, and custom server platforms at hyperscalers, it's still rare to find Coreboot support on modern, retail boards. That "Dasharo" open-source firmware effort for the MSI Z690-A WiFi DDR4 has come together nicely over a matter of weeks and the developers are now celebrating their v1.0 release...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Falla di sicurezza nelle CPU Intel e AMD: quanto è davvero pericolosa Hertzbleed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Falla-di-sicurezza-nelle-CPU-Intel-e-AMD-quanto-e-davvero-pericolosa-Hertzbleed_24643</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Falla-di-sicurezza-nelle-CPU-Intel-e-AMD-quanto-e-davvero-pericolosa-Hertzbleed_24643"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T09:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[La caccia alle vulnerabilità di tipo side-channel all'interno dei browser Web è diventata uno degli sport più in voga in ambito accademico.Un team di ricercatori delle università del Texas, dell'Illinois Urbana-Champaign e di Washington hanno scoperto una nuova vulnerabilità che affligge tanto le CPU Intel quanto le CPU AMD.Battezzato Hertzbleed il nuovo attacco può portare alla sottrazione delle chiavi crittografiche osservando le variazioni nella frequenza del processore attivate e gestite attraverso il meccanismo DVFS (dynamic voltage and frequency scaling).Ciò è possibile perché sia sulla piattaforma Intel che su quella AMD l'adattamento delle frequenze di lavoro è funzione dei consumi energetici e dei carichi di lavoro.DVFS attiva il throttling delle prestazioni per garantire che il sistema non superi i limiti termici e di potenza durante carichi elevati; contribuisce inoltre a ridurre il consumo energetico complessivo quando la CPU è scarsamente sollecitata.Hertzbleed dimostra come gli attacchi possano essere lanciati anche in modalità remota.Intel conferma che Hertzbleed interessa tutti i suoi processori e che l'attacco può essere sfruttato da remoto in attacchi ad alta complessità che non richiedono l'interazione dell'utente.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Programmi per tagliare, dividere e unire file Audio e MP3]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2009/02/audio-editor-su-file-mp3-per-mixare.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2009/02/audio-editor-su-file-mp3-per-mixare.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T09:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Una delle attività che è possibile svolgere con efficacia sul PC è senza ombra di dubbio la modifica dei file MP3. Se abbiamo una grande raccolta di brani in formato digitale e vogliamo ricavare una suoneria da inviare al telefono, l'uso di questi programmi vi permetterà di ricavare solo il ritornello o la parte preferita del brano, così da poterla successivamente inviare al telefono.

 In...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft's "Dozen" Prepares For Vulkan 1.1 Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Microsoft-Dzn-Vulkan-1.1-Nears</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Microsoft-Dzn-Vulkan-1.1-Nears"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T09:40:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Merged earlier this year into Mesa was "Dozen" for Vulkan on Direct3D 12 for use with Microsoft's Windows Subsystem for Linux or in Windows cases where there may be a D3D12 driver installed but no Vulkan support. This is akin to the layering work Microsoft already supports for leveraging Mesa to provide OpenCL and OpenGL atop Direct3D 12. That "Dozen" driver is now readying Vulkan 1.1 support...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Android: le app che rubano i dati sul Play Store sono in forte crescita]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Android-le-app-che-rubano-i-dati-sul-Play-Store-sono-in-forte-crescita_24642</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Android-le-app-che-rubano-i-dati-sul-Play-Store-sono-in-forte-crescita_24642"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T09:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I ricercatori di Dr. Web riferiscono che le applicazioni Android contenenti adware e trojan capaci di sottrarre informazioni personali degli utenti sono in forte crescita e a maggio 2022 sono diventate le minacce più diffuse per i possessori di dispositivi mobili basati sul robottino verde.Ai vertici per diffusione ci sono le app Android che integrano componenti in grado di rubare dati attingendo al contenuto delle notifiche generate da altre applicazioni installate sullo stesso dispositivo. L'obiettivo principale consiste nel sottrarre i codici OTP per superare l'autenticazione a due fattori e assumere il controllo degli altrui account.Il fatto è che molte applicazioni malevole riescono ancora oggi a infiltrarsi nel Google Play Store superando le verifiche automatizzate e violando le norme alle quali tutti gli sviluppatori dovrebbero attenersi (il download di componenti da server di terze parti è proibito).Come si legge nel report di Dr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux SoC Patches Revised For The AMD Pensando Elba]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMD-Pensando-Elba-Patches</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMD-Pensando-Elba-Patches"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T09:18:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier this year Pensando engineers began posting Linux patches for enabling their Elba DPU SoC. This data processing unit is powered by 16 x Arm Cortex-A72 cores and designed for supporting up to dual 200GE networking with this SoC intended for high-end networking equipment. It didn't take long for the AMD integration less than one month after AMD completed its Pensando acquisition with the new Linux patches now reflected as the AMD Pensando Elba...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cookies: come funzionano le protezioni di Mozilla e Google]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Cookies-come-funzionano-le-protezioni-di-Mozilla-e-Google_24641</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Cookies-come-funzionano-le-protezioni-di-Mozilla-e-Google_24641"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T08:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gli editori online che come noi sostengono le proprie attività senza chiedere un centesimo ai lettori utilizzano l'advertising per autofinanziarsi. La maggior parte dei circuiti pubblicitari utilizza i cookie, piccoli file di testo che vengono generati sui dispositivi degli utenti, per tracciare le visite sui siti Web che contengono lo stesso codice per la gestione dell'advertising.Il legislatore europeo ha pensato di dover regolamentare la questione decidendo però di non intervenire né sui circuiti pubblicitari né sugli sviluppatori di browser Web: ad attivarsi per bloccare i cookie di terza parte è l''ultima ruota del carro' ovvero i gestori di siti Web, anche quelli amatoriali e di piccole dimensioni.Registriamo ad oggi un'attenzione sproporzionata sui cookie quando dalla notte dei tempi il browser contiene gli strumenti per rimuoverli completamente, anche all'atto della chiusura del programma. Abbiamo visto come cancellare la cronologia del browser in modo completo in modo da non lasciare sul dispositivo alcuna traccia della navigazione online.Per non parlare della modalità di navigazione in incognito che consente di avviare una nuova sessione di navigazione cancellando tutti i dati, cookie compresi, alla chiusura della finestra.Troppa attenzione sui cookie, dicevamo, quando esistono modalità subdole per tracciare le attività online degli utenti senza rendere palese l'utilizzo di queste stesse tecniche (i.e.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Program class]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcpyfl/program_class/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcpyfl/program_class/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T08:44:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey,
 what was the command to see the class of a program? I remember having crosshair for mouse and then click on program and it was telling me the class for my config so I can bind it to a ws.... I cant find it
    submitted by    /u/Fair-Promise4552  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel Arc A380 Desktop Graphics Launch In China]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-Arc-A380-China</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-Arc-A380-China"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T08:23:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overnight Intel announced that the Arc A380 desktop GPU has launched in China and will begin appearing in the Chinese market this month...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Patch day Microsoft di giugno 2022: risolta anche la vulnerabilità Follina]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Patch-day-Microsoft-di-giugno-2022-risolta-anche-la-vulnerabilita-Follina_24640</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Patch-day-Microsoft-di-giugno-2022-risolta-anche-la-vulnerabilita-Follina_24640"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T07:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Come ogni mese eccoci a fare il punto sulle vulnerabilità che Microsoft ha risolto nei suoi software.Il patch day Microsoft di giugno 2022 ha fatto registrare il rilascio di un totale di 55 aggiornamenti di sicurezza. Con il suo intervento l'azienda di Redmond risolve una falla zero day già nota ai criminali informatici e 3 vulnerabilità a elevata criticità.La lacuna di sicurezza zero day è l'attacco conosciuto con l'appellativo Follina del quale abbiamo parlato nei giorni scorsi.Conosciuto con l'identificativo CVE-2022-30190, il problema riguarda tutte le versioni di Windows ed è molto utilizzato dagli aggressori per disporre l'esecuzione di codice arbitrario sui sistemi delle vittime senza alcun tipo di interazione da parte degli utenti.La falla è insita nel componente Windows Support Diagnostic Tool (MSDT), utilizzato per inviare a Microsoft informazioni sui crash delle applicazioni in esecuzione.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thousands of GitHub, AWS, Docker tokens exposed in Travis CI logs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/thousands-of-github-aws-docker-tokens-exposed-in-travis-ci-logs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/thousands-of-github-aws-docker-tokens-exposed-in-travis-ci-logs/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T07:21:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For a second time in less than a year, the Travis CI platform for software development and testing has exposed user data containing authentication tokens that could give access to developers' accounts on GitHub, Amazon Web Services, and Docker Hub. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Ilascu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trouble installing Arch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcnsle/trouble_installing_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcnsle/trouble_installing_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T06:11:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the bios I disabled secure boot and I chose my flash drive as the first option and windows as the 2nd option and when I exit the bios I am greeted back with windows.
 My laptop is the Lenovo G580
    submitted by    /u/GreenScoutis  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft explains how it is retiring Internet Explorer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179183</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/15/microsoft-explains-how-it-is-retiring-internet-explorer/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T05:14:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On June 15, 2022, Microsoft is retiring its Internet Explorer browser. The move affects most Windows 10 devices, but there are devices on which Internet Explorer remains available. Even on Windows 10, […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Microsoft explains how it is retiring Internet Explorer appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hibernation fails and locks me out completely]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcmolo/hibernation_fails_and_locks_me_out_completely/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcmolo/hibernation_fails_and_locks_me_out_completely/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T05:01:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have 16GB RAM and 10 GB swap, sometimes when the RAM is around 9GB and I hibernate the hibernation fails with the error no space left on the device.
 I have xss-lock which uses I3lock as a way to lock the screen and it runs before hibernation as per systemd inhibitors, when the hibernation fails I never get the keyboard back on the lock screen although I can see it via SSH that it's present.
 Even loginctl isn't able to unlock the screen. Any clues or tips as to what may help? Reisub was disabled I have enabled it now.
    submitted by    /u/afro_coder  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Android SDK fails to run: How to install it properly?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vclvj4/android_sdk_fails_to_run_how_to_install_it/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vclvj4/android_sdk_fails_to_run_how_to_install_it/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T04:12:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SOLVED:
 I installed android-sdk package for flutter. But flutter doctor cannot detect android sdk. Then sdkmanager fails to run like,
 ``` sdkmanager
 Exception in thread "main" java.lang.NoClassDefFoundError: javax/xml/bind/annotation/XmlSchema at com.android.repository.api.SchemaModule$SchemaModuleVersion.<init>(SchemaModule.java:156) at com.android.repository.api.SchemaModule.<init>(SchemaModule.java:75) at com.android.sdklib.repository.AndroidSdkHandler.<clinit>(AndroidSdkHandler.java:81) at com.android.sdklib.tool.sdkmanager.SdkManagerCli.main(SdkManagerCli.java:73) at com.android.sdklib.tool.sdkmanager.SdkManagerCli.main(SdkManagerCli.java:48) Caused by: java.lang.ClassNotFoundException: javax.xml.bind.annotation.XmlSchema at java.base/jdk.internal.loader.BuiltinClassLoader.loadClass(BuiltinClassLoader.java:641) at java.base/jdk.internal.loader.ClassLoaders$AppClassLoader.loadClass(ClassLoaders.java:188) at java.base/java.lang.ClassLoader.loadClass(ClassLoader.java:521) ... 5 more ```
 I tried reinstalling, rebooting, removing /opt/{android-sdk,flutter} several times. Nothing helped.
 Can you help me?
 Thanks
    submitted by    /u/mishab_mizzunet  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to find Chrome rendered font?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcjh2w/how_to_find_chrome_rendered_font/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcjh2w/how_to_find_chrome_rendered_font/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T02:01:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Firefox, there is Inspector->Fonts tab.
 In Chrome, there is no Fonts tab. This post says chrome has Element->Computed -> Rendered Fonts, but on my box (version 102.x). Did chrome remove this functionality, or move it somewhere else?
    submitted by    /u/notnullnone  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Panda Wireless PAU09 & Arch Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcis4s/panda_wireless_pau09_arch_linux/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcis4s/panda_wireless_pau09_arch_linux/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T01:25:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have had many many problems getting the PAU09 to work on arch, sometimes it works for hours, other times not at all, and some times for a few minutes, after that dmesg is either spammed with rt2x00usb_vendor_request: Error - Vendor request 0x07 failed for offset 0x101c with error -110 or rt2800usb_fill_rxdone: Error - Bad frame size (varying number), forcing to 0, rt2x00lib_rxdone: Error - Wrong frame size 0 max 3840
 Please help, as I can not stay online for long without getting disconnected
    submitted by    /u/Official_Nugget  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SSD vs. SSHD: Are Hybrid Drives Worth It in 2022?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=post-ideas&amp;p=350605</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/13762015/ssd-vs-sshd-are-hybrid-drives-worth-it"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In only a few years, the solid state disks (SSD) have nearly replaced magnetic hard disks (HDD) as the default storage option in laptops and PCs. However, there is also now an option of a solid state hybrid drive (SSHD), offering the best of SSD and HDD. So which one is better? The only way to find out is through a head-to-head comparison as shown here. 
   

Content

Differences Between SSD and SSHD
1. Raw Speed Comparison
2. Benchmark Speed Comparison
3. Load Time Comparison 
4. Price vs. Capacity Comparison
5. Life Expectancy: SSD vs. SSHD
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:SSD vs. HDD vs. USB Flash Drive: Everything You Need to Know
    
Differences Between SSD and SSHD
    
SSD is flash storage similar to a USB drive but is much... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sayak Boral</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ransomware gang creates site for employees to search for their stolen data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ransomware-gang-creates-site-for-employees-to-search-for-their-stolen-data/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ransomware-gang-creates-site-for-employees-to-search-for-their-stolen-data/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T23:03:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ALPHV ransomware gang, aka BlackCat, has brought extortion to a new level by creating a dedicated website that allows the customers and employees of their victim to check if their data was stolen in an attack [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zoom windows are magic cloaks? (screen sharing issues)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcfutj/zoom_windows_are_magic_cloaks_screen_sharing/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcfutj/zoom_windows_are_magic_cloaks_screen_sharing/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T22:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sharing my whole screen in Zoom is somewhat broken for me, as Zoom's own windows obscure the stream in weird ways. I noticed this running it with dwm, but easily reproduced it with KDE Plasma.
 For background on how the program works, there are three windows involved: - The screen sharing overlay, on all desktops. Present when screen sharing. - The meeting overlay, on all desktops. Present when screen sharing. - The Zoom home menu. Functions as a normal window with normal window decorations.
 Issues with sharing the whole screen in KDE Plasma: - The panel rendering is inconsistent. On occasion it will disappear or go black in the stream. See this host view (pink censoring added in editing). - On any desktop other than the first, parts of the stream are obscured by the Zoom overlays. Within…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Proton 7.0-3 With More Games Running Well On Linux, Experimental Preps More Changes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Proton-7.0-3-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Proton-7.0-3-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T22:31:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Valve today promoted Proton 7.0-3 to stable as the newest version of this software based on Wine and leveraging DXVK / VKD3D-Proton and other components for running Windows games with great success on Linux. Proton 7.0-3 is now available for Steam Play when firing up the Steam client while Valve also today issued a new Proton Experimental update...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[arch is stuck too much !!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcf302/arch_is_stuck_too_much/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcf302/arch_is_stuck_too_much/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T22:16:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, my arch stucks too much and I can do nothing. When it happens I see that the clock seconds is frozen (not changing) I can't even use my system like that ! anyone got that problem ??
 I use gnome 42.2 BTW. If you need any command to troubleshoot tell me!
    submitted by    /u/Spare_Prize1148  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GIMP 2.10.32 Released With JPEG-XL Backported & Other Work While Waiting On GIMP 3.0]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=GIMP-2.10.32-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=GIMP-2.10.32-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T22:12:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have been writing about GIMP 3.0 for nearly a decade and with that stable release still out of sight, GIMP 2.10.32 is out as a six-month update to the aging GIMP 2.10 stable series...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adobe Photoshop Might Soon Be Available for Free]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=811617</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/811617/adobe-photoshop-might-soon-be-available-for-free/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T21:37:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adobe Photoshop has been a paid product for its entire lifetime (unless you sail on the high seas), but now the company is testing a free version accessible through the web.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Broadcom]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vce2b6/broadcom/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vce2b6/broadcom/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T21:27:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So I have a MacBook Pro 7,1 and it has a bcm4322 Wi-Fi card I’ve tried broadcom-wl and broadcom-wl-dkms and b43-firmware but I can’t get Wi-Fi to work after a reboot I’ve tried everything such as blacklisting modules and I’m just kind of stuck…
    submitted by    /u/Expensive_Pudding846  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows Security Not Opening in Windows? Here are 6 Fixes]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=488171</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15368624/fix-windows-security-not-opening"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows Security, which also includes an antivirus program known as Windows Defender, is designed to protect your PC from viruses and malware. But just like other Windows apps, it can run into problems.
    
One of the issues is Windows Security failing to start. Fortunately, we have some quick fixes for you.
   

Content

1. Reset or Repair Windows Security
2. Use SFC and DISM
3. Disable Background Apps
4. Disable and Uninstall Third-Party Security Tools
5. Install the Latest Windows Updates
6. Restart Windows Security Center Service
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:The Best Windows 10 and 11 Easter Eggs to Seek Out
    
1. Reset or Repair Windows Security
    
Windows 11 comes with a native repair tool that can identify minor issues in apps and resolve them automatically. Windows Security is no exception.... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Kanyoro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are the mirrors throttling me?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcdmsc/are_the_mirrors_throttling_me/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcdmsc/are_the_mirrors_throttling_me/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T21:06:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey folks! So I have lately installed arch about a dozen times and the same thing keeps happening to me, no matter if I change my PC, network, am in a VM or on real hardware. To my knowledge the arch iso updates the mirrors once. Everytime my download rate starts at 50mb/s which gets the job done really quickly, but over the course of 10-30s it goes down to just 100kb/s and stays at that rate. Which surprisingly only happens with Arch. Am I being throttled in some way or another and is there a way to fix this issue, as it makes the download take an hour or two instead of the 3 minutes it would usually take. Thanks :)
    submitted by    /u/OakArtz  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Change Windows 10’s Wallpaper Without Activation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=717894</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/717894/how-to-change-windows-10s-wallpaper-without-activation/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you use an unactivated copy of Windows 10, you know that you can’t change your desktop wallpaper using the Settings app. But there’s a workaround to change the desktop background on an unactivated copy of Windows 10.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Is NVIDIA Shield TV so Expensive?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120880/why-is-nvidia-shield-tv-so-expensive/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120880/why-is-nvidia-shield-tv-so-expensive/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T20:56:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most streaming sticks from Roku, Google, and Amazon cost less than $50 and support 4K video. But the NVIDIA Shield TV starts at $150, a price that’s only matched by Apple TV boxes. It’s an outrageous amount of money to pay for a streaming stick, but still, the NVIDIA Shield TV is worth every penny.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Requesting thoughts + answers about double GPU]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vccb3o/requesting_thoughts_answers_about_double_gpu/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vccb3o/requesting_thoughts_answers_about_double_gpu/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T20:08:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So ever since I built my 1st system I've wanted to do xfire. I hear negative things about it and until now my GPU was 3x what I paid for it thanks to coin miners. Now prices are starting to settle down and I can get an identical graphics card for a realistic price. So I have questions/would like thoughts about the pros and cons of this setup.
 I mostly use my computer to work but also for gaming. I have 2 monitors + 2 tvs that I use for screens. I recently switched over to Arch as my base system and load various OSes via VMs which I really, really enjoy. 
 The problem is I don't know how much a 2nd GPU would help me or if it would do more harm than good. I understand it would use much more energy, have little payoff in terms of framerate, but am considering it both for xfire, passthru, and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Relative newbie to Arch, but computer-literate1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcc7zk/relative_newbie_to_arch_but_computerliterate1/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcc7zk/relative_newbie_to_arch_but_computerliterate1/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T20:04:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi,
 I've been dicking with computers for around 45 years, so no not a newbie in that sense.
 Then I migrated from Mandriva, through Magiea, and then into Ubuntu.
 Now trying for the first time to install raw Arch. Tried six times on my old BIOS-boot netbook and once in a UEFI-boot virtual machine on my current whoop-de-whoop laptop.
 On all of these, everything goes swimmingly, until the point when I exit the chroot environment and then reboot. All I ever then get is a 'grub' prompt rather than a usable OS!
 I'm guessing I've either missed a step, or something else is messed up. Assistance would be welcome.
    submitted by    /u/Bytebrother  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Copy Files to a USB Flash Drive on a Mac]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=720039</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/720039/how-to-copy-files-to-a-usb-flash-drive-on-a-mac/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’d like to copy files to a USB flash drive on a Mac so you can transfer them to another machine or back them up, it’s easy to do using Finder in macOS. Here’s how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Single Beaver Caused Internet Outages in Canada]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=811604</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/811604/a-single-beaver-caused-internet-outages-in-canada/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T19:58:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Internet outages are common, especially in rural areas where it can take a while for internet service providers to find the source of a problem. That just happened earlier this month in Canada, where a beaver was responsible for a long-lasting internet outage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Hertzbleed side-channel attack affects Intel, AMD CPUs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-hertzbleed-side-channel-attack-affects-intel-amd-cpus/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-hertzbleed-side-channel-attack-affects-intel-amd-cpus/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T19:55:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new side-channel attack known as Hertzbleed allows remote attackers to steal full cryptographic keys by observing variations in CPU frequency enabled by dynamic voltage and frequency scaling (DVFS). [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My NUC server, plugged into a monitor, doesn't display anything until the Arch login prompt, skipping boot screens and the screen where I can choose what disk to boot into. How can I fix this?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcbutr/my_nuc_server_plugged_into_a_monitor_doesnt/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcbutr/my_nuc_server_plugged_into_a_monitor_doesnt/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T19:47:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Problem: My NUC server, plugged into a monitor, doesn't display anything until the login prompt, skipping boot screens and the screen where I can choose what disk to boot into.
 Background: I installed Arch on a NUC and plugged in a keyboard (USB) and a monitor (Mini Display Port on the NUC to HDMI on the monitor). Nothing appears on the monitor until I get to the login prompt, so it skips right over the NUC splash screen and the screen that lets me select what disk to boot into. Very rarely if I turn on the monitor and the NUC at exactly the right times with respect to each other, I can see the disk selection screen for a brief moment. And if I press any keys to prevent the system from getting to the arch login prompt (e.g. F2/ F10/ <Down + enter> to enter the firmware options screen), then nothing at all appears on my screen at any point. It's not even a black screen - the monitor is telling me there is no input whatsoever (except, like I said, when the the login screen appears.)
 Occasionally I also see some of the logs for a moment before the login (the ones starting with [ok]
 ).
 My question: I want to be able to select a different disk to boot from (e.g. a. USB with arch.iso so I can reinstall arch) but I can't access the screen to do that. Any ideas?
 What I've tried: Holding shift on startup; using a different Mini-DP to HDMI cable; plugging into my television's HDMI instead of the monitor
    submitted by    /u/_cs  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Laptop energy saving TLP package. Any experienced here?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcbo0y/laptop_energy_saving_tlp_package_any_experienced/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcbo0y/laptop_energy_saving_tlp_package_any_experienced/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T19:39:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello!
 It is my intention to install in my laptop with Arch in order to save battery the package TLP (https://wiki.archlinux.org/title/TLP) and I wanted to know your experiences with this software.
 The package is presented as a install-and-forget. That is pretty anti-arch philosophy, so I wanted to read some opinion/experience with it.
 Alternatives are welcome, my main way to save energy right now is to low the brightness. It ain't much but it's honest work.
 Thank you all!
    submitted by    /u/HansDCJ  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Android malware on the Google Play Store gets 2 million downloads]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/android-malware-on-the-google-play-store-gets-2-million-downloads/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/android-malware-on-the-google-play-store-gets-2-million-downloads/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T19:36:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered adware and information-stealing malware on the Google Play Store last month, with at least five still available and having amassed over two million downloads. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save $60 on an Amazon Fire HD 10 Kids Tablet]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=426537</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/14739303/amazon-fire-hd-10-kids-pro-tablet"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is your child already bored and looking for stuff to do this summer? Consider an Amazon Fire HD 10 Kids Tablet to keep their minds sharp during the summer months. They can have their own tablet – yet one that will be safe as well, eliminating your parental concerns.
    
Bear in mind that this is in no way a child’s toy. It’s a full-featured tablet for ages 6 through 12. It has an octa-core processor, 3GB RAM, and a 10.1″ Full HD display with strengthened aluminosilicate, dual cameras, and USB-C port. The storage is expandable up to 1 TB. You’ll have no concerns about the tablet breaking, as it carries a two-year worry-free guarantee.
   
 
   
A one-year Amazon Kids+ subscription is included with the Fire 10 Kids Tablet. It unlocks more than 20,000 apps, games, books, videos, songs, and audiobooks. The purchase includes educational content from PBS Kids, Nickelodeon, Disney, and more. The subscription will automatically renew after one year, when you will be charged $4.99 plus tax monthly. Easily cancel at... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bluetooth earphones connected but make no sound]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcavsh/bluetooth_earphones_connected_but_make_no_sound/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vcavsh/bluetooth_earphones_connected_but_make_no_sound/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T19:03:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi there, I am one of the arch newbies and I am in the phase of switching from Windows to a Linux distro.
 I decided to install arch today.
 However, when I try to connect my bluetooth earphones, they are connected but make no sound.
 Can someone help me?
 Thanks.
    submitted by    /u/AsuxAX  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Delete Videos on Facebook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=810067</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/810067/how-to-delete-videos-on-facebook/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T19:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Regret uploading that video to Facebook that you thought was funny? No worries, you can always delete the videos you’ve uploaded to your Facebook account. You can do this from both your desktop and your mobile, and we’ll show you how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 KB5014697 update adds Spotlight for Desktop, fixes 33 bugs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-kb5014697-update-adds-spotlight-for-desktop-fixes-33-bugs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-kb5014697-update-adds-spotlight-for-desktop-fixes-33-bugs/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T18:18:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has released the Windows 11 KB5014697 cumulative update with security updates, improvements, and the new Spotlight for Desktop feature that automatically changes your desktop background. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Windows Security Updates June 2022 overview]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179174</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/14/microsoft-windows-security-updates-june-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T18:04:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft released security updates and non-security updates for all client and server versions of Windows on the June 2022 Patch Day. Other Microsoft products, including Visual Studio, SQL Server, Windows Autopilot, Microsoft […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Microsoft Windows Security Updates June 2022 overview appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 10 KB5014699 and KB5014692 updates released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-10-kb5014699-and-kb5014692-updates-released/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-10-kb5014699-and-kb5014692-updates-released/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T18:02:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has released the Windows 10 KB5014699 and KB5014692 cumulative updates for versions 21H2, version 21H1, version 20H2, and 1809 to fix security vulnerabilities and resolve bugs. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mayank Parmar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Unblock a Number on Android]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=810057</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/810057/how-to-unblock-a-number-on-android/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T18:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’d like to start receiving calls and text messages from a blocked number, you’ll have to unblock that number on your Android phone. It’s quick and easy to do this on most phones and we’ll show you how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft patches actively exploited Follina Windows zero-day]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-patches-actively-exploited-follina-windows-zero-day/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-patches-actively-exploited-follina-windows-zero-day/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T18:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has released security updates with the June 2022 cumulative Windows Updates to address a critical Windows zero-day vulnerability known as Follina and actively exploited in ongoing attacks. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft June 2022 Patch Tuesday fixes 1 zero-day, 55 flaws]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-june-2022-patch-tuesday-fixes-1-zero-day-55-flaws/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-june-2022-patch-tuesday-fixes-1-zero-day-55-flaws/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T17:45:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today is Microsoft's June 2022 Patch Tuesday, and with it comes fixes for 55 vulnerabilities, including fixes for the Windows MSDT 'Follina' zero-day vulnerability and new Intel MMIO flaws. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux Patched For New Intel "MMIO Stale Data" Vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=MMIO-Stale-Data-Vulnerabilities</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=MMIO-Stale-Data-Vulnerabilities"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T17:39:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In addition to the Hertzbleed frequency scaling side-channel attack being made public today as part of "Patch Tuesday" and affecting both Intel and AMD CPUs, Intel is additionally disclosing a set of "MMIO Stale Data" vulnerabilities. The Linux kernel has already been patched for these new vulnerabilities affecting multiple generations of Intel CPUs from Rocket Lake back to Haswell X and Skylake...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Browser-Based Photoshop Will Be Free for Everyone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120873/browser-based-photoshop-will-be-free-for-everyone/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120873/browser-based-photoshop-will-be-free-for-everyone/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T17:29:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adobe Photoshop will soon be free for everyone, thanks to a basic web-based version of the app. The company is currently testing the free trial in Canada, where those interested can access the suite of Photoshop editing tools from a web browser.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft PowerPoint Keyboard Shortcuts]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=485212</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15368403/powerpoint-keyboard-shortcuts"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T17:25:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft PowerPoint has remained the “go to” presentation app since Microsoft first released it in 1990. Despite its wild success, Microsoft PowerPoint can be a bit of a pain to navigate at times, both when creating and presenting your work. However, knowing some of the commonly used keyboard shortcuts for the program can help you save time and energy while you prepare and present your next PowerPoint at work or on the go.
   
   
  
Download this Cheatsheet
 Enter your email below to receive this PDF cheatsheet in your Inbox.
     
  
  
   
                   #cheatsheet-box{border:1px solid #ddd;background-color:#d9edf7;}              ... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Megan Glosson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Siti per comprare componenti PC al miglior prezzo]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2018/07/siti-per-comprare-componenti-pc.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2018/07/siti-per-comprare-componenti-pc.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T17:24:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon è un punto di riferimento per tutti gli utenti che vogliono assemblare un PC partendo da zero e acquistando tutte le componenti necessarie per l'assemblaggio, ma i prezzi non sempre sono i più economici disponibili, in particolare con le schede video e le schede madri.

 Per poter realizzare il nostro futuro PC fisso (magari dedicato al gaming) con tutte le componenti necessarie spendendo...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keychron's Q5 QMK Keyboard Offers Full-Sized Functionality In a Small Package]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120869/keychrons-q5-qmk-keyboard-offers-full-sized-functionality-in-a-small-package/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120869/keychrons-q5-qmk-keyboard-offers-full-sized-functionality-in-a-small-package/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T17:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Keychron just added an impressive new keyboard to its mechanical arsenal. The Q5 QMK comes in the rare 1800 (96%) layout, offering full-sized features like a function row and numpad in a compact package. Of course, it’s also fully customizable, has a backlight, and comes with Gateron G Pro switches.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hertzbleed Disclosed As New Family Of Side-Channel Attacks Affecting Intel + AMD]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Hertzbleed</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Hertzbleed"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T17:12:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hertzbleed has been made public today as a new family of side-channel attacks making use of frequency side channels. Both Intel and AMD have issued security advisories as a result...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gaming vs. Regular Mouse Pads: What’s the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=803040</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/803040/gaming-vs-regular-mouse-pads/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T17:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mouse pads are very cheap compared to other computer accessories. You can find gaming and regular pads around the same size for as low as $5-10. The price increases in size, so if you’re looking at a large pad, it’ll be about $20-30 with extra-large options around $40.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Nguyen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Verizon Will Boost 5G Service With More Mid-Band Frequencies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=811441</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/811441/verizon-will-boost-5g-service-with-more-mid-band-frequencies/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T16:50:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rollout of 5G networks in the United States has been slow-moving, especially for Verizon and AT&T. However, Verizon is now testing a new network feature that should improve coverage in some areas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram founder criticizes Apple for web app limitations on iOS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179169</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/14/telegram-founder-criticizes-apple-safari-on-ios/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T16:35:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram founder Pavel Durov has criticized Apple for limiting web developers on iOS and iPadOS. He isn't the first to lash out at Safari on iOS. Apple's mobile browser has been slammed […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Telegram founder criticizes Apple for web app limitations on iOS appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ford Halts All Mustang Mach-E Sales Over Dangerous Battery Malfunction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120861/ford-halts-all-mustang-mach-e-sales-over-dangerous-battery-malfunction/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120861/ford-halts-all-mustang-mach-e-sales-over-dangerous-battery-malfunction/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T16:35:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ford has issued a stop-sale order and instructed all dealers to temporarily stop selling or demoing the popular new Mustang Mach-E over safety concerns that it could lose power while in motion, among other things.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ghacks Deals: Surfshark VPN 2-4 year subscriptions 80% off]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179172</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/14/ghacks-deals-surfshark-vpn-2-4-year-subscriptions-80-off/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T16:32:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mike reviewed Surfshark's VPN service back in October 2021 and concluded that it offered good options and performance. Now is your chance to grab a 2-year, 3-year or 4-year Surfshark subscription for […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Ghacks Deals: Surfshark VPN 2-4 year subscriptions 80% off appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox Now Protects Its Users From Third Party Cookies by Default]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120859/firefox-now-protects-its-users-from-third-party-cookies-by-default/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120859/firefox-now-protects-its-users-from-third-party-cookies-by-default/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T16:16:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Firefox desktop browser now enables Total Cookie Protection by default. This feature, which initially launched in 2021 to enhance the security of Private Browsing mode, limits the third-party cookies’ ability to track you throughout the web.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to set Firefox as your default browser on Windows]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.mozilla.org/foxtail/2020/01/20/how-to-set-firefox-as-your-default-browser-on-windows/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.mozilla.org/en/products/firefox/how-to-set-firefox-as-your-default-browser-on-windows/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T16:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During a software update, your settings can sometimes change or revert back to their original state. For example, if your computer has multiple browsers installed, you may end up with a different default browser than Firefox. That’s easy to fix so that Firefox is there for you when you expect it, like when you click […]
The post How to set Firefox as your default browser on Windows appeared first on The Mozilla Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>M.J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mic with JACK super distorted?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vc6v9y/mic_with_jack_super_distorted/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vc6v9y/mic_with_jack_super_distorted/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T16:04:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So I had this problem with PulseAudio but I fixed it by using the fix in the arch wiki (Here), and now I'm having the same problem but with JACK. is there any fix? All the fixes I found online have all been for PulseAudio. 
 ​
 Thanks!
    submitted by    /u/DiamondDanMan12  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Fastest Ways to Search the Web in Chrome]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=810270</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/810270/the-fastest-ways-to-search-the-web-in-chrome/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Searching the web is one of the most common things people do in web browsers. Whether you use Google, Bing, or DuckDuckGo, there are things you want to find. We’ll show you the fastest ways to do it in Chrome.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Owner of ‘DownThem’ DDoS service gets 2 years in prison]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/owner-of-downthem-ddos-service-gets-2-years-in-prison/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/owner-of-downthem-ddos-service-gets-2-years-in-prison/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T15:40:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matthew Gatrel, 33, a citizen of Illinois, has been sentenced to two years in prison for operating platforms offering DDoS (distributed denial of service) services to subscribers. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come trasferire i messaggi WhatsApp da Android a iOS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Come-trasferire-i-messaggi-WhatsApp-da-Android-a-iOS_24639</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Come-trasferire-i-messaggi-WhatsApp-da-Android-a-iOS_24639"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dopo la novità di WhatsApp Cloud API, uno strumento particolarmente utile per gli sviluppatori che hanno la necessità di integrare le applicazioni aziendali con il network di messaggistica di proprietà di Facebook, è Mark Zuckerberg ad annunciare l'arrivo di un'altra novità.Lo scorso anno è stata aggiunta una funzione per trasferire i messaggi WhatsApp da iOS ad Android, chat e allegati corrispondenti. In un primo momento il trasferimento delle chat WhatsApp era limitato ad alcuni smartphone Samsung; successivamente Google ha esteso il supporto ai suoi Pixel.In un altro articolo abbiamo visto come non perdere le chat WhatsApp cambiando telefono.Adesso il numero uno di Facebook rivela in anteprima che WhatsApp può spostare i messaggi da Android a iOS preservando la crittografia end-to-end.Al momento il meccanismo di migrazione WhatsApp da Android a iOS supporta la versione 15.5 del sistema operativo Apple (iOS 16 non è ancora ufficialmente compatibile).Il passaggio dei dati da un telefono all'altro avviene se entrambi i dispositivi, Android e iOS, sono connessi alla medesima rete WiFi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung Offers $50 Galaxy Phone Screen Repairs for a Limited Time]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120847/samsung-offers-50-galaxy-phone-screen-repairs-for-a-limited-time/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120847/samsung-offers-50-galaxy-phone-screen-repairs-for-a-limited-time/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T15:27:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For a limited time this month, Samsung is generously replacing cracked and damaged smartphone screens at the low price of only $50. If you’ve ever broken a screen on your fancy new flagship phone, you know the cost can be crazy expensive without insurance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is a Mini PC and Should You Buy One?]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=491193</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15368179/what-is-mini-pc"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re in the market for a new computer, you might find yourself a bit overwhelmed when contemplating all the options available on the market. But before you rush out and purchase another laptop, stop and consider if a mini PC would be better suited to your needs. In a work-from-home environment, these miniature versions of powerful PCs could be the answer for a lot of folks.
   

Content

What Are Mini PCs
Use Cases for Mini PCs
Choosing a Mini PC
Ready-to-Go Mini PCs
Barebones Mini PCs
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Turn Your Raspberry Pi into a Video Conferencing Station
    
What Are Mini PCs
    
Mini PCs are exactly that: scaled-down versions of desktop computers. They come in a variety of sizes and offer unique advantages, as well as some drawbacks.
  ... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Yoder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lightroom Gets Video Editing Support with Color Grading]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120838/lightroom-gets-video-editing-support-with-color-grading/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120838/lightroom-gets-video-editing-support-with-color-grading/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T15:24:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of Lightroom’s most requested features is finally here. The latest Lightroom update (v 5.4) lets you edit videos with basic trimming and color grading tools. You can even apply your custom photography presets to videos.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Back in Arch!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vc5s5t/back_in_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vc5s5t/back_in_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T15:16:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well, I'm back using Arch again (coming from NixOS for about a week). After a few attempts setting EFI, I was finally able to get Legacy installed and booting up properly (See this post).
 Everything is running great. I've spent most of the morning reinstalling my programs I use on a daily basis. But everything is working fine under Legacy. I did it all manually (no archinstall script) because archinstall doesn't really cover everything for my system. I have a second HDD I use for my /home directory. It's a 4TB drive and I just never seemed to get that second drive to work the way I want it with archinstall. That would have to be something the archinstall developers need to work on. 
 But, we're all good here now. I'm gonna kinda miss NixOS though. It has so much potential. But Arch is more than welcome to live on my system now.
    submitted by    /u/Phydoux  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox now blocks cross-site tracking by default for all users]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/firefox-now-blocks-cross-site-tracking-by-default-for-all-users/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/firefox-now-blocks-cross-site-tracking-by-default-for-all-users/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T15:04:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla says that starting today, all Firefox users will now be protected by default against cross-site tracking while browsing the Internet. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Integrate Zoho Voice With Zoho Desk]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/?p=60049</id>
        <link href="https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/integrate-zoho-voice-zoho-desk/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T15:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Integrating Zoho Voice with Zoho Desk gives users the ability to manage both their call center and contact center services from one location. Having]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hongkiat.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Evaluate Formulas Step-by-Step in Microsoft Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=807481</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/807481/how-to-evaluate-formulas-step-by-step-in-microsoft-excel/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T15:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re collaborating on a spreadsheet, you may want to break down a formula someone entered. While many times this easy, there are others where the formula is more complicated. Excel provides a tool to evaluate formulas step-by-step.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Internet Explorer ritirato il 15 giugno 2022: cosa implica per gli utenti]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Internet-Explorer-ritirato-il-15-giugno-2022-cosa-implica-per-gli-utenti_24462</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Internet-Explorer-ritirato-il-15-giugno-2022-cosa-implica-per-gli-utenti_24462"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T14:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Era il 16 agosto 1995 quando Microsoft presentò la prima versione di Internet Explorer, browser che mirava a combattere lo strapotere assoluto dello storico Netscape Navigator.Agli albori Internet Explorer veniva distribuito come parte integrante del pacchetto Plus! per Windows 95, che forse alcuni dei nostri lettori ricorderanno, ed era basato sul motore di rendering Spyglass Mosaic il cui utilizzo era stato ottenuto in licenza da Microsoft.La società di Redmond non ha dovuto lavorare troppo per rendere popolare il suo browser: non importava se Internet Explorer fosse migliore o peggiore della concorrenza. Semplicemente includendolo come parte integrante dei suoi sistemi operativi, Microsoft riuscì a scalzare Netscape e consolidare un monopolio durato anni.Nel 2002 il browser Phoenix, poi diventato Firefox, lanciò la vera sfida a Internet Explorer cominciando a guadagnare importanti quote di mercato a danno del browser Microsoft con Opera che nel frattempo denunciò la società per abuso di posizione dominante.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare mitigates record-breaking HTTPS DDoS attack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cloudflare-mitigates-record-breaking-https-ddos-attack/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cloudflare-mitigates-record-breaking-https-ddos-attack/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T14:31:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Internet infrastructure firm Cloudflare said today that it mitigated a 26 million request per second distributed denial-of-service (DDoS) attack, the largest HTTPS DDoS attack detected to date. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox Now Blocks Cross-Site Cookie Tracking Everywhere]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=811311</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/811311/firefox-now-blocks-cross-site-cookie-tracking-everywhere/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T14:24:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox is one of two major browsers left with a non-Chromium engine (the other being Apple’s Safari), which means it can experiment with lower-level changes that Google isn’t interested in. Now one of those changes is rolling out to everyone: Total Cookie Protection.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Withings ScanWatch Review: Timeless Style Meets Modern Tech]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/120080/withings-scanwatch-review/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/120080/withings-scanwatch-review/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T14:24:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re considering a smartwatch to monitor your health stats, but aren’t too impressed with sporty styles or digital watch faces, the Withings ScanWatch’s gorgeous analog design and premium health-tracking features are the perfect companions for your wrist.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arnold Carreiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to setup a default dns server for all networks?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vc4887/how_to_setup_a_default_dns_server_for_all_networks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vc4887/how_to_setup_a_default_dns_server_for_all_networks/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T14:04:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have setup adguard-home on arch and everytime I change my network I have to change the dns used by that netwrok to localhost. Is there anyway to make all these networks default to local host??
    submitted by    /u/Sad-Excitement9311  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Gaming TVs of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=749603</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/749603/best-gaming-tvs/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The best TVs for gaming don’t just show picture-perfect visuals; they also provide features like high refresh rates to ensure your gaming experience is top-notch. Our recommendations include the right mix of features to make big-screen gaming perfect whether you’re playing on a console or PC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gaurav Shukla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>