<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-05-17T01:51:25.531Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A few questions about the wm and de]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/urb15m/a_few_questions_about_the_wm_and_de/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/urb15m/a_few_questions_about_the_wm_and_de/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T01:15:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My friend told me that the wm is more effective than de and he suggested me to try it. But I have tried many wms like i3,dwm, awesomewm, and so on. However, I found it is too difficult to configure. I can't understand why people promote it on effective and professional. I agree with the opinion that it is professional. But I really don't understand why people call it is more effective.
    submitted by    /u/oneighto  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Switching to Arch from Ubuntu after 15+ years]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uradap/switching_to_arch_from_ubuntu_after_15_years/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uradap/switching_to_arch_from_ubuntu_after_15_years/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T00:39:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am fairly new to the arch community. I didn't really start using Arch (btw) until about 6 months ago. For context, I have used a great many distros, many of them debian based (ubuntu, mint, lubuntu), over the years. I got into Linux in the mid 2000s, after a computer failure left me without a hard drive and a friend showed me how to boot from a usb and I taught myself to install to USB, back when 4gb was an expensive(ish) buy for a usb drive. 
 I loved linux immediately, and although Ubuntu was my first distro, I hopped a lot, usually just multi booting, always with Windows too, just in case. I eventually became more comfortable with linux to the point I started running my own servers for small webhosting projects. I also found I liked using a linux desktop for php development as well. E…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[HELP] horizontal glitches (tear) specially in firefox while scrolling]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uraagw/help_horizontal_glitches_tear_specially_in/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uraagw/help_horizontal_glitches_tear_specially_in/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T00:34:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have been scratching my head for this problem and can’t seem to figure it out. I have reinstalled arch multiple time but it always come back. 
 Issue:
 Issue can be easily spot in firefox while scrolling specially arch wiki (white background and lots of texts). 
 Glitches appears as horizontal bar and in that bar almost all fonts gets little bigger kind of thing so it feels like there is some kind of glass cylinder making some font little different and then other.
 In a full screen it is easy to spot as well.
 Troubleshoot:
  
 So far i have tried installation arch multiple time but I think all the packages I install are same except windows manager, first it was xmonad and now its qtile
  I have tried manjaro (kde, sway, xfce) all works fine.
  I have 20-intel.conf for TearFree and TrippleBuffer but no help. 
  Already uninstalled picom compositor.
  From arch wiki also disabled vsync as well but no help.
  
Hardware:
  
 i5-8250u
  UHD-620
  
Driver that i have right now:
  
 mesa
  xf86-video-intel
  vulkan-intel
  
Any help would be really good.
    submitted by    /u/dhruvin3  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 of the Best Smartphones for Seniors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=199014</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/6170740/best-smartphones-for-seniors"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smartphones, for the most part, have opened up technology to seniors and the older generation — their intuitive and large touch-screens proving much friendlier to use than old mobile phones with buttons (or circle-dial phones).
    
When looking at the best smartphone for seniors, we took various criteria into account like screen brightness and size, special accessibility features, and modernity. Do your grandma and grandpa think an Android is the metal trashcan from “Lost In Space”? It’s time to take them under the arm and guide them into the modern age. The phones listed below should be enough to convince them that smartphone technology isn’t all that scary.
   

Content

1. Motorola Moto G Power (2021)
2. Doro 8080
3. Samsung Galaxy Note 8
4. EmporiaSmart.5
5. Google Pixel 3XL
6. Jitterbug Smart3
7. Nokia 6300
8. iPhone SE (2022)
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexandra Arici</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to disable middle mouse paste?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ur9m4h/how_to_disable_middle_mouse_paste/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ur9m4h/how_to_disable_middle_mouse_paste/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T23:58:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I need to disable it. This is madness. I go and scroll and I paste stuff. I already installed xmousepasteblock and it did not work. This is the last component I need to have arch be perfect for me. I am on kde if that helps.
    submitted by    /u/VotedDragon_reddit  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML attachments remain popular among phishing actors in 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/html-attachments-remain-popular-among-phishing-actors-in-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/html-attachments-remain-popular-among-phishing-actors-in-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T22:32:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HTML files remain one of the most popular attachments used in phishing attacks for the first four months of 2022, showing that the technique remains effective against antispam engines and works well on the victims themselves. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inkscape 1.2 Open-Source Vector Graphics Program Released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Inkscape-1.2-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Inkscape-1.2-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T22:30:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's been nearly one year since the release of Inkscape 1.1 while today it has been succeeded by Inkscape 1.2 as a major feature update...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alienware bios not showing arch.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ur7m6u/alienware_bios_not_showing_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ur7m6u/alienware_bios_not_showing_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T22:16:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is showing the following:
 Windows Boot Manager
 Onboard NIC (IPV4)
 Onboard NIC (IPV6)
 ubuntu
 What do I have to do to get this to work? I just installed it and I thought it should work, but it didn't. When I was using ubuntu, it was able to be picked up by my bios. Arch is simply not there. The only way to boot into it is by going into a separate boot manager. Windows is first boot. I am running on an alienware aurora r11. Please help if you can.
    submitted by    /u/VotedDragon_reddit  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FreeBSD 13.1 Released With UEFI Boot Enhancements, Driver Improvements]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=FreeBSD-13.1-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=FreeBSD-13.1-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T22:12:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After taking a few extra weeks to bake, FreeBSD 13.1 is out today as the newest stable release of this leading BSD operating system...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come aggiungere un programma portable alle app predefinite di windows per aprire i file]]></title>
        <id>3574|20220517000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/portable-1843/come-aggiungere-programma-portable-app-predefinite-windows-aprire-file-3574"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ci sono persone che preferiscono utilizzare i programmi portable perché “sporcano” meno il sistema operativo, rispetto a un normale programma installato, inoltre sono più facili da eliminare perché, se non ci interessano più, basta cancellarli. Uno dei pochi svantaggi è che non vengono direttamente registrati tra i programmi utilizzabili per aprire un determinato tipo di file. In genere, il programma portable può avere le sue opzioni per poterlo fare, oppure possiamo noi cambiare manualmente questo tipo di associazione, ma grazie a Portable Registrator possiamo rendere più semplice questa associazione e registrare le applicazioni portable tra quelle utilizzabili.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 of the Best Collection Organizing Apps for Android and iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=365524</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/13919248/best-collection-organizing-android-apps"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Almost everybody collects something. But keeping up with that collection isn’t always easy. You could just write it all down, but wouldn’t an app be easier? There are plenty of great apps just for collecting one type of thing. However, collection organizing apps are ideal for managing nearly any type of collection and even multiple collections in a single app.
   

Content

1. Itemtopia
2. MyCollections
3. Memento Database
4. Libib
5. My Collections
6. My ... Collection
7. Airtable
8. Magic Home Inventory
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:The Best Google Docs Templates to Organize Your Life
    
1. Itemtopia
    
Itemtopia (Android / iOS) is designed to help you track everything from your book collection to receipts. Take images, add pricing, create custom fields, and even add unique spaces to track where your belongings are at any time.... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Crystal Crowder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Third-party web trackers log what you type before submitting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/third-party-web-trackers-log-what-you-type-before-submitting/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/third-party-web-trackers-log-what-you-type-before-submitting/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T21:15:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An extensive study looking into the top 100k ranking websites has revealed that many are leaking information you enter in the site forms to third-party trackers before you even press submit. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is “Black Crush” on a Display?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=728797</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/728797/what-is-black-crush-on-a-display/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you heard the term “black crush” while looking at TV or monitor reviews? The problem is getting more attention now that display manufacturers are trying to improve black reproduction, particularly on LED-lit LCD models. So what are “crushed blacks,” and do you need to worry about them?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US links Thanos and Jigsaw ransomware to 55-year-old doctor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-links-thanos-and-jigsaw-ransomware-to-55-year-old-doctor/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-links-thanos-and-jigsaw-ransomware-to-55-year-old-doctor/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T20:46:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US Department of Justice today said that Moises Luis Zagala Gonzalez (Zagala), a 55-year-old cardiologist with French and Venezuelan citizenship residing in Ciudad Bolivar, Venezuela, created and rented Jigsaw and Thanos ransomware to cybercriminals. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add Local TV Channels to Your Plex Server]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118023/how-to-add-local-tv-channels-to-your-plex-server/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118023/how-to-add-local-tv-channels-to-your-plex-server/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T20:10:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cutting the cord doesn’t mean giving up on live TV. Local channels are totally free and often include content that you care about, including sports. But if you want to make the antenna TV experience a bit more modern, you should add local channels to your Plex server for a killer channel guide, remote streaming, DVR functionality, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the Built-In Stocks Feature in Microsoft Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=703580</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/703580/how-to-use-the-built-in-stocks-feature-in-microsoft-excel/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you need stock market data for your spreadsheet, you can save time and get up-to-date information with the built-in Stocks data type in Microsoft Excel. Here’s how to populate your sheet with details like ticker symbols, market caps, previous close, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get the Tronsmart Onyx Ace Pro Wireless Earbuds for $27]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=489718</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15304905/tronsmart-onyx-ace-pro-wireless-earbuds"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you looking to take your tunes with you this summer? You can get a quality set of earbuds for 55% off when you buy the Tronsmart Onyx Ace Pro Wireless Earbuds. Enjoy an optimized experience, Qualcomm chip, dual mics, clear calls, gaming mode, and up to 27 hours of playtime.
    
Get four mics in these earbuds, the same number you’ll find in the Apple AirPods, to ensure your callers will be able to hear you clearly. Hear them just the same with the Qualcomm cVc audio technology, including aptX, AAC, and SBC. If you enjoy sharing your gameplay, make sure your opponents will hear you well with the gaming mode on these earbuds.
    

    
Connect easily to the Tronsmart Onyx Ace Pro Wireless Earbuds with Bluetooth v5.2 and Qualcomm ACC3040. Get up to 6.5 hours of playtime on a single charge, more than with the Apple AirPods, and expand that to 27 hours when utilizing the charging case. Recharge the case and earbuds through USB-C.
    
Change functions with touch... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Color Gamut?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=802159</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/802159/what-is-color-gamut/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve shopped for monitors, laptops, smartphones, or printers, you’ve likely seen retailers promoting the width of their products’ color gamuts. So what is a color gamut, and how does its size affect display or print quality?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gaurav Shukla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple emergency update fixes zero-day used to hack Macs, Watches]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/apple-emergency-update-fixes-zero-day-used-to-hack-macs-watches/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/apple-emergency-update-fixes-zero-day-used-to-hack-macs-watches/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T18:33:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple has released security updates to address a zero-day vulnerability that threat actors can exploit in attacks targeting Macs and Apple Watch devices. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s What’s New in macOS 12.4, iOS 15.5, & Apple Podcasts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=805558</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/805558/heres-whats-new-in-macos-12.4-ios-15.5-apple-podcasts/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T18:31:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple released a bunch of new software updates on Monday, May 16, 2022, including new system upgrades for the Mac, iPhone, iPad, Apple Watch, Apple TV, and HomePod speakers. Here’s everything that’s new.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shutdown/Reboot takes a very long time followed by an error message]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ur2joc/shutdownreboot_takes_a_very_long_time_followed_by/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ur2joc/shutdownreboot_takes_a_very_long_time_followed_by/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T18:27:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the message i get. I am running a minimal arch install with kde plasma and i get this issue after about two consecutive reboots/shutdowns and it repeats the same pattern. Thanks for any help!
 Also im using nvidia proprietary drivers from frogging family(the AIO nvidia installer: link)
    submitted by    /u/Neo_Nethshan  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PNY XLR8 Gaming REV 2x8GB DDR4-3600 Memory]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31120</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31120"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T18:20:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PNY recently sent over their new XLR8 Gaming REV 16GB (2 x 8GB) DDR4-3600MHz memory that only lists compatibility with Microsoft Windows 11 and older, but fear not, it does work fine for Linux gamers and others looking for DDR4-3600 memory with RGB lighting and running well with the latest Intel and AMD processors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox feels a tiny bit faster in GNOME 42/Wayland than in Sway 1.7]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ur2atm/firefox_feels_a_tiny_bit_faster_in_gnome/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ur2atm/firefox_feels_a_tiny_bit_faster_in_gnome/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T18:15:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Guys,
 I know this is not easily measurable and it perhaps depends on the machine used but anyway...
 Has anybody else also experienced that Firefox feels a bit faster and snappier (lower latency) in the current GNOME 42/Wayland than in SwayWM? Frankly, I expected the opposite to be true because Sway feels so vanilla. So I expected less layers => faster perfomance...
 Machine: * Desktop * amdgpu
    submitted by    /u/Original_Two9716  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ukraine supporters in Germany targeted with PowerShell RAT malware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ukraine-supporters-in-germany-targeted-with-powershell-rat-malware/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ukraine-supporters-in-germany-targeted-with-powershell-rat-malware/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T18:05:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An unknown threat actor is targeting German users interested in the Ukraine crisis, infecting them with a custom PowerShell RAT (remote access trojan) and stealing their data. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shadowsocks vs. VPNs: Which Should You Use?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=795925</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/795925/shadowsocks-vs.-vpns-which-should-you-use/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T18:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to escape internet censorship, you may have wondered whether a VPN or Shadowsocks is the better choice for you. Both are powerful tools that will help you evade any blocks, but each comes with its own strengths and weaknesses. Let’s compare the two.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fergus O'Sullivan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Doing This Can Help Preserve the Flavor of Your Coffee]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lifesavvy.com/129218/doing-this-can-help-preserve-the-flavor-of-your-coffee/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lifesavvy.com/129218/doing-this-can-help-preserve-the-flavor-of-your-coffee/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T18:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nothing says, “Wake up,” like the smell of freshly brewed coffee. However, if you want it to retain that rich taste, you might not want to let it sit on the hot plate for hours.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shea Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to setup/configure gpg?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ur1ujl/how_to_setupconfigure_gpg/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ur1ujl/how_to_setupconfigure_gpg/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T17:55:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The wiki says,
  
The default configuration files are ~/.gnupg/gpg.conf and ~/.gnupg/dirmngr.conf. 
 ... 
 You will find skeleton files in /usr/share/doc/gnupg/. These files are copied to ~/.gnupg the first time gpg is run if they do not exist there. Other examples are found in #See also.
  
But this is wrong. I've run gpg and I don't have those files. Neither do I have the skeleton in the /usr/ directory. I do have the file /usr/share/doc/gnupg/examples/gpgconf.conf, but ironically this file clearly states at the beginning that,
  
# This is a legacy mechanism. The modern way is to use global 
 # configuration files like /etc/gnupg/gpg.conf which are more 
 # flexible and better integrated into the configuration system.
  
But, there is no /etc/gnupg/gpg.conf.
 #########################################################################
 The wiki also says that we should add public key servers to the file ~/.gnupg/dirmngr.conf. But at openpgp.org it says we should add the key servers to the file gpg.conf.
 #########################################################################
 There are a lot of contradictory statements here.
 How do we set this program up?
 ​
 Thanks
    submitted by    /u/Pound_Hash  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get Beyerdynamic's Best Headphones At Big Discounts This Week]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118074/get-beyerdynamics-best-headphones-at-big-discounts-this-week/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118074/get-beyerdynamics-best-headphones-at-big-discounts-this-week/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T17:45:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re looking to ditch your old headphones or upgrade to something better, Beyerdynamic has a huge sale going on for the next week you won’t want to miss. We’re talking about the Beyerdynamic MMX 300 or DT-770 Pros at large discounts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sudden bugs in KDE Plasma after upgrading]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ur1mkp/sudden_bugs_in_kde_plasma_after_upgrading/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ur1mkp/sudden_bugs_in_kde_plasma_after_upgrading/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T17:45:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey there, I successfully run Arch-Linux with KDE for a couple of years without any bigger problems. However, today I upgraded my system and since then KDE plasma (X11) is full of bugs. Tray icons of non-plasma programs didn't show up, plasma-nm (even if it wasn't updated) couldn't connect to any openvpn connection (it worked with openvpn XY.conf via the terminal), opening a file from dolphin took ages and I couldn't switch my keyboard layouts anymore from the panel nor my global shortcuts.
 I did checked the logs, but I couldn't find any errors, I checked the arch bug tracker of all kde programs I've upgraded, but I couldn't find any bug. I reset my panels and set them up again, but it didn't change anything for me, I tired a wayland session, which did allow me to change the keyboard layout again, but didn't solve any of the other problems.
 However, as I had to get back to work, I downgraded all my packages via the arch archive to 2022-05-12 (the time I ran the last time updates) and since then everything runs smooth.
 Here the list of packages I've upgraded today (and now downgraded): https://pastebin.com/GZq8AF2n
 Do you guys experience the same problems? Do you have an idea which programs cause the bugs, so we/I can make a helpful bug report?
 Cheers and thanks in advance.
    submitted by    /u/dagdrommer94  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I can't login with arch KDE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ur1m6e/i_cant_login_with_arch_kde/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ur1m6e/i_cant_login_with_arch_kde/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T17:44:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I already tried changing password from the console but the password si correct l, but when I go to login it says "login failed", please help me
    submitted by    /u/MauroLoL1234  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NVidia rilascia driver open source per Linux: cosa significa]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=NVidia-rilascia-driver-open-source-per-Linux-cosa-significa_24521</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=NVidia-rilascia-driver-open-source-per-Linux-cosa-significa_24521"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T17:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Una notizia della quale in questi giorni si è parlato poco e che ha invece una portata storica è l'annuncio di NVidia che ha deciso di pubblicare il codice sorgente dei driver delle sue schede video per Linux.Uno dei motivi che hanno frenato lo sviluppo di un ampio ventaglio di applicazioni su Linux è lo scarso supporto dei driver NVidia.Da qualche giorno, invece, chiunque può esaminare il codice di NVidia e gli sviluppatori possono inviare correzioni e nuove funzionalità per migliorare i driver: Canonical, SUSE e Red Hat hanno accolto con grande entusiasmo la decisione della società di Jen-Hsun Huang che finalmente rende open source i suoi driver grafici per Linux.Tanti di voi si ricorderanno della 'delicata' uscita di Linus Torvalds che senza mezze misure, a giugno 2012, si riferì a NVidia come alla 'peggiore azienda con cui la comunità Linux ha avuto a che fare'.Da quelle dichiarazioni esplosive molte cose sono cambiate, fortunatamente in meglio.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iwctl not detecting any devices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ur1cc4/iwctl_not_detecting_any_devices/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ur1cc4/iwctl_not_detecting_any_devices/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T17:32:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm trying to install arch Linux in my VM and when I do iwctl device list, there are no devices, does anyone know what may be the problem?
 In the virtual box menu it says my network adapter is Intel PRO/1000 MT Desktop (NAT)
    submitted by    /u/Improvisable  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[70mai Dash Cam M500 Review]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=486777</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15302111/70mai-dash-cam-m500"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T17:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Having dash cam footage during an accident or capturing what happens to your car in a parking lot can save you a lot of time and headaches. Picking the perfect dash cam, though, isn’t always easy. The 70mai Dash Cam M500 is designed to make it easier to record your travels and monitor your car in parking lots. I recently had the opportunity take this dash cam for a test drive to test out its features.
    
This is a sponsored article and was made possible by 70mai. The actual contents and opinions are the sole views of the author who maintains editorial independence even when a post is sponsored.
    
Overview of Features
    
The 70mai Dash Cam M500 packs a lot of features into a small package. Unlike most dash cams that require a microSD card, this one has 64 GB of eMMC built-in storage. Not only does this type of storage usually last longer than your average SD card, but you don’t have to worry about a card being damaged and losing your footage.
    
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Crystal Crowder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA warns not to install May Windows updates on domain controllers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisa-warns-not-to-install-may-windows-updates-on-domain-controllers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisa-warns-not-to-install-may-windows-updates-on-domain-controllers/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T17:24:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has removed a Windows security flaw from its catalog of known exploited vulnerabilities due to Active Directory (AD) authentication issues caused by the May 2022 updates that patch it. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is the difference between pacman-key --refresh-keys and pacman -S archlinux-keyring]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ur12q4/what_is_the_difference_between_pacmankey/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ur12q4/what_is_the_difference_between_pacmankey/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T17:20:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[i only ever use pacman -S archlinux-keyring after a pacman -Syu fails because of key issue.
    submitted by    /u/callmejoe9  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s How Mozilla Thunderbird Is Making a Comeback in 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=805530</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/805530/heres-how-mozilla-thunderbird-is-making-a-comeback-in-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T17:07:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thunderbird has been around since 2003, but it has stalled in recent years due to dwindling interest from Mozilla and limited funds. However, the project is now making a resurgence, and it might be worth your time to try Thunderbird.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I can't login with KDE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ur0mfe/i_cant_login_with_kde/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ur0mfe/i_cant_login_with_kde/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T17:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I just installed arch for the first time using "archinstall", the password was right, I made sure I inserted the correct one in the configuration, but when I'm logging in it says login failed
    submitted by    /u/MauroLoL1234  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Token vs. Coin: What’s the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=799927</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/799927/crypto-token-vs.-coin-whats-the-difference/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T17:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tokens and coins are similar. The difference between a coin or a token may be a technicality, but understanding the difference can help you better understand how blockchains and cryptocurrencies function.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>RJ Fulton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NYC to Get a Fleet of Weird, Fast, Three-Wheeler EVs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118024/nyc-to-get-a-fleet-of-weird-fast-three-wheeler-evs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118024/nyc-to-get-a-fleet-of-weird-fast-three-wheeler-evs/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T16:37:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Oregon-based mobility company Arcimoto makes all sorts of three-wheel EVs, from its Fun Utility Vehicles (FUVs) to tricycles. And now, thanks to a partnership with the urban e-bike brand JOCO, soon you’ll see its FUVs all over New York City.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kali Linux 2022.2 released with 10 new tools, WSL improvements, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/kali-linux-20222-released-with-10-new-tools-wsl-improvements-and-more/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/kali-linux-20222-released-with-10-new-tools-wsl-improvements-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T16:35:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Offensive Security has released ​Kali Linux 2022.2, the second version in 2022, with desktop enhancements, a fun April Fools screensaver, WSL GUI improvements, terminal tweaks, and best of all, new tools to play with! [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NVIDIA Updates Legacy 470 & 390 Series Linux Drivers, New Bump For 510 Series]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=NVIDIA-May-16-2022-Linux</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=NVIDIA-May-16-2022-Linux"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While not as exciting as last week's NVIDIA 515 series Linux driver that kicks off their open-source Linux kernel driver effort, but today they issued a minor point release for the current stable 510 series as well as updating their prior legacy driver branches...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Le app per inviare file da smartphone Android e iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2013/04/inviare-file-da-un-cellulare-a-un-altro.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2013/04/inviare-file-da-un-cellulare-a-un-altro.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T16:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Il file sharing non è proprio il punto di forza di un iPhone, che di fatto obbliga ad utilizzare il Bluetooth per il trasferimento tra dispositivi: purtroppo questo tipo di connessione non è esattamente il metodo più veloce e comodo.

 Se abbiamo un iPhone mentre l'amico ha un telefono Android (e viceversa) sarebbe molto utile scoprire come ricevere o inviare rapidamente qualsiasi tipo di file,...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NVidia GeForce RTX 40: le nuove schede grafiche sul mercato forse già a luglio]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=NVidia-GeForce-RTX-40-le-nuove-schede-grafiche-sul-mercato-forse-gia-a-luglio_24520</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=NVidia-GeForce-RTX-40-le-nuove-schede-grafiche-sul-mercato-forse-gia-a-luglio_24520"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T16:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NVidia si starebbe preparando al lancio della nuova gamma di schede grafiche GeForce RTX 40: potrebbero essere presentate già a fine maggio in occasione del Computex 2022 per poi arrivare sul mercato a luglio prossimo.A quanto si apprende in via non ufficiale le RTX 40 saranno contraddistinte da un consumo energetico elevato che corrisponderà a un incisivo aumento di potenza: si parla di prestazioni addirittura raddoppiate, in alcuni casi, rispetto alle RTX 30.Le prime schede grafiche ad arrivare sul mercato saranno le RTX 4070, 4080 e 4090, con consumi di 300W, 400W e 600W.Una GeForce RTX 4090 utilizzerà una GPU AD102 realizzata sfruttando il processo costruttivo a 5 nm di TSMC e dovrebbe basare il suo funzionamento su qualcosa come 16.128 shader.Gli shader sarebbero supportati da un bus a 384 bit e memoria GDDR6 a 21 GHz per una larghezza di banda complessiva pari a 1 TB/s. Il TGP dovrebbe attestarsi sui 450W.Con la versione 'Ti', il chip grafico potrebbe essere quindi ancora più potente e spingersi fino a un massimo di 18.432 shader.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Install windows alongside Arch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uqzg6s/install_windows_alongside_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uqzg6s/install_windows_alongside_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T16:09:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My situation:
 I currently have Arch installed on /dev/sda. (btrfs filesystem)
 I have my old windows install on /dev/sdb which i want to replace with a fresh windows install.
 /dev/sdc is my external drive with important files from sdb.
 ​
 Will i run into any issues when dualbooting Arch in a btrfs filesystem and windows in ntfs?
 ​
 ​
 edit: my bootloader is grub
 ​
 ​
 ​
 ​
 output of fstab
 ​
 Disk /dev/sda: 111.8 GiB, 120040980480 bytes, 234455040 sectors
 Disk model: WDC WDS120G2G0B-
 Units: sectors of 1 * 512 = 512 bytes
 Sector size (logical/physical): 512 bytes / 512 bytes
 I/O size (minimum/optimal): 512 bytes / 512 bytes
 Disklabel type: gpt
 Disk identifier: 4502A5FC-6403-4B8D-AE78-ACA1AD97E225
 First usable LBA: 34
 Last usable LBA: 234455006
 Alternative LBA: 234455039
 Part…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sony Confirms PlayStation Plus Launch Date and Classic Games List]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118025/sony-confirms-playstation-plus-launch-date-and-classic-games-list/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118025/sony-confirms-playstation-plus-launch-date-and-classic-games-list/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T16:02:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sony initially announced its revamped PlayStation Plus subscription plans back in March. Now, the company has (finally!!!) shared the service’s official launch date and a drool-worthy list of the classic games library members will have access to (be still our little gamer hearts!).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzanne Humphries</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Pluto TV, and Is It Really Free?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=804577</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/804577/what-is-pluto-tv-and-is-it-really-free/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The streaming TV space is very crowded these days. All the big-name companies have their own services, plus there are dozens of lesser-known options. “Pluto TV” sits somewhere in the middle and it has a lot to like.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Fire Smart TVs and Streaming Sticks Are Nearly Half Off]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118018/amazon-fire-smart-tvs-and-streaming-sticks-are-nearly-half-off/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118018/amazon-fire-smart-tvs-and-streaming-sticks-are-nearly-half-off/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T15:47:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hoping to upgrade to 4K or get a snappy new streaming stick? Amazon is running a massive sale on Fire TV devices, including smart TVs, with some products seeing discounts up to 42% off. It’s like Black Friday came early!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sophos antivirus driver caused BSODs after Windows KB5013943 update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/software/sophos-antivirus-driver-caused-bsods-after-windows-kb5013943-update/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/software/sophos-antivirus-driver-caused-bsods-after-windows-kb5013943-update/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T15:43:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sophos has released a fix for a known issue triggering blue screens of death (aka BSODs) on Windows 11 systems running Sophos Home antivirus software after installing the KB5013943 upda [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VA-API works and doesn't in a weird way]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uqytqb/vaapi_works_and_doesnt_in_a_weird_way/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uqytqb/vaapi_works_and_doesnt_in_a_weird_way/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T15:41:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi guys, in principal it works but doesn't.
 ThinkPad T460 Intel Core i5 6300 KDE on X11 Kernel: 5.15 
 I've got the drivers installed (libva-intel-driver), vainfo says it's fine and I got it to work. I read the Arch wiki in all details.In Firefox with rdd sandbox deactivated it works well... until it didn't while the video played. I don't know why. Right now after reboot it works.
 Playback with mpv doesn't work but it worked before. mpv.conf is set to activate vaapi but it worked without hassle before I set it there. Playing back with Haruna, which uses mpv, doesn't use vaapi until I open settings and navigate to playback where I set it to vaapi, then it uses surprinsingly the hardware decode units. Maybe less than it should but I'm not sure about that.
 What the hell is going on? I get the Firefox thing, which will be hopefully resolved in the near future. But everything in all it works until it doesn't. It's so unstable.I could try it once more in Wayland but back then it didn't.
    submitted by    /u/Deinorius  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stampante 3D Creality CR-10 Smart: una fuoriclasse in offerta a meno di 270 euro]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Stampante-3D-Creality-CR-10-Smart-una-fuoriclasse-in-offerta-a-meno-di-270-euro_24519</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Stampante-3D-Creality-CR-10-Smart-una-fuoriclasse-in-offerta-a-meno-di-270-euro_24519"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Non possiamo esimerci dal segnalarvi una stampante 3D che in passato si era già messa in evidenza per una serie di caratteristiche uniche che la contraddistinguono e che oggi è disponibile in promozione a un prezzo davvero scontato.La stampante 3D Creality CR-10 Smart è un dispositivo da scrivania di grandi dimensioni che offre funzioni e prestazioni di primo livello. Il vantaggio è che Creality CR-10 Smart viene adesso proposta al prezzo speciale di soli 267,39 euro con spedizione dai magazzini europei del venditore. Per assicurarsi lo sconto migliore è necessario digitare il codice coupon CC763 al momento dell'ordine.La stampante arriva già ampiamente pre-assemblata: basta 'issare' l'asse Z, installare i tiranti, collegare alcuni cavi. Il tutto non richiede più di 15-20 minuti di tempo.
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ZFS and missing kernel images]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uqypra/zfs_and_missing_kernel_images/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uqypra/zfs_and_missing_kernel_images/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T15:36:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am unsure if this belongs to /zfs or /archlinux, but lets give it a shot here.
 I updated my Arch on ZFS. On reboot, Grub complains that the vmlinuz image cant be found.
 After a reboot from an USB with my Arch stick (with zfs), I was able to import and mount the zpool. All my files in /home is there, and the rest of the Linux files too. But /boot is empty except for the grub files. No initrd or vmlinuz files to be found.
 # zpool list
 zroot 446G 51G 392G ...
 # mkdir /zzz
 There is two zfs filesystems, the root fs and a home fs. Both are shown when I do an zfs list
 zroot
 zroot/rootfs /zzz
 zroot/rootfs/home /zzz/home
 The disk also have an EFI partition, but it is not used for kernel images. The only files there are related to EFI itself.
 # zfs get mountpoint
 List of the root filesystem and all snapshots. Looks good including the snapshot I made before the (failed) update today.
 zfs mount -a
 # arch-chroot /zzz
 ls -l /boot
 NADA
 What now? Do I need to redo the (quite complex) linux+zfs installation, or is there some way to recover.
    submitted by    /u/andersostling56  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[1.5 million apps on Google and Apple's app stores may be removed for not being updated in 2 years]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178609</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/05/16/1-5-million-apps-on-google-and-apples-app-stores-may-be-removed-for-not-being-updated-in-2-years/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T15:34:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few weeks ago, Apple began warning developers that they would be removing apps that haven't been updated in a long time, from the App Store. The Cupertino company is not alone […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post 1.5 million apps on Google and Apple's app stores may be removed for not being updated in 2 years appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Haven't updated in several years -- better to do a clean install?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uqynps/havent_updated_in_several_years_better_to_do_a/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uqynps/havent_updated_in_several_years_better_to_do_a/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T15:33:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm currently running 4.18.16 and I haven't done a full system upgrade in years. Would it be better to do a clean re-install at this point?
    submitted by    /u/MedicalRaisin  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build and Install a Custom Kernel on Ubuntu]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=189896</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/5896565/build-custom-kernel-ubuntu"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The thought of compiling your own kernels strikes fear in the hearts of new Linux users. It sounds terrifying, building the most crucial part of your system from scratch. The truth is, though, building the Linux kernel in Ubuntu is really easy.
    
Building Linux kernels does not require programming. Some of the best programmers in the world have already written all of the code. You just have to pick the features that you want and put it all together. Here we will show you how to build and install a custom kernel on Ubuntu.
   

Content

Getting the Dependencies
Getting the Kernel Source for Ubuntu
Setting Up for Your Build
Configuring the Ubuntu Kernel
Building Kernel Packages for Ubuntu
Installing the Kernel
Installing Custom Binary Kernels
Installing Mainline in Ubuntu
Using Mainline

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Downgrade the Kernel in Linux
    
Getting the Dependencies
... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramces Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla Halts Cybertruck Orders In Several Regions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118017/tesla-halts-cybertruck-orders-in-several-regions/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118017/tesla-halts-cybertruck-orders-in-several-regions/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T15:16:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After countless Cybertruck delays, Tesla still hasn’t figured out what it wants to do with the exciting new electric truck. While Cybertruck pricing disappeared from websites late last year, now it looks like it’s unavailable to order across Europe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Embed a Microsoft Excel Sheet on Your Blog or Site]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=802803</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/802803/embed-excel-file-in-website/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T15:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While you can easily share an Excel workbook or spreadsheet, you might want to make it available to a larger audience. If you have a blog or website, you can embed the file by copying and pasting the embed code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come attivare il 5G di Fastweb]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/05/come-attivare-il-5g-di-fastweb.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/05/come-attivare-il-5g-di-fastweb.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T14:46:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fastweb è tra i migliori operatori di telefonia mobile disponibili in Italia grazie a offerte chiare, senza nessun vincolo o costo nascosto e facilmente abbinabile ad un abbonamento casalingo, così da pagare su una sola bolletta sia la linea fissa sia una (o più) SIM in abbonamento. Anche questo operatore sta attivando il 5G sul territorio italiano, con una copertura che aumenta ogni giorno che...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boost Mobile Now Lets You Watch Ads to Lower Your Phone Bill]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118011/boost-mobile-now-lets-you-watch-ads-to-lower-your-phone-bill/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118011/boost-mobile-now-lets-you-watch-ads-to-lower-your-phone-bill/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T14:40:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re desperate to save on your Boost Mobile bill, prepare to watch some ads. The BoostOne app (iOS/Android) now supports BoostCoins, a “blockchain-based” currency that you can redeem for billing credits. But as you’ve probably guessed, earning BoostCoins is a tedious process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 Will Analyze Your Selected Text & Suggest Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=805487</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/805487/windows-11-will-analyze-your-selected-text-suggest-actions/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T14:38:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft is working on many new features for Windows 11, and now the company has started testing something interesting: a new text selection popup that looks similar to what is available on iPhone, iPad, and Android.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[while i was installing arch , i got an error. so I took out the usb but then I saw that there was no windows option in bios. it just vanished. i don't have any idea. i didn't deleted the windows partition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uqx2yq/while_i_was_installing_arch_i_got_an_error_so_i/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uqx2yq/while_i_was_installing_arch_i_got_an_error_so_i/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T14:20:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I think i accidentally formatted efi partition can i restore it
    submitted by    /u/ICanCodeBro  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Engineering firm Parker discloses data breach after ransomware attack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/engineering-firm-parker-discloses-data-breach-after-ransomware-attack/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/engineering-firm-parker-discloses-data-breach-after-ransomware-attack/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T14:17:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Parker-Hannifin Corporation announced a data breach exposing employees' personal information after the Conti ransomware gang began publishing allegedly stolen data last month. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Photography Lighting Kits of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=796099</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/796099/best-photography-lighting-kit/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T14:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With all the options out there, choosing a lighting setup for photography can be intimidating. Whether you need a flash kit, a studio setup, or something you can take on the go, we have the best lighting kits for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Bogna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Condividere stampante in rete: ecco come fare]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Condividere-stampante-in-rete-ecco-come-fare_12110</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Condividere-stampante-in-rete-ecco-come-fare_12110"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Molte delle stampanti oggi in commercio integrano il supporto di rete: sono capaci di collegarsi al router così come con qualunque sistema client, ricevono dal router stesso un indirizzo privato via DHCP. In alternativa, ed è il nostro consiglio, è possibile assegnare alla stampante un indirizzo IP locale statico.Le stampanti più moderne sono capaci di collegarsi al router via cavo Ethernet oppure utilizzando una connessione WiFi.Se si parla di un dispositivo che offre supporto Ethernet/WiFi, condividere stampante in rete è molto semplice anche se qualche imprevisto può sempre essere in agguato.
Condividere una stampante con supporto di rete
 Le stampanti con supporto di rete sono in assoluto le più semplici e immediate da configurarsi.Di solito è sufficiente collegare la stampante al router con il cavo di rete o via WiFi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here's Everything Coming to Netflix the Week of May 16, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lifesavvy.com/129196/heres-everything-coming-to-netflix-the-week-of-may-16-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lifesavvy.com/129196/heres-everything-coming-to-netflix-the-week-of-may-16-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T13:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re halfway through May, but that doesn’t mean Netflix’s streaming content has slowed since the beginning of the month. The streaming service has as many quality drops this week as it did two weeks ago.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shea Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does anybody else feel like the arch linux installation guide is not that great?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uqvzx1/does_anybody_else_feel_like_the_arch_linux/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uqvzx1/does_anybody_else_feel_like_the_arch_linux/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T13:28:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oh boy I hope I don't get removed. I will try to keep it short. Look into gentoo installation guide, everything is elaborated. It explains everything in one page. I learned to install arch just via watching youtube videos and reading the gentoo wiki. The installation guide for example, does not explain on how to make new mount points. It simply touches on the command and link it to another page. An linux user using ubuntu, fedora, or anything similar will may have never learned how to make new folders. Arch Linux expects you to know that. If you don't they simply link it to the main page of the particular command. One example is on gentoo wiki about the filesystems they elaborate a small para about the basics of the filesystem. Then they link it to the main page if you want to read more. You could install gentoo without the need to go to another page in the wiki. In arch wiki you need to go through atleast 10 different pages to be able to have a working system. The solution is they need to elaborate more on certain topics like what is EFI partition, certain commands.
 PS - hello
 EDIT- Thanks for downvoting
    submitted by    /u/imnotpathetic  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Govee Neon Rope Lights Review: A Fun Way to Personalize Any Room]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/116893/govee-neon-rope-lights-review-a-fun-way-to-personalize-any-room/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/116893/govee-neon-rope-lights-review-a-fun-way-to-personalize-any-room/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T13:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Govee is one of the best brands out there when it comes to smart lights for your home. With one of its newest products, the Neon Rope Lights, Govee makes it possible to bring fun, retro designs to your home and create a statement piece.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Chaney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is an Expensive SD Card Better for a Raspberry Pi?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=801819</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/801819/is-an-expensive-sd-card-better-for-a-raspberry-pi/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T13:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Raspberry Pi is a cheap and cheerful computer packing a hefty punch. But will a cheap and cheerful SD card provide stable storage, or must you spend more? Here’s the lowdown.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKay</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jemalloc 5.3 Released With Many Speed & Space Optimizations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Jemalloc-5.3-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Jemalloc-5.3-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week marked the first update to the jemalloc memory allocation library since August of 2019. This malloc() implementation focused concurrency and memory fragmentation avoidance has seen more speed optimizations and other improvements in this new jemalloc 5.3 release...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iphone’s hotspot is not iwctl’s friend]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uqv9dw/iphones_hotspot_is_not_iwctls_friend/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uqv9dw/iphones_hotspot_is_not_iwctls_friend/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T12:52:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s not my will to bore you with my life, but I usually connect my laptop with Arch Linux to my iPhone on the train.
 The point is that I use iwctl to connect the laptop to the iPhone, but I need several tries to get a success connection. iwctl will return me operation failed several times until a success connection. In the iPhone before to fail it says there is a device connected.
 When I arrive at home and try the same command to my home’s wifi, it works perfectly.
 I don’t have multiple daemon or services of dhcp or nm ( I checked it could be the problem ).
 What would you propose to seek the solution? Here the things I thought:
  
Destroy the privative-software-based device iPhone and get a linux-based smartphone.
 Create a sh that retries until it’s connected. (Actually, I made it, but it’s dirty working that way)
 Install network manager (I did not, because I would like to work with iwctl, it is not laptop’s fault 😔)
  
Any idea or comment are welcome. I upvote, I’m not an asshole.
    submitted by    /u/HansDCJ  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migliori 10 programmi per modificare PDF]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2016/05/migliori-10-programmi-per-modificare-pdf.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2016/05/migliori-10-programmi-per-modificare-pdf.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T12:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Per poter modificare i PDF in passato era necessario acquistare per forza una licenza d'uso di Adobe Acrobat Reader, ossia il programma più utilizzato per modificare questo tipo di documento. Per fortuna le cose sono cambiate e, al giorno d'oggi, possiamo utilizzare una grande varietà di programmi per modificare i PDF sul nostro PC, senza dover sborsare un euro.

 Nella guida che segue vi...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Features Google Pixel Phones Should Steal From Samsung]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=802554</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/802554/5-features-google-pixel-phones-should-steal-from-samsung/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T12:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Love it or hate it, Samsung Galaxy devices have tons of features. Pixel phones, on the other hand, are very simple. Google could learn a thing or two from Samsung and make Pixel devices even better. We have some suggestions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft warns: This botnet has new tricks to target Linux and Windows systems]]></title>
        <id>d84863a5-c56e-49ab-9043-a8728c60a543</id>
        <link href="https://www.zdnet.com/article/microsoft-warns-this-botnet-has-new-tricks-to-target-linux-and-windows-systems/#ftag=RSSbaffb68"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T11:49:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft is warning admins of a botnet that employs multiple exploits and steals database credentials.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest topics for ZDNet in Windows</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple eFuse Driver Coming To Linux 5.19]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Apple-eFuse-For-Linux-5.19</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Apple-eFuse-For-Linux-5.19"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In addition to Linux 5.19 set to add NVMe support for the Apple M1 systems, the Apple eFuse driver also from the open-source community is geared up for landing in this next version of the Linux kernel...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft's replaces bundled Quick Assist app with Microsoft Store version]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178597</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/05/16/microsofts-replaces-bundled-quick-assist-app-with-microsoft-store-version/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T11:08:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quick Assist is a remote assistance application that is part of Microsoft's Windows 10 and 11 operating systems. Up until now, Quick Assist was available to all users to get remote assistance, […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Microsoft's replaces bundled Quick Assist app with Microsoft Store version appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Do I See “FBI Surveillance Van” in My Wi-Fi List?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=802909</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/802909/why-do-i-see-fbi-surveillance-van-in-my-wi-fi-list/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T11:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re trying to connect to a Wi-Fi access point and you see “FBI Surveillance Van” in your SSID list, should you be worried? Is there an FBI van outside your door? We’ll get to the bottom of this surprisingly common situation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AU Optronics presenta i pannelli a 480 Hz per monitor e display dei notebook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=AU-Optronics-presenta-i-pannelli-a-480-Hz-per-monitor-e-display-dei-notebook_24518</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=AU-Optronics-presenta-i-pannelli-a-480-Hz-per-monitor-e-display-dei-notebook_24518"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T10:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AU Optronics (AUO) è uno dei principali produttori al mondo di pannelli per monitor e display di tutti i tipi. L'azienda, con sede centrale a Taiwan, è all'avanguardia per ciò che riguarda la presentazione di prodotti capaci di offrire frequenze di refresh elevate.La novità più recente consiste nella presentazione di una coppia di pannelli con risoluzione FullHD, refresh a 480 Hz e tempo di risposta inferiore al millisecondo.Si tratta di prodotti che andranno a sostituire gli attuali pannelli a 360 Hz presenti in molti portatili e monitor di fascia alta destinati ai videogiocatori che possono disporre di budget importanti.L'unico aspetto negativo per ciò che riguarda la nuova proposta di AU Optronics, è che si tratta di pannelli in tecnologia TN: da più parti si solleva quindi qualche dubbio sulla fedeltà cromatica.In un altro articolo abbiamo visto come scegliere il monitor del PC e descritto le differenze tra pannelli TN, IPS e VA.In ogni caso, AU Optronics fa segnare un record perché quelli presentati sono i primi dispositivi FullHD al mondo a raggiungere una frequenza di refresh di 480 Hz.Sebbene i portavoce di AU Optronics non si siano sbilanciati sulla data di disponibilità, diverse fonti confermano che i pannelli per i display a 480 Hz potrebbero cominciare a essere prodotti già durante quest'anno.Il video pubblicato a questo indirizzo mostra molti altri pannelli AU Optronics: tra di essi vi sono un IPS UHD a 165 Hz, diversi modelli per i sistemi di infotainment delle auto e gli AmLED, un tipo di mini LED..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are rust binaries a security concern because of how dependencies are handled?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uqsy8v/are_rust_binaries_a_security_concern_because_of/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uqsy8v/are_rust_binaries_a_security_concern_because_of/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T10:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As far as I know, when rust binaries are built their dependencies are downloaded and built into the executable. I'm a fan of having all binaries link to shared libraries instead, in order to be able to fix all instances of a given vulnerability with a single package upgrade instead of worrying about whether they have propagated to every dependent executable I use.
 In practice, does the package of a rust binary leave me open to vulnerabilities longer than a package that links to everything dynamically would? I would love to get some packagers' perspective on this as well. Do you see issues with this dependency handling approach? Your experience from other languages might also be relevant if they use the same model.
 EDIT: adding another question; those of you who do consider it a security concern, do you abstain from using programs written in rust or do you find the risk acceptable in order to use the apps you like?
    submitted by    /u/patatahooligan  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Raspberry Pi's Vulkan Driver Has Been Adding More Extensions, Multi-Sync Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=V3DV-Vulkan-May-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=V3DV-Vulkan-May-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Consulting firm Igalia that has been working on the Mesa V3DV open-source Vulkan driver for the Raspberry Pi 4 and newer has published a summary of recent accomplishments for this Mesa solution...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kon Boot, come funziona il programma per superare il login di Windows e macOS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Kon-Boot-come-funziona-il-programma-per-superare-il-login-di-Windows-e-macOS_24517</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Kon-Boot-come-funziona-il-programma-per-superare-il-login-di-Windows-e-macOS_24517"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T10:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Se si ha la necessità di accedere a un PC Windows o a un sistema macOS pur non conoscendo la password per il login, Kon Boot è una delle soluzioni che si sono storicamente rivelate più affidabili.Kon Boot nasce nel 2008 e con il tempo ha subìto molteplici aggiornamenti adattandosi alla continua evoluzione della tecnologia.La differenza rispetto ad altre soluzioni per superare il login di Windows e bypassare l'inserimento della password, anche sulle macchine basate su macOS, è che Kon Boot inietta il suo codice in memoria prima del caricamento del sistema operativo.Questa tattica permette a Kon Boot di modificare temporaneamente il comportamento del sistema di autenticazione utilizzato da Windows e macOS permettendo il semplice superamento della password.Kon Boot non modifica la configurazione di Windows e di macOS né cambia le password degli account già presenti: il suo comportamento è assimilabile a quello di un bootkit benigno.A meno che l'utente non confermi a Kon Boot la volontà di creare un nuovo account amministratore, dopo il caricamento del programma è sufficiente accedere con qualunque utente digitando una password casuale e premendo Invio.Kon Boot va installato in una chiavetta USB (lo sviluppatore consiglia l'utilizzo di un'unità da almeno 16 GB di capienza) e il supporto viene automaticamente reso avviabile: lasciando inserita la chiavetta ed effettuando il boot da tale supporto, il programma disporrà il caricamento del codice per la 'neutralizzazione' della procedura di autenticazione del sistema operativo.Per ripristinare la situazione precedente, a login effettuato basta semplicemente rimuovere la chiavetta con Kon Boot quindi spegnere la macchina oppure riavviarla.Kon Boot è assolutamente sicuro ma alcuni antimalware tendono a segnalarlo come una minaccia: ciò non deriva dal fatto che il programma contiene codice malevolo ma è semplicemente legato alla natura dell'utilità.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mesa's Radeon Vulkan Driver Lands Indirect Ray-Tracing Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=RADV-Indirect-Ray-Tracing-Lands</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=RADV-Indirect-Ray-Tracing-Lands"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mesa's Radeon Vulkan driver "RADV" continues working on maturing its ray-tracing implementation after the initial code was merged last year. RADV ray-tracing is still treated as experimental and not as reliable as the proprietary NVIDIA Vulkan driver's ray-tracing support that has been around much longer, but it's getting there and at least is open-source -- unlike AMD's official AMDVLK driver that continues to not support Vulkan RT unlike their proprietary driver alternative...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Posts Latest Code For KCFI As Better Control-Flow Integrity For The Linux Kernel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-KCFI-RFC-v2</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-KCFI-RFC-v2"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T09:42:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google engineer Sami Tolvanen has posted the second "request for comments" patch series on KCFI as a Control-Flow Integrity implementation better geared for Linux kernel usage than the existing CFI support...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mesa 22.2 Continues Modernizing With More GLSL IR Code Replaced By NIR]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Mesa-22.2-NIR-Varying-Linker</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Mesa-22.2-NIR-Varying-Linker"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T09:15:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mesa developer Timothy Arceri of Valve's Linux graphics driver team has added a NIR varying linker for GLSL...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Western Digital presenta tante novità in ambito storage: hard disk e SSD per i vari segmenti di mercato]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Western-Digital-presenta-tante-novita-in-ambito-storage-hard-disk-e-SSD-per-i-vari-segmenti-di-mercato_24516</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Western-Digital-presenta-tante-novita-in-ambito-storage-hard-disk-e-SSD-per-i-vari-segmenti-di-mercato_24516"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T08:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Western Digital ha tenuto una presentazione molto articolata durante la quale ha descritto la sua visione per lo storage del futuro svelando una serie di prodotti innovativi.La missione consiste nello sbloccare il potenziale dei dati rendendo disponibile tutto il loro valore. Allo stesso tempo Western Digital ha svelato alcune importanti innovazioni sia in ambito hard disk che sul piano delle memorie flash utilizzabili sia dalle aziende che dagli utenti privati.Si parte con le unità SSD NVMe WD_BLACK SN850X basate su interfaccia PCIe Gen 4 per trasferimenti di dati fino a 7.300 MB/s.Offrono latenza ridotta al minimo, caricamento predittivo e gestione termica adattiva, tutte caratteristiche particolarmente apprezzate dagli appassionati di gaming alla continua ricerca di prestazioni senza compromessi.

La WD_BLACK Dashboard, grazie alla sua nuova modalità Game Mode 2.0 disponibile solo per Windows, offre funzionalità per potenziare le prestazioni del PC in modo che i giocatori possano giocare, eseguire lo streaming, registrare e raggiungere le massime performance possibili.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux 5.18 Anticipated For Next Weekend, Linux 5.18-rc7 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.18-rc7-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.18-rc7-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T08:36:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linus Torvalds has released what is likely the last release candidate before officially declaring Linux 5.18 next weekend if all goes according to plan...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can't change the font of startup log]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uqq5o2/cant_change_the_font_of_startup_log/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uqq5o2/cant_change_the_font_of_startup_log/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T07:19:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I put FONT=ter-v24b in /etc/vconsole.conf and did a reboot. While tty and poweroff log font have changed, startup log (the stuff printed onscreen before gdm opens) is still displayed in small font. sd-vconsole mkinitcpio hook is present. What am I doing wrong?
    submitted by    /u/Saikat0511  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First look at Portmaster, an open source cross-platform network monitor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178592</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/05/16/first-look-at-portmaster-an-open-source-cross-platform-network-monitor/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T06:57:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Portmaster is a free open source cross-platform network activity monitor that is available in an early version for Windows and the Linux distributions Ubuntu and Fedora. Portmaster combines traditional network activity monitoring […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post First look at Portmaster, an open source cross-platform network monitor appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[With NVIDIA releasing source code, should I still buy AMD (price is higher where I live)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uqn5o4/with_nvidia_releasing_source_code_should_i_still/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uqn5o4/with_nvidia_releasing_source_code_should_i_still/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T04:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My NVIDIA GPU died on the day they announced the release of source code (the irony!).
 I need to buy another one. But AMD GPUs with similar specs are priced higher than NVIDIA ones where I live.
 I have never had any issue with driver though in my Arch Linux installation. But I always felt guilt about using NVIDIA (due to closed source) and planned to buy an AMD GPU as the next one, because of the open source.
 Is it justified at this moment to spend more to get an AMD GPU?
 (Posting this in r/archlinux because I want the Arch Linux perspective)
    submitted by    /u/spark29  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blender doesn't run after system update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uqlamu/blender_doesnt_run_after_system_update/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uqlamu/blender_doesnt_run_after_system_update/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T02:12:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Title. I need help getting it to work again.
 This is the output I get when I try to run it from the command line:
 blender: symbol lookup error: blender: undefined symbol: _ZNKSt7__cxx1112basic_stringIcSt11char_traitsIcESaIcEE7compareEPKc, version LLVM_13 
 I tried looking up that output online, but all I got was an unrelated issue relating to Alembic.
 Blender version: blender 17:3.1.2-2
 Edit: fixed after another update
    submitted by    /u/ChromaCat248  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can't switch to TTY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uqjm9m/cant_switch_to_tty/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uqjm9m/cant_switch_to_tty/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T00:38:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ctrl + alt +f keys don't work, same if I hold fn. I've tested with the same keyboard on Garuda Linux and it works normally. Only GUI seems to work on this install. I used the normal arch iso and went through archinstall.
    submitted by    /u/dasenase  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PAPPL 1.2 Released With Full Localization Support, More IPP Features]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=PAPPL-1.2-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=PAPPL-1.2-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T00:36:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PAPPL as the free software project started by CUPS founder Michael Sweet after departing Apple more than two years ago, this C-based framework/library for creating CUPS Printer Applications is out with a major feature release...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia drivers dont detect gpu]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uqhcxu/nvidia_drivers_dont_detect_gpu/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uqhcxu/nvidia_drivers_dont_detect_gpu/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-15T22:34:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[its in the title. i have an rtx 2060. nvidia-smi shows "no devices where found", and dmesg shows nvidia-drm failing to do something. nouveau can load, but it isnt quite useable. this occurs on both nvidia and nvidia-open, as well as their respective dkms variants. journalctl shows it failing to load some glx module as well. how might i be able to fix this? (i am early loading the modules). this all started occuring after install gdm-plymouth and plymouth-git. both of which have since been removed
    submitted by    /u/jumper775  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's new and improved in Windows 11 22H2, coming soon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/whats-new-and-improved-in-windows-11-22h2-coming-soon/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/whats-new-and-improved-in-windows-11-22h2-coming-soon/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-15T22:15:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 version 22H2 aka Sun Valley 2 is set to launch later this year. Unlike the original Windows 11 release, it won't be a massive update with radical design changes. Instead, Sun Valley 2 will be similar to Windows 10 Anniversary Update, so you can expect minor improvements and a few new features. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mayank Parmar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Safe to update?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uqgtax/safe_to_update/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uqgtax/safe_to_update/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-15T22:07:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I usually update my system about once a week, but I've been reading a lot about errors with the current nvidia drivers. Is it safe to update now? I'm not concerned about reinstalling if something happens, but I'd rather not.
    submitted by    /u/keroeslux  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recensione Trifo Max: robot aspirapolvere, lavapavimenti e sentinella antifurto tutto-in-uno]]></title>
        <id>3568|20220516000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/domotica-iot-internet-of-things-6322/recensione-trifo-max-robot-aspirapolvere-lavapavimenti-sentinella-antifurto-tutto-3568"/>
        <updated>2022-05-15T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fra il mio lavoro regolare, l'impegno con TurboLab.it e il canale YouTube, ho davvero poco tempo libero. Per questo motivo, devo fare il possibile per automatizzare e ottimizzare ogni altra attività. Una fra queste è la pulizia della casa, ed è quindi con grande piacere che ho provato Trifo Max: un robot-aspirapolvere dotato anche di serbatoio per il lavaggio dei pavimenti e di telecamera di sicurezza incorporata, in grado di trasmettere un flusso audio-video in tempo reale oppure rilevare il movimento. Vediamo dunque come si è comportato in questa recensione dell'aspirapolvere Trifo Max
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is AppFlash on Android and Do You Need It?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=362344</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/13862715/what-is-appflash-android"/>
        <updated>2022-05-15T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Device carriers and manufacturers have never quite understood users – we don’t like or need bloatware. Yet, Verizon decided all Android users needed AppFlash on their devices. It quietly appeared on existing devices in 2017 and later became preinstalled. 
    
After a lot of opposition, Verizon eventually stopped supporting AppFlash and disabled it  on existing devices through updates (whereas newer devices don’t come with it preinstalled). Yep, it’s all been a bit messy, so here’s everything you need to know.
   

Content

What Is AppFlash?
Is AppFlash Safe?
How to Disable AppFlash
Dealing with AppFlash Crashes
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Access an Android Phone with a Broken Screen
    
What Is AppFlash?
    
According to Verizon, AppFlash was a content discovery service, designed to be an all-in-one app for finding everything... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Crystal Crowder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Update an Xbox Wireless Controller Using a PC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=728815</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/728815/how-to-update-xbox-wireless-controller-using-a-pc/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-15T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s easy to update the Microsoft Wireless Controller (for Xbox Series X|S) using a Windows 10 PC. You’ll just need to download a Microsoft app, plug in your controller, and follow the onscreen instructions. Here’s how to do it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pranay Parab</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Reboot or Factory Reset Your Google Chromecast]]></title>
        <id>http://www.howtogeek.com/?p=204378</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/204378/how-to-reboot-or-factory-reset-your-google-chromecast/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-15T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chromecast devices—including Chromecast with Google TV—are known for being simple, but that doesn’t mean they don’t require a reboot or factory reset from time to time. We’ll show you how to do it in a few different ways.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia suspend - performance and GPU usage is low on resume for currently running game.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uqdv25/nvidia_suspend_performance_and_gpu_usage_is_low/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uqdv25/nvidia_suspend_performance_and_gpu_usage_is_low/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-15T19:45:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was trying to suspend and resume while a game is running and I followed the instructions here and from the arch wiki to allow suspending the VRAM to disk, but on resume the GPU usage is low (~50-70%) and performance is poor.
 I'm not sure where to start trying to solve this problem. After closing the game and opening it again performance is fine again.
 Any help is appreciated. I didn't see the service spit out any errors, but it's possible I don't know where to look.
    submitted by    /u/themountaincow  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can't copy large screenshots to web-based applications, unless copied from a file or from GIMP/Krita]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uqdgqg/cant_copy_large_screenshots_to_webbased/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uqdgqg/cant_copy_large_screenshots_to_webbased/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-15T19:26:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, this is an odd problem I'm having with using screenshot programs. 
 When I take a screenshot, if the region is too large (for instance, my entire 4k screen), I'm unable to copy it to "web-based" applications. Discord, web-browser (vivaldi), and element-desktop, are all the ones I've tested it with. They all do the same thing, just empty files or empty screenshots with a 0B size. If I do a smaller selection (like a 800x600 region), then I'm able to copy from my clipboard just fine.
 Weirdly though, I'm able to copy images from online just fine, some well past 16k resolution. Also, when using the screenshot programs, only those "web-based" applications are affected, I can copy into Krita and GIMP just fine, and if I copy from there, I can then copy it into those "web-based" applications just fine. I'm also able to copy large images from files just fine as well.
 I've tried this with flameshot, shutter, spectacle, and they all do the same thing. 
 I'm running a fresh install of arch with just i3-gaps + KDE, X11, no compositor (tried picom and that didn't fix it, so I removed it).
 Any ideas? Anyone else had this issue and resolved it? Thanks.
    submitted by    /u/wekede  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pip cannot import name 'InvalidSchemeCombination']]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uqddc9/pip_cannot_import_name_invalidschemecombination/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uqddc9/pip_cannot_import_name_invalidschemecombination/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-15T19:22:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My pip stops working. Any advice how to solve it? Thanks.
 Traceback (most recent call last): File "/usr/bin/pip", line 33, in <module> sys.exit(load_entry_point('pip==21.0', 'console_scripts', 'pip')()) File "/usr/bin/pip", line 25, in importlib_load_entry_point return next(matches).load() File "/usr/lib/python3.10/importlib/metadata/__init__.py", line 171, in load module = import_module(match.group('module')) File "/usr/lib/python3.10/importlib/__init__.py", line 126, in import_module return _bootstrap._gcd_import(name[level:], package, level) File "<frozen importlib._bootstrap>", line 1050, in _gcd_import File "<frozen importlib._bootstrap>", line 1027, in _find_and_load File "<frozen importlib._bootstrap>", line 1006, in _find_and_load_unlocked File "<frozen importlib._bootstrap>", lin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Empty the Trash on Android]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=803372</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/803372/how-to-empty-trash-on-android/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-15T19:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unlike a desktop computer’s trash system, Android doesn’t offer a universal recycle bin that stores your deleted files. Instead, most Android apps manage their own trash, which you have to individually empty to free up your phone’s storage. Here’s how to do that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Wants to Pay You For Your Shopping Data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117892/amazon-wants-to-pay-you-for-your-shopping-data/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117892/amazon-wants-to-pay-you-for-your-shopping-data/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-15T19:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon’s latest idea, a cashback rewards system, is offering you the chance to get a little money back on select purchases at your favorite stores. But a darker motive lurks behind the lightly lucrative veneer of the concept: data collection.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzanne Humphries</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers are exploiting critical bug in Zyxel firewalls and VPNs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-are-exploiting-critical-bug-in-zyxel-firewalls-and-vpns/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-are-exploiting-critical-bug-in-zyxel-firewalls-and-vpns/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-15T18:47:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers have started to exploit a recently patched critical vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2022-30525, that affects Zyxel firewall and VPN devices for businesses. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Ilascu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is there absolutely no way to get wifi working on a MacBook Pro 16,1?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uqc4ow/is_there_absolutely_no_way_to_get_wifi_working_on/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uqc4ow/is_there_absolutely_no_way_to_get_wifi_working_on/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-15T18:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to this, there's no supported firmware for the BCM4364 card. Does this mean I have no hope of using Arch without an ethernet cable? Is there any way to revert back to MacOS and take the firmware from there?
    submitted by    /u/MxpleSyrup  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Download a Google Doc]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=803400</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/803400/google-docs-download/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-15T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Google Docs’ download option, you can download some or all documents from the cloud to your desktop and mobile devices in various formats. These formats include the popular ones like PDF and Microsoft Word (DOCX). We’ll show you how to do that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[efly: First Official Release]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uqbcxh/efly_first_official_release/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uqbcxh/efly_first_official_release/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-15T17:47:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[last week i announced efly, a new arch-based live medium for installing arch linux - or for using as a portable linux live system. however, some changes still needed to be made to make the system fully usable. you can now download ready-made boot images from the github page.
 instructions on how to build it yourself are provided on github. otherwise you can try it out directly:
  sudo pacman -S archiso wget https://github.com/flying-dude/efly/releases/download/latest/efly-live.iso run_archiso -i efly-live.iso 
 if you have plugged in a USB stick with corresponding device node /dev/sdY, then you can turn it into a bootable live medium like this (and yes, you can literally just copy an image to a block device and it'll work):
  sudo cp efly-live.iso /dev/sdY 
 i also placed a modified version of the qemu wrapper in the repo, since i needed an option to mount virtfs file systems. here is an example from the help page:
  Share a folder with qemu: $ run_archiso_efly archiso-2020.05.23-x86_64.iso -- -virtfs local,path=/path/to/share,mount_tag=host0,security_model=passthrough,id=host0 Mount shared folder inside qemu: $ mkdir virtfs; sudo mount -t 9p -o trans=virtio host0 virtfs/ 
 changelog:
  
browser: konqueror -> chromium
 drop into tty when losing X server
 modified the prompt style of fish shell: 
 example showing prompt when in folder /usr/local/bin:
 old style: efly@arch /u/l/bin>
 new style: [efly@arch] bin/ $
 
  
   submitted by    /u/flying-dude  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did libstdc++ 12.1 break builds for anyone else?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uqb7k7/did_libstdc_121_break_builds_for_anyone_else/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uqb7k7/did_libstdc_121_break_builds_for_anyone_else/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-15T17:40:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Libstdc++ seems to have moved std::size_t and std::nullptr_t into the cstddef header as size_t and nullptr_t. I changed my code but it looks like other standard headers (type_traits for me) still use the old style and as such I'm getting a slew of build errors. Just wondering if anyone else is seeing this?
    submitted by    /u/rao000  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting an error when trying to use prime-run "Segmentation fault(core dumped)"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uqarxj/getting_an_error_when_trying_to_use_primerun/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uqarxj/getting_an_error_when_trying_to_use_primerun/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-15T17:19:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I tried to run obs on and pretty much any thing on my dGpu and it would show me this error when trying prime-run glxinfo or prime-run glxgears would show me this error. Everything was working perfectly till a few hours ago, not sure if its the new driver version or me lacking a package.
    submitted by    /u/MaterialNet  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These New Smart Screws Send Out Alerts When They're Loose]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117940/these-new-smart-screws-send-out-alerts-when-theyre-loose/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117940/these-new-smart-screws-send-out-alerts-when-theyre-loose/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-15T17:13:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We get to hear about innovations with laptops, smartphones, earbuds, and the like all the time, but rarely about smaller smart technology. However, that’s what makes things like this new smart self-powered screw so exciting. Yep, you heard us—a smart screw.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzanne Humphries</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When to Replace Your Old Keyboard]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=796147</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/796147/when-to-replace-your-old-keyboard/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-15T17:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is your keyboard comfortable to use all day long? Is typing feel effortless and your time on the computer enjoyable? Here’s when you might want to consider replacing your old keyboard.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Nguyen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox Ctrl+F Pc Speaker BLEEEP]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uq9xtw/firefox_ctrlf_pc_speaker_bleeep/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uq9xtw/firefox_ctrlf_pc_speaker_bleeep/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-15T16:39:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My PC Speaker Bleeps really loud when i search something while pressing keys on my keyboard. i don't know how to disable this without fully disabling the pc speaker because i need it for other stuff, but its annoying like this and i use this shortcut very much. can anybody help?
    submitted by    /u/yaktoma2007  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fake Pixelmon NFT site infects you with password-stealing malware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fake-pixelmon-nft-site-infects-you-with-password-stealing-malware/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fake-pixelmon-nft-site-infects-you-with-password-stealing-malware/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-15T16:34:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A fake Pixelmon NFT site entices fans with free tokens and collectibles while infecting them with malware that steals their cryptocurrency wallets. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to add arch linux signatures and keys to secure boot?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uq9fld/how_to_add_arch_linux_signatures_and_keys_to/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uq9fld/how_to_add_arch_linux_signatures_and_keys_to/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-15T16:15:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello,
 I have absolutely no knowledge about linux or secure boot or whatever but I want to dual boot arch and windows.
 However, secure boot is blocking the boot of arch linux and I don't want to disable secure boot since it leaves my PC vulnerable.
 I wanted to ask on how I can add my own signatures and keys to secure boot so I can boot up arch linux with secure boot being enabled.
 I kind of looked through the secure boot section and there was an append option which lets me add my own certificates and stuff, if that helps.
 Thanks.
    submitted by    /u/AsuxAX  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Should You Buy a Portable Nintendo Switch Dock?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=799979</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/799979/should-you-buy-a-portable-nintendo-switch-dock/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-15T16:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you travel with your Nintendo Switch you might appreciate the ability to play docked when you’re near a TV or monitor away from home. The official dock is a lot bigger than necessary to get the job done. That’s why you might want to consider a portable dock instead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is this? Is it safe to remove nvidia foir nvidia-dkms for it? It seems a bit suspicious.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uq8wkd/what_is_this_is_it_safe_to_remove_nvidia_foir/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uq8wkd/what_is_this_is_it_safe_to_remove_nvidia_foir/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-15T15:50:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I did pacman -Syu and got this:  warning: removing 'nvidia' from target list because it conflicts with 'nvidia-dkms' :: nvidia-dkms and nvidia are in conflict (NVIDIA-MODULE). Remove nvidia? `
    submitted by    /u/deter0  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Windows 10 and 11 Easter Eggs to Seek Out]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=333627</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/14580447/windows10-easter-eggs-and-secrets"/>
        <updated>2022-05-15T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has a long and entertaining history of hiding Easter eggs, secret games and other oddities in its operating systems. Who can forget Hall of Tortured Souls in Microsoft Office in Windows 95, or Pinball in Word 97? 
    
Windows 10 and Windows 11 aren’t quite as playful as previous iterations, phasing Easter eggs out since it began its Trustworthy Computing Initiative in 2002. But there are still a few hidden surprises here and there. Here are our favorite Windows Easter eggs and secrets.
   

Content

1. The Spinning Cog (Windows 11)
2. Doom's Dedicated Port
3. Make Phone Calls
4. Star Wars CMD Movie
5. God Mode
6. Hobbits (Windows 10)
7. Cortana Games

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:15 Safe Websites for Downloading Windows Software
    
1. The Spinning Cog (Windows 11)
    
If you ever stumble upon the recognizable Settings cog icon in... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Crystal Crowder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla Semi Truck Orders Open As Release Date Looms]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117930/tesla-semi-truck-orders-open-as-release-date-looms/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117930/tesla-semi-truck-orders-open-as-release-date-looms/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-15T15:23:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla’s long-delayed electric Semi truck is finally inching closer to reality, as the company just opened orders and reservations in the United States. This news comes as the release date remains a mystery.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Akonadi crashes after system upgrade]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uq80vt/akonadi_crashes_after_system_upgrade/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uq80vt/akonadi_crashes_after_system_upgrade/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-15T15:07:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi!
 I've just upgraded my system (which pulled in a bunch of new KDE package versions) and after restarting, Akonadi and everything using it, e.g. Kmail, don't work anymore.
 akonadictl start produces the following output:
 org.kde.pim.akonadictl: Starting Akonadi Server... org.kde.pim.akonadictl: done. Connecting to deprecated signal QDBusConnectionInterface::serviceOwnerChanged(QString,QString,QString) org.kde.pim.akonadiserver: Starting up the Akonadi Server... akonadi.collectionattributetable OK akonadi.collectionmimetyperelation OK akonadi.collectionpimitemrelation OK /usr/bin/mysqlcheck: Got error: 2013: Lost connection to server during query when executing 'CHECK TABLE ... FOR UPGRADE' org.kde.pim.akonadiserver: Failed to verify database server version org.kde.pim.akonadiserver: Query error: "Server has gone away QMYSQL: Unable to execute query" org.kde.pim.akonadiserver: Database error: "" org.kde.pim.akonadiserver: Shutting down AkonadiServer... org.kde.pim.akonadicontrol: Application '/usr/bin/akonadiserver' exited normally... 
 Has anyone encountered similar issues? Any ideas what to do in order to fix this? 
 Thanks!
    submitted by    /u/lx901  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make a Table in Google Sheets Using a Table Chart]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=798871</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/798871/how-to-make-a-table-chart-in-google-sheets-using-a-chart/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-15T15:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unlike Microsoft Excel, Google Sheets doesn’t offer an official method for inserting a table. As a workaround, you could create what looks like a table using borders and filters, but another option is to use a table chart in Google Sheets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows admins frustrated by Quick Assist moving to Microsoft Store]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-admins-frustrated-by-quick-assist-moving-to-microsoft-store/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-admins-frustrated-by-quick-assist-moving-to-microsoft-store/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-15T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows admins have been expressing their dismay at Microsoft's decision to move the Quick Assist remote assistance tool to the Microsoft Store. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Bluetooth Speakers of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=743546</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/743546/best-bluetooth-speakers/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-15T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Finding the perfect Bluetooth speaker can be overwhelming due to the staggering amount of options on the market. Cut the laborious part out of your shopping experience and let our top picks guide you through the process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Fysz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Issues with second monitor displaying at incorrect size (size, not resolution.)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uq6pdv/issues_with_second_monitor_displaying_at/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uq6pdv/issues_with_second_monitor_displaying_at/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-15T13:58:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm not entirely sure how to describe this issue in a way a search engine would understand, and I haven't done enough troubleshooting to ask the forums without getting someone annoyed at me, so I'm posting here to ask if anyone else has had the same issue as me:
 I just build a new pc with a modern graphics card, but my second monitor is attempting to display a screen larger than itself. It's displaying the correct resolution, but seems to think the screen size itself is an inch larger than it actually is, so my mouse and my windows can go about a cm or so offscreen at any given edge. It's really annoying, as maximizing applications will prevent me from seeing their borders. It also looks really ugly, as despite the monitor displaying the correct resolution internally, it's actually displaying a weird, large fraction of the 1440p that it's supposed to (since the borders are cut off) and it looks downscaled.
 This issue did not occur with my previous computer, and my primary monitor is working perfectly fine. Both monitors are 2560x1440. This issue persisted all the way from initial install from the bootable medium, through installation of KDE.
 Possible causes I've thought of:
  
I'm using an HDMI cable instead of a DisplayPort cable (I don't have the spare cable to test this, though)
 The monitor is too old for it to report its size to my GPU properly, so it's receiving an incorrect size.
  
Does anyone have any help or suggestions for troubleshooting?
    submitted by    /u/Psychological-Owl908  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>