<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-05-26T01:59:16.616Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can I have a workspace with tor and another without it?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uxw6h2/can_i_have_a_workspace_with_tor_and_another/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uxw6h2/can_i_have_a_workspace_with_tor_and_another/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T01:20:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I want to use tor for something other than browsing but I don't want to divide the resources of my computer by having a virtual machine running all the time. Is there other way to use tor? I just want to commit to a NSFW project on Github but I don't want Micro$oft selling my data for everyone to know.
 The ideal for me would be to have a tor workspace and a clear net one.
    submitted by    /u/ConsistentSense4760  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Move a Column in Microsoft Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=post-ideas&amp;p=474415</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15330255/howto-move-column-excel"/>
        <updated>2022-05-26T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Excel comes with a long list of shortcuts and formulas that help you execute a wide range of operations. Naturally, one might need help from external sources to discover all the tips and tricks that can be applied within the application.
    
In this article, we will look at three different ways to move a column in a Microsoft Excel worksheet. The following methods apply to Microsoft Excel 2019 and newer versions.
   

Content

1. Use Drag and Drop to Move a Column in Excel
2. Use Cut and Paste to Move Excel Columns
3. Use Sort to Switch Columns in Excel 
How to Move a Table Column in Excel
Use Macros

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:The Essential VLOOKUP Guide for Excel and Google Sheets
    
1. Use Drag and Drop to Move a Column in Excel
    
The “drag... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ojash Yadav</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VMWare bugs with Arch?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uxu0v9/vmware_bugs_with_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uxu0v9/vmware_bugs_with_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T23:25:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I noticed that some weird colors appear inside my browser when I'm using Arch on a VM.. Does anyone know stuff about that?
 ​
 https://media.discordapp.net/attachments/852196337431740419/979112428514201680/Screenshot_from_2022-05-25_21-06-33.png?width=1609&height=905
    submitted by    /u/InvitedToHell  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Environment Variables]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uxtsuz/environment_variables/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uxtsuz/environment_variables/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T23:13:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi all, 
 I am using a yubikey for SSH authentication but I am running into a problem where GUI apps unless I run them from the terminal don't use the GPG agent, since I am only launching it thru .zshrc. And I am pulling my hair trying to launching the gpg-agent when I log into my GNOME session, everything I tried doesn't work such as - .profile, .zshenv, .zprofile, ../environment.d/file.conf, etc.. Anyone have any idea what the best way to do this is?
    submitted by    /u/The_Jo_Ker  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux 5.19 Networking Brings Big Improvements With Big TCP, PureLiFi, More Hardware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-Networking</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-Networking"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T22:40:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The networking subsystem updates have landed in the Linux 5.19 kernel with big updates to core networking code as well as a lot of individual driver work this cycle both for wired and wireless networking...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTC fines Twitter $150M for using 2FA info for targeted advertising]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/ftc-fines-twitter-150m-for-using-2fa-info-for-targeted-advertising/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/ftc-fines-twitter-150m-for-using-2fa-info-for-targeted-advertising/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T21:51:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Federal Trade Commission has fined Twitter $150 million for using phone numbers and email addresses collected to enable two-factor authentication for targeted advertising. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Easiest Ways to Access Blocked Websites]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=477659</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15330084/best-ways-access-blocked-websites"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether the URL you want to visit is blocked by your ISP or georestricted by site owners, you can remove the restrictions yourself. Maybe you want to help friends who live in countries where they can’t access the sites you take for granted due to government censorship. Alternatively, your favorite VPNs might be blocked by your ISP. With this guide, you can unblock anything you want. We will show you the easiest ways to access blocked websites.
   

Content

How ISPs Block Websites
1. Virtual Private Network (VPN)
2. Mirror Sites and Alternate URLs
3. Free Web Proxies
4. The Tor Project
5. Changed DNS Settings
6. SSH Tunneling
7. Use the Wayback Machine
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Block Websites on Chrome, Firefox, Edge, Safari, Android, and iOS
    
How ISPs Block Websites
  ... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sayak Boral</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rant: Some of you need to go and read more than just the installation guide.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uxr1rm/rant_some_of_you_need_to_go_and_read_more_than/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uxr1rm/rant_some_of_you_need_to_go_and_read_more_than/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T21:02:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I had to go back and have a look at the wiki to ensure I wasn't going crazy, but the Arch Linux principles are, and have always been, pretty crystal clear. While the language has been refined over the years, they are still the same in spirit as they were 10+ years ago when I first read them. If you haven't done so, consider giving the Arch Linux overview a read.
 Yes, it does bother me when someone posts a thread to this sub questioning the quality of a product that they get at no cost, complaining about problems caused by upstream bugs, and also complaining about solutions offered by community members. It bothers me a great deal and if you have read and agree with the Arch Linux principles, it should bother you, too.
 I do respond to such threads with links to the wiki and snark, because I'm genuinely offended at the implications of such posts. The implication being that Arch isn't meeting the user's needs in certain areas, and that someone else is responsible for shoring up those shortcomings to fulfill their expectations. And what really gets my goat, is that what they often consider failures of the distro are actually features, in light of user centrality. It would be far more constructive for a user to check for/open bug reports, and would constitute an actual semblance of contribution to the community, instead of complaining.
 Edit: markdown
    submitted by    /u/krakenfury_  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Disable Bing in the Windows 10 Start Menu]]></title>
        <id>http://www.howtogeek.com/?p=224159</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/224159/how-to-disable-bing-in-the-windows-10-start-menu/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 10, by default, sends everything you search for in the Start Menu to their servers to give you results from Bing search — so you better make sure that you don’t type anything private into your own PC’s Start Menu. Or, you could just disable the Bing integration in the Start Menu.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft adds support for WSL2 distros on Windows Server 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-adds-support-for-wsl2-distros-on-windows-server-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-adds-support-for-wsl2-distros-on-windows-server-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T20:54:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has announced that Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSL2) distros are now supported on Windows Server 2022 after installing this week's cumulative update previews. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Plex Finally Has a Linux Desktop Player]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=807755</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/807755/plex-finally-has-a-linux-desktop-player/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T20:43:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plex is one of the most popular ways to stream your own media collection, but there hasn’t been an officially-available app for playing all Plex content on Linux — until now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch disappears from GRUB -- I found a solution.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uxq4e6/arch_disappears_from_grub_i_found_a_solution/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uxq4e6/arch_disappears_from_grub_i_found_a_solution/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T20:18:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Arch entry kept disappearing from my GRUB. Yes, even after a successful install following the Wiki closely. I noticed that this was happening to a lot of people, so I'd like to share a simple solution that I found that fixes this problem permanently. 
 After you install the GRUB and the efibootmgr, and after you run grub-mkconfig and get confirmation that it was done, here's what you do. 
 Go into your boot diretory by typing 
 # cd boot
 # ls (this will list the contents of this directory. EFI should be in there)
 # cd efi
 # ls (whatever you named your GRUB id should show up here. I named mine ARCH, so I'll just use that in this example)
 # mkdir boot (you'll need to create a boot directory here)
 # cd ARCH (now, remember, I named mine ARCH, yours will be different. If you followed the Wiki precisely, yours will be named GRUB)
 # ls (this will list the contents of this directory. There should be just one entry called grubx64.efi)
 # cp grubx64.efi ../boot/bootx64.efi (copy this boot file into the boot folder so that it can be read by the GRUB)
 # exit
 # reboot
 That's it. It'll work.
    submitted by    /u/ricktramp  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Safely Clean Your TV or Monitor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=762437</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/762437/how-to-safely-clean-your-tv-or-monitor/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s definitely a wrong way to clean your TV or monitor screen. Mess it up and you’ll be looking at scratches, smears, or worse for a long time. Get it right and your display will gleam like the day you bought it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple’s Self Service Repair Program Seems Like a Mess]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=807696</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/807696/apples-self-service-repair-program-seems-like-a-mess/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T19:41:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple finally launched a self-repair program for the iPhone last month, (theoretically) allowing anyone to fix their own iPhone without taking it to an authorized repair shop. However, it doesn’t seem like a great solution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Do Your Echo Speaker's Color Lights Mean?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119038/what-do-your-echo-speakers-color-lights-mean/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119038/what-do-your-echo-speakers-color-lights-mean/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T19:31:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Because they don’t have screens, Amazon Echo smart speakers use colored lights to communicate their needs or get your attention. But what does Alexa want this time? Interpreting an Echo speaker’s lights isn’t always easy, and in some cases, one color could mean several different things.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New ‘Cheers’ Linux ransomware targets VMware ESXi servers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-cheers-linux-ransomware-targets-vmware-esxi-servers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-cheers-linux-ransomware-targets-vmware-esxi-servers/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T19:25:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new ransomware named 'Cheers' has appeared in the cybercrime space and has started its operations by targeting vulnerable VMware ESXi servers. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save $52 on a Ring Alarm Kit with Video Doorbell]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=492704</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15329973/ring-alarm-kit-with-video-doorbell"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re heading back into the office and looking at doing less remote work, you want to be sure your home is safe while you’re gone. A Ring Alarm Kit with Video Doorbell could really come in handy and could make all the difference in terms of how comfortable you are with the situation. You can get it for more than $52.51 off the regular price.
    
This bundle includes a base station, keypad, four contact sensors, motion detector, range extender, and video doorbell. It works great in one- and two-bedroom homes and gives you whole-home protection while blending into your home to be unnoticeable.
    

    
The DIY Ring Alarm Kit with Video Doorbell includes an intuitive keypad with emergency buttons as well as smaller contact sensors that will blend seamlessly into your home decor. It allows you to receive mobile notifications when your system is triggered, change modes, and monitor the devices all from the Ring app.
    
Set up the system easily by plugging in the base station,... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NVIDIA VA-API 0.0.6 Driver Works On Multi-Threaded Decode, Improved GPU Selection]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=NVIDIA-VA-API-Driver-0.0.6</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=NVIDIA-VA-API-Driver-0.0.6"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The open-source, unofficial project providing a NVIDIA VA-API driver on Linux systems built atop the proprietary driver's NVDEC video decode interface is out with a new feature release. This NVIDIA-VAAPI-Driver effort continues to be driven in large part for allowing GPU-accelerated video acceleration in Firefox and other software only targeting the open Video Acceleration API...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Docs Has a Handy New Text Selection Feature]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=807684</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/807684/google-docs-has-a-handy-new-text-selection-feature/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T18:52:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Docs adds new features all the time, but now Google has added a useful new text feature: the ability to select multiple blocks of text at once.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['NFL Plus' Replaces Free Streaming with One That Costs Money]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119084/nfl-plus-replaces-free-streaming-with-one-that-costs-money/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119084/nfl-plus-replaces-free-streaming-with-one-that-costs-money/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T18:46:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No one needs another monthly streaming service and payment, but that’s what’s coming later this summer with “NFL Plus.” The National Football league is expected to launch the new NFL+ service in July, and it’ll replace the free mobile streaming service fans have enjoyed for the last several years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RadeonSI Adds EGL Context High Priority Support To Help Wayland Compositors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=RadeonSI-EGL-Context-Priority</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=RadeonSI-EGL-Context-Priority"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T18:44:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Landing today in the RadeonSI Gallium3D driver code-base for Mesa 22.2 is support for the EGL_IMG_context_priority extension. The RadeonSI EGL_IMG_context_priority support was contributed by a KDE developer with the motivation of ensuring Wayland compositors can have high priority for rendering...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to exit visudo]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uxo1wb/how_to_exit_visudo/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uxo1wb/how_to_exit_visudo/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T18:42:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I got stuck on [root@archiso /]# visudo blue text wall, I was adding standart user, and entered this instead EDITOR=nano visudo. How do exit it? I feel so stupid rn
 Edit
 Also I deleted some entries by accident while trying to exit somehow, so I need to exit it without saving it and trying opening it the way I want.
    submitted by    /u/Royal_Mongoose2907  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to install PlayOnLinux?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uxnye6/how_to_install_playonlinux/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uxnye6/how_to_install_playonlinux/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T18:38:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's gone in the regular repository and broken in the AUR. Can't find anyway to install. PlayOnLinux 4, not the terrible one on Flathub.
    submitted by    /u/ASTRODAWGFATHER  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft adds Office subscriptions to Windows 11 account settings]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-adds-office-subscriptions-to-windows-11-account-settings/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-adds-office-subscriptions-to-windows-11-account-settings/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T18:31:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has improved the account settings in the latest Windows 11 preview build, a settings page that now lists Office subscriptions linked to the user's Microsoft 365 account. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Does a Magic Eraser Actually Work?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lifesavvy.com/130458/how-does-a-magic-eraser-actually-work/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lifesavvy.com/130458/how-does-a-magic-eraser-actually-work/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T18:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Got crayon marks on your wall? How about scuffed areas along your baseboards? If so, you’ve probably reached for a Mr. Clean Magic Eraser before. These handy little sponges seem to magically remove marks, but have you ever wondered how that ‘magic’ actually works?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shea Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Enable Emergency Bypass on iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=805989</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/805989/emergency-bypass-iphone/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T18:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’d like to allow certain people to call, FaceTime, or message you when you’ve enabled Do Not Disturb mode, activate your iPhone’s Emergency Bypass option for those people. We’ll show you how to do just that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to View Your Saved Credit Card Numbers in Microsoft Edge]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=805877</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/805877/how-to-view-your-saved-credit-card-numbers-in-microsoft-edge/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T18:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you need to view, edit, or delete credit card numbers automatically saved by Microsoft Edge, it’s easy to do so using the browser’s payment info settings. Here’s how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dyson's Latest Crazy Idea is a Robot for Chores]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119048/dysons-latest-crazy-idea-is-a-robot-for-chores/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119048/dysons-latest-crazy-idea-is-a-robot-for-chores/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T17:47:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dyson is no stranger to crazy ideas. From its air-purifying headphones to mounting lasers on a vacuum to help find small particles of dust. However, the company recently revealed it’s secretly working on crazy robots it hopes will eventually do household chores we all hate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chromebook Keyboard Shortcuts]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=cheatsheet&amp;p=487944</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15329816/chromebook-keyboard-shortcuts"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T17:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Keyboard shortcuts make our day-to-day tasks easier on any device. Thankfully, Chromebook offers a huge list of keyboard shortcuts.
    
You can close windows, activate the split-screen mode, swap monitors, create desks, edit and format text, launch apps, turn on accessibility features, and do much more using Chromebook keyboard shortcuts.
    
We have divided the Chrome OS keyboard shortcuts based on their functionality in this cheatsheet. To find shortcuts on this page, press Ctrl + F and type whatever you are looking for.
    
Note: If your Chromebook keyboard doesn’t have the Search key, you must press the Launcher key instead to use the shortcut.
   
   
  
Download this Cheatsheet
 Enter your email below to receive this PDF cheatsheet in your Inbox.
     
  
  
... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mehvish Mushtaq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DuckDuckGo’s Browser Can’t Block Microsoft Tracking Scripts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=807530</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/807530/duckduckgos-browser-can%e2%80%99t-block-microsoft-tracking-scripts/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T17:23:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DuckDuckGo is best known as a private search engine, but the company also has a private web browser for mobile devices (with a desktop version on the way). However, the browser is currently in hot water, after a security researcher discovered an exception for Microsoft trackers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux 5.19 Finally Removes Obsolete x86 a.out Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-Drops-x86-a.out</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-Drops-x86-a.out"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T17:15:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Way back in 2019 the Linux kernel deprecated a.out support given that it was superseded by ELF, which itself has already been supported for over two decades going back to Linux 1.x kernels. With Linux 5.19, the obsolete 32-bit x86 a.out support is finally being removed for good from the kernel...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Proton: cos'è l'ecosistema che vuole tutelare la privacy degli utenti]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Proton-cos-e-l-ecosistema-che-vuole-tutelare-la-privacy-degli-utenti_24563</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Proton-cos-e-l-ecosistema-che-vuole-tutelare-la-privacy-degli-utenti_24563"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T17:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ProtonMail e ProtonVPN sono due servizi molto conosciuti: il primo è un servizio per lo scambio di email in forma cifrata che è stato fondato nel 2013 da alcuni ricercatori del CERN di Ginevra (Svizzera); il secondo è un servizio VPN che permette di stabilire un tunnel crittografato tra il dispositivo client dell'utente e un server remoto (i pacchetti dati vengono protetti e non possono essere monitorati, letti o modificati da parte di soggetti terzi). Come altri servizi VPN, anche ProtonVPN consente di superare censure, limitazioni geografiche, raggiungere siti Web e servizi diversamente non fruibili, proteggere i dati che si scambiano con i server remoti durante l'utilizzo di connessioni potenzialmente insicure (si pensi a reti WiFi pubbliche o aperte).Servizi quali ProtonMail e ProtonVPN sono erogati da un'azienda (Proton Technologies AG) con sede in Svizzera: essi si attengono alle normative del Paese elvetico e alla sua giurisdizione.Qualche tempo fa l'azienda fu costretta a comunicare l'indirizzo IP reale di un utente connesso con i suoi servizi tanto che quel comportamento destò un vespaio di polemiche e determinò l'arrivo del padre del World Wide Web Tim Berners-Lee come responsabile per gli aspetti legati alla privacy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Today Only: Huge Sale on Hard Drives and Memory Cards, Plus Much More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=807591</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/807591/today-only-huge-sale-on-hard-drives-and-memory-cards-plus-much-more/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T17:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Memorial Day is almost here, and in addition to a long relaxing weekend, there are plenty of special deals to be had. Today only, you can save up to 60% on hard drives and SD cards from some of the top names in the industry. Throughout this week, you can also claim special offers on Google Pixel phones, our favorite OLED TV of 2022, and plenty more. Read on for details!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zach Laidlaw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New ChromeLoader malware surge threatens browsers worldwide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-chromeloader-malware-surge-threatens-browsers-worldwide/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-chromeloader-malware-surge-threatens-browsers-worldwide/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ChromeLoader malware is seeing an uptick in detections this month, following a relatively stable operation volume since the start of the year, which means that the malvertiser is now becoming a widespread threat. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Turn Off Delivery Optimization on Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=793154</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/793154/turn-off-delivery-optimization-windows-11/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Delivery Optimization is a feature that enables users to download a Windows update from other devices on the same network. This peer-to-peer service sometimes reduces bandwidth issues during updates, but could also pose a problem if you have data caps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marshall Gunnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nothing Phone 1 Design Revealed as Release Details Leak]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119037/nothing-phone-1-design-revealed-as-release-details-leak/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119037/nothing-phone-1-design-revealed-as-release-details-leak/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T16:51:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nothing is a company founded by Carl Pei, one of the original co-founders of the OnePlus brand. For months, Nothing has teased its new phone, and now we’re finally getting more details about the Nothing Phone (1).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tails 5.0 Linux users warned against using it "for sensitive information"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/tails-50-linux-users-warned-against-using-it-for-sensitive-information/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/tails-50-linux-users-warned-against-using-it-for-sensitive-information/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T16:41:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tails developers have warned users to stop using the portable Debian-based Linux distro until the next release if they're entering or accessing sensitive information using the bundled Tor Browser application. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[python packaging without setup.py or a wheel?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uxlfrg/python_packaging_without_setuppy_or_a_wheel/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uxlfrg/python_packaging_without_setuppy_or_a_wheel/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T16:41:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am maintaining a particular AUR package that has just added a new dependency. This new dependency is a very simple python package containing only a single .py file, a tests.py, LICENSE, and README.md.
 I can see that the GitHub repo for the new dependency also contains some of the new standard python packaging: pyproject.toml and setup.cfg. The pytproject.toml specifies the build-backend = "setuptools.build_meta".
 However, this is the first python package I have attempted to package for the AUR which appears to be using setuptools but does not have a setup.py file. I attempted to use the "Standards based" approach on the current version of https://wiki.archlinux.org/title/Python_package_guidelines but no wheel is found in the packaging step:
 Traceback (most recent call last): File "/usr/lib/python3.10/runpy.py", line 196, in _run_module_as_main return _run_code(code, main_globals, None, File "/usr/lib/python3.10/runpy.py", line 86, in _run_code exec(code, run_globals) File "/usr/lib/python3.10/site-packages/installer/__main__.py", line 85, in <module> _main(sys.argv[1:], "python -m installer") File "/usr/lib/python3.10/site-packages/installer/__main__.py", line 73, in _main with WheelFile.open(args.wheel) as source: File "/usr/lib/python3.10/contextlib.py", line 135, in __enter__ return next(self.gen) File "/usr/lib/python3.10/site-packages/installer/sources.py", line 122, in open with zipfile.ZipFile(path) as f: File "/usr/lib/python3.10/zipfile.py", line 1249, in __init__ self.fp = io.open(file, filemode) FileNotFoundError: [Errno 2] No such file or directory: 'dist/*.whl' 
 The README.md of course, recommends simply pip install but this is not acceptable for a dependency of the primary AUR package which I maintian. How should I proceed? How do you package python scripts for the AUR appropriately without building a wheel as per the wiki or using a setup.py as I have always done previously?
    submitted by    /u/SutekhThrowingSuckIt  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Speed test, verificare la velocità della connessione in modo rapido]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Speed-test-verificare-la-velocita-della-connessione-in-modo-rapido_15693</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Speed-test-verificare-la-velocita-della-connessione-in-modo-rapido_15693"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T16:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Se il trasferimento dati da e verso la rete risulta lento, per farsi un'idea della velocità della connessione Internet è possibile utilizzare diversi strumenti.Gli speed test possono essere utilizzati per verificare le prestazioni di qualunque tipo di connessione: gli accessi a Internet da postazione fissa in tecnologia xDSL, su fibra ottica FTTH, FWA (Fixed Wireless Access), satellitare ma anche la banda disponibile su WiFi oppure utilizzando la connessione dati dell'operatore di telefonia mobile con tecnologie 4G o 5G.Di speed test ne esistono davvero tanti: di seguito vi presentiamo i migliori, utili per monitorare in tempo reale le prestazioni della connessione Internet sia in download che in upload.Uno speed test va tuttavia considerato come uno strumento utile a fotografare il comportamento della connessione nel momento esatto in cui lo si utilizza: esso non fornisce un giudizio sulla qualità della linea.Prima di effettuare il test della connessione è fondamentale tenere a mente alcuni aspetti fondamentali.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bloccare su WhatsApp numeri sconosciuti o contatti sgraditi]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2018/03/bloccare-numeri-sconosciuti-su-whatsapp.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2018/03/bloccare-numeri-sconosciuti-su-whatsapp.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T16:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WhatsApp permette di contattare solo le persone di cui abbiamo il numero di telefono e di poter essere contattati da chiunque abbia il nostro numero, senza bisogno di richieste di amicizia o simili come avviene invece con altre app come Skype o Facebook Messenger.

 Tutti coloro che installano l'applicazione sono iscritti a WhatsApp in modo automatico tramite il numero di telefono e possono...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The SteelSeries Arctis Nova Pro Headphones Promise Premium Everything]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119018/the-steelseries-arctis-nova-pro-headphones-promise-premium-everything/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119018/the-steelseries-arctis-nova-pro-headphones-promise-premium-everything/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T16:06:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SteelSeries just announced the two latest members of its Arctis headset line—the Arctis Nova Pro and the Arctics Nova Pro Wireless—and offers versions compatible with Xbox, PC and PlayStation for each. Both offer a veritable kitchen sink of premium features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzanne Humphries</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smartwatch vs. Fitness Tracker: What’s the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=802111</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/802111/smartwatch-vs.-fitness-tracker-whats-the-difference/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T16:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to wearable gadgets, there are two terms you hear a lot: “fitness tracker” and “smartwatch.” These two types of devices have a lot of similarities, but a few big differences. Which one is right for you?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[figuring out when a package was replaced?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uxkhm4/figuring_out_when_a_package_was_replaced/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uxkhm4/figuring_out_when_a_package_was_replaced/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T15:57:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You know how sometimes when you run an update and you are prompted to replace one package with a different package?
 Is there a means by which I can output a list with the history of every instance in which that has occurred and the packages involved?
    submitted by    /u/reenmini  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Mac App Is Great for People With Short Attention Spans]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=798968</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/798968/working-from-home-boost-your-productivity-with-setapp-for-mac/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T15:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Working from home has become wildly popular over the past few years, but it has also introduced us to challenges we hadn’t considered. Pets, projects around the house, random distractions on the internet — all serve to deter focus and hamper productivity. Can a suite of work-focused apps help you get back on track? We’ll discuss how to stay productive while working from home with Setapp, a popular subscription service with more than 200 incredible apps for Mac.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sponsored</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Darknet market Versus shuts down after hacker leaks security flaw]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/darknet-market-versus-shuts-down-after-hacker-leaks-security-flaw/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/darknet-market-versus-shuts-down-after-hacker-leaks-security-flaw/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T15:54:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[​The Versus Market, one of the most popular English-speaking criminal darknet markets, is shutting down after discovering a severe exploit that could have allowed access to its database and exposed the IP address of its servers. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The New Motorola Razr 3 Foldable Looks Better In Leaked Video]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119021/the-new-motorola-razr-3-foldable-looks-better-in-leaked-video/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119021/the-new-motorola-razr-3-foldable-looks-better-in-leaked-video/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T15:37:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Motorola’s upcoming Razr 3 foldable phone has been in the works since last year, and we got our first glance at it earlier this month. Now, a newly leaked video is giving us a better hands-on look at the vastly improved design.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IKEA's Upcoming Matter Hub Could Solve Its Smart Home Woes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119016/ikeas-upcoming-matter-hub-could-solve-its-smart-home-woes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119016/ikeas-upcoming-matter-hub-could-solve-its-smart-home-woes/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T15:35:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve ever struggled with IKEA’s smart home ecosystem, it seems that things are about to get better. IKEA just debuted the DIRIGERA, an upcoming smart home hub that uses Matter (plus a brand new app) to streamline customers’ smart home experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome 102: Lens per le immagini, percorsi di ricerca e gestione delle schede aperte]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Chrome-102-Lens-per-le-immagini-percorsi-di-ricerca-e-gestione-delle-schede-aperte_24562</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Chrome-102-Lens-per-le-immagini-percorsi-di-ricerca-e-gestione-delle-schede-aperte_24562"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T15:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google ha avviato la distribuzione di Chrome 102, la più recente versione stabile del suo browser Web che, innanzi tutto, risolve 32 vulnerabilità di cui una a elevata criticità. Per verificare la versione di Chrome in uso suggeriamo di digitare chrome://settings/help nella barra degli indirizzi e premere Invio: quest'operazione ha anche l'effetto di forzare l'aggiornamento di Chrome nel caso in cui si utilizzasse una precedente versione.Oltre alle tante novità principalmente rivolte agli sviluppatori, Chrome 102 integra qualche caratteristica 'inedita'. Alcune di esse avevano debuttato 'dietro le quinte' nelle precedenti versioni del browser ed erano attivabili usando Chrome flags.
Percorsi di ricerca
 Abbiamo visto cosa sono i Percorsi nella cronologia di navigazione di Chrome: si tratta di raccolte di pagine Web che si riferiscono a una o più sessioni di navigazione ma che riguardano esattamente lo stesso argomento.Con Chrome 102 i Percorsi di ricerca sono attivabili dalla barra degli indirizzi del browser che diventa ancora più intelligente.Provate a digitare uno o più termini riferiti alle attività svolte in precedenza sul Web: si supponga di aver cercato informazioni per una tematica lavorativa, per un viaggio che si sta pianificando, per l'elaborazione di un documento tecnico.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google vs. Bing vs. DuckDuckGo: Which Is Best?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=post-ideas&amp;p=82315</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/13784475/google-vs-bing-vs-duck-duck-go"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since most of us heavily rely on search engines, it can be frustrating if it does not provide the results we hope for. However, deciding on a search engine is a highly personal choice. As it stands today, Google is the most popular, Bing is playing catchup, and DuckDuckGo is trying a privacy-centric approach. So how do you know which one is right for you? Let’s compare Google, Bing and DuckDuckGo and see where each search giant succeeds and where they fall behind the competition.
   

Content

Search Results
Privacy
Unique Features
Homepage Design
Other Considerations
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Use Google Search Like a Power User
    
Search Results
    
Obviously, the most important aspect of any search engine is the accuracy of the results it provides based on the data you input. So, let’s see how each... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Megan Glosson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Steam quickly use up all VRAM when switching to TTY.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uxjn4m/steam_quickly_use_up_all_vram_when_switching_to/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uxjn4m/steam_quickly_use_up_all_vram_when_switching_to/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T15:17:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I had to run some CUDA stuffs so to get the best performance I often ran them in TTY. However, after a few seconds the programs started to complain about insufficient VRAM.
 Through nvtop I could see that, in TTY, VRAM was quickly being used up. But this didn't happen in normal DE (Plasma). There were only Xorg, plasmashell, and steam using the GPU. Weirdly, nvtop didn't show that steam was using more VRAM, only that the total memory usage getting fill up. Completely quit steam temporarily solved the issue. But it happened again after reopening steam.
 After one hour troubleshooting, I ended up delete ~/.local/share/steam and let it reinstall and that seemed to finally fix it. Don't exactly know what could have caused steam to behave like that.
 PS: Now I know that steam consistently uses about 100 MB of VRAM just sitting in the tray, I might have to reconsider letting it run in the background.
    submitted by    /u/BillTran163  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Microsoft Word Update Will Prevent Accidental Changes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=807502</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/807502/this-microsoft-word-update-will-prevent-accidental-changes/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T15:11:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Word already has view-only and review modes, for when you want to look at a document without making changes, but not everyone knows about those options. Microsoft is now testing a more visible switch for different modes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Ways to Use Named Ranges in Google Sheets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=802893</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/802893/ways-to-use-named-ranges-in-google-sheets/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T15:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to get more efficient when working with ranges in your Google Sheets? While it’s often a matter of preference, there are situations where named ranges can be beneficial and make certain tasks easier.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A quale età comprare lo smartphone ad un bambino?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/05/a-quale-eta-comprare-lo-smartphone-ad.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/05/a-quale-eta-comprare-lo-smartphone-ad.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T14:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tra i dilemmi che affliggono i genitori odierni troviamo anche la tecnologia: in una casa completamente tecnologica e in una società che di fatto è diventata totalmente dipendente dai telefoni e dai tablet, come possiamo tutelare i bambini più piccoli dal diventare a loro volta dipendenti della tecnologia? La severità iniziale è un bene o rischiamo di far diventare i figli delle persone arretrate...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anyone else notice a slight drop in quality with Arch Linux?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uxj3q7/anyone_else_notice_a_slight_drop_in_quality_with/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uxj3q7/anyone_else_notice_a_slight_drop_in_quality_with/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T14:51:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What's up fellow Archers. Just making a post to highlight a few things I've noticed with Arch Linux lately. None of them major of course. It's just minor annoyances that are building up.
  
 "why don't you just patch them yourself locally?"
 because not everyone has those abilities and it would be nice for everyone to have a nice, clean running Arch env.
 "Why don't you just downgrade those packages?"
 because that may break dependencies, etc
  
 1) This may speak to a couple people but the latest update to systemd has an annoying shutdown message and beep https://bbs.archlinux.org/viewtopic.php?id=276662
  
 2) kernel output regression every single time you start your computer: https://bugs.archlinux.org/task/69155 been waiting for this one for almost 2 months now to be fixed.
  
 3) Every single shutdown I get messages about unmounts failing https://bugs.archlinux.org/task/63697?project=1&order=votes&sort=desc&order2=dateopened&sort2=desc
    submitted by    /u/linux_masterrace  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gigabyte A5 K1, ACPI BIOS Error, Unable to install Arch linux & other distro]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uxj22i/gigabyte_a5_k1_acpi_bios_error_unable_to_install/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uxj22i/gigabyte_a5_k1_acpi_bios_error_unable_to_install/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T14:49:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, after some performance testing on windows i decided to setup my main OS - Arch linux, i downloaded latest iso, booted it and then during initial loading i got this error:
 [ 0.250531] ACPI BIOS Error (bug): Could not resolve symbol [\_SB.PCI0.LPC0.EC0], AE_NOT_FOUND (20211217/dswload2-162) [ 0.250551] ACPI Error: AE_NOT_FOUND, During name lookup/catalog (20211217/psobject-220) :: running early hook [udev] Starting version 250.5-1-arch :: running early hook [archiso_pxe_nbd] :: running hook [udev] :: Triggering uevents... :: running hook [memdisk] :: running hook [archiso] :: running hook [archiso_loop_mnt] :: running hook [archiso_pxe_common] :: running hook [archiso_pxe_nbd] :: running hook [archiso_pxe_http] :: running hook [archiso_pxe_nfs] 
 and then the boot process appears to be suspended and nothing else is loaded, I don't even have root access. I updated BIOS to the latest version atm. (FB10 (2022/05/12)), disabled secure boot, fast boot, but the problem still occurs... I also tested other distributions: Ubuntu 22.04 LTS, Manjaro 21.2.6, Debian 11 but the problem is still there, and laptop hangs in infinite loop on OS loading splash screen. Im basically unable to boot any linux distribution.. Is it even possible to fix this problem ?
    submitted by    /u/Mir_han  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Satechi USB4 Multiport Adapter with 8K HDMI Review: Ready for Anything]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118001/satechi-usb4-multiport-adapter-with-8k-hdmi-review-ready-for-anything/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118001/satechi-usb4-multiport-adapter-with-8k-hdmi-review-ready-for-anything/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T14:24:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern laptops continue to become thinner, lighter, and more portable than ever, but perhaps the only downside is that slimmer models tend to feature fewer ports overall. The Satechi USB-4 Multiport Adapter with 8K HDMI is a must-have tool for connecting essential tech to your new computer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arnold Carreiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save Big on SanDisk SSDs, HDDs, and More During This One-Day Sale]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119011/save-big-on-sandisk-ssds-hdds-and-more-during-this-one-day-sale/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119011/save-big-on-sandisk-ssds-hdds-and-more-during-this-one-day-sale/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T14:16:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Documents and photos that you leave on your computer aren’t sure enough. It’s time to back up those important files and save yourself a ton of heartbreak in the future. Luckily, Amazon is running a huge one-day sale on SSDs, HDDs, and other storage devices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OneNote: cos'è e come cambia l'applicazione per prendere appunti]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=OneNote-cos-e-e-come-cambia-l-applicazione-per-prendere-appunti_24561</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=OneNote-cos-e-e-come-cambia-l-applicazione-per-prendere-appunti_24561"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T14:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft aveva annunciato lo scorso anno l'intenzione di unire la 'versione moderna' della sua app OneNote per Windows 10 e 11 con la più tradizionale release Win32. Il progetto è stato parzialmente portato a termine con il nuovo OneNote che già unisce i due mondi e include alcune nuove caratteristiche, con altre funzioni che saranno via via introdotte nei mesi a seguire.Su Windows 10 e Windows 11 non si dovranno insomma più gestire due applicazioni OneNote separate perché tutto risulta ora condensato in un'unica app.L'app OneNote aggiornata ha un layout simile alla versione classica ma presenta un aspetto completamente rinnovato per adattarsi a Windows 11. C'è ancora l'interfaccia a schede nella parte superiore della finestra per passare da uno strumento all'altro ma per chi è abituato alla visualizzazione più semplice di OneNote per Windows 11 è disponibile un pulsante che permette di passare a una barra multifunzione semplificata.A parte gli aspetti estetici, che hanno comunque la loro valenza, il nuovo OneNote si mette in evidenza per il supporto e il riconoscimento della scrittura ('ink').]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unable to setup Hardware acceleration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uxi6h9/unable_to_setup_hardware_acceleration/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uxi6h9/unable_to_setup_hardware_acceleration/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T14:07:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm following the guide on Archwiki for hardware acceleration but cannot do it properly like in the 
 Here is the output when I verify the packages
 $ vainfo Floating point exception (core dumped) 
 ​
 $ vdpauinfo display: :0 screen: 0 Xlib: extension "NV-GLX" missing on display ":0". Xlib: extension "NV-GLX" missing on display ":0". Error creating VDPAU device: 1 
 I also edited the /etc/environment with following lines added:
 LIBVA_DRIVER_NAME=vdpau VDPAU_DRIVER=nvidia 
 The information of my system:
 - Hardware: GTX 1030
 - nvidia version 515 (lastest)
 - Wayland session
 Can anyone suggest me the work around to solve this?
 Thanks!
    submitted by    /u/nghiahust  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Usb stick doesn't get recognised after installing custom kernel (tkg-pds) .]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uxi5o5/usb_stick_doesnt_get_recognised_after_installing/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uxi5o5/usb_stick_doesnt_get_recognised_after_installing/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T14:06:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Usb stick doesn't get recognised after installing custom kernel (tkg-pds) .
 While USB does work on the default kernel ,fdisk -l on the custom kernel doesnt show anything besides the internal hard drives .
 ​
 modprobe: FATAL: Module usb-storage not found in directory /lib/modules/5.17.9-258-tkg-pds 
 Edit : SOLVED/it was due to an option being enabled in the customization file to use modeprobed db to clean the cfg from unneeded modules while not having build the database of loaded modules with "modprobed-db store" before compiling the kernel ... Or just disable that option altogether.
    submitted by    /u/freedifyy  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Budget Speakers of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=802939</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/802939/best-budget-speaker/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T14:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Speakers can get expensive quickly, but you don’t need to spend a lot of money to upgrade your sound. No matter what you’re listening to, these speakers bring the boom but don’t break the bank.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kris Wouk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is 100% Cybersecurity Readiness Possible? Medical Device Pros Weigh In]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/is-100-percent-cybersecurity-readiness-possible-medical-device-pros-weigh-in/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/is-100-percent-cybersecurity-readiness-possible-medical-device-pros-weigh-in/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T14:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As medical devices become more connected and reliant on software, their codebase grows both in size and complexity, and they are increasingly reliant on third-party and open source software components.  Learn more from 150 senior decision makers who oversee product security or cybersecurity compliance in the medical device industry, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sponsored by Cybellum</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can't install arch because TL-WN722N isn't found in iwctl neither in ip l]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uxhujw/cant_install_arch_because_tlwn722n_isnt_found_in/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uxhujw/cant_install_arch_because_tlwn722n_isnt_found_in/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T13:51:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The driver is installed on the linux kernel as it works in debian and ubuntu from the beggining, but not here.
 I'm kind of nood and found this old thread with the same issue but I don't know what to do. 
 Using my phone as a Wifi receiver doesn't get detected, I've also tried it.
 Edit: Just wanted to say that V1del solved it in the comments, amazing man.
    submitted by    /u/carlosserretq  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The FDA Says No to This Avocado Storage Hack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lifesavvy.com/130538/the-fda-says-no-to-this-avocado-storage-hack/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lifesavvy.com/130538/the-fda-says-no-to-this-avocado-storage-hack/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone loves a good hack—after all, they can make life easier. One that recently went viral, though, has gotten the no-go from the Food and Drug Administration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shea Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacker says hijacking libraries, stealing AWS keys was ethical research]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hacker-says-hijacking-libraries-stealing-aws-keys-was-ethical-research/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hacker-says-hijacking-libraries-stealing-aws-keys-was-ethical-research/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T13:42:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The hacker of 'ctx' and 'PHPass' libraries has now broken silence and explained the reasons behind this hijack to BleepingComputer. According to the hacker, this was a bug bounty exercise and no malicious activity was intended. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ax Sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DuckDuckGo Privacy Browser app does not block Microsoft trackers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178771</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/05/25/duckduckgo-privacy-browser-app-does-not-block-microsoft-trackers/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T13:40:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DuckDuckGo Privacy Browser isn't totally private, a security researcher has revealed. The privacy-focused search engine's app, for iOS and Android, is not blocking trackers from Microsoft. The news came to light when […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post DuckDuckGo Privacy Browser app does not block Microsoft trackers appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Installing ibus removes visual feedback from ctrl-shift-U]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uxhh2u/installing_ibus_removes_visual_feedback_from/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uxhh2u/installing_ibus_removes_visual_feedback_from/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T13:32:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Normally, pressing ctrl-shift-U in most gtk3 programs shows an underlined u and allows typing some hex digits. Installing the ibus package, even without setting any envvars, removes this visual feedback (functinally c-s-u still works, but the underlined u and hex digits do not appear). Deleting /usr/lib/gtk-3.0/3.0.0/immodules/im-ibus.so restores that functionality to normal, but obviously has some other drawbacks.
 How do I avoid this? I like that underlined u.
 (Ibus itself also doesn't appear to work even with the envvars in place, but that's a separate issue.)
    submitted by    /u/caagr98  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yeedi Vac Review: A Budget-Friendly Modular Robovac]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lifesavvy.com/130019/yeedi-vac-review/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lifesavvy.com/130019/yeedi-vac-review/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T13:30:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yeedi, a sister company to the more widely known Ecovacs, is a robot vacuum company that appears to be targeting a specific market. If you’re in the market for a robot vacuum with some premium features but a solidly budget price point, the basic Yeedi Vac is worth a look.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Fitzpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux 5.19 Heavy On Intel Power Management & Thermal Improvements]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-PM-ACPI-Thermal</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-PM-ACPI-Thermal"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The power management, ACPI, and thermal control updates are ready for Linux 5.19. This cycle there is a lot of PM/thermal work as usual on the Arm side while Intel also continues with a lot of changes from new hardware support to improving overheat handling of laptops for S0ix handling...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interpol arrests alleged leader of the SilverTerrier BEC gang]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/interpol-arrests-alleged-leader-of-the-silverterrier-bec-gang/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/interpol-arrests-alleged-leader-of-the-silverterrier-bec-gang/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T13:04:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a year-long investigation that involved Interpol and several cybersecurity companies, the Nigeria Police Force has arrested an individual believed to be in the top ranks of a prominent business email compromise (BEC) group known as SilverTerrier or TMT. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Ilascu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to list every package that provides virtual package X?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uxgwk5/how_to_list_every_package_that_provides_virtual/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uxgwk5/how_to_list_every_package_that_provides_virtual/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T13:02:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So, sometimes, I have this problem where
  
I install a package 'A' which requires a virtual package 'X' provided by packages "X" (real package with no `provides` array defined), "Y", and "Z".
 
pacman gives me a choice among all three of them
 
I choose "Z"
 
 Note that I also use the "X" provider directly and not just as a dependency for "A"
  
After a few days I realize that "Z" does not work for my use-case
  
Now
 To install an alternative to "Z", I need to uninstall both "A" AND "Z" since "A" depends on an "X" provider and I do not know how to find the names of the packages alternative to "X" i.e. the packages that provide "X". This could be very dangerous if the reverse dependency tree is very long.
 Can anyone help me with this?
 No urgency, btw.
    submitted by    /u/MazharHussainKhan  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shooting in VR Is the Real Next Generation Experience]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=802156</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/802156/shooting-in-vr-is-the-real-next-generation-experience/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T13:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The PlayStation 5 and Xbox Series X represent the next generation (well, the current generation if we’re being pedantic), but first-person shooters offer pretty much the same experience as they always have. In VR, things couldn’t be more different.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sydney Butler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here's How You Can Free Up More Space in Google Drive]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117723/heres-how-you-can-free-up-more-space-in-google-drive/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117723/heres-how-you-can-free-up-more-space-in-google-drive/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T13:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It happens to the best of us—you create a few word documents and upload some high-quality images from your family vacation, and voila! Google Drive is screaming at you about how there’s no space left. Fortunately, it’s easy to see what’s taking up the most space and how to free up more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzanne Humphries</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bandi Italia a 1 Giga: ecco le regioni che saranno coperte in fibra da FiberCop e Open Fiber]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Bandi-Italia-a-1-Giga-ecco-le-regioni-che-saranno-coperte-in-fibra-da-FiberCop-e-Open-Fiber_24559</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Bandi-Italia-a-1-Giga-ecco-le-regioni-che-saranno-coperte-in-fibra-da-FiberCop-e-Open-Fiber_24559"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T12:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Le due aziende che in Italia si occupano della realizzazione di reti per le telecomunicazioni con fornitura del servizio all'ingrosso (wholesale) sono FiberCop e Open Fiber.Abbiamo visto cos'è FiberCop e cosa fa e come Open Fiber porta la fibra ottica nelle case e negli uffici.In entrambi i casi le due aziende, la prima partecipata TIM (58%), Fastweb (4,5%) e dal fondo statunitense KKR (37,5%), la seconda da Cassa Depositi e Prestiti (60%) e Fibre Networks Holdings-Gruppo Macquarie (40%), non forniscono il servizio di connettività a banda ultralarga agli utenti finali ma permettono alle società partner (altri provider di telecomunicazioni) l'utilizzo della rete fino al router dell'abbonato.Il piano Italia a 1 Giga prevede che entro fine 2026 vengano raggiunti con una connessione ultrabroadband ad almeno 1 Gbps in download tutti i numeri civici d'Italia che insistono su aree grigie e nere e dove oggi non si superano i 300 Mbps in download.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come sostituire la linea telefonica col VoIP e quanto conviene]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2014/12/meglio-una-linea-telefonica-fissa-o-voip.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2014/12/meglio-una-linea-telefonica-fissa-o-voip.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T12:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Molti ormai utilizzano solo lo smartphone per contattare le persone e molti ormai sono abituati fare le chiamate telefoniche solo dai telefoni cellulari. Anche se chiamare con il telefono fisso può sembrare una cosa "da vecchi", possiamo aggiornare la tecnologia di comunicazione tramite rete fissa utilizzando il VoIP, ossia facendo passare le chiamate direttamente su Internet senza adoperare la...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[bootctl complaining about $KERNEL_INSTALL_LAYOUT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uxfu78/bootctl_complaining_about_kernel_install_layout/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uxfu78/bootctl_complaining_about_kernel_install_layout/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T12:03:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I run bootctl update it says:  Read $KERNEL\_INSTALL\_LAYOUT from /etc/machine-info. Please move it to the layout= setting of /etc/kernel/install.conf.  It stills updates the efi files and my system boots fine, can the message be safely ignored?
    submitted by    /u/Saikat0511  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do I Need a New USB Cable for Fast Charging?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=795359</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/795359/do-i-need-a-new-usb-cable-for-fast-charging/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T12:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fast charging minimizes downtime away from your phone or tablet, but it can be tricky with so many various standards. So if you’ve got a new phone or charger, do you need a new cable too? Well, it depends.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kris Wouk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SpiceJet airline passengers stranded after ransomware attack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/spicejet-airline-passengers-stranded-after-ransomware-attack/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/spicejet-airline-passengers-stranded-after-ransomware-attack/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T11:43:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Indian low-cost airline SpiceJet has informed its customers of an attempted ransomware attack that has impacted some of its systems and caused delays on flight departures today. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BPFDoor malware uses Solaris vulnerability to get root privileges]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/bpfdoor-malware-uses-solaris-vulnerability-to-get-root-privileges/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/bpfdoor-malware-uses-solaris-vulnerability-to-get-root-privileges/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T11:21:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New research into the inner workings of the stealthy BPFdoor malware for Linux and Solaris reveals that the threat actor behind it leveraged an old vulnerability to achieve persistence on targeted systems. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Ilascu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Archinstall : BTRFS not working on Virt-Manager]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uxetf4/archinstall_btrfs_not_working_on_virtmanager/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uxetf4/archinstall_btrfs_not_working_on_virtmanager/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T11:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm testing out the latest version of archinstall (version 2.4.3rc1) by git cloning the archinstall repo while in the live environment and have noticed that it doesn't seem to like BTRFS. EXT4 works as expected. 
 It gets to mounting the partitions, hits some kind of bug, and spits out a bunch of text that ends with "TypeError: cannot pickle 'generator' object"
 I've only been testing through Virt-Manager so I dont know if 2.4.3rc1 acts any differently on bare metal. 
 Anyone encounter this? Any guidance is appreciated!
    submitted by    /u/kantoking0206  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Should You Buy a Drone?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=796188</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/796188/should-i-buy-a-drone/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Drones are more accessible than ever before and now come in a range of sizes and price points. But before you reach for your wallet, there are a few things you might want to mull over.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TUXEDO Aura 15 Gen2 - AMD Ryzen 5000 Series Powered, Linux Laptop]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31147</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31147"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bavarian PC vendor TUXEDO Computers that specializes in various Linux pre-loaded notebooks and desktop computers recently launched their Aura 15 Gen2 laptop focused on being an "affordable business allrounder" and powered by AMD Ryzen 5000 series processors with integrated Vega graphics to make for a nice open-source driver experience. TUXEDO sent over the Aura 15 Gen2 for a round of testing and here's a look at this Ubuntu Linux laptop's performance and capabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GCC 13 Compiler Finally Adds Support For AMD GFX90A "Aldebaran"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=GCC-13-AMD-GFX90A-Aldebaran</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=GCC-13-AMD-GFX90A-Aldebaran"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T10:28:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was over a year ago that AMD initially added the "GFX90A" target to their LLVM AMDGPU compiler back-end while now this week added to the GNU Compiler Collection for the GCC 13 release not due out until next year is its GFX90A support for the GNU toolchain...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DuckDuckGo Not Totally Private: It Allows Microsoft Trackers]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=492504</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15329046/duckduckgo-allows-microsoft-trackers"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T10:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re concerned about Internet privacy and started using the DuckDuckGo browser or search engine with no concerns that your data wasn’t private, you’ll want to read on. While many people eschewed Google and Microsoft, opting for the privacy provided by DuckDuckGo, they’re not really in the clear. DuckDuckGo gets its search results from Microsoft’s Bing search engine, and it’s now come to light that DuckDuckGo doesn’t block Microsoft’s trackers.
   
Also read:12 Things that Bing Does Better than Google
    
DuckDuckGo’s Agreement with Microsoft
    
In truth, DuckDuckGo gets most of its results from Bing, though all results are from other search engines. It has gained fans with its claim that it strips trackers from the results before it displays them.
    
However, if you click a Microsoft ad, your IP address is sent to Microsoft. Some users already know that, and DuckDuckGo did not try to hide it. What’s at question, though, is how much of... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly Half A Million Lines Of New Graphics Driver Code Sent In For Linux 5.19]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-DRM-Driver-Updates</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-DRM-Driver-Updates"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T10:02:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Airlie this morning sent in the Direct Rendering Manager (DRM) subsystem updates for the Linux 5.19 merge window. Most notable with the DRM display/graphics driver updates for this next kernel version is a lot of work on Intel Arc Graphics DG2/Alchemist in getting that support ready plus initial Raptor Lake enablement. as well as AMD preparing for next-generation CDNA Instinct products and RDNA3 Radeon RX 7000 series graphics cards...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stratis 3.1 Released For Red Hat's Linux Storage Management Solution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Stratis-3.1-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Stratis-3.1-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T09:20:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's been five years already since Red Hat started Stratis as a configuration daemon built atop LVM and XFS in aiming to provide advanced storage functionality in user-space akin to what is offered by the advanced Btrfs and ZFS file-systems...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[okular annnotation font family can not show correctly?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uxdb0v/okular_annnotation_font_family_can_not_show/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uxdb0v/okular_annnotation_font_family_can_not_show/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T09:09:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I use okular to read and edit pdf, when I use typewriter or inlinenote to create a n annotation and then choose a chinese font family for it, it show correctly. But when I close and repoen this pdf file, I find annotation font family become noto sans and the keyboard input becomes slow, does someone know why?
    submitted by    /u/ReasonableAd362  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ARMv9 Scalable Matrix Extension Support Lands In Linux 5.19]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-AArch64</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-AArch64"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T08:40:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 64-bit Arm (AArch64) architecture changes have been merged into the in-development Linux 5.19 kernel...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux's RNG Code Continues Modernization Effort With v5.19]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-RNG</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-RNG"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T08:35:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security researcher Jason Donenfeld known as the founder of the WireGuard project has recently been focused on modernizing the Linux kernel's random number generator (RNG/random) code. With the Linux 5.19 kernel there is yet more work landing...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Chrome 102 update patches 32 security issues (one critical)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178768</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/05/25/google-chrome-102-update-patches-32-security-issues-one-critical/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T08:35:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google published updates for the company's Chrome web browser on May 24, 2022. The desktop version updates address security issues in the web browser. The Chrome team is delighted to announce the […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Google Chrome 102 update patches 32 security issues (one critical) appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creare siti Web e applicazioni in modo rapido con Power Pages e Power Apps Express Design]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Creare-siti-Web-e-applicazioni-in-modo-rapido-con-Power-Pages-e-Power-Apps-Express-Design_24558</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Creare-siti-Web-e-applicazioni-in-modo-rapido-con-Power-Pages-e-Power-Apps-Express-Design_24558"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T07:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft aggiorna Power Platform, la piattaforma che consente di sviluppare progetti e app senza richiedere competenze di programmazione avanzate.Ad arricchire la famiglia quest'anno è stato aggiunto Power Pages, un generatore di siti Web che permette di creare pagine moderne e accattivanti con un limitatissimo impegno in termini di coding.Gli utenti possono iniziare a progettare un sito Web da zero aggiungendo testo, video, immagini, moduli e così via oppure utilizzare uno dei modelli offerti da Microsoft.Per venire incontro agli utenti più evoluti, tuttavia, Power Pages si integra anche con Visual Studio Code, GitHub ed Azure DevOps: in un altro articolo abbiamo parlato della filosofia DevOps per lo sviluppo software.

L'altra novità che Microsoft ha appena presentato si chiama Power Apps Express Design: si tratta di uno strumento che trasforma un'immagine, il contenuto di un file PDF o anche un disegno in un'applicazione vera e propria.È un approccio che permette di passare facilmente dalla fase di progettazione alla creazione di un'app funzionante con i suoi controlli e le funzionalità per la gestione dei dati inseriti dall'utente.Con Power Virtual Agents 2.0 realizzare un bot diventa ancora più semplice e immediato grazie alla possibilità di sfruttare le funzionalità avanzate di Azure Bot Framework Composer.L'area di progettazione utilizzata da Power Virtual Agents include adesso caratteristiche completamente nuove come la possibilità di passare dalla visualizzazione grafica a quella del codice oltre al supporto per i contenuti multimediali: in questo modo i bot possono inviare immagini, video e altro ancora.Da questa pagina è possibile registrarsi per accedere in anteprima al nuovo Power Virtual Agents.

Infine, un'altra novità importante riguarda Power BI: Datamart semplifica la creazione di set di dati utilizzando origini diverse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[display the layout name in terminal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uxc9qm/display_the_layout_name_in_terminal/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uxc9qm/display_the_layout_name_in_terminal/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T07:47:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[i use kitty and I use it function to have multiple terminals in single window. I am currently having 4 layout set grid,tall,fat and stack. I want to do such that name of layout,first letter of layout or its symbol is in the corners of terminal is it possible if yes the how.
    submitted by    /u/h4636oh  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recuperare messaggi cancellati di WhatsApp con UltData]]></title>
        <id>3575|20220525093300</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/recupero-dati-819/recuperare-messaggi-cancellati-whatsapp-ultdata-3575"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T07:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hai premuto per sbaglio il bottone per il ripristino alle impostazioni iniziali? Hai cancellato alcuni file importanti per sbaglio? Se la risposta è sì, la prima cosa che dovresti fare è cercare un metodo per recuperarli. La buona notizia, infatti, è che si possono recuperare i file cancellati.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is a MUX Switch and Why Should Your Next Gaming Laptop Have One?]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=485339</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15328450/what-is-mux-switch"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T05:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern gaming laptops are so good that eking every last drop of performance out of the hardware isn’t always necessary. Even so, gamers can take things even further with the MUX switch. This is now a fairly common piece of tech that could easily boost your gaming laptop’s performance by 10-15% in most cases. Stay tuned to find out how it works and why your next gaming laptop should have one. 
   

Content

Graphics Processing in Gaming Laptops
What Is a MUX Switch?
Is the MUX Switch Better than Switchable Graphics?
Are There Disadvantages to a MUX Switch?
Who Should Buy a Laptop With a MUX Switch?
What Games Benefit the Most From a MUX Switch? 
How Do I Check If My Laptop has a MUX Switch?
Laptops With the MUX Switch 
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:Is AMD Ryzen... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julian van der Merwe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Version control for system-wide config/dotfiles - best practices?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ux9kr3/version_control_for_systemwide_configdotfiles/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ux9kr3/version_control_for_systemwide_configdotfiles/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T04:41:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, I'm new to Arch, and this is my first post here.
 For context, I'm setting up a personal machine mainly for coding/development work.
 In my research on dotfile version control, all of the resources I've found discuss the matter for user-specific configurations. For example:
  
The first sentence of the Arch wiki article on dotfiles states "User-specific application configuration is traditionally stored in so called dotfiles" (Source)
 In the Hacker News article on using a git bare repo, it uses --work-tree=$HOME when setting up the repo, so I don't think it would track any system-wide configs i.e. in the /etc folder. (Source)
  
In regards to system-wide configs, the author of yadm mentioned:
  
This isn’t a use I would particularly endorse, as there are generally other configuration management tools for system level configurations; Ansible, Puppet, etc. (Source)
  
However, it seems like Ansible and Puppet are tools more geared towards servers, rather than PCs? (Correct me if I'm wrong here please.)
 If not using Ansible or Puppet, are there any other best practices for version controlling system-wide configs for PCs?
 I'd like to use the git bare method, so maybe I just set --work-tree=/, then add the /etc/ config files to the git repo as needed?
 Or, put the system-wide config files in my $HOME directory, then symlink them to /etc/?
 For context, I'm trying to set up an "override" sudoer file in /etc/sudoers.d/
 EDIT: Added a source link for the HN article (forgot to add it on first draft)
    submitted by    /u/moonlighter69  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vivaldi Snapshot gets a new way to customize the toolbar; will soon let you block autoplay videos]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178743</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/05/25/how-to-customize-the-toolbar-in-vivaldi-browser/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T04:40:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vivaldi latest Snapshot channel will soon add a much-needed feature to the browser, blocking autoplay videos. It's about time, other browsers have had this option for a long time. This feature was […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Vivaldi Snapshot gets a new way to customize the toolbar; will soon let you block autoplay videos appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DoNotSpy11 for Windows 11 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178762</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/05/25/donotspy11-for-windows-11-is-now-available/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T04:38:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The developer of the popular privacy tool DoNotSpy10 released DoNotSpy11 for Windows 11 on May 24, 2022. The tools give users control over more than 140 privacy related features on Windows devices. […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post DoNotSpy11 for Windows 11 is now available appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[difficulties with package install workflow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ux5wm6/difficulties_with_package_install_workflow/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ux5wm6/difficulties_with_package_install_workflow/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T01:11:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fairly recently switched from ubuntu-based distros to arch-based and a main reason was the package management. Now that I am here I am having a bit of issues with the workflow. Is there any good information about efficient ways to search for and install packages?
 Either the terminal or a GUI works fine if I want to install a single, specific package. Otherwise I find it pretty frustrating and slow. 
 I have repeatedly read advice that it's better to use the terminal but how do you do this without endless copy and pasting? With a GUI you can click click click to select what is desired. In the terminal it is very cumbersome. It's hard to read a list of dozens of results on the terminal. 
 However both pamac-manager and especially octopi GUI package managers have a big problem which is that if you select multiple packages for install and there is a problem with any of them, the whole job fails. It's hard to figure out where the problem is. 
 Also would like to learn about the different variations of the same package that are usually available and why I would choose one or the other. Is there a way to specify a preference? I have found that accidentally mixing them causes dependency issues. 
 I would appreciate any advice or links to reading on the subject. The documentation for the package manager and related tools themselves do not seem really to contain this kind of information and not sure how or where to look.
    submitted by    /u/sprayfoamparty  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stuck on loading initial ramdisk]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ux5q5i/stuck_on_loading_initial_ramdisk/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ux5q5i/stuck_on_loading_initial_ramdisk/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T01:01:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi today I was creating a dual boot for my pc and in the process accidentally deleted my grub boot loader 
 I have followed multiple tutorials on reinstalling the boot loader like the one below:
 example tutorial
 However no matter what I pick to boot for my computer hangs on loading initial ramdisk. 
 I have tried to remove quiet and increase the log level to 7 but both reveal nothing new… 
 Any help with this is greatly appreciated
    submitted by    /u/Snakeyes22  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 WhatsApp Alternatives That Respect Your Privacy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=post-ideas&amp;p=162461</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/4349013/alternatives-to-whatsapp"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When social media giant Facebook (now Meta) purchased everyone’s favorite mobile messaging app WhatsApp, users were promised their data would be private and that they wouldn’t be subject to the shady things that Mark Zuckerberg and crew are known for. As time has gone on, more and more privacy has been taken away from Whatsapp users in the name of “analytical data.” 
    
Gone are the days when you could trust this app to be totally private and not expect to get data mined for valuable information – information that could easily be sold to advertisers. Here we show you the best alternatives to WhatsApp that actually respect your privacy.
   

Content

1. Element
2. Wire
3. Telegram
4. Signal
5. Wickr Me
7. Conversations
8. Threema
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Send Disappearing Messages in Popular Chat Apps
   ... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexandra Arici</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Running Arch Linux on an Asus Chromebook (C202SA-YS02-GR TERRA)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ux3s0o/running_arch_linux_on_an_asus_chromebook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ux3s0o/running_arch_linux_on_an_asus_chromebook/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T23:16:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Super proud of it too. -` .o+` hiddenusername@cracktop `ooo/ -------------- `+oooo: OS: Arch Linux x86_64 `+oooooo: Host: Terra 1.0 -+oooooo+: Kernel: 5.17.9-arch1-1 `/:-:++oooo+: Uptime: 8 mins `/++++/+++++++: Packages: 762 (pacman) `/++++++++++++++: Shell: bash 5.1.16 `/+++ooooooooooooo/` Resolution: 1366x768 ./ooosssso++osssssso+` DE: Cinnamon 5.2.7 .oossssso-````/ossssss+` WM: Mutter (Muffin) -osssssso. :ssssssso. WM Theme: Adapta-Nokto (Adapta-Nokto) :osssssss/ osssso+++. Theme: Adwaita-dark [GTK2/3] /ossssssss/ +ssssooo/- Icons: Adwaita [GTK2/3] `/ossssso+/:- -:/+osssso+- Terminal: guake `+sso+:-` `.-/+oso: CPU: Intel Celeron N3060 (2) @ 2.480GHz `++:. `-/+/ GPU: Intel Atom/Celeron/Pentium Processor x5-E8000/J3xxx/N3xxx .` `/ Memory: 1948MiB / 3870MiB 
    submitted by    /u/SureHeIs  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 KB5014019 update fixes app crashes, slow copying]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-kb5014019-update-fixes-app-crashes-slow-copying/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-kb5014019-update-fixes-app-crashes-slow-copying/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T22:42:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has released optional cumulative update previews for Windows 11, Windows 10 version 1809, and Windows Server 2022, with fixes for Direct3D issues impacting client and server systems. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Btrfs Gets Some Buttery Good Improvements With Linux 5.19]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Btrfs-Linux-5.19-Changes</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Btrfs-Linux-5.19-Changes"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T22:41:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Sterba of SUSE has submitted the ~4k lines of code worth of feature changes for the Btrfs file-system driver in the Linux 5.19 kernel...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DuckDuckGo browser allows Microsoft trackers due to search agreement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/duckduckgo-browser-allows-microsoft-trackers-due-to-search-agreement/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/duckduckgo-browser-allows-microsoft-trackers-due-to-search-agreement/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T22:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The privacy-focused DuckDuckGo browser purposely allows Microsoft trackers on third-party sites due to an agreement in their syndicated search content contract between the two companies. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come risolvere l’errore FortiGate does not support dual stack (-5100) in FortiClient VPN]]></title>
        <id>3584|20220525000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/vpn-2942/come-risolvere-lerrore-fortigate-does-not-support-dual-stack-5100-forticlient-vpn-3584"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[L’utilizzo di un client VPN permette agli utenti che si trovano a lavorare da casa di potersi collegare agli applicativi aziendali tramite una connessione più protetta e sicura. FortiClient VPN è uno di questi programmi utilizzati dal cliente che seguo per lavoro, solo che, ogni tanto, si blocca durante il caricamento e presenta l’errore FortiGate does not support dual stack (-5100)
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla fixes Firefox, Thunderbird zero-days exploited at Pwn2Own]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/mozilla-fixes-firefox-thunderbird-zero-days-exploited-at-pwn2own/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/mozilla-fixes-firefox-thunderbird-zero-days-exploited-at-pwn2own/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T21:31:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla has released security updates for multiple products to address zero-day vulnerabilities exploited during the Pwn2Own Vancouver 2022 hacking contest. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PGP Encryption: How It Works and How You Can Get Started]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=253958</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/8942938/pgp-encryption-how-it-works"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t let the name “Pretty Good Privacy” mislead you. PGP encryption is the gold standard for encrypted communication and has been used by everyone from nuclear activists to criminals since its invention in 1991. While the execution is complex, the concept is simple: you can encrypt text, making it unreadable to anyone who doesn’t have the key to decode it.
   

Content

How Does PGP Encryption Work?
What Can I Use PGP Encryption For?
How Do I Get Started?
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:Why Encryption Is Not Working on Windows 11 Home, and How to Fix It
    
How Does PGP Encryption Work?
    
Imagine you want to send someone a letter but don’t want anyone except the recipient to be able to read it. The best way to... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Crystal Crowder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make Windows 10’s Taskbar Clock Display Seconds]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=325096</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/325096/how-to-make-windows-10s-taskbar-clock-display-seconds/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 10’s taskbar clock can display the precise time down to the second. This feature requires a registry hack to enable, and only works on Windows 10. Windows 7 users will instead need a third-party utility like T-Clock Redux to do this instead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch installation question]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ux0x9f/arch_installation_question/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ux0x9f/arch_installation_question/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T20:59:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello guys. I am new here :D So I am trying to install arch on my laptop and everything is more or less straightforward except disk partition part, because I have two partitions on my nwme drive. One is being used by windows 11 another is for linux. So I have used ubuntu/ mint before, and I had really no problem installing them, but arc is fucking with my newb brain. Anyway first I have tried to do old fashioned comand line install and I have made partitions( boot/swap/file system) on /dev/nvme0n1p5(p1/p2/p3)but when I wanted to format them on the next step with the command, it would come back as partition is not existing. Ok, so then I used script to install, which also does not show partitions i created before. It shows there is free space but in selection it shows nothing. I booted back to windows just to format that unpartitioned space to exfat so I know which partition i need to work with, but this is where I left confused. Do i need to delete this partition? Should i split it in 3 partitions again for boot, swap and file system for arch or should i create just one and script will do the rest? I really dont want to delete all my partitions accidentally so I am asking for little help. Thanks 🙏
    submitted by    /u/Royal_Mongoose2907  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft’s New OneNote for Windows Looks Great]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=807366</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/807366/microsofts-new-onenote-for-windows-looks-great/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T20:53:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft confirmed last year that it was merging the modern (“OneNote for Windows 10”) and classic (Win32) OneNote applications on Windows into one combined application, and now the company has detailed its recent and upcoming changes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to check if any package on my system depends on a certain package]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uwzyma/how_to_check_if_any_package_on_my_system_depends/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uwzyma/how_to_check_if_any_package_on_my_system_depends/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T20:17:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everytime I update my system it takes some extra time only for pywal. It asks me if want to clean build, show diffs and then takes a few seconds. I want to get rid of it but I'm not sure if anything depends on that package. Can anyone help me out here? Thanks!
    submitted by    /u/Lazy-Substance-5161  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up Multiple User Profiles on Android]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=333484</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/333484/how-to-set-up-multiple-user-profiles-on-android/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you share an Android device with other people, it can be tough to keep your account separate from theirs. Fortunately, Android supports multiple user profiles, allowing users to share devices without fear of encroaching on each other.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anyone use Arch as a server OS?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uwzj7m/anyone_use_arch_as_a_server_os/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uwzj7m/anyone_use_arch_as_a_server_os/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T19:58:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Title pretty much says it all. I was curious what people's experience with Arch as a server OS has been and what's it running? 
 I've been thinking of installing something like a LAMP stack on an Arch server and fixing it when it (inevitably?) breaks to hone my Linux admin skills.
    submitted by    /u/DurinsBane19  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shutdown message and beep after upgrading to systemd-251]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uwzhui/shutdown_message_and_beep_after_upgrading_to/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uwzhui/shutdown_message_and_beep_after_upgrading_to/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T19:56:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Does anyone have this issue where your device will beep and display a shutdown message when you shutdown or reboot or even hibernate? Downgrading to systemd-250 made the issue stop if someone has a fix would be appreciated.
 EDIT: I've look at the arch forum people there are having similar issues
 https://bbs.archlinux.org/viewtopic.php?id=276662
 https://bbs.archlinux.org/viewtopic.php?id=276631
 Edit again: I temporary blacklisted the pcspkr module so the beeping goes away till a solution is found 
    submitted by    /u/WinterSniper_0  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Copies the App Store’s Worst Feature for Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=807339</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/807339/microsoft-copies-the-app-stores-worst-feature-for-windows/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T19:38:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The app store on Windows, known as the Microsoft Store, received a much-needed overhaul just in time for Windows 11. Soon, it will become even more like the app stores on iPhone and Android — to a fault.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are EVs a Danger in Traffic Jams?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118940/are-evs-a-danger-in-traffic-jams/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118940/are-evs-a-danger-in-traffic-jams/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T19:35:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every few months we see the same story floating around on social media that electric cars are more likely to die and get stuck during a traffic jam. Suggesting they are dangerous, have no heaters, or will run out of battery in around three hours. So, are EVs a danger in traffic jams? Absolutely not.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers target Russian govt with fake Windows updates pushing RATs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-target-russian-govt-with-fake-windows-updates-pushing-rats/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-target-russian-govt-with-fake-windows-updates-pushing-rats/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T19:27:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers are targeting Russian government agencies with phishing emails that pretend to be Windows security updates and other lures to install remote access malware. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BIOS brick after using sbctl]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uwytxm/bios_brick_after_using_sbctl/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uwytxm/bios_brick_after_using_sbctl/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T19:26:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today I tried to setup secure boot, I used sbctl exactly as per the GitHub instructions:
  
sbctl create-keys
 sbctl enroll-keys
  
Rebooted.
 Now the computer is bricked, I can't do anything there because the UEFI screen simply doesn't appear. My BIOS is a Gigabyte B550 which has Q-Flash Plus but it doesn't seem to work as well... Any ideas?
 To be honest, the documentation of the tool should warn you that even the two first steps can brick your BIOS.
    submitted by    /u/edu4rdshl  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get an Amazon Echo Auto with Alexa for Under $20]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=352412</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/14663996/deal-amazon-echo-auto-with-alexa"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’re probably looking at a very busy summer ahead. Wouldn’t it be helpful to have a voice assistant in your car to help with appointments, shopping lists, and directions? You can get an Amazon Echo Auto with Alexa for under $20. You have to admit that’s a deal that’s hard to pass up.
    
The small device connects to the Alexa app on your phone using your car’s speakers via auxiliary input or a Bluetooth connection with your phone. It connects to your car via a vent mount. Amazon created it specifically to add convenience to your car trips, employing eight microphones and far-field technology to allow it to hear you over the traffic, your music, air conditioning, etc.
    

    
Your boredom with the same local radio stations ends here. You can control the Amazon Echo Auto through the Alexa app on your phone and ask it to stream Amazon Music, Apple Music, Spotify, SiriusXM, Audible, and radio stations via TuneIn and iHeartRadio. Catch up on your favorite podcasts and be fully entertained.
 ... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Chrome 102 Released With Capture Handle, File Handling For Given MIME Types]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Google-Chrome-102</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Google-Chrome-102"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T19:12:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google just promoted Chrome 102 to stable as the latest feature update to their cross-platform web browser...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is it possible to configure the color output of pacman?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uwyets/is_it_possible_to_configure_the_color_output_of/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uwyets/is_it_possible_to_configure_the_color_output_of/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T19:07:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If I enable color in pacman.conf, some elements are displayed in a bold red (for example, the community repo). I can't work with this because I'm colorblind - I have to remove any boldface color from my system. Is this possible with pacman? Or is my only recourse to disable color output?
 Thanks
    submitted by    /u/Pound_Hash  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Customize Appointment Schedule Availability in Google Calendar]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=800281</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/800281/customize-appointment-schedule-availability-google-calendar/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T19:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An alternative to Appointment Slots in Google Calendar, the Appointment Schedules feature lets you create schedules allowing clients and colleagues to book appointments with you. What’s nice about the feature is that it offers flexibility to completely customize your availability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dell G15 5525 - Microphone not working]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uwy53s/dell_g15_5525_microphone_not_working/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uwy53s/dell_g15_5525_microphone_not_working/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T18:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, I've been trying to configure/enable my microphone on Archlinux (it works fine on Windows) 
 Result of arecord --list-devices cmd:
 carte 2 : Generic_1 [HD-Audio Generic], périphérique 0 : ALC3204 Analog [ALC3204 Analog]
 Sous-périphériques : 0/1
 Sous-périphérique #0 : subdevice #0
 carte 2 : Generic_1 [HD-Audio Generic], périphérique 2 : ALC3204 Alt Analog [ALC3204 Alt Analog]
 Sous-périphériques : 1/1
 Sous-périphérique #0 : subdevice #0 
 Already checked in alsamixer, and nothing is muted or at 0.
 Also i've tried to capture my voice, but I only get noise using this cmd:
 arecord -f dat -D hw:2,0 -d 5 test.wav
 ​
 Can someone tell me what I'm missing ?
 Thank you
    submitted by    /u/SlixeFR  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why is java 17 getting installed?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uwxz18/why_is_java_17_getting_installed/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uwxz18/why_is_java_17_getting_installed/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T18:48:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is output from pacman.log that shows java 17 getting installed but I'm not sure why. I install jre11-openjdk before https://aur.archlinux.org/packages/datagrip (with yay) since it's a dependency, then I install https://aur.archlinux.org/packages/elasticsearch7 which has jre11-openjdk-headless as a dependency.
 I'm not running pacman -S --noconfirm --config /etc/pacman.conf -- extra/jre17-openjdk-headless extra/jre17-openjdk extra/java-environment-common extra/jdk17-openjdk myself so what is doing it? Is it coming from a dependency? I looked in PKGBUILD for these packages but couldn't see anything that explains why it's there or how I can stop it from getting installed.
 [PACMAN] Running '/usr/bin/pacman --noconfirm --noprogressbar --needed --sync jre11-openjdk' [ALPM] transaction star…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft: Credit card stealers are getting much stealthier]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-credit-card-stealers-are-getting-much-stealthier/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-credit-card-stealers-are-getting-much-stealthier/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T18:44:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft's security researchers have observed a worrying trend in credit card skimming, where threat actors employ more advanced techniques to hide their malicious info-stealing code. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux 5.19 Makes It Much Easier To Clear CPUID Features]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-Better-clearcpuid</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-Better-clearcpuid"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T18:40:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Linux x86/x86_64 kernel has long honored the "clearcpuid=" kernel parameter to disable select CPUID features from being used by the kernel or readily advertised. However, it hasn't been very intuitive to use since it relied on passing the bit numbers for the specific features. With Linux 5.19 it's much easier to deal with in now allowing the CPUID string from /proc/cpuinfo to be passed if wanting particular CPUID features disabled...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulkan 1.3.215 Released With Barycentric Fragment Shader Extension]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Vulkan-1.3.215-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Vulkan-1.3.215-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T18:12:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vulkan 1.3.215 is out today with a handful of fixes/clarifications to the Vulkan specification plus one new extension...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add a MetaMask Wallet to iPhone or Android]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=800641</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/800641/how-to-add-a-metamask-wallet-to-iphone-or-android/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T18:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MetaMask is a popular cryptocurrency wallet that you can download to your phone for free. Once installed, you can connect MetaMask to all kinds of DeFi applications (dApps) to easily send and receive cryptocurrency.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>RJ Fulton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nginx 1.22 Released With OpenSSL 3.0 Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Nginx-1.22-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Nginx-1.22-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T18:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nginx as the lightweight web-server known for its speedy performance is out today with the version 1.22 feature release...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA adds 41 vulnerabilities to list of bugs used in cyberattacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisa-adds-41-vulnerabilities-to-list-of-bugs-used-in-cyberattacks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisa-adds-41-vulnerabilities-to-list-of-bugs-used-in-cyberattacks/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T17:50:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Cybersecurity & Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has added 41 vulnerabilities to its catalog of known exploited flaws over the past two days, including flaws for the Android kernel and Cisco IOS XR. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Senate: Govt’s ransomware fight hindered by limited reporting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-senate-govt-s-ransomware-fight-hindered-by-limited-reporting/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-senate-govt-s-ransomware-fight-hindered-by-limited-reporting/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T17:34:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A report published today by U.S. Senator Gary Peters, Chairman of the Senate Homeland Security and Governmental Affairs Committee, says law enforcement and regulatory agencies lack insight into ransomware attacks to fight against them effectively. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Android Apps on Windows 11 Are Rolling Out to More Countries]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=807331</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/807331/android-apps-on-windows-11-are-rolling-out-to-more-countries/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T17:18:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has been working on a Windows Subsystem for Android, allowing Android apps and games to easily run on top of Windows 11. Now the feature is rolling out to more countries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Will Soon Allow Anyone to Make Windows 11 Widgets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=807322</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/807322/microsoft-will-soon-allow-anyone-to-make-windows-11-widgets/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T17:16:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Build took place earlier today, and one of many announcements was that Microsoft will soon allow third-party developers to create widgets for Windows 11.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DuckDuckGo Isn't as Private as You Thought]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118915/duckduckgo-isnt-as-private-as-you-thought/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118915/duckduckgo-isnt-as-private-as-you-thought/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T17:09:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DuckDuckGo made a deal with the devil. Due to a confidential search agreement, the DuckDuckGo browser does not block all Microsoft trackers. What’s worse, DuckDuckGo only acknowledged this “privacy hole” after it was discovered by a security researcher.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Search Engine Keeps Changing to Yahoo? Here’s What to Do]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=806217</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/806217/search-engine-keeps-changing-to-yahoo-heres-what-to-do/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T17:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If your browser homepage and search engine keep mysteriously changing to Yahoo!, your computer is probably infected with a browser hijacker. While resetting your browser might seem to fix the problem, here’s how to do the job properly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Russ Ware</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Screencastify Chrome extension flaws allow webcam hijacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/screencastify-chrome-extension-flaws-allow-webcam-hijacks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/screencastify-chrome-extension-flaws-allow-webcam-hijacks/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T16:45:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The popular Screencastify Chrome extension has fixed a vulnerability that allowed malicious sites to hijack users' webcams and steal recorded videos. However, security flaws still exist that could be exploited by unscrupulous insiders. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dev Box: cosa sono le workstation virtuali per gli sviluppatori]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Dev-Box-cosa-sono-le-workstation-virtuali-per-gli-sviluppatori_24557</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Dev-Box-cosa-sono-le-workstation-virtuali-per-gli-sviluppatori_24557"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T16:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Abbiamo già visto cos'è Windows 365 Cloud PC, la piattaforma che permette di eseguire installazioni di Windows 10 e Windows 11 da un normale browser Web.Le installazioni di Windows sono create sul cloud utilizzando la piattaforma Azure e sono gestibili come se fossero parte di un'infrastruttura locale.In occasione dell'evento Build 2022, Microsoft ha presentato il nuovo concetto di Dev Box. In breve si tratta di workstation virtuali che sfruttano lo stesso schema utilizzato con Windows 365 e permettono di utilizzare sistemi già preconfigurati con tutto ciò che è necessario per sviluppare applicazioni con i vari linguaggi, framework, piattaforme, componenti, editor, ambienti di programmazione e così via.

Gestire workstation utilizzate dagli sviluppatori per creare le applicazioni è oggi fondamentale per stare al passo con i ritmi dei moderni.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Graviton3 Benchmarks - Nice Performance Uplift With AWS EC2 C7g]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31142</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31142"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the end of last year Amazon announced their new Graviton3 processors with around 25% more compute performance than their prior Graviton2 AArch64 processors, up to 2x the FP and crypto performance, DDR5 system memory support, and other improvements to their in-house processor for the AWS cloud. Yesterday the C7g instances reached general availability for making Graviton3 processors available to AWS customers. Here are some initial benchmarks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Se il telefono si scalda, come raffreddare lo smartphone (Android e iPhone)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2017/03/se-il-telefono-si-scalda-come.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2017/03/se-il-telefono-si-scalda-come.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T16:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In alcune situazione estreme anche un moderno telefono si surriscalda, fino a diventare rovente (non è possibile toccare la parte posteriore o lo schermo). Questo può capitare per diverse ragioni: perché una qualche app sta usando il processore in modo massiccio o perché siamo vittime di qualche malfunzionamento interno.

 Non va sottovalutato anche il lasciare il telefono al sole in una giornata...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trend Micro fixes bug Chinese hackers exploited for espionage]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/trend-micro-fixes-bug-chinese-hackers-exploited-for-espionage/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/trend-micro-fixes-bug-chinese-hackers-exploited-for-espionage/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T16:09:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trend Micro says it patched a DLL hijacking flaw in Trend Micro Security used by a Chinese threat group to side-load malicious DLLs and deploy malware. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows on ARM: Microsoft vuole fare sul serio con Project Volterra. Cos'è]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-on-ARM-Microsoft-vuole-fare-sul-serio-con-Project-Volterra-Cos-e_24556</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-on-ARM-Microsoft-vuole-fare-sul-serio-con-Project-Volterra-Cos-e_24556"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T16:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Correva l'anno 2016 quando Microsoft e Qualcomm annunciarono la loro partnership incentrata su Windows on ARM.Da allora la 'maturazione' di Windows sulla piattaforma ARM è stata piuttosto lenta: basti pensare che soltanto l'anno scorso Windows 11 on ARM ha aggiunto il supporto per le applicazioni x64 grazie all'emulazione gettando un ponte con le tradizionali installazioni del sistema operativo effettuate su sistemi basati su processore Intel o AMD.In occasione della conferenza Microsoft Build 2022, l'azienda di Redmond ha annunciato un kit di sviluppo chiamato Project Volterra.Project Volterra è una sorta di mini PC basato su SoC Qualcomm Snapdragon che permetterà agli sviluppatori di realizzare e provare le applicazioni ARM per Windows su hardware reale.Si tratta di un'importante pietra miliare con cui Microsoft conferma di nuovo la sua volontà di investire su Windows on ARM.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How “Wafer-Scale” CPUs Could Revolutionize Supercomputers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=797021</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/797021/wafer-scale-cpus-revolutionize-supercomputers/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T16:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CPUs have been getting faster over the years thanks to ever-smaller components. But as we’re heading towards the limit of how small circuits can get, where do we go? One answer is to make your chips “wafer-scale” in size.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sydney Butler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome Gets a Clean and Simple Google Lens Update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118881/chrome-gets-a-clean-and-simple-google-lens-update/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118881/chrome-gets-a-clean-and-simple-google-lens-update/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T16:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just two months ago, Google Lens replaced the traditional “reverse image search” function in the Chrome desktop browser. And it’s already getting a neat update! Instead of opening in a new tab, Google Lens now has a dedicated sidebar in Chrome.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why You Shouldn't Wash New Produce Immediately]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lifesavvy.com/130331/why-you-shouldnt-wash-new-produce-immediately/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lifesavvy.com/130331/why-you-shouldnt-wash-new-produce-immediately/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T16:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re all looking to save time, but if you wash your produce while putting away your groceries, you might want to skip that step from now on.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shea Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux Continues Playing Catch Up To Windows For Desktop Hardware Monitoring Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-HWMON</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-HWMON"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In recent kernel versions there has been an uptick in new driver activity around improving hardware sensor monitoring support for AMD/Intel desktop motherboards, but still it's generally behind that of the support found under Microsoft Windows. With Linux 5.19 there is more hardware monitoring "HWMON" subsystem work with improving sensor coverage on various motherboards and other components...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DropPoint makes drag and drop operations easier]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178757</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/05/24/droppoint-makes-drag-and-drop-operations-easier/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T15:30:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows, Mac OS and Linux support drag and drop operations to move or copy files from one location to another. The open source cross-platform application DropPoint aims to make drag & drop […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post DropPoint makes drag and drop operations easier appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hit the Track With the New LEGO Ferrari Daytona SP3 Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118898/hit-the-track-with-the-new-lego-ferrari-daytona-sp3-edition/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118898/hit-the-track-with-the-new-lego-ferrari-daytona-sp3-edition/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T15:28:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LEGO Technic garage just unveiled its latest supercar, the stunning and iconic LEGO Ferrari Daytona SP3 edition. And while we loved the LEGO Technic Ferarri 488 GTE a few years ago, this new model is packed full of details and has a higher price tag.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Home directory structure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uwtgdr/home_directory_structure/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uwtgdr/home_directory_structure/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T15:28:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey guys! I have a question regarding the home folder structure. Should I just create the folders I'll use myself or should I just use xdg dirs? Are there any disadvantages of not using it?
    submitted by    /u/TR0V40_  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fix “Windows Modules Installer Worker” High CPU Usage]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=post-ideas&amp;p=474416</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15326893/fix-windows-modules-installer-worker-high-cpu-usage"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T15:25:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes you may experience a steep rise in temperature or a sudden drop in performance while using your PC. It can be attributed to the various processes running in the background, specifically “Windows modules installer worker”, as it tends to eat up a huge chunk of CPU and disk resources. Luckily, there are many ways to fix this error. We discuss a few of them below.
   

Content

1. Restart the Windows Update Service
2. Run Windows Update Troubleshooter
3. Change Internet Settings
4. Run an SFC Scan
5. Disable the Windows Update Service

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Fix Wmpnetwk.exe High CPU and Memory Usage in Windows
    
What Is Windows Modules Installer Worker?
    
Windows Modules Installer Worker (also known as WMIW or TiWorker.exe) is an essential cog in the machinery of your operating system. Its... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ojash Yadav</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save 20% on a Plex Pass Lifetime Membership Through May 27th]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118893/save-20-on-a-plex-pass-lifetime-membership-through-may-27th/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118893/save-20-on-a-plex-pass-lifetime-membership-through-may-27th/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T15:08:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why pay $5 a month for Plex Pass when you can get a lifetime membership for 20% off? That’s right; you can unlock features like offline viewing, intro skipping, hardware transcoding, and live TV DVR at a huge discount. Just use coupon code GEEKOUT during checkout!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google TV is Finally Rolling Out User Profiles]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118888/google-tv-is-finally-rolling-out-user-profiles/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118888/google-tv-is-finally-rolling-out-user-profiles/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T15:01:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google TV users just got a fantastic surprise—the service is now finally rolling out individual user Profiles. The highly-desired feature is now rolling out after a series of delays and is super easy to set up on your device once it updates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzanne Humphries</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Find the Next (Potential) NFT Project to Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/?p=59727</id>
        <link href="https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/finding-the-next-nft/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T15:01:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NFT industry's unfathomable growth has led to numerous opportunities, raking billions of dollars within the past few years, and according to NFT sales]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rean</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How (and Why) to Use Google Sheets’ Operator Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=799168</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/799168/how-to-use-google-sheets-operator-functions/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T15:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Sheets like Microsoft Excel offers many functions for calculations and tasks. While you can use symbols to perform mathematical comparisons, it may be beneficial to use the functions we’ll discuss instead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ghacks Deals: The 2022 Complete Game Developer Bundle]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178744</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/05/24/ghacks-deals-the-2022-complete-game-developer-bundle/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T14:59:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2022 Complete Game Developer Bundle includes ten game development courses. You learn how to create a variety of games using different platforms, including Unreal Engine and Unity. Games you will be […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Ghacks Deals: The 2022 Complete Game Developer Bundle appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch GUI full Wayland without any xorg dependency is it possible? For now the site only has twm's with xorg, I would like to remove xorg completely and just use Wayland.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uwsjul/arch_gui_full_wayland_without_any_xorg_dependency/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uwsjul/arch_gui_full_wayland_without_any_xorg_dependency/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T14:48:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/Pointers58  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migliori alternative gratuite a Excel da usare online]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/05/migliori-alternative-gratuite-excel-da.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/05/migliori-alternative-gratuite-excel-da.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Excel è un programma che non manca mai su nessun PC aziendale, così da poter gestire facilmente ogni tipo di foglio di calcolo. Se però utilizziamo temporaneamente il computer di un'altra persona o un computer pubblico senza Excel installato, possiamo rimediare subito alla sua assenza utilizzando uno dei siti pensati per modificare i fogli di calcolo direttamente online, agendo...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s How to Get Google Assistant on the Galaxy Watch 4]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=807228</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/807228/heres-how-to-get-google-assistant-on-the-galaxy-watch-4/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T14:36:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung’s Galaxy Watch 4 is one of the best smartwatches around, but unlike every other Wear OS device, it didn’t have Google Assistant. Now that has finally changed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers to release exploit for new VMware auth bypass, patch now]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/researchers-to-release-exploit-for-new-vmware-auth-bypass-patch-now/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/researchers-to-release-exploit-for-new-vmware-auth-bypass-patch-now/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T14:16:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Proof-of-concept exploit code is about to be published for a vulnerability that allows administrative access without authentication in several VMware products. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Ilascu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These New ASUS ExpertBook Laptops Go Crazy with Specs and Battery Life]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118834/these-new-asus-expertbook-laptops-go-crazy-with-specs-and-battery-life/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118834/these-new-asus-expertbook-laptops-go-crazy-with-specs-and-battery-life/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T14:02:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ASUS is expanding its professional ExpertBook lineup with two killer laptops, the ExpertBook B9 and ExpertBook B7 Flip. Both laptops feature impressive specs, a flashy design, and surprisingly, a great battery life.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Issue with sound in Gnomr]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uwrk71/issue_with_sound_in_gnomr/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uwrk71/issue_with_sound_in_gnomr/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T14:02:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For some reason on my work laptop, whenever I try and play a video or go on a zoom call, the sound doesn’t work initially. This is fixed by going into the gnome settings and switching to a different sound device then back to the original sound device that I wanted to use. I don’t have this issue on my other devices running arch (but don’t run gnome), anyone have any idea what this is caused by or his to fix it?
    submitted by    /u/ss7m  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Gaming Keyboards of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=753080</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/753080/best-gaming-keyboards/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A great keyboard is important for PC gaming. Speed, stability, and build quality are all huge factors. But with so many styles available on the market today, it’s hard to tell which keyboards are the best for you. We help narrow it down.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David McAdam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>