<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-07-25T02:06:10.406Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Expected Challenges Switching to Arch?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w7bzmq/expected_challenges_switching_to_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w7bzmq/expected_challenges_switching_to_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T01:43:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've always been an Ubuntu guy (now Lubuntu) but I'd like to step my game up and move to Arch so I can learn a bit more. Is there anything I need to prepare for as far as getting the system up and running, and to stay running? Thanks.
    submitted by    /u/frenetickticktick  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trying to teach someone shell scripting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w789uf/trying_to_teach_someone_shell_scripting/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w789uf/trying_to_teach_someone_shell_scripting/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T22:48:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trying to teach my friend shell scripting. This is what I came up with: ```
 !/bin/bash
 eegrep(){ echo $@; } bzz(){ bzip2 $@; } nogrep=/dev/null grepmo=50 [ -z $grepc ] && { cd -- mkdir grep.rd &> $nogrep cd grep.rd [ ! -f grep.sh ] \ && cat dirname $0/basename $0 \ | tee grep.sh \ && chmod +x grep.sh export grepc=$grepmo }
 mkdir grep.d cp grep.sh grep.d cd grep.d
 eegrep fgrep > grep.f cp grep.f grep.2bz bzz grep.2bz grep fgrep grep.f bzgrep fgrep *.bz2
 [ $grepc -gt 0 ] && { eegrep $grepc greps && { a=$PWD cd $HOME/grep.rd exa --tree --level=$grepmo cd $a } export grepc=$((grepc - 1)) ./grep.sh cd .. rm -rf grep.d } ```
    submitted by    /u/TheTsar  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come avviare più facilmente windows in modalità provvisoria]]></title>
        <id>3627|20220725000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/windows-10/come-avviare-piu-facilmente-windows-modalita-provvisoria-3627"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[La modalità provvisoria di Windows permette di avviare il sistema operativo in modo ridotto nelle funzioni, nei servizi e nei driver. Questo può permettere, non è sempre detto che ci si riesca, di riprendere il controllo di un computer dove un driver danneggiato, o un servizio che non parte, impediscono il normale avvio del sistema operativo. Però, come vedete in questo articolo, arrivare alla modalità provvisoria può richiedere numerosi passaggi che magari non abbiamo voglia, o la capacità, di fare. Così un modo molto più veloce per arrivare alla modalità provvisoria è quello offerto dal programma portable Safe Mode Launcher.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch doesn’t display full output of command on fresh arch install?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w769xt/arch_doesnt_display_full_output_of_command_on/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w769xt/arch_doesnt_display_full_output_of_command_on/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T21:20:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EDIT: Turns out the console was set in the wrong resolution, so I used fbset to correct it
 ​
 I‘m trying to use Pacman to install a desktop environment on bash but when I run the command the output gets cut off and I can’t scroll down to read it.
 ​
 I’ve tried:
  
using the ‘less’ command with Pacman however I don’t think that works since Pacman requires input
 Increasing the frame buffer and updating grub
  
Any suggestions would be greatly appreciated
    submitted by    /u/ChewyCashew614  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dropped into emergency shell after installing with archinstall]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w75zrx/dropped_into_emergency_shell_after_installing/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w75zrx/dropped_into_emergency_shell_after_installing/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T21:08:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So I’m trying to dual-boot with Windows 10, I have a btrfs partition and am using my EFI partition as my boot partition. Archinstall went fine until I rebooted and got this error. This is my first time using Arch and all help is appreciated.
    submitted by    /u/Osoa_  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux 5.19-rc8 Released With More Retbleed Fixes, Intel GuC Firmware Fix]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/news/Linux-5.19-rc8-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/news/Linux-5.19-rc8-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T21:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As was expected given all the recent kernel activity, Linux 5.19-rc8 was released today rather than going straight to the Linux 5.19 stable release, which has been diverted now to next Sunday. Linux 5.19-rc8 ships with many last minute fixes for this summer 2022 kernel update...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Enable the Ultimate Performance Power Plan in Windows 10]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=368781</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/368781/how-to-enable-ultimate-performance-power-plan-in-windows-10/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has added an “Ultimate Performance” power scheme to Windows 10 April 2018 Update. It’s built upon the High-Performance power scheme but tries to eke out every little bit of performance possible. Here’s how to enable it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brady Gavin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Where does the archlinux wallpaper pack get installed to]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w74oli/where_does_the_archlinux_wallpaper_pack_get/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w74oli/where_does_the_archlinux_wallpaper_pack_get/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T20:11:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I downloaded the arch linux wall paper pack to use in my qtile install but im not sure where it actually downloads the pngs to by default
    submitted by    /u/OutsideNo1877  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your Phone Has a Biometric Kill Switch, Here’s Why You Should Use It]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=814149</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/814149/your-phone-has-a-biometric-kill-switch-heres-why-you-should-use-it/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern iPhones and Android phones have super-convenient biometric security, but it isn’t always the best idea to leave it on. Luckily your phone probably has a biometric killswitch that can disable any biometric lock in seconds. All you have to do is learn how to use it!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sydney Butler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 Search Bar Not Working? Here’s 9 Ways to Fix It]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=430149</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/14805200/windows-11-search-bar-not-working"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For many Windows users, the Windows Search bar is the most important utility. On a Windows 11 device, however, you may find this option disabled. This is, in fact, a common issue facing those who plan to get the free upgrade from Windows 10 to Windows 11. There’s no single reason behind it being disabled. Therefore, our solutions below range from quick, easy fixes to more elaborate troubleshooting, including a reset option.
   

Content

Why Is Windows 11 Search Disabled?
1. Enable Search Button on Taskbar
2. Check for Windows Updates
3. Use Search and Indexing Troubleshooter in Windows 11
4. Restart the Windows Search Service
5. Tweak the Touch Keyboard and Handwriting Panel Service
6. Enable Search History on Device and Clear Past Search History
7. Ensure Your Search Results Aren't Within Excluded Folders
8. Use CTRL + ALT + DEL
9. Reset Windows 11
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sayak Boral</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Portable Console Runs on a Pi Pico, and You Can Actually Buy It!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/123914/this-portable-console-runs-on-a-pi-pico-and-you-can-actually-buy-it/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/123914/this-portable-console-runs-on-a-pi-pico-and-you-can-actually-buy-it/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T19:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Believe it or not, but the tiny Raspberry Pi Pico is perfectly capable of running games. In fact, it’s such a fun little platform that Pimoroni turned it into a portable console—the PicoSystem. And you can buy this console pre-assembled for $59.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Clear the Cache in Microsoft Edge]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=818358</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/818358/how-to-clear-cache-in-edge/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T19:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you want to fix specific website issues or resolve other problems with your browser, it’s easy to clear Microsoft Edge’s cache on your desktop and mobile devices. You can also get the browser to automatically delete your cache on each exit. We’ll show you how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Uninstall Steam Games]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=818914</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/818914/how-to-uninstall-steam-games/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T18:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you don’t play a specific game anymore, it makes sense to uninstall it from Steam on your computer. Doing so frees up your storage space and declutters your Steam library. We’ll show you two different ways to do that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Screen flickering black for a milisecond every few minutes. Even in TTY.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w71ciq/screen_flickering_black_for_a_milisecond_every/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w71ciq/screen_flickering_black_for_a_milisecond_every/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T17:46:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am using 180hz 2560x1440 lg 27GP850. I recently bought it as a new one.
 It works fine on windows, no flickering but on linux it turns screen black every few minutes for a millisecond. Sometimes it flickers like a 3 times a row and stops for a next few minutes. I saw that It doesn't happen in full screen games. I am using xwayland gnome but I checked on x11 KDE plasma and it also happens. 
 XRANDR output
 Screen 0: minimum 16 x 16, current 4000 x 1599, maximum 32767 x 32767
 XWAYLAND0 connected primary 2560x1440+0+0 (normal left inverted right x axis y axis) 700mm x 390mm
 2560x1440 179.90*+
 1920x1440 179.86 
 [some other resolutions...]
 inxi -G output 
 Graphics:
 Device-1: AMD Navi 23 [Radeon RX 6600/6600 XT/6600M] driver: amdgpu
 v: kernel
 Display: wayland server: X.org v: 1.21.1.4 with: Xwayland v: 22.1.3
 compositor: gnome-shell v: 42.3.1 driver: X: loaded: amdgpu
 unloaded: modesetting,vesa gpu: amdgpu resolution: 1: 2560x1440~180Hz
 2: 1440x900~75Hz
 OpenGL: renderer: AMD Radeon RX 6600 XT (dimgrey_cavefish LLVM 14.0.6
 DRM 3.46 5.18.13-arch1-1)
 v: 4.6 Mesa 22.1.3
 CPU: I5 10400F
 GPU: RX 6600 XT (bought 3 months ago as a new one)
 RAM: 16GiB
 Monitor settings: 
 Overclock: ON (It doesn't change anything if I turn this off only refresh rate goes from 165 to 180hz)
 response time: faster (It also doesn't change anything)
 Energy saving: OFF
 HDR: off 
 motion blur reduction: off
 VRR: ON (in gnome settings)
    submitted by    /u/efoxpl3244  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nerf Ditches the Dart In Its New "Gelfire" Blaster]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/123925/nerf-ditches-the-dart-in-its-new-gelfire-blaster/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/123925/nerf-ditches-the-dart-in-its-new-gelfire-blaster/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T17:13:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The famous foam darts are missing from Nerf’s latest product, the Gelfire Mythic blaster. It shoots new “Gelfire” rounds, which are small hydrated balls that explode on impact. And oddly enough, it comes with some eye protection.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Turn Off the Touch Screen on Chromebook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=820175</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/820175/how-to-turn-off-the-touch-screen-on-chromebook/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T17:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many Chromebooks have touchscreen displays, which are great if you like to use your laptop in “tablet mode.” However, if you don’t use the touchscreen, it may just be a source of accidental touches. You can turn it off.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Restore my grub efi entry for my linux install]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6z8c4/restore_my_grub_efi_entry_for_my_linux_install/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6z8c4/restore_my_grub_efi_entry_for_my_linux_install/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T16:14:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So basically I dual boot windows and arch but one day I logged into windows after like a month of not opening it to use a school software and it f**king decides to do some update and completely delete my bootable arch system, it didn't delete the partition though so my data was still safe. I decided to install another os by just making a 60gb partition and now I can boot into my previous original arch install through the grub of the new one and everything works. 
 Question is I can't figure out how to get the old grub entry back into my efi so I can delete this new one and not have an unnecessary install just to boot into my other install. I tried doing grub-mkconfig -o /boot/grub/grub.cfg but that didn't work. Help would be appreciated as I can't find clear answer on the net either for this specific problem
    submitted by    /u/Previous_Royal2168  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 Ways to Insert a Video in Google Docs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=811491</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/811491/insert-a-video-in-google-docs/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T16:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While Microsoft Word lets you add and play a video directly in your document, Google Docs doesn’t currently offer this same feature. If you want to embed a video to your Google Doc, we’ll show you a few workarounds to make it happen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Zari 0.1.0: A command to run all your tasks in one go!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6ykin/announcing_zari_010_a_command_to_run_all_your/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6ykin/announcing_zari_010_a_command_to_run_all_your/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T15:45:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Project Page. The Release Page.
 Hey everyone! I too wrote some code and I'd like to share it with you. The project is called Zari and it has now reached a state in which I feel like it's worthy of a 0.1.0 release. 
 Of course, since this is my first Rust project and with it being just the first release I bet there are some coding guidelines or standards I'm breaking, so please let me know if you see any improvements!
 What is it?
 Zari is a task execution program with a focus on simplicity and giving control to the user.
 In short, it allows you to configure multiple one-liners which will be executed sequentially. By letting Zari handle these commands, you can configure once and forget about it. An example would be to update all the various package managers on your system!
 Where to f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can't update my system. [error: failed retrieving file 'core.db'] Any help is appreciated.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6yga8/cant_update_my_system_error_failed_retrieving/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6yga8/cant_update_my_system_error_failed_retrieving/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T15:39:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Edit: SOLVED. Canada's mirrors weren't working for some reason, but US mirrors did work. 
 When I try to sudo pacman -Syu or sudo pacman -Syyu, it prompts an error:
  core.db failed to download error: failed retrieving file 'core.db' from mirror.0xem.ma : The requested URL returned an error: 503 error: failed to syncronize all databases (failed to retrieve some files) 
 I've tried going into /etc/pacman.d/mirrorlist and changed the mirror, but I get the same error. 
 Thanks.
    submitted by    /u/tonystark29  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nintendo Wii U and 3DS eShops Get an Official Closing Date]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/123904/nintendo-wii-u-and-3ds-eshops-get-an-official-closing-date/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/123904/nintendo-wii-u-and-3ds-eshops-get-an-official-closing-date/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T15:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In February, Nintendo revealed that the Wii U and popular Nintendo 3DS eShops would officially close sometime in 2023, marking the end of purchases. This means gamers can no longer buy any content, including games, apps, wallpapers, themes, and anything else.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Edge-Lit vs. Direct-Lit vs. Full-Array TVs: What’s the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=818768</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/818768/edge-lit-vs-direct-lit-vs-full-array-tvs/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T15:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern LCD TVs rely on LED backlighting to produce the visuals you see on the screen. But their picture quality and price can differ based on their backlighting system. So, what are these backlighting systems, and how are they different?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gaurav Shukla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Debug Options]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6xi3c/debug_options/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6xi3c/debug_options/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T14:57:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello folks, after reading today’s news on phoronix.com related to DEBUG versus performance impact, I wonder how many of us disabled those debugging flags ? Or what kind of options you turn on or off, and how do you set things on or off? In other words I’m seeking a proper guide for newbies :)) Thanks
    submitted by    /u/Balauru_Nr1  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aur builder that checks pkgbuilds?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6x9cr/aur_builder_that_checks_pkgbuilds/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6x9cr/aur_builder_that_checks_pkgbuilds/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T14:46:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been using chaoticaur due to speed/convenience but later learned that it's a blind builder. Are there any similar services that actually check the pkgbuild to ensure it hasn't been compromised?
    submitted by    /u/Zackptg5  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Printers of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=767282</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/767282/best-printer/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you need a printer for work-from-home tasks, family printing needs, or both, picking the right printer can be a challenge. We’ve picked the best printer for you based on budget and feature set.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Albert Bassili</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migliori smartphone con schermo grande (6,5 pollici o superiori)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2014/03/migliori-cellulari-phablet-con-schermo.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2014/03/migliori-cellulari-phablet-con-schermo.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T13:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gli smartphone con lo schermo grande possono intimidire gli utenti più tradizionali abituati agli schermi più piccoli, ma una volta provati difficilmente si torna indietro visto l'elevato livello di dettaglio e colori che è possibile ammirare su un display così ampio.
 Questi smartphone però hanno due inconvenienti: non si possono facilmente utilizzare con una sola mano (il rischio di farli cadere è molto alto) e sono ingombranti da tenere in una tasca dei pantaloni o dei jeans, quindi obbliga (almeno gli uomini) a trovare un altro posto in cui conservarlo quando siamo fuori casa.
 Se si può far fronte a questi due problemi e vogliamo assolutamente provare uno smartphone dallo schermo grande, così da poter giocare, vedere film e serie TV maniera più dettagliata e bella rispetto ad uno smar…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Innocn 40C1R ultrawide 144Hz monitor review: Plenty of room and fast refresh rate]]></title>
        <id>05a11ad2-83f6-47ab-9ed7-94cdb69361cd</id>
        <link href="https://www.zdnet.com/home-and-office/home-entertainment/innocn-40c1r-ultrawide-144hz-monitor-review/#ftag=RSSbaffb68"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T13:21:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want a single monitor to help you get work done, the 40-inch ultrawide Innocn 40C1R provides plenty of room for multiple apps and multiple input devices. It's optimized for gaming, but it's also great for productivity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest stories for ZDNet in Windows</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Alternate Versions of The Game of Life of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/122945/the-best-alternate-versions-of-the-game-of-life-of-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/122945/the-best-alternate-versions-of-the-game-of-life-of-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T13:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s a reason that The Game of Life has stuck around since it first published in 1960. It’s great! More than that, though, it’s a game that lends itself well to multiple iterations, just like Clue and Monopoly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Chaney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Flash Storage?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=815593</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/815593/what-is-flash-storage/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve been shopping for an SSD or using memory cards for cameras, you’ll probably encounter the term “flash memory.” But what is flash memory and how does it work? We’ll explain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Shark Movies to Stream During Shark Week]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=819180</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/819180/best-shark-movies-to-stream/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T12:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What better way to celebrate Shark Week than with shark movies? Real-life sharks may be majestic creatures, but in the movies, they’re terrifying villains. From suspenseful classics to entertainingly dumb B-movies, here are the best shark movies to stream online.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Bell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wi-Fi disconnects and reconnects very often no matter which]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6t5e7/wifi_disconnects_and_reconnects_very_often_no/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6t5e7/wifi_disconnects_and_reconnects_very_often_no/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T11:07:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I installed Arch, the tutorial I followed said to install networkmanager, iwd, and dhcpcd.
 I connected to Wi-Fi with iwctl and dhcpcd, then sudo systemctl enable NetworkManager.service and sudo systemctl start NetworkManager.service.
 I've already looked for solutions, and many say this problem is caused by multiple network managers fighting to connect through a single interface.
 So I just removed networkmanager and wpa_supplicant so I guess I'm only using iwd and dhcpcd now, but nothing has changed. 
 Is there anything I might still have installed that would be causing this?
    submitted by    /u/loganr914  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Is It Called Roku?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=818516</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/818516/why-is-it-called-roku/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roku is a name that has become so common to see that you probably don’t think much about where it came from. Roku devices can be found in millions of households, but what does “Roku” actually mean? Is it anything?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Fedora Linux Rawhide Kernel Is Becoming Too Slow With Its Many Debug Options]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/news/Fedora-Rawhide-Debug-Too-Slow</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/news/Fedora-Rawhide-Debug-Too-Slow"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T10:57:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fedora is one of the Linux distributions that ships with a plethora of debug options during its "Rawhide" development phase to ease in diagnosing issues that turn up during testing rather than building everything in a release mode during the development cycle. While these debug options are good for debugging, the performance impact continues adding up and reaching a point that the Fedora Rawhide debug kernel is too slow for some tasks...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux 5.19-rc8 Still Getting Bandaged From Retbleed Mitigation Fallout]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/news/Linux-5.19-More-Retbleed-Fixes</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/news/Linux-5.19-More-Retbleed-Fixes"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T10:43:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While normally big CPU security mitigation work done behind closed-doors is in good shape for the vulnerability embargo date, Retbleed has been an exception. Nearly two weeks since Retbleed was made public, the Linux kernel patches around it continue with more now sent in today ahead of Linux 5.19-rc8 to address fallout from the mitigation handling...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Run Docker Compose Containers With GPU Access]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?post_type=devops&amp;p=804233</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/devops/how-to-run-docker-compose-containers-with-gpu-access/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T10:40:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GPU access in Docker lets you containerize demanding workloads such as machine learning applications. GPUs aren’t automatically available when you start a new container but they can be activated with the --gpus flag for docker run or by adding extra fields to a docker-compose.yml file.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel GSC Support Continues To Get Squared Away For DG2/Alchemist]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/news/Intel-GSC-Arc-Alchemist-v6</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/news/Intel-GSC-Arc-Alchemist-v6"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T10:25:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While much of Intel's Arc Graphics DG2/Alchemist enablement appears to be in decent shape for Linux 5.20 with the small BAR support expected to land, the compute support being exposed to user-space in 5.19, etc, one of the few remaining pieces is the GSC support. The Intel GSC is their new Graphics System Controller found with their discrete GPU and used for security-related operations...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[libby: a simple CLI tool to quickly download books from libgen (Library Genesis)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6rv89/libby_a_simple_cli_tool_to_quickly_download_books/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6rv89/libby_a_simple_cli_tool_to_quickly_download_books/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T09:40:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[libby scrapes Library Genesis with curl and pup and gives you a list of downloads with fzf. I made this because I felt the alternatives were too slow. Feel free to add issues/feature requests/PRs!
 The tool is available on the AUR as libby-git.
 Demo
 GitHub
 Source
    submitted by    /u/Waste_Perception_233  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Experimental Patches Updated Working On FSCRYPT Encryption For Btrfs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/news/Btrfs-FSCRYPT-Encryption-RFC-v2</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/news/Btrfs-FSCRYPT-Encryption-RFC-v2"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T09:23:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the Btrfs file-system has many advanced features like transparent file-system compression and built-in RAID, at the moment it lacks native file-system encryption. Fortunately, there are patches that continue to be worked on that aim to provide such functionality...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Dockerfile From an Existing Image]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?post_type=devops&amp;p=800689</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/devops/how-to-create-a-dockerfile-from-an-existing-image/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T08:04:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Docker images are created by building Dockerfiles. The build process executes the instructions in the Dockerfile to create the filesystem layers that form the final image.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grub says "error: symbol `grub_debug_malloc' not found"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6psvp/grub_says_error_symbol_grub_debug_malloc_not_found/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6psvp/grub_says_error_symbol_grub_debug_malloc_not_found/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T07:19:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have a dual booted system with Windows 11 and Arch. When I try to boot it, I get the aforementioned error. Any idea about how I can fix this?
 SOLVED: Refer to this comment by MiteshPandav. Thanks
    submitted by    /u/pr0_Disappointment  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Find Pattern Matches Across Multiple Lines With grep]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?post_type=devops&amp;p=800691</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/devops/how-to-find-pattern-matches-across-multiple-lines-with-grep/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T06:02:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[grep is a command line text searching utility that is able to find patterns and strings in files and other types of input. Most matches will match on one line only, but it’s often useful to match across multiple new lines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Heddings</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 update rolled back because of Start Menu opening issues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179906</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/07/24/windows-11-update-rolled-back-because-of-start-menu-opening-issues/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T05:18:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft confirmed a new Windows 11 issue this weekend that is causing Start Menu opening issues on the operating system. Some users started to report the issue to Microsoft after installation of […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Windows 11 update rolled back because of Start Menu opening issues appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why arent the archlinux-keyring package automatically updated before any other packages when doing pacman -Syu?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6kwm7/why_arent_the_archlinuxkeyring_package/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6kwm7/why_arent_the_archlinuxkeyring_package/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T02:32:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Often when I havent updated my system in a while, I get problems with gpg signatures upon updating the system. Every time this happens, I need to update the archlinux-keyring before once again running -Syu. Why doesnt pacman see that theres a newer keyring for and updates that before everything else? Wouldnt this make "late system upgrades" easier for everybody?
    submitted by    /u/Druz3  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hi guys can you share the arch.zip file for creating a bootable usb the tool I am using can't use iso and I couldnt find a .zip file on the download page. HELP PLEASE?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6iuzg/hi_guys_can_you_share_the_archzip_file_for/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6iuzg/hi_guys_can_you_share_the_archzip_file_for/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T00:46:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/Piano-Nerd  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux x86 32-bit Is Vulnerable To Retbleed But Don't Expect It To Get Fixed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/news/Linux-x86-Retbleed</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/news/Linux-x86-Retbleed"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T23:39:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While relevant Intel and AMD processors have been mitigated for the recent Retbleed security vulnerability affecting older generations of processors, those mitigations currently just work for x86_64 kernels and will not work if running an x86 (32-bit) kernel on affected hardware. But it's unlikely to get fixed unless some passionate individual steps up as the upstream developers and vendors have long since moved on to just caring about x86_64...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to install MacBook keyboard and trackpad drivers?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6hdf0/how_to_install_macbook_keyboard_and_trackpad/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6hdf0/how_to_install_macbook_keyboard_and_trackpad/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T23:33:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey guys, just installed XeroLinux on my MacBook Pro. I am currently using an external keyboard and mouse but was wondering if it was possible to get the native keyboard and trackpad to work with this installation. This is my first time trying Linux.
    submitted by    /u/FaMaterial  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qtile failing to run with wayland module not found wlroots]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6h51n/qtile_failing_to_run_with_wayland_module_not/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6h51n/qtile_failing_to_run_with_wayland_module_not/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T23:22:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As far as im aware i installed everything i needed but when i try to start qtile i have installed everything else i thought i need but im still getting this error and am not sure where to go
    submitted by    /u/OutsideNo1877  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[archfi]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6h4em/archfi/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6h4em/archfi/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T23:21:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve tried to install arch using archfi tool However when I finish the installation and reboot it brings me back to the console What should I do??
    submitted by    /u/_ch0ck  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[i did it again O.o git and aur replacement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6gsp4/i_did_it_again_oo_git_and_aur_replacement/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6gsp4/i_did_it_again_oo_git_and_aur_replacement/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T23:05:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[hi there again, i need your help again. 
 i started using linux-hardened and trying using kazium but this is one of the packages that stopped working using a "safer" kernel. and here it comes someone on the internet recommended to not to use flatpak may solve the bwrap restrictions of this kernel. 
 SO the dump me tought lets try the AUR kalzium-git without checking what packages it would install.
 And after a lot of :"yes sure why i wouldn't replace a lot of kde's packages with their outdated unmaintained packages" i found out i may made a mistake. Don't use:
 yes | yay package name 
 is there a way to replace all git packages with their pacman match, they all have git- in there name.
 and i runned a backup a few days ago with:
 rsync -aAXHvz --exclude={"/dev/*","/proc/*","/sys/*","/tmp/*…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fail to mount.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6ehnu/fail_to_mount/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6ehnu/fail_to_mount/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T21:21:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was screwing around trying to get League of Legends to work.
 After I rebooted, I get a message saying a dependency in /home/ failed, and I get a failure to mount /dev/sda1 From the emergency shell, I can run mount -a, systemctl enable sddm, exit and it boots/works just fine after that. I found it can be a problem with /etc/fstab but can't seem to locate the issue.
 /etc/fstab
  Static information about the filesystems. # See fstab(5) for details. # <file system> <dir> <type> <options> <dump> <pass> # /dev/sda2 UUID=85b9b5a1-3272-4606-a72a-4f292cabe8de / ext4 rw,relatime 0 1 # /dev/sda1 UUID=98C7-00DB /boot vfat rw,relatime,fmask=0022,dmask=0022,codepage=437,iocharset=ascii,shortname=mixed,utf8,errors=remount-ro 0 2 # /dev/sdb1 UUID=d9db346f-3279-4861-b073-19ec0962accd /home ext4 rw,relatime 0 2 
 lsblk -f
 NAME FSTYPE FSVER LABEL UUID FSAVAIL FSUSE% MOUNTPOINTS sda ├─sda1 vfat FAT32 98C7-00DB 402.5M 21% /boot └─sda2 ext4 1.0 85b9b5a1-3272-4606-a72a-4f292cabe8de 182.1G 12% / sdb └─sdb1 ext4 1.0 d9db346f-3279-4861-b073-19ec0962accd 2.5T 2% /home zram0 [SWAP] 
 I'm absolutely sure I'm missing something dumb here, just not sure what. Thank you so much in advance.
    submitted by    /u/Autistigasmatic  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[two questions about archinstall (the pacman version not the default one)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6eh5q/two_questions_about_archinstall_the_pacman/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6eh5q/two_questions_about_archinstall_the_pacman/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T21:20:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have two question's about the script after archinstall is done, both of which are in the "/dev/(disk)" section.
  
what does the "encrypted" option do; obviously it encrypts, but if I change it from true to false will it really just encrypt the partition or do you have to do anything else too? and if so, what kind of encryption will it perform?
 what does the "wipe" option do?
  
ty.
 edit: here's a link to what I'm talking about
    submitted by    /u/Amber___yo  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Don’t Need a Product Key to Install and Use Windows 10]]></title>
        <id>http://www.howtogeek.com/?p=244678</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/244678/you-dont-need-a-product-key-to-install-and-use-windows-10/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft allows anyone to download Windows 10 for free and install it without a product key. It’ll keep working for the foreseeable future, with only a few small cosmetic restrictions. And you can even pay to upgrade to a licensed copy of Windows 10 after you install it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thinkpad P50 DWM problem on wake from lid closed sleep]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6dslx/thinkpad_p50_dwm_problem_on_wake_from_lid_closed/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6dslx/thinkpad_p50_dwm_problem_on_wake_from_lid_closed/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T20:49:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi all,
 I am running Arch on a Thinkpad P50 with DWM as my window manager. I'm experiencing a problem with waking the computer from lid-closed sleep, where the computer wakes but the screen is black, except for a small horizontal line at the topmost left corner of the screen. The keyboard won't respond in this state, so I can't get another terminal open to diagnose or kill the display manager. 
 Arch is otherwise running perfectly on the P50, but this issue is really annoying and I would love to resolve it. The problem is that I don't know where to start, and would really appreciate some guidance / tips from the community. I perused the forums and reddit, and couldn't find a post with the same issue - but I am sure that this is not unique to me. I'm running 5.18.13-arch1-1. No display manager is used; just a call to exec dwm in .xinitrc. 
 I can provide whatever logging info would be helpful. I have the same build running on a Thinkpad X220, and that installation is bullet proof - so I wonder if it has to do with the hybrid graphics setup on the P50? I have the following graphics drivers installed: mesa, lib32-mesa, nvidia.
 Thanks again.
    submitted by    /u/Away_Inflation_411  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HarfBuzz 5.0 Released With Progress On Supporting The "Boring Expansion" Font Spec]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/news/HarfBuzz-5.0-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/news/HarfBuzz-5.0-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T20:38:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HarfBuzz is the open-source text shaping engine that is widely used by many different libraries and applications. The HarfBuzz code is critical to the Linux desktop and many open-source applications while this weekend is celebrating its big "5.0" release. With HarfBuzz 5.0 the developers have been working on the "Boring Expansion" font spec support...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can multiple instances of aurutils aur sync -Sc pkgname1 pkgname2... be run parallel?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6damp/can_multiple_instances_of_aurutils_aur_sync_sc/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6damp/can_multiple_instances_of_aurutils_aur_sync_sc/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T20:26:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/doskanoness  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Change Directories in Command Prompt on Windows 10]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=659411</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/659411/how-to-change-directories-in-command-prompt-on-windows-10/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the first things you’ll need to learn as you become more familiar with Command Prompt on Windows 10 is how to change directories in the operating system’s file system. There are a few ways you can do this, so we’ll walk you through them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marshall Gunnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[16 Interesting Discord Servers to Join (And Where You Can Find More)]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=post-ideas&amp;p=425157</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/14777747/best-discord-servers"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While it was once a chat app that lived and breathed as a place for gamers to communicate, Discord has evolved into “Your Place to Talk and Hang Out.” It is available on Windows, macOS, iOS, and Android, and you can jump in and out of conversations as often as you would like. In fact, the biggest challenge with Discord may be where to find the best servers for your situation. Fortunately, we can help with that.
   

Content

1. Your Favorite Podcast/Streamer/YouTuber/Subreddit
2. r/CryptoCurrency
3. Movies & Filmmaking
4. Minecraft and/or Any Other Games
5. Fantasy Football Chat
6. Invincible
7. ChillZone
8. Anime Soul Discord
9. Game Dev League
10. Boiler Room Trading
11. Apple
12. Xbox/PlayStation
13. Marvel Studios
14. The Car Community
15. Memeology
16. Study Together
Finding More Discord Servers
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Change Your Username and Nickname... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexandra Arici</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Relive Your Favorite Music Concerts with Setify]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/123912/relive-your-favorite-music-concerts-with-setify/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/123912/relive-your-favorite-music-concerts-with-setify/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T19:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever loved the set list at a live concert so much that you wish you could easily listen to it over and over again? Or missed a concert by your favorite artist but still want to hear each song? If so, the web app Setify is worth checking out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Photo Album in Microsoft PowerPoint]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=812552</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/812552/how-to-create-a-photo-album-in-microsoft-powerpoint/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T19:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Slideshows are great for more than just business-related presentations. You can use Microsoft PowerPoint to create a photo album and add music or visual effects for a memorable show.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pulseaudio monitor acting weird with bluetooth earphones]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6a5vs/pulseaudio_monitor_acting_weird_with_bluetooth/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w6a5vs/pulseaudio_monitor_acting_weird_with_bluetooth/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T18:04:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This issue as far as i know has been limited to my bluetooth earphones [Oneplus Wireless Z2]
 This started after i switched the profiles from a2dp to hfp to use the inbuilt microphone for a video call
 Now i am not able to get output in cava and also not able to get desktop audio in obs when the bluetooth earphones are connected 
 I have tried:
 1)change the audio source in cava to the monitor corresponding to the earphones 
 2) changed sources in obs but to no avail
 3) unpairing and repairing the earphones
 I am using KDE Plasma
 Here are the outputs inxi -A, pacmd list-sources : https://pastebin.com/DM4gmDHr
 Please let me know if i left out some important information
 Thanks for all the help
    submitted by    /u/its_RaCl  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Turn Off Caps Lock on a Chromebook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=820198</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/820198/how-to-turn-off-caps-lock-on-a-chromebook/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T18:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chromebooks have very unique keyboard layouts. Where most keyboards have a Caps Lock key, Chromebooks have a search key instead. Using Caps Lock takes a little extra work, which means turning it off is a little more complex too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HFP Audio is no longer available, stuck on troubleshooting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w69mij/hfp_audio_is_no_longer_available_stuck_on/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w69mij/hfp_audio_is_no_longer_available_stuck_on/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T17:40:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi,
 I've been using a set of bluetooth headphones for the last several months. A2DP has always worked great for listening to music and videos but obviously I needed to switch to HFP in order for the microphone to work. I'm using pulseaudio and was able to enable the HFP profile pretty painlessly with pavcontrol.
 This was fine until a couple of weeks ago, now my system is showing unavailable in `pactl list`:
 Profiles: a2dp_sink: High Fidelity Playback (A2DP Sink) (sinks: 1, sources: 0, priority: 40, available: yes) handsfree_head_unit: Handsfree Head Unit (HFP) (sinks: 1, sources: 1, priority: 30, available: no) off: Off (sinks: 0, sources: 0, priority: 0, available: yes) 
 I followed the steps in the wiki relating to HFP issues. But I'm at a bit of a dead end. I tried running:
 dbus-send --print-reply --system --dest=org.ofono /phonesim org.ofono.Modem.SetProperty string:"Powered" variant:boolean:true 
 With the error
 Error org.freedesktop.DBus.Error.UnknownObject: Method "SetProperty" with signature "sv" on interface "org.ofono.Modem" doesn't exist 
 So I checked to make sure I have activated the modem, but downloading the git repo for ofono and running test/list-modems just creates a draggable text area on my screen for some reason, then exits out.
 I then went and checked the python code and ran the first couple of lines:
 import dbus bus = dbus.SystemBus() manager = dbus.Interface(bus.get_object('org.ofono', '/'),'org.ofono.Manager') modems = manager.GetModems() print(modems) >>> dbus.Array([], signature=dbus.Signature('(oa{sv})')) 
 So looks like modems is empty and I'm not sure where to go from here?
 Any help much appreciated.
 Also curious why the headset is only recently not working, have had no similar issues on my phone.
 Thank you
    submitted by    /u/jzia93  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD Sensor Fusion Hub "SFH1.1" Support Coming In Linux 5.20 For Newer Laptops]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/news/AMD-Sensor-Fusion-Hub-SFH-1.1</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/news/AMD-Sensor-Fusion-Hub-SFH-1.1"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T17:23:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the upcoming Linux 5.20 cycle is support for AMD's Sensor Fusion Hub v1.1 revision being found in newer Ryzen laptops...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mattel Teams Up With Elon Musk's SpaceX to Create New Toys]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/123923/mattel-teams-up-with-elon-musks-spacex-to-create-new-toys/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/123923/mattel-teams-up-with-elon-musks-spacex-to-create-new-toys/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T17:13:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Popular toy maker Mattel is teaming up with Elon Musk’s SpaceX company to produce a new line of space-themed toys and rockets. On Wednesday, the two announced a multi-year deal to deliver Matchbox brand SpaceX toys and merchandise by 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Share a Wi-Fi Password From Mac to iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=814352</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/814352/how-to-share-a-wi-fi-password-from-mac-to-iphone/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T17:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you need to share a Wi-Fi password from a Mac to an iPhone, you can do it fairly easily between your own devices and those of friends or family. Here’s how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean hackers attack EU targets with Konni RAT malware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/north-korean-hackers-attack-eu-targets-with-konni-rat-malware/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/north-korean-hackers-attack-eu-targets-with-konni-rat-malware/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T16:08:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat analysts have uncovered a new campaign attributed to APT37, a North Korean group of hackers, targeting high-value organizations in the Czech Republic, Poland, and other European countries. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up Facebook Marketplace Alerts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=819768</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/819768/how-to-set-up-facebook-marketplace-alerts/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T16:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Facebook Marketplace has become the go-to place for selling things online. If you’re on the lookout for a specific item, an alert can help you snag a great deal before everyone else. We’ll show you how to do it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Banana Pi BPI-W3 Lets You Build a Powerful Router or NAS Device]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/123901/the-banana-pi-bpi-w3-lets-you-build-a-powerful-router-or-nas-device/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/123901/the-banana-pi-bpi-w3-lets-you-build-a-powerful-router-or-nas-device/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T15:23:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While it still doesn’t have a price, the new Banana Pi BPI-W3 looks like a dream—especially if you want a custom NAS solution. Not only is it the most powerful Banana Pi router board to date, but it packs impressive specs that you rarely see on a single-board computer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome use subject to restrictions in Dutch schools over data security concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/chrome-use-subject-to-restrictions-in-dutch-schools-over-data-security-concerns/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/chrome-use-subject-to-restrictions-in-dutch-schools-over-data-security-concerns/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T15:12:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ministry of Education in the Netherlands has decided to place a conditional ban on the use of the Chrome OS and Chrome web browser until August 2023 over concerns about data privacy. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Close Are We to Uploading Your Mind?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=814693</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/814693/how-close-are-we-to-uploading-your-mind/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T15:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mind uploading, technically known as “whole brain emulation,” is the idea that you can digitize a brain (and presumably the mind) and have that mind live on within the computer long after the body is dust. But how realistic is this idea?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sydney Butler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating custom keyboard layouts that work across DE's and WM's]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w65t2g/creating_custom_keyboard_layouts_that_work_across/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w65t2g/creating_custom_keyboard_layouts_that_work_across/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T14:51:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Long story short, I only type on the workman keyboard layout, it's the only layout I'm proficient in. Most DE's and Linux installs already have the vanilla English version of it, however, I also type in Spanish and French, so I'd like to have a (preferably GUI) program to remap some of the keys in order to have the special characters unique to those languages. I already did some research and apparently xbindkeys is that sort of program but I can't seem to get it to work, has anyone else had this problem? Anyhow, I'm also looking for alternatives to tackle this problem. Thanks in advance!
 Note: before switching to Linux, I had this problem sorted on Windows 10 with a program called Keytweak, it let me remap keys to my liking, this would be the kind of thing I'm looking for. There was also a Windows layout creator that was very useful.
 Extra question: is there a way to bind ctrl+delete to delete the entire word on Arch/KDE plasma.
    submitted by    /u/basedand-sarahpilled  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel GuC Firmware Fix Submitted For Linux 5.19]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/news/Intel-GuC-Firmware-Fix-Linux</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/news/Intel-GuC-Firmware-Fix-Linux"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T14:29:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sent in on Friday night were this week's batch of Direct Rendering Manager (DRM) driver fixes for Linux 5.19-rc8 due out on Sunday. While usually the late-stage changes tend to be not too eventful, this pull does carry some extra interest since it does fix the Intel GuC firmware breakage I wrote about last week that ended up breaking Alder Lake P graphics on Linux 5.19 unless also upgrading the firmware version...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>