<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-07-04T02:17:18.796Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ibus works wired after a update about gnome-shell]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vqwhve/ibus_works_wired_after_a_update_about_gnomeshell/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vqwhve/ibus_works_wired_after_a_update_about_gnomeshell/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-04T01:55:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I updated my system this morning and after rebooting I found that my Ibus selecting menu becomes very long and nothing is shown on it. It can still input Chinese but it becomes very hard to use. Is it possible to fix it?
    submitted by    /u/Weiliang_1503  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No longer booting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vqv62b/no_longer_booting/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vqv62b/no_longer_booting/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-04T00:39:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently updated my whole system. Now when I try to boot it says A start job is running for /dev/mmcblk0p1 after which it says Timed out waiting for device /dev/mmcblk0p1 and goes into emergency mode and says Cannot open access to console, the root account is locked. How do I fix this?
 Edit: I restored a time shift backup and now I get Failed to mount /boot. when booting Is my system even recoverable?
 Edit: I'm on a Thinkpad and I'm pretty mmcblk0p1 refers to a partition on an SD card, so I'm not sure why that's even referenced at boot.
    submitted by    /u/ZombieDuckLord  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Installing WiFi Drivers on WiFi-less System]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vqv14q/installing_wifi_drivers_on_wifiless_system/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vqv14q/installing_wifi_drivers_on_wifiless_system/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-04T00:31:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi all,
 I'm a new Arch user (and pretty much new Linux user) and I'm currently going through the process of installing Arch as a dual-boot option. I'm not here to discuss why I'm doing that in the first place, as it's kind of a long story.
 I have the Arch ISO on a bootable USB drive and have successfully booted into it. However, the Windows user in me came out and I completely forgot about my WiFi USB adapter and that I have no drivers for it. There is no wired internet in my apartment, and I don't have access to the router, so a wired connection is not an option.
 The drivers for my chipset can be found on the AUR. I've spent the last few hours trying to compile the package on a VM on my laptop and transfer it to my PC via USB, but I keep running into increasingly frustrating issues and gave up.
 I'm fairly new to Linux and am in over my head, so I came to the experts: what do you think would be the easiest way to install these drivers? I still have full access to Windows (where I'm typing this), so I was wondering if there was a way to install them directly using File Explorer, but, again, I have very little idea what I'm talking about. Any advice at all would be very much appreciated.
 Thank you for your time.
 EDIT: more information
 I have attempted to use the adapter as-is to no avail. Using dmesg -W and plugging it in outputs:
 usb 3-3: new high-speed USB device number 6 using xhci_hcd usb 3-3: new USB device found, idVendor=0b05, idProduct=184c, bcdDevice= 2.10 usb 3-3: new USB device strings: Mfr=1, Product=2, SerialNumber=3 usb 3-3: Product: 802.11ac NIC usb 3-3: Manufacturer: RealTek usb 3-3: SerialNumber: 123456 
 It is also listed when lsusb is used. I've tried restarting iwd as suggested by almost every forum post with this issue, but the device and adapter lists remain empty after all permutations of the process.
    submitted by    /u/woodencupboard  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How good is video HAL on Arch linux for Intel GPUs?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vqtxdm/how_good_is_video_hal_on_arch_linux_for_intel_gpus/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vqtxdm/how_good_is_video_hal_on_arch_linux_for_intel_gpus/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T23:29:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am casual gamer on Stadia and notice by default Hardware VP9 was not enabled which was also absent for YouTube videos. I followed Arch Linux wiki to enable Guc/HuC and GPU HAL in my system and chromium (with vaapi patch) and Firefox. After I did that the video played in Chromium would process with hardware decoding but it was intermittently freezing/blacking out especially if I opened developer pane view and then resumed if I maximized video. On Firefox, the video playback was stable but suffered with lower FFPs performance. In both scenarios intel_gpu_top showed no more than 3% of video usage. This was my experience with video playback in 2K (1440p). Overall its pretty disappointing and now I ran chromium without HAL flags unless I play Stadia.
 My stats:
  
most recent 5.18.x kernel
 KDE/Wayland -graphics: Intel XE Mesa/i915 -VAAPI - iHD
  
Hardware:
  
Dell XPS 9305
 RAM: 8GB RAM
 Storage: 500GB NVMe
 CPU: TGL i5-1135G7
 UEFI CPU/Power setting: Maximum performance/always connected
 Monitor resolution: 1440p
 Stadia game resolution: 1080p
  
   submitted by    /u/ZD_plguy17  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux 5.19-rc5 Released - "Slightly Smaller Than Normal"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-rc5-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-rc5-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T23:06:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A week ago with Linux 5.19-rc4 there was concern over that weekly release being larger than normal, but this week with Linux 5.19-rc5 it's smaller than normal, which is pleasing Linux creator Linus Torvalds...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come cancellare (quasi) tutti i cookie da Firefox alla sua chiusura]]></title>
        <id>3613|20220704000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/browser-455/come-cancellare-quasi-tutti-cookie-firefox-chiusura-3613"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Le persone che tengono molto alla loro privacy non vogliono lasciare traccia della navigazione nel proprio computer, così magari impostano il browser in modo che cancelli tutti i dati nel momento della chiusura del programma. Solo che così facendo vengono cancellati tutti i cookie e i siti che visitate abitualmente si dimenticano di voi. Così ogni volta che accedete a Google, Youtube o a un forum dove siete iscritti vi richiederà la login o di confermare qualche preferenza. Il cookie serve in sostanza al sito per riconoscervi e sapere quali sono le vostre preferenze o abitudini.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Clean the Dust Out of Your Laptop]]></title>
        <id>http://www.howtogeek.com/?p=194479</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/194479/how-to-clean-the-dust-out-of-your-laptop/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve had your laptop for a year or two, it may be full of dust. Dust clogs fans, vents, and heat sinks, preventing your PC from cooling down properly. You can remove a good amount of this dust, even if you can’t open your laptop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UFW allow of a port range won´t run]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vqqp63/ufw_allow_of_a_port_range_wont_run/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vqqp63/ufw_allow_of_a_port_range_wont_run/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T20:47:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi guys, I have been dealing with a strange issue today.
 I would like to check out KDE Connect, and a required step is to allow port range 1714:1764 UDP and TCP to pair with the device. https://userbase.kde.org/KDEConnect#I_have_two_devices_running_KDE_Connect_on_the_same_network.2C_but_they_can.27t_see_each_other
 Sadly, both me doing the rule manually from the shell, or using a gui for ufw, will fail with the following:
 ERROR: problem running ufw-initWarning: Extension multiport revision 0 not supported, missing kernel module?iptables-restore v1.8.8 (legacy): invalid port/service \1714:1764' specifiedError occurred at line: 19
 I have been trying to search for this error, or for a missing package to install to allow iptables to function correctly in this regard, but failed.
 Do anybody of you have a hint for me how to get this module running?
 Is this a known issue or a misconfiguration on my side somewhere?
 Thanks
    submitted by    /u/funforums  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a Spotify "Iceberg" and Show Off Your Love of Music]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/122177/create-a-spotify-iceberg-and-show-off-your-love-of-music/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/122177/create-a-spotify-iceberg-and-show-off-your-love-of-music/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T20:04:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spotify wrapped year in review playlists are a popular trend each year, but lately, you’ve probably seen those weird Spotify iceberg images all over Twitter or TikTok. So what is a Spotify Iceberg, and how can you make your own?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Find EV Charging Stations in Google Maps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=762729</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/762729/how-to-find-ev-charging-stations-in-google-maps/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Charging stations for electric vehicles are not nearly as plentiful as gas stations. They can also be harder to spot from the road. Thankfully, Google Maps makes it easy to find chargers for your electric car.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Privacy protection agency seizes servers of hacked travel company]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/privacy-protection-agency-seizes-servers-of-hacked-travel-company/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/privacy-protection-agency-seizes-servers-of-hacked-travel-company/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T19:34:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Privacy Protection Authority in Israel seized servers hosting multiple travel booking websites because their operator failed to address security issues that enabled data breaches affecting more than 300,000 individuals. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Ilascu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Failed to start Load Kernel Modules and Failed to start Wireless Service]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vqp480/failed_to_start_load_kernel_modules_and_failed_to/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vqp480/failed_to_start_load_kernel_modules_and_failed_to/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T19:30:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently installed Arch, but I noticed that I was unable to see any wireless access points with iwctl. Someone suggested that I may need linux-firmware, so I used my installation medium and arch-chroot to grab it. I also did a pacman -Syu. Now, when I try to boot into the OS after decrypting my partition, I see [FAILED] Failed to start Load Kernel Modules. and several instances of [FAILED] Failed to start Wireless services. before proceeding to the login screen. I can still login, but when I tried to launch iwctl, I got stuck on "waiting for IWD to respond," so clearly I broke something.
 I did some googling, and it seems that this can be caused by an unmounted /boot, but if I am understanding the output of lsblk -f correctly, then mine is mounted. I could also see /boot in my fstab (I should maybe mention, however, that it is on a different partition).
 My googling also revealed that not having mounted boot while in chroot and then updating the system may have caused the issue. I tried reinstalling linux after making sure to mount boot while in chroot but that didn't help. I also tried running mkinitcpio -p linux in arch-chroot, but that didn't help either unfortunately.
 I also tried extending the fstab as suggested here, with no luck.
 Any idea what I can try next?
    submitted by    /u/networks_dumbass  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Desktop Environments of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=385386</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/14271904/best-desktop-environments"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T19:25:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Linux users, we’re often spoiled for choice when it comes to software. There are some basic programs that we keep coming back to that are so integrated into the stack that we forget they’re even there. However, when it comes to things like desktop environments, it can be hard to determine the best option for exactly what you’re going to use it for. We have reviewed different Linux Desktop Environments, and there’s a lot of overlap between use cases. Here we show you the best Linux Desktop Environments for your particular use case.
    
Note: the following list is not listed in any particular order, and Window Managers are not included.
   

Content

1. GNOME Shell
2. KDE Plasma
3. Cinnamon / Pantheon
4. XFCE
5. Budgie
6. Deepin
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}    
1. GNOME Shell
    
For (New) Laptop Users
    
For users of new laptops, I would recommend GNOME. One thing is for sure: Gnome is not the easiest to use straightaway. Its design... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miguel Leiva-Gomez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make Folders and Organize Apps on iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=811962</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/811962/how-to-make-folders-iphone/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T19:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To better organize your apps, your iPhone allows you to create folders in which you can put relevant apps together. This makes finding apps easier and declutters your phone’s home screen. We’ll show you how to create and delete such folders on your iPhone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I'm new to Arch, loving it so far, I just need a bit of help installing NVIDIA drivers on a bit older card.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vqnur1/im_new_to_arch_loving_it_so_far_i_just_need_a_bit/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vqnur1/im_new_to_arch_loving_it_so_far_i_just_need_a_bit/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T18:30:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So I've installed Arch with archinstall pretty easily, it works VERY well, and I'm impressed! Honestly, after I set it up, It's probably gonna be my daily driver, however, I don't know how to install NVIDIA drivers on older GPUs on Arch based distros.
 I have a GTX 660 2GB GPU from MSI.
 I want to install the 
 > nvidia-470xx-dkms
 package, but I have no idea how, and while you're at it, could you please tell me what else should I take notice of, and what to do after driver installation, cheers!
    submitted by    /u/nasergaser  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Smash Drums' VR Game Gets a Huge Multiplayer Upgrade]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/122168/smash-drums-vr-game-gets-a-huge-multiplayer-upgrade/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/122168/smash-drums-vr-game-gets-a-huge-multiplayer-upgrade/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T18:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ready to jam with your friends in VR? The latest Smash Drums update comes with a huge multiplayer upgrade, making it easier to play with friends or strangers. Plus, a new Challenges feature lets you set up tournaments that everyone can play asynchronously—you know, at their own pace.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add and Assign Roles in Discord]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809671</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809671/how-to-add-assign-roles-discord/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T18:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To help you manage your servers, Discord allows you to create custom roles and assign them to your server members. This way, the members can moderate your server’s content and help ease your schedule. We’ll show you how to do that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why dual boot Windows with Arch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vqn3no/why_dual_boot_windows_with_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vqn3no/why_dual_boot_windows_with_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T17:53:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are a lot of posts and articles about how you dual boot, and the wiki of course, but nothing says why or if you should. This is a two part question:
  
One of the main benefits of Arch is that it is a bare bones, diy system, meaning you know everything that is on your system because you put it there. This provides you better control over your system, performance in removing unnecessary background tasks like usage statistics, and encapsulation of the personal data on your machine. With a Windows OS, all that goes out the window. You have a lot of noise and diagnostics programs, and Arch's rolling release model is great, but Windows is still going to force reboot my computer for updates right, making Arch moot right? The reason to run Windows at all, in my case, is exe applications that don't have an Linux executable/aren't in aur. For that I used a vm on my laptop. But moving towards a dedicated PC for workstation for programming and streaming as well as entertainment/gaming station, I may need to switch back to Windows for less compatibility issues with new games or streaming programs. So if I need to use Windows for compatibility, why use Arch at all? Or has Linux gaming come far enough to feel confident there won't be as many compatibility issues staying with Arch?
 
If dual booting Arch and Windows does make sense (eg. I like Arch but if I need Windows for compatibility with software), is there a way to cut out the noise from it and make it more like Arch? Removing the unnecessary background diagnostics tasks, facial authentication, automatic updates, etc. Or what is the most lightweight Windows OS to dual boot with Arch that would resolve Arch compatibility issues?
 
    submitted by    /u/Outrageous-Machine-5  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch not showing up in UEFI boot menu, while Fedora does.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vqm5gn/arch_not_showing_up_in_uefi_boot_menu_while/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vqm5gn/arch_not_showing_up_in_uefi_boot_menu_while/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T17:07:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I flashed the arch iso (archlinux-x86_64.iso) using balenaEtcher onto a USB drive. I reboot my machine, but the drive does not show up in the UEFI boot selection menu.
 I thought it may be a problem with my drive, but after flashing fedora onto it, the machine boots successfully.
 I checked the SHA256 of the iso, and tried both OSes with Fedora Media Writer. Same result.
 I read the wiki, but it seems to be about problems after booting into the usb. I am new to arch, so I may not have found the correct wiki page.
 Help?
    submitted by    /u/veryanonomyous  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AirPods Not Switching Between Devices? Try These Fixes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=811339</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/811339/airpods-not-switching-between-devices/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T17:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple’s wireless AirPods and some Beats models automatically switch between devices depending on which you are using. This can be a time-saver when hopping between devices, but sometimes it doesn’t work as advertised. Here are some things to try if your AirPods won’t play ball.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Archboot 2022.07 - Arch Linux images released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vqlp75/archboot_202207_arch_linux_images_released/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vqlp75/archboot_202207_arch_linux_images_released/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T16:46:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/tobiaspowalowski  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TP-Link Routers and Smart Home Devices Get a Huge Discount for July 4th Weekend]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/122159/tp-link-routers-and-smart-home-devices-get-a-huge-discount-for-july-4th/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/122159/tp-link-routers-and-smart-home-devices-get-a-huge-discount-for-july-4th/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T16:34:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want internet that’s more reliable or a home that’s got some brains, now’s the time to buy new equipment. TP-Link is running a huge July 4th sale on routers, mesh Wi-Fi kits, range extenders, and smart home products.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fix an iPhone Stuck on the Apple Logo: 5 Solutions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=812197</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/812197/iphone-stuck-on-apple-logo/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T16:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is your iPhone seemingly stuck in purgatory? Are you staring at a stubborn Apple logo or a progress bar that doesn’t seem to move? You’re not alone. Here are some things you can try to fix your unresponsive device.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reinstall of Wireplumber killed audio]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vqjvyy/reinstall_of_wireplumber_killed_audio/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vqjvyy/reinstall_of_wireplumber_killed_audio/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T15:19:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Been looking for a solution the last hour. Time to ask.
 So back a month ago wireplumber was removed for media-session. Last update switched it back. Lost audio.
 Jul 03 10:01:10 linuxbox systemd[747]: Started Multimedia Service Session Manager.
 Jul 03 10:01:11 linuxbox wireplumber[755]: Failed to set scheduler settings: Operation not permitted
 Only conf file I had for media-session was ~/.config/pipewire/media-session.d/alsa-monitor.conf so my optical out would not sleep. Moved it out.
 Haven't come across any .pacnew files in any directories so far.
 ron@linuxbox ~ $ wireplumber
 C 10:20:43.846699 GLib (null):(null):(null): Failed to set scheduler settings: Operation not permitted
 M 10:25:02.747500 script/policy-node policy-node.lua:587:chunk: 1 pending linkable(s) not activated in 20sec. This should never happen.
    submitted by    /u/Venlaw  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free smartphone stalkerware detection tool gets dedicated hub]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/free-smartphone-stalkerware-detection-tool-gets-dedicated-hub/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/free-smartphone-stalkerware-detection-tool-gets-dedicated-hub/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T15:12:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kaspersky has launched a new information hub to help with their open-source stalkerware detection tool named TinyCheck, created in 2019 to help people detect if their devices are being monitored. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Forward Multiple Emails in Gmail]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=812286</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/812286/how-to-forward-multiple-emails-in-gmail/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T15:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Gmail’s built-in forwarding options, you can forward multiple of your emails as regular emails and as email attachments. We’ll show you how to do both of these from Gmail’s web version as the mobile app doesn’t support these features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Defender adds network protection for Android, iOS devices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-defender-adds-network-protection-for-android-ios-devices/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-defender-adds-network-protection-for-android-ios-devices/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T14:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has announced the introduction of a new Microsoft Defender for Endpoint (MDE) feature in public preview to help organizations detect weaknesses affecting Android and iOS devices in their enterprise networks. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Bluetooth Trackers of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=724315</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/724315/best-bluetooth-trackers/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nobody likes losing their items, which is why there’s a large market for Bluetooth trackers. These handy little gadgets can help you keep track of almost anything. Which one is the best? We have a few recommendations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Flickering in sway with 515.57 nvidia driver]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vqi2sy/flickering_in_sway_with_51557_nvidia_driver/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vqi2sy/flickering_in_sway_with_51557_nvidia_driver/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T13:51:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://reddit.com/r/swaywm/comments/vqehiq/flickering_in_sway_with_51557_nvidia_driver/
    submitted by    /u/4vkn43k3  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to install Nvidia on one kernel and keep Nouveau on another? Multiple kernels on the same system without conflicting packages?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vqi24d/how_to_install_nvidia_on_one_kernel_and_keep/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vqi24d/how_to_install_nvidia_on_one_kernel_and_keep/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T13:50:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi all, I've read through the Nvidia and Nouveau pages on the wiki, but havent seen a multiple kernel setup where nouveau and nvidia drivers exist on the same system but are activated.by different kernels.
 Does anyone have any experience in such a setup?
    submitted by    /u/tomatoaway  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD Gets Back To Working On Their "Jadeite" Platform For Linux In 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMD-Jadeite-Linux-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMD-Jadeite-Linux-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T13:05:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Somewhat surprisingly, AMD engineers have been working on some new Linux kernel patches for their aging Jadeite platform...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[System complete freezes when running a fullscreen old game with Wine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vqh54n/system_complete_freezes_when_running_a_fullscreen/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vqh54n/system_complete_freezes_when_running_a_fullscreen/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T13:01:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Full
 Recently I wanted to play an old game that I like a lot, GTA San Andreas, so I installed in Bottles
 The installation process went fine and everything looks alright, although when I tried to play, the game just starts in fullscreen and crashes my entire laptop
 I tried change configs, using system wine or caffe, running 64bit or 32bit env, activating and deactivating DXVK, VKD3D, Dedicated GPU, Sync, Windows versions, Gamemode, etc. The only thing that change something, is when I start in windowed mode
 I also tried to install directly with wine (no Bottles or anything else, just wine) and the results are the same
 So, when wine is windowed mode I can open the game and play, but when I let wine run fullscreen, my laptop freezes and I have to hard shutdown holding the power button
 TLDR
 I want play an old game, but if I let wine run in fullscreen, freezes my entire laptop, while running wine in windowed mode the game plays smooth
 My configurations
  
Arch Linux
 Kernel: 5.18.8-arch1-1
 Wine version: wine-7.11
 Gnome 42.2
 X11
 12 GB Ram DDR4
 Laptop Aspire E15 E5-553G-T4TJ
  
Post
 I have no idea what's happening and I can't find any log or crash message as well
    submitted by    /u/RudahXimenes  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[21 Things You Didn't Know Alexa Could Do]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/121158/21-things-you-didnt-know-alexa-could-do/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/121158/21-things-you-didnt-know-alexa-could-do/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes, you have no hands free to look up an answer to a burning question. Over 300 million households have smart home assistants as of 2022, and for good reason: They make life so much easier. Amazon Alexa has many hidden features that many users don’t know about.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>April Miller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forget Humidity, Dew Point Is How It Really Feels Outside]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=733421</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/733421/forget-humidity-dew-point-is-how-it-really-feels-outside/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Humidity can have a huge effect on how hot it really feels outside. Thankfully, weather apps typically include humidity numbers, but you’re probably looking at the wrong ones. What you should be checking is the dew point.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migliori telefoni da regalare ai figli, bambini o ragazzi]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/07/migliori-telefoni-da-regalare-ai-figli.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/07/migliori-telefoni-da-regalare-ai-figli.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T12:17:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Non è mai semplice regalare un telefono ai bambini o agli adolescenti, visto che spesso tendono a rimanere attaccati allo schermo dello smartphone per ore ed ore, trascurando gli impegni scolastici e la vita sociale. 
Purtroppo ai giorni nostri non possiamo sottrarci dal regalare lo smartphone ai bambini per evitare l'emarginazione, ma conviene puntare su modelli adatti alla loro età ed evitare...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[M1 and M2 Macs Are Emulation Powerhouses]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=812430</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/812430/m1-and-m2-macs-are-emulation-powerhouses/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T12:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you have an Apple Silicon Mac or are thinking of buying one, you should know that Apple’s new processors are great for emulation purposes. Whether it’s modern 3D consoles or 2D classics, the sheer quantity of native Apple Silicon emulators is something to be celebrated.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Much Does It Cost to Operate an Electric Lawn Mower?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=812090</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/812090/how-much-does-it-cost-to-operate-an-electric-lawn-mower/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Between the increasing cost of gas and the wide variety of electric lawn mowers on the market now, you might be curious how much it costs to own and operate one compared to a gas model. Here’s what you need to know.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Fitzpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Time Comes For GTK5, It Might Be Wayland-Only On Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=GTK5-Might-Drop-X11</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=GTK5-Might-Drop-X11"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T10:48:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While GTK4 is still in its early stages and it will presumably be some years before "GTK5" even begins to take shape, GNOME developers are already thinking of ditching X11 support for that next major GTK release -- effectively making it Wayland-only on Linux...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[(help)temporary failure in name resolution error in installation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vqeqo6/helptemporary_failure_in_name_resolution_error_in/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vqeqo6/helptemporary_failure_in_name_resolution_error_in/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T10:35:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am successfully connected to my wifi (no errors) using iwctl
 But when I try  ping google.com  It says: ``` ping: google.com: Temporary failure in name resolution
 ```
 I searched in google, they say you have a bad resolv.conf
 But I don't have a resolv.conf What i can do
    submitted by    /u/JX720  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[External graphics configuration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vqe7m6/external_graphics_configuration/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vqe7m6/external_graphics_configuration/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T09:59:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi!
 I'm currently NOT using an eGPU but I'm looking for a new laptop (must be a laptop cus I'm a student) and I haven't made my mind if I want a gaming laptop with decent battery life (e.g. Zephyrus G14) or a more work-oriented, cheaper laptop and later save for an eGPU so I can play some heavier games. One of my main uncertainties is how hard would it be to configure Arch to use the external eGPU.
 If someone has some experience with eGPUs on Arch, can you clarify this for me, please? 
 Thanks in advance!
    submitted by    /u/MrQuatrelle  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel Media Driver 2022Q2 Adds HDR10/HVS Support For DG2, Raptor Lake P Enabling]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-Media-Driver-2022Q2</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-Media-Driver-2022Q2"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T09:22:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In addition to Intel this week releasing the VA-API 2.15 video acceleration library, their open-source engineers also published their newest quarterly feature release of their open-source Intel Media Driver that implements the VA-API interface for their graphics hardware...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sound Open Firmware 2.2 Released With Optimizations. Continued Zephyr Porting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Sound-Open-Firmware-2.2</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Sound-Open-Firmware-2.2"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T08:56:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in 2018 Intel announced Sound Open Firmware (SOF) as their push for open-source sound firmware and looking to drive new software innovations in the audio DSP space. Out this week is Sound Open Firmware 2.2 for providing the newest features for this open-source software stack supporting Windows and Linux...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to configure and use Pipewire?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vqd3ss/how_to_configure_and_use_pipewire/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vqd3ss/how_to_configure_and_use_pipewire/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T08:39:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm trying to use Pipewire for simple audio tasks like listening to music, youtube videos, and zoom calls. I've got it working at a very basic level with the pipewire and pipewire-{alsa,pulse} packages, and I have output through my laptop speakers. I am also able to control the output level with alsamixer. However, how can I learn about doing more complex things like selecting the audio output, changing input levels, using media keys on my keyboard, etc? I've looked around on the internet and can't find much, and the Pipewire docs are all about programming with C/C++. Thanks in advance!
    submitted by    /u/HeyCanIBorrowThat  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Etnaviv Gallium3D Lands Async Shader Compilation With ARB_parallel_shader_compile]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Etnaviv-Async-Shader-Compile</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Etnaviv-Async-Shader-Compile"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T08:36:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For those interested in the Etnaviv Gallium3D driver that provides reverse-engineered, open-source OpenGL support for Vivante graphics IP its newest feature is supporting GLSL asynchronous shader compilation...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Microsoft wants SSD boot drives in Windows PCs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179507</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/07/03/report-microsoft-wants-ssd-boot-drives-in-windows-pcs/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T06:12:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft appears to be pushing manufacturers of Windows PCs to ship Windows 11 devices with Solid State Drives (SSD), according to a report by storage industry analyst Trendfocus. Windows 11 PC manufacturer […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Report: Microsoft wants SSD boot drives in Windows PCs appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are any FOSS arch devs (developers using arch, not just developing) migrating away from github?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vqanx5/are_any_foss_arch_devs_developers_using_arch_not/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vqanx5/are_any_foss_arch_devs_developers_using_arch_not/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T05:51:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[reason I'm asking is cause I just learned of github copilot indiscriminitely stealing open source code regardless of license from Software Freedom Conservancy - Give Up Github: The Time Has Come!, https://old.reddit.com/r/opensource/comments/vidiq2/github_copilot_legally_stealingselling_licensed/, https://old.reddit.com/r/programming/comments/og8gxv/github_support_just_straight_up_confirmed_in_an/ 
 also I'm curious as to if the FSF has made any moves/announcements following this situation
    submitted by    /u/GuildMasterJin  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Relying on login password with tpm2 and Secure boot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vq6ml3/relying_on_login_password_with_tpm2_and_secure/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vq6ml3/relying_on_login_password_with_tpm2_and_secure/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T01:53:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone,
 When using secure boot with custom keys, and luks full disk encryption tied to the TPM PCR 7 (secure boot state), a system can be encrypted but booted unattended up to the login prompt (GDM in my case).
 What steps, if any, can be taken to secure the login prompt in order to achieve security level similar to a luks password prompt at boot ? 
 Thanks !
    submitted by    /u/cvlc12  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[NOOB] Trying to understand Xterm]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vq5ho8/noob_trying_to_understand_xterm/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vq5ho8/noob_trying_to_understand_xterm/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T00:48:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have used pre-fab distros for years. I got hooked on building Arch into my dream machine about 6 months ago and have built and rebuilt my OS at least 15 times. I have decided to build a server without a DE and only the items I need to serve what I need. I do have a monitor on it and would like Xterm to look as good as possible.
 If I am understanding the Arch Wiki there is no config file and all configuration must be done through X Resources. I could use some tips or opinions on the best settings and the best way to go about making it look decent. I am using zsh.... I'm sure some will find that to be blasphemy but I love the powerlevel look and I have built a decent config that I am used to.
    submitted by    /u/TheGassyNinja  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My audio output keeps switching between analogue and digital]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vq5anf/my_audio_output_keeps_switching_between_analogue/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vq5anf/my_audio_output_keeps_switching_between_analogue/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T00:37:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pretty much the title.
 So I ran Arch on my previous PC (using gnome), and one day after an update my audio started playing up in a kind of peculiar way. Let's say that I have two options in my settings to pick from for audio output, Analogue Hi Res, and Digital Hi Res. When I would boot and triy to do something like play a song, the song would be stuck in a kind of "pending to play" state until I open the settings panel and changed from whatever output device had been selected on boot (let's say digital) to whatever option wasn't yet selected (so let's say analogue).
 Ok so it's choosing the wrong audio device on startup yeah? Nope lol. After choosing the correct output device and having sound play, if I would pause or halt the system audio for even a short amount of time (I'm talking less than 10 seconds), when I would resume playback the audio player would be stuck in the same halted loading state until I go back into the settings panel and change the output device back again (so back to digital from analogue in this example). This would have to have been repeated every time I paused system audio, because the audio would just continuously ping pong between analogue and digital.
 I thought this was just something I had done stupidly having had Arch running on this system for over 4 years, and didn't bother digging into the problem because I was building a new machine anyway.
 Well, I built the new machine, and it was working fine for a few weeks until today. I ran a system update and noticed that wireplumber was in conflict with pipewire-media-session. I chose to replace the lib wireplumber, and then boom. The output device switching issue resumed again.
 Does anyone have any idea what's doing on? Or where I would start to debug this? It's driving me mad hahaha.
 Thanks in advance.
    submitted by    /u/Tigh_Gherr  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Slow boot time on dual-boot laptop.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vq4pjp/slow_boot_time_on_dualboot_laptop/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vq4pjp/slow_boot_time_on_dualboot_laptop/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T00:04:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have a laptop where I set up an installation of Arch and an installation of Debian. Whenever I boot into Arch, I get a message "start job is running for /dev/disk/by-uuid/aa....", which lasts a minute and a half, followed by the message "dependency failed for /dev/disk/by-uuid/aa...." and then "dependency failed for Swaps" (note the uuid value shown matches the swap partition's). After this the system does successfully boot into Arch. Any help you can offer will be much appreciated, I have provided more details bellow.
 - The Arch installation uses sytemd-boot to boot, Debian's comes using grub.
 - The two installations each have their own root partition, they share an EFI partition, a swap partition, and a storage partition I made to store pictures, documents, etc.
 - As far as I can tell the fstab file in the Arch installation is correct (has the partitions I would expect to be there).
 -The computer defaults to Debian's boot menu, where there is an option to boot into Arch. I have tried going into the BIOS and entering through Arch's boot menu, when I do this the problem persists.
 ​
 Once again, any help will be greatly appreciated.
 Edit: Added a detail I thought was important.
    submitted by    /u/RRRitter  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch ISO 2022.07.01 got thinner by ~65 MiB]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vq489x/arch_iso_20220701_got_thinner_by_65_mib/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vq489x/arch_iso_20220701_got_thinner_by_65_mib/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-02T23:38:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well, that's not a big deal (or a great post either), but there were posts on the subreddit about ISO getting fattier and fattier over time, and this time it got decently slimmer.
  
2022.07.01 - 833957888 B ~ 795.32421875 MiB
 2022.06.01 - 903163904 B ~ 861.32421875 MiB
  
Interestingly the decimal fractional part stayed the same.
    submitted by    /u/murlakatamenka  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Suspend is failing with nvidia and wayland.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vq3uey/suspend_is_failing_with_nvidia_and_wayland/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vq3uey/suspend_is_failing_with_nvidia_and_wayland/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-02T23:18:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After hit suspend on gnome menu Screen turns black for ~1 minute, suspend eventually fails (or crash), the machine resumes to Gnome lock screen.
 ​
 Ive set those arguments in modprobe.d: (Wihtout those flags the suspend service works but all video returns currupted.)
 ​
 options nvidia NVreg_PreserveVideoMemoryAllocations=1 NVreg_TemporaryFilePath=/var/tmp 
 ​
 and 3 nvidia services are active: nvidia-suspend, nvidia-hibernate and nvidia-resume (this i was forced to enable in order to GDM display "wayland" options. With this disabled it was needed to change 61-gdm rules with same suspend behaviour.)
 ​
 [gabriel@arch ~]$ systemctl status nvidia-suspend.service ○ nvidia-suspend.service - NVIDIA system suspend actions Loaded: loaded (/usr/lib/systemd/system/nvidia-suspend.service; enabled; …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NVIDIA 515.49.06 Linux Vulkan Beta Driver Released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=NVIDIA-515.49.06-Linux-Beta</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=NVIDIA-515.49.06-Linux-Beta"/>
        <updated>2022-07-02T23:16:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For those enjoying some Linux gaming over the US holiday weekend, NVIDIA issued a rare Saturday driver update in the form of new Vulkan driver betas for Windows and Linux...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anyone else get this with the new iso?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vq38rh/anyone_else_get_this_with_the_new_iso/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vq38rh/anyone_else_get_this_with_the_new_iso/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-02T22:47:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There was a ding that came out of my pc speaker everytime I boot the new iso. Also, there's new grub options such as the speakup screen reader. Anyone else have the pc speaker ding ding?
    submitted by    /u/UnixElitist  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iwd unable to detect or connect to wifi networks after hard crash]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vq26e1/iwd_unable_to_detect_or_connect_to_wifi_networks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vq26e1/iwd_unable_to_detect_or_connect_to_wifi_networks/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-02T21:53:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello. My Dell Latitude E6420 running Arch recently had an unexpected abrupt poweroff (battery came loose by accident) and now it won't connect to wifi. I'm using iwd with dhcpcd.
 Output of iwctl station wlan0 scan && iwctl station wlan0 get-networks just says "No networks available". iwd.service and dhcpcd.service are running; I enabled them manually with systemctl to make sure.
 rfkill shows two wlan devices, phy0 and dell-wifi. Both are soft and hard unblocked.
 ping 9.9.9.9 simply says "Network is unreachable".
 Output of uname -a:
 Linux little-iron-4 5.18.7-arch1-1 #1 SMP PREEMPT_DYNAMIC Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:22:01 +0000 x86_64 GNU/Linux
    submitted by    /u/anon25783  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How can I make my laptop keyboard work for entering the LUKS encryption PIN at boot?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vq1r74/how_can_i_make_my_laptop_keyboard_work_for/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vq1r74/how_can_i_make_my_laptop_keyboard_work_for/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-02T21:32:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello Archers,
 I've just gotten up and running with my first ever Arch install, on my laptop, and almost everything is working great. 
 The one snag is: I've encrypted the hard drive using [https://wiki.archlinux.org/title/Dm-crypt/Encrypting_an_entire_system#LVM_on_LUKS](LVM on LUKS). At boot, I'm prompted to type the encryption passphrase. With a USB keyboard, I can type it in no problem. But during boot my laptop's built-in keyboard is non-functional - no keystrokes register at all, it's as though it's disconnected - so I have no way of booting without a USB keyboard attached. 
 The keyboard itself is physically fine, and works perfectly in the bootloader and in the DE. 
 /etc/mkinitcpio.conf:
 MODULES=(usbhid xhci_hcd i915) HOOKS=(base udev keyboard keymap numlock autodetect modconf b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PC recognizes live USB only after switching Secure Boot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vq1r3l/pc_recognizes_live_usb_only_after_switching/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vq1r3l/pc_recognizes_live_usb_only_after_switching/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-02T21:32:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I don't think the issue is in the arch itself, but as the thing happened while I was trying to install arch, I decided to write here.
 So, I have been trying to install Arch from a USB drive and PC just doesn't see the USB until I switch Secure Boot mode to either on of off. Then the system boots up normally (of course, if I turned SB back off after that), but if I reboot, it happens again.
 I made the installation medium using Rufus, installation is in UEFI mode.
 Laptop: Lenovo Ideapad Gaming 3 15IMH05 
    submitted by    /u/elpsykongaroo  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does Your Smartphone Really Need a Screen Protector?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.howtogeek.com/?p=190107</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/190107/does-your-smartphone-really-need-a-screen-protector/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-02T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smartphones are expensive — you wouldn’t want to spend up to $1,000 or more and end up with a scratched screen. Many people still buy screen protectors to protect their purchase, but are they still necessary with modern display advancements?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What We're Playing: 'Backbone' Is a Neat Noir Adventure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/121849/what-were-playing-backbone-is-a-neat-noir-adventure/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/121849/what-were-playing-backbone-is-a-neat-noir-adventure/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-02T20:04:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re at all interested in solving mysteries or exploring a post-noir, dystopian world, you’ll love playing Backbone. It has elements of a visual novel, but you actually move around the world and have to interact with things and solve puzzles to progress the story.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Chaney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s the Best Way to Save Money on Streaming in 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=799173</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/799173/heres-the-best-way-to-save-money-on-streaming-in-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-02T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Saving money is always a great idea, but with inflation eating into everything and streaming service price hikes, cutting streaming expenses feels particularly important. Here’s how to save money while still enjoying your favorite streaming services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Fitzpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up an iPad or iPhone for Seniors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=247380</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/8275897/iphone-accessibility-hacks"/>
        <updated>2022-07-02T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s no denying we all love our electronic devices these days. In fact, even seniors enjoy using iPads and iPhones to FaceTime with loved ones or entertain themselves. But, as people age, these devices may not be fully accessible to them fresh out of the box. Enter Apple’s inbuilt accessibility settings – the best way to set up an iOS device for seniors to help them use an iPad or an iPhone more simply. Let’s see how to configure these devices for ease of access.
    
Note: Most of the suggestions listed below can be accessed from “Settings -> Accessibility.”
   

Content

1. Increase Icon Size
2. Adjust Font Size and Boldness
3. Enable Zoom and Magnify
4. Increase Screen Contrast
5. Enable Voice Commands
6. Turn on Subtitles and Captioning
7. Adjust Hearing Settings
8. Turn On Assistive Touch
9. Turn On Touch Accommodations
10. Enable Guided Access
11. Set Up Shortcuts
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Megan Glosson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to reduce Home partition size and increase root partition?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vpytnx/how_to_reduce_home_partition_size_and_increase/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vpytnx/how_to_reduce_home_partition_size_and_increase/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-02T19:09:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have recently switched to Arch and out of my 2TB HDD i want to allocate 50 or 100GB to Root partition by reducing the Home partition. Can someone suggest me how to do that ? in google search i found ways to extend the partition with free space already existing, I want help in creating the free space from Home partition and then extending / partition with fdisk. Or is it better to have same partition for both root & home? if yes, how to merge both the partitions?
 ​
 sda 8:0 0 1.8T 0 disk 
 ├─sda1 8:1 0 511M 0 part /boot
 ├─sda2 8:2 0 19.5G 0 part /
 └─sda3 8:3 0 1.8T 0 part /home
    submitted by    /u/adarigirishkumar  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Send Videos on Discord]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809676</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809676/how-to-send-videos-on-discord/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-02T19:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have a cool video that you’d like to share with your friends on Discord? If so, the platform makes it easy to share your video content in both channels and direct messages. We’ll show you how to do that on Discord on both desktop and mobile.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Different RAM capacity reported on two machines with same amount of RAM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vpyjiv/different_ram_capacity_reported_on_two_machines/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vpyjiv/different_ram_capacity_reported_on_two_machines/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-02T18:56:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone,
 on my desktop system, the total ram size is reported as 32021 (free -m), whereas on my laptop, it is reported as 27893 with the same command.
 This puzzles me, as both systems have 2 16GB RAM sticks installed, so to my understanding free -m should show the same (or at least very similar) total capacity.
 Any idea why this happens, and how to fix it?
 (Both systems were installed using the same install script, both run the same software, nothing has been changed in terms of memory, both systems are up to date)
    submitted by    /u/XyZaaH  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anyone Notice Problems with Proton Since Latest Update?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vpy5vv/anyone_notice_problems_with_proton_since_latest/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vpy5vv/anyone_notice_problems_with_proton_since_latest/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-02T18:37:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I did an update this morning and found that all proton games would crash afterwards.
 I couldn't pin down exactly what the problem is but it appears that all proton versions, experimental and otherwise would cause directx errors. This was with forcing radv and regular radeon drivers. 
 I ended up restoring from a timeshift backup for now as I didn't have a lot of time to crawl through journalctl.
    submitted by    /u/jdfthetech  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How does kernel deal with multiple 'initrd=' boot parameters?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vpxx68/how_does_kernel_deal_with_multiple_initrd_boot/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vpxx68/how_does_kernel_deal_with_multiple_initrd_boot/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-02T18:25:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[microcode and DSDT are examples where an extra initramfs file is inserted before the regular one (generated by mkinitcpio). So how does kernel deal with those?
 I know for the regular one, such as \initramfs-linux.img, kernel would mount it to / and execute the /init file. But if there are more than one initrd= params, does boot loader load all of them in one shot to some memory area and kernel process them one by one according to some rules? Does kernel unmount/delete the first one before mounting the next one to /? For example, if I insert an intel-ucode.img in front of initramfs-linux.img, does kernel also mount it at /? what happens afterwards then since there is no /init file in the ucode image, so how does kernel know what to do with it? and how does kernel know it needs to load the next initramfs file which is initramfs-linux.img?
 I tried adding debug boot parameter, but still didn't see any log file under /run/initramfs/, what did I miss?
    submitted by    /u/notnullnone  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Reset All Settings on iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=812275</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/812275/reset-all-settings-iphone/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-02T18:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you customized too many setting options on your iPhone and now want to start from scratch? If so, your iPhone makes it easy to bring all your settings to their factory values. We’ll show you how to do just that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sony Announces New "InZone" Gaming Monitors and Headsets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/122258/sony-announces-new-inzone-gaming-monitors-and-headsets/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/122258/sony-announces-new-inzone-gaming-monitors-and-headsets/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-02T18:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want a bunch of PS5-themed hardware, prepare to get in the zone. Sony is about to launch a new gaming brand called InZone with a focus on monitors and headsets. Interestingly, these products work with both PlayStation and PC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alacritty not applying opacity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vpx4ao/alacritty_not_applying_opacity/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vpx4ao/alacritty_not_applying_opacity/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-02T17:47:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, I'm farily new to arch and I'm trying it out on VirtualBox before using it on my actual PC.
 Right now I have qtile installed as a window manager, and I'm using picom as a compositor. My problem is that when changing my shell fomr bash to zsh (or any other, like fish), the opacity in my terminal (alacritty) just stops working.
 I Have no idea what the problem could be, since by using bash and picom it works just fine. Also alacritty itself does not change its background opacity when I set it inside the configuration file, but only if I have picom running.
 Any help?
    submitted by    /u/_shunpo_  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Darktable 4.0 Released With Rewritten UI, Much Improved OpenCL Performance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Darktable-4.0-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Darktable-4.0-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-07-02T17:15:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Darktable 4.0 has debuted today as a major update to this open-source, cross-platform RAW photography software suite...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to See EXIF Metadata in Photos on iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=811214</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/811214/how-to-see-exif-metadata-in-photos-on-iphone/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-02T17:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every photo you take on your iPhone includes EXIF metadata, which records information about how, when, and where you took the photo. Previously, you needed a special utility to see EXIF metadata on iPhone, but with iOS 15 and up, you can see it directly in the Photos app. Here’s how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supercharge Your Tesla for Free During Off-Peak Hours This Holiday Weekend]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/122245/supercharge-your-tesla-for-free-during-off-peak-hours-this-holiday-weekend/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/122245/supercharge-your-tesla-for-free-during-off-peak-hours-this-holiday-weekend/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-02T16:34:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the long 4th of July weekend, Tesla will offer free Supercharging in select regions for customers during off-peak hours. This is likely a move to help limit traffic and lines at popular charging stations during one of the year’s busiest travel days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia + XWayland = stutter?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vpvdwk/nvidia_xwayland_stutter/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vpvdwk/nvidia_xwayland_stutter/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-02T16:23:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, few weeks ago, I switched to using Wayland. Setup was quite easy following the wiki. However, when I try to run XWayland applications (wine/proton games in my case), I get massive stuttering - especially when moving camera or when character are moving in the scene. The weird thing is, there was originally no such problem and this seems to only start last week. I went through the wiki again, reinstalling what was needed, but without any luck. I am running Gnome, but had the same problem when I switched to KDE on Wayland. 
 I also saw wiki mentioning EGLStreams vs GBM buffer APIs, but I not sure what to make of it as this only occurs in XWayland applications - native games that are not running through wine work flawlessly.
 Am I missing something or do others have the same problem?
    submitted by    /u/citizen_418  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Remove Google TV Profiles]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=813849</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/813849/how-to-remove-google-tv-profiles/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-02T16:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[User profiles are a great way to give everyone in your house their own personal place on Google TV. It’s easy to add user profiles, but what about removing them? We’ll show you how it’s done.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Safe to remove old kernel modules?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vpusa4/safe_to_remove_old_kernel_modules/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vpusa4/safe_to_remove_old_kernel_modules/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-02T15:56:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey all, I recently noticed every time a dkms module needed to be updated it was installing into a whole bunch of old kernels. I went to look into /lib/modules and found that it was over 5GB in size and full of old kernel modules. Are these safe to delete?
 lsing the directory:
 drwxr-xr-x 3 root root 4.0K Jun 17 2021 5.12.10-arch1-1 drwxr-xr-x 3 root root 4.0K Jun 20 2021 5.12.11-arch1-1 drwxr-xr-x 3 root root 4.0K Jun 27 2021 5.12.12-arch1-1 drwxr-xr-x 3 root root 4.0K May 18 2021 5.12.3-arch1-1 drwxr-xr-x 3 root root 4.0K May 20 2021 5.12.4-arch1-2 drwxr-xr-x 3 root root 4.0K May 25 2021 5.12.5-arch1-1 drwxr-xr-x 3 root root 4.0K May 28 2021 5.12.6-arch1-1 drwxr-xr-x 3 root root 4.0K May 31 2021 5.12.7-arch1-1 drwxr-xr-x 3 root root 4.0K Jun 4 2021 5.12.8-arch1-1 drwxr-xr-x 3 root root 4.0K Jun 14 2021 5.12.9-arch1-1 drwxr-xr-x 5 root root 4.0K Sep 10 2021 5.13.13-arch1-1 drwxr-xr-x 3 root root 4.0K Jan 17 10:15 5.16.0-arch1-1 drwxr-xr-x 3 root root 4.0K Jan 17 10:15 5.16.0-zen1-1-zen drwxr-xr-x 5 root root 4.0K Jul 2 16:43 5.17.5-arch1-2 drwxr-xr-x 5 root root 4.0K Jul 2 16:43 5.17.6-arch1-1 drwxr-xr-x 5 root root 4.0K Jul 2 16:43 5.17.7-arch1-1 drwxr-xr-x 5 root root 4.0K Jul 2 16:43 5.17.7-arch1-2 drwxr-xr-x 5 root root 4.0K Jul 2 16:42 5.17.8-arch1-1 drwxr-xr-x 5 root root 4.0K Jul 2 16:43 5.17.9-arch1-1 drwxr-xr-x 5 root root 4.0K Jul 2 16:42 5.18.0-arch1-1 drwxr-xr-x 5 root root 4.0K Jul 2 16:42 5.18.1-arch1-1 drwxr-xr-x 5 root root 4.0K Jul 2 16:43 5.18.2-arch1-1 drwxr-xr-x 5 root root 4.0K Jul 2 16:42 5.18.3-arch1-1 drwxr-xr-x 5 root root 4.0K Jul 2 16:43 5.18.5-arch1-1 drwxr-xr-x 5 root root 4.0K Jul 2 16:42 5.18.6-arch1-1 drwxr-xr-x 5 root root 4.0K Jul 2 16:42 5.18.7-arch1-1 drwxr-xr-x 5 root root 4.0K Jul 2 16:43 5.18.8-arch1-1 drwxr-xr-x 5 root root 4.0K Jul 2 16:43 5.18.8-zen1-1-zen 
 This is 100% due to the kernel-modules-hook package I had installed which I've since removed
    submitted by    /u/big_Gorb  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[wlan0 powered off]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vpugvs/wlan0_powered_off/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vpugvs/wlan0_powered_off/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-02T15:41:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey, I'm trying to connect to my wifi on the arch installation but when i: device list, it shows that wlan0 is powered off. Like:
 Name address powered adapter mode Wlan0 mac addr off phy0 station
 When I: station wlan0 scan, it says; No station on device: 'wlan0
 Can I get help?
    submitted by    /u/Hen0r  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rogue HackerOne employee steals bug reports to sell on the side]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/rogue-hackerone-employee-steals-bug-reports-to-sell-on-the-side/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/rogue-hackerone-employee-steals-bug-reports-to-sell-on-the-side/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-02T15:36:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A HackerOne employee stole vulnerability reports submitted through the bug bounty platform and disclosed them to affected customers to claim financial rewards. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Ilascu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Verified Twitter accounts hacked to send fake suspension notices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/verified-twitter-accounts-hacked-to-send-fake-suspension-notices/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/verified-twitter-accounts-hacked-to-send-fake-suspension-notices/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-02T15:12:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Parallel Downloads]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vpts3i/parallel_downloads/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vpts3i/parallel_downloads/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-02T15:07:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is there a way to color code the completed or downloading (Doesn't really matter) files? I have ParellelDownloads set to 8 and it's difficult to keep track of what's been downloaded and what's downloading on a large screen. Mostly for aesthetics really.
    submitted by    /u/Phydoux  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Check the UV Index]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=731035</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/731035/how-to-check-the-uv-index/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-02T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s nothing like a beautiful sunny day, but it can end in itchy pain if you’re not careful. Using sunscreen and knowing when the sun is harshest can help with that. The UV Index makes that easier to understand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GUI elements of some applications are not positioned properly]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vpsv5f/gui_elements_of_some_applications_are_not/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vpsv5f/gui_elements_of_some_applications_are_not/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-02T14:22:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are few applications like vlc, VirtualBox, etc. that have their GUI elements somewhat not positioned properly. The screenshots below will explain what I mean. This wasn't a problem before reinstalling my arch linux.
 https://ibb.co/QCnV3Kd
 It looks the same even on full screen
    submitted by    /u/Wonderful-Conflict-3  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>