<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-06-20T01:58:59.066Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.0</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Failed to start Load Kernel Modules and Failed to start Wireless Service]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vg9x9s/failed_to_start_load_kernel_modules_and_failed_to/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vg9x9s/failed_to_start_load_kernel_modules_and_failed_to/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-20T01:39:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently installed Arch, but I noticed that I was unable to see any wireless access points with iwctl. Someone suggested that I may need linux-firmware, so I used my installation medium and arch-chroot to grab it. I also did a pacman -Syu. Now, when I try to boot into the OS after decrypting my partition, I see [FAILED] Failed to start Load Kernel Modules. and several instances of [FAILED] Failed to start Wireless services. before proceeding to the login screen. I can still login, but when I tried to launch iwctl, I got stuck on "waiting for IWD to respond," so clearly I broke something.
 I did some googling, and it seems that this can be caused by an unmounted /boot, but if I am understanding the output of lsblk -f correctly, then mine is mounted. I could also see /boot in my fstab (I should maybe mention, however, that it is on a different partition).
 My googling also revealed that not having mounted boot while in chroot and then updating the system may have caused the issue. I tried reinstalling linux after making sure to mount boot while in chroot but that didn't help. I also tried running mkinitcpio -p linux in arch-chroot, but that didn't help either unfortunately.
 Any idea what I can try next?
    submitted by    /u/networks_dumbass  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating an Arch Linux ARM QEMU VM on a Mac M1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vg8n8c/creating_an_arch_linux_arm_qemu_vm_on_a_mac_m1/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vg8n8c/creating_an_arch_linux_arm_qemu_vm_on_a_mac_m1/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-20T00:27:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I created a simple self-contained script that does the following basic steps:
  
Download an EFI BIOS
 Download an Arch Linux ARM bootable ISO image
 Create a raw data image with a FAT filesystem that contains some scripts to use on first boot, and an empty raw Linux image
 Boot up ISO image
 User runs a command to mount and execute a setup script
 Setup script partitions the empty raw Linux image, downloads and extracts a base Arch Linux ARM image into it, and shuts down
 Host script converts the raw Linux image into a compressed sparse qcow2 image
 Creates an ArchLinux.app bundle that can be double clicked in the Finder or added to the Dock to run the VM
  
There were a few bits that were a little tricky to figure out:
  
Due to differences between x86 and arm boot processes, a bootable …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to update the standard repos and AUR with one command and once entering sudo password?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vg8az2/how_to_update_the_standard_repos_and_aur_with_one/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vg8az2/how_to_update_the_standard_repos_and_aur_with_one/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-20T00:07:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I wrote this little thing to update. The only problem is that I have few AUR packages installed that have to be built from source and that takes time. So when paru asks me for my sudo password, it updates the standard packages and then the AUR and asks for a sudo password again. And usually I let the update run on my computer and leave the room and do something else and come back to it seeing it did compile the AUR packages, but didn't install them because the sudo password prompt timed out.
 I thought sudo suing to the root user and then running paru, but paru prevents installing AUR packages as root.
 Any ideas?
 #!/bin/bash source /home/spikeyamk/git-repos/scripts/sel_cpu_gov.sh function update() { if [ "$(whereis emerge)" != "emerge:" ] then ( echo 3; ) | gov sudo emerge --sync sudo emerge --ask -uDU --keep-going --with-bdeps=y @world elif [ "$(whereis paru)" != "paru:" ] then paru -Syyu --noconfirm --skipreview elif [ "$(whereis apt)" != "apt:" ] then sudo apt update sudo apt upgrade fi if [ "$(whereis flatpak)" != "flatpak:" ] then flatpak update fi } 
    submitted by    /u/Empty_Issue_3569  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linus Torvalds Releases Linux 5.19-rc3 Father's Day Kernel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-rc3</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-rc3"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T22:03:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linus Torvalds spent some of Father's Day today merging last minute pull requests for the week and issuing Linux 5.19-rc3 as the newest weekly test kernel...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch Linux on an old MacBook - Legacy BIOS or UEFI?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vg5tbi/arch_linux_on_an_old_macbook_legacy_bios_or_uefi/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vg5tbi/arch_linux_on_an_old_macbook_legacy_bios_or_uefi/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T22:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m preparing to install Arch on my old MacBook from 2008 (Core 2 Duo and NVIDIA 9600M GT) because the newest OS X it supports is super outdated, and windows 10 runs like ass, but I’m not sure which install mode to use. I know that Windows won’t even install in UEFI mode and it defaults to a “hybrid MBR”, but OS X runs in UEFI mode so I’m not sure what the right choice is. Do I install in BIOS mode (i386-pc) or UEFI mode (x86_64-efi)?
    submitted by    /u/FF13_IS_BEST  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come togliere gli articoli consigliati dal menu start di Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>3594|20220620000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/windows-10/come-togliere-articoli-consigliati-menu-start-windows-11-3594"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Una delle parti che meno comprendo nel menu Start di Windows 11 sono gli Articoli Consigliati, una lista di elementi aperti di recente che si può svuotare ma non eliminare così da recuperare lo spazio per avere un menu Start più ampio.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung’s Android Browser Is Great, Actually]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=790140</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/790140/samsungs-android-browser-is-great-actually/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s a stigma attached to apps from phone manufacturers. They tend to feel like unnecessary bloatware. However, Samsung Internet—the company’s blandly named browser—is an exception. It’s actually quite good, and it’s not only for Samsung Galaxy phones.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iwd being weird? I type iwctl, and it says "NetworkConfigurationEnabled: Disabled"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vg4h09/iwd_being_weird_i_type_iwctl_and_it_says/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vg4h09/iwd_being_weird_i_type_iwctl_and_it_says/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T20:56:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I also tried to connect to my wifi, and it brought up the prompt to put in the password, and seemingly let me connect, but then when I tried to ping it didn't work.
 Edit: I rebooted, and now it just is doing the thing where it doesn't start.
 Edit2: I'm too tired for this, I'll deal with this in the morning. 
    submitted by    /u/DqrkAngel42  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FDA Approves Parkinson's Symptom Tracker for Apple Watch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/121244/fda-approves-parkinsons-symptom-tracker-for-apple-watch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/121244/fda-approves-parkinsons-symptom-tracker-for-apple-watch/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T20:04:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The United States Food and Drug Administration just cleared StrivePD, an app that tracks and detects Parkinson’s symptoms using Apple’s Movement Disorder API. Rune Labs, the company behind this app, hopes that it will accelerate Parkinson’s research and improve the lives of patients.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Change Mouse Sensitivity on Windows 10 or 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=786909</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/786909/how-to-change-mouse-sensitivity-on-windows-10-or-11/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bad sensitivity settings can be frustrating — a mouse that is not sensitive enough might require you to pick it up repeatedly just to get across the screen. A mouse that is too sensitive might make it difficult to click accurately. Here’s how to change it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Lewis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Disk decryption screen on boot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vg2msv/disk_decryption_screen_on_boot/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vg2msv/disk_decryption_screen_on_boot/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T19:29:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I know its possible but I dont know how to do it. I have arch laptop with full screen encryption. I want to have GUI screen for decrypting screen on boot. Like this for grub.
    submitted by    /u/LinuxHeki  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set a Timer on Your iPhone Camera]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=416435</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/14670063/set-timer-on-iphone-camera"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With each new year, Apple’s iPhone receives photography updates in the form of either software or hardware enhancements. A couple of years ago, that was the ability to use a timer, perfect for taking photos and videos hands-free. While this feature exists in the Apple Camera app, it is somewhat hidden. Follow these steps to find and use your iPhone’s camera timer.
   
Also read:How to Crop or Trim a Video on Android and iPhone
    
How to Access and Use iPhone’s Camera Timer 
    
The timer feature in the iPhone’s Camera app not only lets you set a countdown to take pictures but it also enables Burst mode automatically. So whenever you set a timer, Burst mode is activated and it captures 10 photos instead of one. You can keep all the 10 photos or select the best of them and delete the rest. Sadly, there is no way to stop iPhone... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mehvish Mushtaq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add a YouTube Video to Google Slides]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=808493</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/808493/how-to-add-a-youtube-video-to-google-slides/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T19:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to spice up your Google Slides presentation by including a YouTube video in it? If so, use Slides’ built-in feature to embed your YouTube videos with customizable options. We’ll show you how to do just that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harley-Davidson Announced an Actual Electric Mountain Bike This Time]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/121238/harley-davidson-announced-an-actual-electric-mountain-bike-this-time/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/121238/harley-davidson-announced-an-actual-electric-mountain-bike-this-time/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T18:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Harley-Davidson’s Serial 1 brand recently unveiled its second mountain e-bike, and this time it actually has suspension. The brand’s first electric mountain bike didn’t, which was rather odd.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Restart Discord]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=807611</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/807611/how-to-restart-discord/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T18:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Restarting Discord isn’t as straightforward as restarting any other app. This is because Discord continues to run in the background even if you’ve closed it. In this guide, we’ll show you how to properly restart Discord on your Windows, Mac, iPhone, iPad, and Android devices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Chrome extensions can be fingerprinted to track you online]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/google-chrome-extensions-can-be-fingerprinted-to-track-you-online/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/google-chrome-extensions-can-be-fingerprinted-to-track-you-online/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T17:59:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A researcher has discovered how to use your installed Google Chrome extensions to generate a fingerprint of your device that can be used to track you online. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qt5 regression prevents KDE plasma from launching]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vfzsth/qt5_regression_prevents_kde_plasma_from_launching/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vfzsth/qt5_regression_prevents_kde_plasma_from_launching/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T17:12:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For reference I use the alhp repos, so it might be unique to them. I launch plasma from tty with the command startplasma-wayland. Today after an upgrade I tried to launch plasma and it hung for a few seconds then crashed. A quick look at recently installed packages led me to the line upgraded qt5-base (5.15.4+kde+r168-1.1 -> 5.15.5+kde+r162-1.1). Downloading and installing qt5-base-5.15.4+kde+r168-1-x86_64.pkg.tar.zst got plasma working again. Hope this helps people.
    submitted by    /u/TheGingerLinuxNut  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Update Apps on Your Amazon Fire TV Stick]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=806591</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/806591/how-to-update-apps-on-firestick/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T17:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you update your official and sideloaded apps on your Amazon Fire TV Stick, you get access to the latest features and bug fixes for those apps. It’s easy to update both kinds of apps, and we’ll show you how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photoshop Can Instantly Make Your Old Family Photos Look New Again]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/121222/photoshop-can-instantly-make-your-old-family-photos-look-new-again/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/121222/photoshop-can-instantly-make-your-old-family-photos-look-new-again/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T16:34:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you have a bunch of old family photos that have been marred by the ravages of time, fixing them in photoshop probably sounds like an ideal solution. But while it’s doable, the process is tedious and difficult. That is until Photoshop’s new neural filter arrives that does the job in a single click.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Hendrickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[System76_power AUR, renders laptop screen useless]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vfypvf/system76_power_aur_renders_laptop_screen_useless/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vfypvf/system76_power_aur_renders_laptop_screen_useless/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T16:20:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I started using Linux around 2 weeks ago, I am trying distros different DE to know which one I like. Right now I installed Arch with KDE using archinstall. I liked the Pop!_Os switch between integrated and dedicated GPU, so searching I got https://wiki.archlinux.org/title/Hybrid_graphics and I installed the System76_power using paru and ran sudo system76-power graphics nvidia, it told me to reboot and I did and then my laptop boots but the screen doesn't turn on or renders anything for login screen(SDDM) where I input my password, I know my laptop is working because I can type my password and login, the splash screen appears, with no spinning animation and I am thrown into desktop with a black screen. Pressed ctrl+alt+tab and ran the command sudo system76-power graphics integrated, and then waiting a little while and rebooted and the screen work. Is there something I can do about this?
 Thanks for any help in advance.
    submitted by    /u/MConanE  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dual-Drive Boot Menu]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vfyn1m/dualdrive_boot_menu/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vfyn1m/dualdrive_boot_menu/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T16:16:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have Windows on one drive and am going to install archlinux on the second one, can I make it so I dont have to go through the F8 BIOS boot menu and pick from the 2 drives from GRUB?
    submitted by    /u/Apollo672  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Headset Microphones vs. Standalone: Which Is Better?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=804075</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/804075/headset-microphone-vs-standalone/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T16:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for a new microphone that actually sounds good? You can either go with a headset or a standalone mic, but which is better? Let’s compare the two to see which you might prefer more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Nguyen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I did a full upgrade like usual and suddenly I have a ZSTD error, ELF header missing. It does not boot.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vfxzrk/i_did_a_full_upgrade_like_usual_and_suddenly_i/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vfxzrk/i_did_a_full_upgrade_like_usual_and_suddenly_i/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T15:46:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I guess I'll have to chroot it and try to fix it... but the question is... how did this happen??? I did nothing weird.
    submitted by    /u/anotheruser123123  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I'm running Arch with Gnome 42.2 on a Microsoft Surface Go 3, and am encountering a device in power settings that's constantly showing 0-1% battery. I'm trying to figure out how to disable it/stop showing me power warnings, but am not having any luck]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vfxskk/im_running_arch_with_gnome_422_on_a_microsoft/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vfxskk/im_running_arch_with_gnome_422_on_a_microsoft/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T15:36:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[the device
 And this is its upower entry:
 Device: /org/freedesktop/UPower/devices/battery_hid_0018o04F3o2A1Cx0009_battery native-path: hid-0018:04F3:2A1C.0009-battery model: ELAN9038:00 04F3:2A1C power supply: no updated: Sun Jun 18 07:34:33 2022 (21 seconds ago) has history: yes has statistics: yes keyboard present: yes rechargeable: yes state: discharging warning-level: critical percentage: 1% icon-name: 'battery-caution-symbolic' 
 Have any of you happened to encounter this issue before?
    submitted by    /u/Memekip  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GhostBSD 22.06.15 Brings Improved NVIDIA Driver Handling, Better Broadcom WiFi Detection]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=GhostBSD-22.06.15-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=GhostBSD-22.06.15-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T15:32:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Out this weekend is a new version of GhostBSD, the desktop-focused operating system built atop a FreeBSD base and catering to the MATE desktop environment...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do You Need a Senior Cell Phone Plan for Your Loved One?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=804471</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/804471/do-you-need-a-senior-cell-phone-plan-for-your-loved-one/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T15:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cell phone plans come in all shapes and sizes nowadays, and there’s a surprisingly robust selection that caters directly to seniors. Here’s everything you need to know about senior cell phone plans before signing up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Bitner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can't find bootable usb stick in filesystem]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vfw4gc/cant_find_bootable_usb_stick_in_filesystem/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vfw4gc/cant_find_bootable_usb_stick_in_filesystem/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T14:15:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have a bootable usb stick with an old arch iso installed and I'm trying to wipe all the data and install the newer one. The problem is that every os that I've tried (linux and windows) doesn't recognize the usb stick as a memory device. Any idea how can I fix that?
 (I've tried to run lsblk or fdisk -l but the usb stick doesn't show up)
    submitted by    /u/ArturoIlPaguro  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Android-wiping BRATA malware is evolving into a persistent threat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/android-wiping-brata-malware-is-evolving-into-a-persistent-threat/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/android-wiping-brata-malware-is-evolving-into-a-persistent-threat/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T14:15:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat actors operating the BRATA banking trojan have evolved their tactics and incorporated new information-stealing features into their malware. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best iPads of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=734086</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/734086/best-ipads-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Buying an iPad was a lot easier when Apple only made one tablet, but now you have many options. Fortunately, with our recommendations, you can get the features you want without spending more than you need to.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Watch Stuck on the Apple Logo? Try These Fixes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=810851</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/810851/apple-watch-stuck-on-apple-logo/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T13:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If your Apple Watch won’t show anything but the Apple logo, it’s probably stuck in a boot loop and can’t start up properly. Though we can’t guarantee success, there are a few things you can try to rescue your Apple Watch when you’re in this situation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is there a way to prevent an application from inhibiting the screensaver?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vfunkr/is_there_a_way_to_prevent_an_application_from/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vfunkr/is_there_a_way_to_prevent_an_application_from/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T12:58:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For a couple of weeks now, chrome has been preventing my screensaver from triggering. No video or audio playing (AFAICT). Is there a general solution for controlling what an application can do wrt the screensaver?
 I'm using i3, xss-lock, no DE...basically just terminals and X
    submitted by    /u/whereiat  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mount dm-crypt crypted drive on another machine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vfu6x7/mount_dmcrypt_crypted_drive_on_another_machine/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vfu6x7/mount_dmcrypt_crypted_drive_on_another_machine/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T12:32:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[hello guys,
 I've got a brand new laptop and would like to move there with a very new installation of arch. I have only one issue, that I can't handle:
 In my current setup I have an SSD drive for the OS related partitions, and an internal HDD for private data which is mounted on boot under my home folder. This is encrypted and store all my private data. I've used dm-crypt to encrypt the drive, and I've chosen to manually write the passphrase on every boot instead of the private key solution. Of course I'd like to move this HDD to my new laptop too.
 My question is that is there any documentation where can I find about how can I migrate an encrypted HDD to another setup? the dm-crypt documentation is not containing this topic on the arch wiki.
 Thanks a lot in advance
    submitted by    /u/montyx99  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gli Smartphone con fotocamera migliore del momento]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2017/12/smartphone-con-fotocamera-migliore.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2017/12/smartphone-con-fotocamera-migliore.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T12:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Il metodo più utilizzato per scattare foto ai giorni nostri è sicuramente lo smartphone, anche grazie alla semplicità d'uso, alla facilità con cui è possibile condividere le foto scattate sui social e ai numerosi filtri ed effetti disponibili per rendere ogni scatto unico nel suo genere.

 Però scattare foto con un qualsiasi smartphone in commercio è ben diverso dallo scattare foto con uno...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is mAh, and How Does It Affect Batteries and Chargers?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=804692</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/804692/what-is-mah/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T12:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you’re shopping for a phone or a portable charger, you’re sure to run into the term milliamp hours or the abbreviation mAh. Unsure of what this means? It’s a simple concept, and figuring out what you need is relatively easy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kris Wouk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Running Arch as a headless remote desktop]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vft3ys/running_arch_as_a_headless_remote_desktop/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vft3ys/running_arch_as_a_headless_remote_desktop/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T11:25:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So I'm trying to setup use my system as a VNC server so I can access it through the internet. I tried setting up tigervnc as per the Arch Wiki and cannot get it to work. I know I can access the system because I can connect to it via ssh. I've tried using ssh tunneling (with and without the localhost variable in .vnc/config) and directly through a VNC specific port which I checked with ss is listening. I've also enabled vncserver@:port.service with systemd
 When I try to connect from another system the error I get is "unable to connect to the socket: Connection refused (111)"
 Am I missing some obvious configuration? Do you guys use another solution/program?
 Any advice would be greatly appreciated :)
    submitted by    /u/jtavizon  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Does “Bop” Mean on the Internet?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=808117</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/808117/what-does-bop-mean/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T11:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Has someone on the internet asked you to recommend a good bop? Get your playlists ready! Here’s what this fun, music-related slang term means and how to use it online.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vann Vicente</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EPEL Statistics Show Recent Surge In Rocky Linux Usage Past AlmaLinux, CentOS Stream]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=EPEL-Stats-Rocky-Linux-Surge</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=EPEL-Stats-Rocky-Linux-Surge"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T10:48:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Statistics published by Fedora for the Extra Packages for Enterprise Linux (EPEL) usage point to a recent surge in Rocky Linux usage -- at least for those with EPEL enabled -- and at least recently appears to surpass the usage for the likes of CentOS Stream, AlmaLinux, and even the RHEL usage with EPEL enabled...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Italia paese di pirati informatici? Si, ma di improvvisati]]></title>
        <id>3600|20220619121954</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/servizi-web-24/italia-paese-pirati-informatici-si-improvvisati-3600"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T10:19:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Un sondaggio di time2play.com condotto su 1.120 italiani di età compresa tra i 18 e i 33 anni rivela che il 63% degli intervistati abbia ammesso di aver visto serie tv e film in maniera illegale. Un danno per l'industria dei contenuti o forse si tratta di forme di ripiego? Vediamo assieme perchè.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rapid7 research reveals which data ransomware groups seek and use for leverage]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179242</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/19/rapid7-research-reveals-which-data-ransomware-groups-seek-and-use-for-leverage/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T10:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to ransomware attacks, some data is more precious to ransomware groups as others. A new research study by Rapid7, Pain Points: Ransomware Data Disclosure Trends, provides insight on the […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Rapid7 research reveals which data ransomware groups seek and use for leverage appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EXT4 Has A Nice One-Line Performance Fix For Cases When Delayed Allocation Is Disabled]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=EXT4-No-Delalloc-Perf-Fix</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=EXT4-No-Delalloc-Perf-Fix"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T10:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When an EXT4 file-system is running low on free space (or when toggled via the "nodelalloc" mount option), EXT4's delayed allocation mode can be disabled. This can result in a significant performance hit but now a patch is pending for what should land in Linux 5.20 with recovering that performance when delayed allocation is disabled...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for - Bluetooth Dongle - That works]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vfrrss/looking_for_bluetooth_dongle_that_works/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vfrrss/looking_for_bluetooth_dongle_that_works/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T09:53:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey, 
 anyone have a bluetooth dongle that works with the newest Kernel?
 If you could also comment the drivers that would be much appreciated <3
    submitted by    /u/SomeGirlWhoIsABoy  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git 2.37-rc1 Released With "git -v" & "git -h" Convenient Options]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Git-2.37-rc1-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Git-2.37-rc1-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T09:42:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following an initial rc0 tag earlier in the week, Git 2.37-rc1 was released on Friday for helping to facilitate testing for the next version of this leading, open-source distributed revision control system...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lightdm won't start after installing Nvidia Drivers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vfrfxu/lightdm_wont_start_after_installing_nvidia_drivers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vfrfxu/lightdm_wont_start_after_installing_nvidia_drivers/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T09:27:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I finished setting up my system and wanted to install the nvidia drivers. Now after rebooting lightdm will not start and Im stuck on the tty. Tried with systemctl start lightdm and just lightdm but none work.
 Using an rtx 3070ti with bspwm
    submitted by    /u/Mike11207  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux KMS setup]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vfqz4l/linux_kms_setup/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vfqz4l/linux_kms_setup/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T08:52:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone. I just installed Arch on a x86_64 CPU board, which has a LVDS display flat connector output (that i don't use).
 I connected it to my monitor using HDMI connector output, and it works fine, except for the boot sequence.
 When the system boots, i can see grub loader screen on hdmi (because it uses uefi frame buffers i guess) and then, when it switches to KMS (Intel graphics driver requires this) i cannot se any plymouth screen, and after boot, it shows a completely gray screen. It keeps showing that forever, and i have to press 'enter' key (blindly) to login and see the desktop environment. I use GNOME, and in the settings, it's like the flat LVDS connector is plugged in (i see a second monitor connected). Once logged in, X loads the right screen configuration and everything works like it should. I believe that everything works just fine, except for the fact that it shows the login (and plymouth graphics) on thr LVDS panel. I have no LVDS to prove this, but i am 85% sure about that.
 I installed intel graphics driver, mesa and lib32-mesa libraries. I early-loaded i915 driver putting MODULES=(i915) in the /etc/mkinitcpio.conf file and rebuilding initramfs images. I tried to switch off LVDS in bios but the bios is very minimal and i don't see any setting for that.
 It seems to be a KMS setting or graphic driver setting.
 Is anyone here more experienced with intel drivers? Where may i find drivers parameters that i can use to disconnect that unused display?
 Thanks!
    submitted by    /u/nemis16  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[laptop mode tools]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vfqsbk/laptop_mode_tools/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vfqsbk/laptop_mode_tools/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T08:38:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi:)
 I have recently installed laptop mode tools, But I don't understand what it actually do. I have read arch wiki.
 Is it something like tlp or power-profile-deamon ? If yes which one should i use?
 does it have any conflicts with them?
 And also can it cause any physical damage to hardware? For example spinning down hdd so much or ... .
 Thanks :)
    submitted by    /u/Sepehr_TH  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch Linux on a 2012 iMac, xorg won't work]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vfqkv9/arch_linux_on_a_2012_imac_xorg_wont_work/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vfqkv9/arch_linux_on_a_2012_imac_xorg_wont_work/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T08:22:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I just got a iMac to use as a small TV / Media center, and wanted to install Arch on it. The installer booted to a black screen. i read online that I can fix it with the "radeon.modeset=0" kernel parameter. Did that, successfully installed arch, booted and got in my DM. (i use LY Wich runs in text mode) after i logged in to my XFCE session the "xorg didn't start because it didn't find an screen" 
 i know that the kernel parameter i set is most likely the problem. I need it because without it the display output will be the DisplayPort port on the iMac. How do I get xorg working? 
 sorry for my terrible English.
    submitted by    /u/thecraftguy_  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fresh install with KDE won't let me log in to the wayland session]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vfok7v/fresh_install_with_kde_wont_let_me_log_in_to_the/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vfok7v/fresh_install_with_kde_wont_let_me_log_in_to_the/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T05:59:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been running endeavour OS on a second drive for some time now and wanted to put arch on my primary ssd.
 archinstall went well, Desktop Profile and KDE, Nvidia Proprietary drivers. X11 Session works as expected, Wayland throws me back to sddm though. Endeavour works fine on the same machine with the same Plasma Version.
 Where can i look to find out what the issue is here?
    submitted by    /u/domsch1988  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your installed browser extension may be used to fingerprint you]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179239</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/19/your-installed-browser-extension-may-be-used-to-fingerprint-you/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T05:53:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Extensions installed in web browsers may be used for tracking purposes. Some extensions use resources that are accessible by sites that are loaded in the browser; the information may be used to […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Your installed browser extension may be used to fingerprint you appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch Linux kernel reports "tainted" due to kernel warning (W) for a module that shows not tainted]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vfl7tq/arch_linux_kernel_reports_tainted_due_to_kernel/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vfl7tq/arch_linux_kernel_reports_tainted_due_to_kernel/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T02:27:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Can anyone help me understand why Linux reports my kernel is tainted? It seems to have happened after updating kernel and wayland on system with secure boot. 
  cat /proc/sys/kernel/tainted 512 
 Then running query on dmesg shows this:
 sudo dmesg | grep -i 'taint' [ 14.376299] CPU: 2 PID: 783 Comm: kwin_wayland Not tainted 5.18.5-arch1-1 #1 e9787f6018c114f5ea5c49a220d7535dfd3a932e 
 Is there a way to clear it? I tried by reinstalling linux kernel but it had no effect. I use self-generated keys to sign my kernels and bootloader.
 ​
 Host Security ID: HSI:2! (v1.8.1) HSI-1 ✔ CSME manufacturing mode: Locked ✔ CSME override: Locked ✔ CSME v0:15.0.35.2039: Valid ✔ Platform Debugging: Disabled ✔ SPI BIOS region: Locked ✔ SPI lock: Enabled ✔ SPI write: Disabled ✔ Supported CPU: Valid ✔ TPM empty…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Airpods output working but not input (KDE plasma DE)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vfkmtj/airpods_output_working_but_not_input_kde_plasma_de/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vfkmtj/airpods_output_working_but_not_input_kde_plasma_de/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T01:53:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I already have pulseaudio and pavucontrol which my output from my airpods depends on but input devices doesn't have my airpods as an option.
    submitted by    /u/Righteous_Warrior  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[Newbie] After about 10 minutes arch fails to work properly]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vfjn50/newbie_after_about_10_minutes_arch_fails_to_work/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vfjn50/newbie_after_about_10_minutes_arch_fails_to_work/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-19T00:56:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, I dont know how it started or what caused this. All I know is that when I last updated packages using pacman a day or two later the issues started coming in.
 After about 10 minutes or so, I can no longer search with Firefox, I can't open any program other than terminal and Thunar. I can get some commands to work with terminal but once I use sudo it seems to not output anything.
 I'm at a loss as to what im supposed to do, any help would be greatly appreciated.
    submitted by    /u/Extaiin  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Bizarre Case Of Zstd's Very Slow Performance On Arch Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Arch-Linux-Bizarre-Zstd</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Arch-Linux-Bizarre-Zstd"/>
        <updated>2022-06-18T23:40:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday I posted benchmarks of six Linux distributions on the HP Dev One, the exciting new Linux laptop launched by HP in collaboration with System76 that is using their Pop!_OS distribution. From those benchmarks one of the bizarre findings was that the Zstd compression performance on Arch Linux simply sucked, but some interested developers dove in and found the rather bizarre culprit why their Zstd performance is so poor in relation to other Linux distributions on the same version...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How can I wake from suspend in openbox?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vfg97c/how_can_i_wake_from_suspend_in_openbox/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vfg97c/how_can_i_wake_from_suspend_in_openbox/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-18T21:51:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi all. Thanks for looking!
 I've installed openbox and xfce4-panel as one user, and as another user Plasma is installed. From what I've gathered, the commands 'systemctl suspend' or 'pm-suspend' should suspend the system and wake it up with a mouse movement or a key press, and it doesn't wake up, but it does in Plasma. What kind of magic incantation does Plasma use to achieve this?
    submitted by    /u/pressman57  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 Ways to Open a Link in a New Tab]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=785821</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/785821/3-ways-to-open-a-link-in-a-new-tab/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-18T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Having a bunch of tabs open is a trademark feature of web browsing. If you don’t want to leave the current tab, you can simply open links in new tabs. We’ll show you how to do it in any desktop browser.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Met with a 'Failed to mount /boot' and 'Dependency failed for local filesystems' error when I tried to do a Timeshift restore on Arch. Any help?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vff0ux/met_with_a_failed_to_mount_boot_and_dependency/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vff0ux/met_with_a_failed_to_mount_boot_and_dependency/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-18T20:49:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I tried to do a Timeshift restore on my Arch Linux, but when I rebooted, I was met with the systemd boot screen stating the errors shown in the title. At the bottom I was prompted to enter root password to enter maintenance mode. I thought it might've had something to do with the NFS mount I added to fstab but it seems not the case after I commented it out and rebooted to the same result.
 When I tried to do another Timeshift restore from the command line I was met with another error stating something like: '/dev/mapper/ not found'. Mega Arch noob here (probably in over my head tbh), any help would be appreciated. Thanks.
 Here's a link to a similar post I made in r/linux4noobs so that you can see the boot screen.
    submitted by    /u/Pending1  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Edifier's NeoBuds Pro S Promise Lossless Audio with a New Codec]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/121216/edifiers-neobuds-pro-s-promise-lossless-audio-with-a-new-codec/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/121216/edifiers-neobuds-pro-s-promise-lossless-audio-with-a-new-codec/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-18T20:04:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coming this July, the new Edifier Neobuds Pro S promise to deliver 24-bit 96 kHz audio with 45% less latency than other wireless earbuds. It’s one of the first notable products to utilize Qualcomm’s Snapdragon Sound codec, and in theory, it should match the quality of wired headphones.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Find and Delete Old Emails in Gmail]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=787285</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/787285/how-to-find-and-delete-old-emails-in-gmail/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-18T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Inbox cleanup is a chore most don’t enjoy. But if you don’t stay on top of things, you can end up with a mess of outdated, unneeded emails. We’ll show you how to quickly find and delete old emails in Gmail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Login to Your Hotmail Account]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=post-ideas&amp;p=421475</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/14728158/retrieve-hotmail-login"/>
        <updated>2022-06-18T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Founded in the mid-90s, Hotmail is one of the oldest email addresses that continues to be used by many. However, it no longer exists as a separate webmail service, as Microsoft’s Outlook handles all Hotmail accounts. This is causing confusion to users who are wondering whether Hotmail is still around and if it will remain operational in the future. The following guide covers how you can retrieve an inactive Hotmail account, create a new Hotmail username, delete it, and change a Hotmail email address to an Outlook one.
   

Content

Where Is My Hotmail Account?
How to Access My Hotmail Account in Outlook?
How to Retrieve Your Old Hotmail Account
How to Create a New Hotmail Account
Rename Hotmail Account to Outlook 
How to Delete Your Hotmail Account?
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Read Yahoo Mail in Any Email App
    
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sayak Boral</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to See Who Is Following You on Facebook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=805269</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/805269/how-to-see-who-is-following-you-on-facebook/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-18T19:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Facebook allows you to see the list of people who follow you on this platform. These people aren’t necessarily your friends but they’ve chosen to follow your posts in their news feed. We’ll show you how to check this list on both your desktop and your mobile phone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yet another bash script for setting wallpaper!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vfcmgw/yet_another_bash_script_for_setting_wallpaper/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vfcmgw/yet_another_bash_script_for_setting_wallpaper/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-18T18:48:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I use these two little shell scripts to set wallpaper in my system. I use i3 as my window manager.
 wallchange:
 #!/bin/sh while getopts "s" opt; do case "$opt" in s ) STARTUP="true" ;; esac done SCREEN_WIDTH=$(cat /sys/class/graphics/*/virtual_size | cut -f1 -d',') SCREEN_HEIGHT=$(cat /sys/class/graphics/*/virtual_size | cut -f2 -d',') WALLPAPER_PATH="$(readlink -f ${HOME}/Pictures/.wallpaper.jpg)" : ${STARTUP:=false} # Set the old wallpaper at startup if it exists [ "${STARTUP}" == "true" ] && [ -f "${WALLPAPER_PATH}" ] && feh --bg-fill ${WALLPAPER_PATH} # Check if you have internet connection wait-for-internet -s 100 [ "$?" == "0" ] && \ { # Download image or show error message wget -O ${WALLPAPER_PATH} https://picsum.photos/${SCREEN_WIDTH}/${SCREEN_HEIGHT} || \ { notify-send --icon=dialog-error "Cannot download wallpaper!"; exit 1;} # Set the downloaded image as wallpaper [ -f "${WALLPAPER_PATH}" ] && feh --bg-fill ${WALLPAPER_PATH} } 
 wait-for-interent:
 #!/bin/sh while getopts "s:c:" opt do case "$opt" in c ) COMMAND="$OPTARG" ;; s ) NUMBER_OF_SECONDS="$OPTARG" ;; esac done : ${NUMBER_OF_SECONDS:=1} for i in $(seq 1 1 "${NUMBER_OF_SECONDS}"); do ping -q -c 1 8.8.8.8 > /dev/null if [ "$?" == "0" ]; then if [ ! -z "${COMMAND}" ]; then eval "${COMMAND}" exit "$?" else exit 0 fi fi sleep 1 done notify-send --icon=notification-network-wireless-disconnected "No internet connection detected!" exit 1 
 The wallchange script downloads a random image from https://picsum.photos and sets it as the wallpaper with the help of feh.
    submitted by    /u/i8ad8  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deformed logo of mozilla and alacritty]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vfc8pe/deformed_logo_of_mozilla_and_alacritty/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vfc8pe/deformed_logo_of_mozilla_and_alacritty/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-18T18:29:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello there. This might seem an absurd and stupid question but the logo on the top of my applications (e.g. mozilla, alacritty) look deformed:
 https://i.postimg.cc/43hgcpLb/image.png
 https://i.postimg.cc/4y4tn4ft/image.png
 It, however, is perfectly fine in case of dolphin:
 https://i.postimg.cc/0yHqBVKq/image.png
 So, is there a way to fix this problem?
    submitted by    /u/Far_Meaning_3958  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Slow internet for some reason only when downloading from terminal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vfc43p/slow_internet_for_some_reason_only_when/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vfc43p/slow_internet_for_some_reason_only_when/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-18T18:23:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Usually i get maybe 2.0mbps but now im getting around 100kbps usually around 70 max on downloads through the terminal i ran a speedtest in my browser and my internet seems relatively normal aside from having somewhat high ping im using network manager in kde
    submitted by    /u/OutsideNo1877  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[os-prober detecting windows but not mint]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vfbwz3/osprober_detecting_windows_but_not_mint/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vfbwz3/osprober_detecting_windows_but_not_mint/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-18T18:13:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[arch's grub is not listing mint though it lists arch and windows, what should I do to add mint in the list? And the os-prober too is detecting only the windows boot manager. Btw in the /boot/efi/EFI/ there is this ubuntu(mint) folder containing the efi files of mint.
    submitted by    /u/Wise_Consideration70  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anyone else got problems with blur on KDE after updating?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vfbt7b/anyone_else_got_problems_with_blur_on_kde_after/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vfbt7b/anyone_else_got_problems_with_blur_on_kde_after/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-18T18:08:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I updated my system today, and blur effects do not seem to work correctly anymore in both Wayland and X. For example, the top bar now appears transparent instead of blurry. Sometimes it appears as a solid colour.
 I also got problems with an external hard drive, which is not being read automatically anymore, so I have to re-scan my music collection every time I open up the player...
    submitted by    /u/elohimeth  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Today's Cinnamon update messed a lot of thing up. Looking for advice.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vfbrlz/todays_cinnamon_update_messed_a_lot_of_thing_up/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vfbrlz/todays_cinnamon_update_messed_a_lot_of_thing_up/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-18T18:06:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just updated the Cinnamon DE. After reboot, half of applets and extensions are not working plus i was greeted with an error message about the same problem.
 The menu feels laggy and about 50% slower than in the last version.
 Any way to fix this? Should i downgrade? Should i switch the DE?
    submitted by    /u/Tiny-Refrigerator-98  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Quote Someone on Discord]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809687</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809687/discord-quote/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-18T18:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By quoting text, you make a piece of text stand out in your Discord messages. There are options to quote specific text in a text string as well as quote entire lines of text on this platform. We’ll show you how to do just that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple's Insanely Priced Dual USB-C Chargers Arrive: Buy These Instead]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/121255/apples-insanely-priced-dual-usb-c-chargers-arrive-buy-these-instead/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/121255/apples-insanely-priced-dual-usb-c-chargers-arrive-buy-these-instead/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-18T18:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In another act of courage, Apple led the charge on selling phones without chargers. You already have one, the company reasoned. But not one that can fast charge your phone or even slow charge your laptop. Enter Apple’s new overpriced dual USB-C chargers. They’re here if you need the “right logo.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Hendrickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QNAP NAS devices targeted by surge of eCh0raix ransomware attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/qnap-nas-devices-targeted-by-surge-of-ech0raix-ransomware-attacks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/qnap-nas-devices-targeted-by-surge-of-ech0raix-ransomware-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-18T17:06:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week a new series of ech0raix ransomware has started targeting vulnerable QNAP Network Attached Storage (NAS) devices according to user reports and sample submissions on the ID-Ransomware platform. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Does “BFD” Mean, and How Do You Use It?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=752721</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/752721/what-does-bfd-mean-and-how-do-you-use-it/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-18T17:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you written about your accomplishments only to have someone call them a “BFD”? Sometimes, a BFD isn’t as big a deal as it seems. Here’s what this sarcastic internet slang term means and how to use it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vann Vicente</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Prime Day to Offer Over 30 Free Games, From 'Mass Effect' to 'GRID Legends']]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/121219/amazon-prime-day-to-offer-over-30-free-games-from-mass-effect-to-grid-legends/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/121219/amazon-prime-day-to-offer-over-30-free-games-from-mass-effect-to-grid-legends/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-18T16:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Prime Day is ready to kick off next month, and along with a slew of deals and discounts, Prime members will be able to get over 30 games completely free. And the list includes some big-name games you won’t want to miss.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unable to use electron flags in config files for vs code under wayland]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vf9bmu/unable_to_use_electron_flags_in_config_files_for/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vf9bmu/unable_to_use_electron_flags_in_config_files_for/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-18T16:06:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey guys, I need to use vs code for a school project. It works when I type into terminal 
  
code --enable-features=UseOzonePlatform --ozone-platform=wayland
  
but I'd like to not have to type the flags every time. I tried putting the flags into ~/.config/electron-flags.conf and into .local/share/applications/code-oss.desktop
 But it has no effect.
 electron-flags.conf:
  --enable-features=UseOzonePlatform --ozone-platform=wayland 
 desktop file:
  Desktop Entry] Name=Code - OSS Comment=Code Editing. Redefined. GenericName=Text Editor Exec=/usr/bin/code-oss --unity-launch --enable-features=UseOzonePlatform --ozone-platform=wayland %F Icon=com.visualstudio.code.oss Type=Application StartupNotify=false StartupWMClass=Code Categories=TextEditor;Development;IDE; MimeType=text/plain;application/x-code-oss-workspace; Actions=new-empty-window; Keywords=vscode; [Desktop Action new-empty-window] Name=New Empty Window Exec=/usr/bin/code-oss --new-window --enable-features=UseOzonePlatform --ozone-platform=wayland %F Icon=com.visualstudio.code.oss 
 I'm thinking an alias could solve it, but I'd prefer to use the "proper" solution.
    submitted by    /u/Sleezebag  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up Google TV User Profiles]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=811305</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/811305/how-to-set-up-google-tv-user-profiles/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-18T16:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google TV focuses on recommendations, but what good are those if someone with different tastes is using your account and screwing them up? Thankfully, Google TV has user profiles for adults and kids. Let’s set it up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome browser extension lets you remove specific sites from search results]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/chrome-browser-extension-lets-you-remove-specific-sites-from-search-results/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/chrome-browser-extension-lets-you-remove-specific-sites-from-search-results/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-18T15:50:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The uBlackList browser extension lets you clean up search results by removing specific sites when searching on Google, DuckDuckGo, Bing, and other search engines. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Browser extension lets you remove specific sites from search results]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/browser-extension-lets-you-remove-specific-sites-from-search-results/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/browser-extension-lets-you-remove-specific-sites-from-search-results/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-18T15:50:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The uBlackList browser extension lets you clean up search results by removing specific sites when searching on Google, DuckDuckGo, Bing, and other search engines. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[unable to start intellij]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vf8xpz/unable_to_start_intellij/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/vf8xpz/unable_to_start_intellij/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-18T15:46:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey, don't know if this is the right place to post, but I can't start intellij idea when using arch linux, running wayland and sway. But I also have similar problems on a different laptop running wayland and gnome.
 WARNING: An illegal reflective access operation has occurred WARNING: Illegal reflective access by com.intellij.util.lang.UrlClassLoader (file:/usr/share/idea/lib/util.jar) to field java.lang.ClassLoader.classLoaderValueMap WARNING: Please consider reporting this to the maintainers of com.intellij.util.lang.UrlClassLoader WARNING: Use --illegal-access=warn to enable warnings of further illegal reflective access operations WARNING: All illegal access operations will be denied in a future release Startup Error Unable to detect graphics environment 
 any ideas(haha)?
    submitted by    /u/Sleezebag  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is a USI Stylus?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=808419</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/808419/what-is-a-usi-stylus/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-18T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some of the most popular styluses, like Apple Pencil and Samsung S-Pen, are only compatible with their respective manufacturer’s devices. But USI is hoping to change that. So here’s what you need to know about the standard and what USI styluses offer you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gaurav Shukla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Budget TVs of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=752241</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/752241/best-budget-tv/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-18T14:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for a budget television? You’re in luck as many affordable TVs on the market are excellent for movies, gaming, and more. But which ones are best? We’ve picked out the best budget TVs you can buy right now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gaurav Shukla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New phishing attack infects devices with Cobalt Strike]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-phishing-attack-infects-devices-with-cobalt-strike/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-phishing-attack-infects-devices-with-cobalt-strike/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-18T14:06:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security researchers have noticed a new malicious spam campaign that delivers the 'Matanbuchus' malware to drop Cobalt Strike beacons on compromised machines. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wave of 'Matanbuchus' spam is infecting devices with Cobalt Strike]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/wave-of-matanbuchus-spam-is-infecting-devices-with-cobalt-strike/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/wave-of-matanbuchus-spam-is-infecting-devices-with-cobalt-strike/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-18T14:06:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security researchers have noticed a new malicious spam campaign that delivers the 'Matanbuchus' malware to drop Cobalt Strike beacons on compromised machines. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>