<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-05-22T01:46:52.853Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rpan studio appimage]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uv0n4f/rpan_studio_appimage/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uv0n4f/rpan_studio_appimage/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-22T01:24:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm trying to use appimage launcher to add rpan studio appimage to my menu system bit for some reason it's not working. 
 OBS Studio works fine but for some reason rpan studio isn't doing that.
 The program runs fine. I just can't get it to show up in the menu.
 I've thought about using an older version but I doubt that will change anything. 
 I'm using Arch Linux with the Cinnamon desktop. Should I try KDE plasma instead?
 System specs are ThinkServer TS140. It's pretty fast with 16gb of ram. 5tb hdd for the /home and the rest is on a 1tb ssd. This system is super fast! 
 I don't know why it isn't working.
    submitted by    /u/Phydoux  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MacBook Air 2020 cannot use keyboard or mousepad]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uv00fe/macbook_air_2020_cannot_use_keyboard_or_mousepad/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uv00fe/macbook_air_2020_cannot_use_keyboard_or_mousepad/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-22T00:47:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So I’ve done initial setup of arch and everything is good (I did that all with an external mouse and keyboard) but I just can’t figure out how to get the mousepad and keyboard to work. I assume that there are some missing drivers or something but my prior research has come up fruitless (unless I missed somthing very obvious) I am as you can tell very new to arch and would appreciate any help.
 Edit: I am using the newest version
    submitted by    /u/Imaginary_Yam_5058  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Steam games causing arch to crash]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uuzey0/steam_games_causing_arch_to_crash/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uuzey0/steam_games_causing_arch_to_crash/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-22T00:12:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whenever I play a steam game abt 30 mins in the screen freezes, audio clips and repeats and then the system restarts.
    submitted by    /u/Bigbopisboi  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vmlinuz issues after a full update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uuz397/vmlinuz_issues_after_a_full_update/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uuz397/vmlinuz_issues_after_a_full_update/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T23:53:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently tried to update my system to the new kernel, after not having updated for maybe two weeks. And upon rebooting after a completed update. I was given a grub boot error. Of an unexpected end of vmlinuz file. I tried rebuilding my mkinitcpio, but that gave me an error of the linux file being incomplete or empty. I then restored from prior backup, and tried updating again. Which led to the same error in grub. I have looked around, and haven’t been able to find any solutions. Any ideas?
    submitted by    /u/Unfair-Front-1836  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cant use makepkg command]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uuxtit/cant_use_makepkg_command/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uuxtit/cant_use_makepkg_command/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T22:41:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Steam Deck User here. I cant use the makepkg -S command -> doesnt find fake root binary. Guides tell me to install base-devel. But when im trying that im getting „untrusted“ issues like that: 
 error: m4: signature from "Antonio Rojas arojas@archlinux.org" is unknown trust :: File /var/cache/pacman/pkg/m4-1.4.19-1-x86_64.pkg.tar.zst is corrupted (invalid or corrupted package (PGP signature)).
 This is only one example, it outputs mulitple of those. I tried to reset the key database and multiple commands i found online but it still doesnt work. Hope someone can help me out :)
    submitted by    /u/Gullible-Constant-62  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is There Something To Improve to my arch install "Guide"?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uuxlxx/is_there_something_to_improve_to_my_arch_install/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uuxlxx/is_there_something_to_improve_to_my_arch_install/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T22:30:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I made my own kind of install "Guide", based on archlinux.org, archlinux.de and some things I found in the arch wiki
 loadkeys (???)
 ip link
 dhcpcd (???)
 gdisk /dev/(???)
 mkfs.fat -F 32 -n BOOT /dev/(???)
 mkfs.btrfs -L ROOT /dev/(???)
 mount -L ROOT /mnt
 mkdir /mnt/boot
 mount -L BOOT /mnt/boot
 pacstrap -i /mnt base base-devel linux linux-firmware btrfs-progs nano git amd-ucode
 genfstab -U /mnt > /mnt/etc/fstab
 arch-chroot /mnt
 echo (hostname) > /etc/hostname
 echo LANG=(???).UTF-8 > /etc/locale.conf
 nano /etc/locale.gen
 locale-gen
 echo KEYMAP=(???)-nodeadkeys > /etc/vconsole.conf
 echo FONT=lat9w-16 >> /etc/vconsole.conf
 ln -sf /usr/share/zoneinfo/(???)/(???) /etc/localtime
 hwclock --systohc
 timedatectl set-ntp true
 timedatectl status
 nano /etc/hosts
 # IPv4
 127.0.0.1 l…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How do I break out of AUR dependency cycle?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uux0vj/how_do_i_break_out_of_aur_dependency_cycle/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uux0vj/how_do_i_break_out_of_aur_dependency_cycle/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T21:59:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So, the package lib32-openjpeg2 on AUR got recently updated to version 2.5.0, but the current one on my system (2.4.0) has a dependency on openjpeg2=2.4.0. So I cannot update with pacman, because then my openjpeg2 would get updated to 2.5.0, which breaks the lib32-openjpeg2 dependency on it being only 2.4.0, and I cannot update lib32-openjpeg2 from AUR (using yay) because it wants to update openjpeg2 from repos before and it fails the same.
 So, what's the way out of this?
  
EDIT: Solved using the --nodeps (-Sd) option.
    submitted by    /u/JonnyRobbie  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to modify /etc/resolv.conf in chroot?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uuwlpf/how_to_modify_etcresolvconf_in_chroot/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uuwlpf/how_to_modify_etcresolvconf_in_chroot/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T21:36:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I'm in the chroot during installation /etc/resolv.conf is a symlink to another file. I want to replace it with my own file but anything I do doesn't work. If I try to remove the symlink or replace it with my own file it says Device or resource busy. How can I do it from inside the chroot? My setup scripts run in chroot so I'd like to solve it there.
    submitted by    /u/Status-Floor3119  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[20 Things to Try When Your Mouse Keeps Freezing in Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=483356</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15319529/fixes-mouse-freezing-windows"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve ever had to navigate Windows with the keyboard alone, you know it’s not easy. You may find yourself in such a situation if your mouse keeps freezing and forcing you to find alternative methods to operate your PC. 
    
The most common reason why your mouse keeps freezing is that the mouse driver has become corrupted. Other reasons include outdated drivers and software, faulty hardware, or even viruses. Fortunately, there are some things you can try that might resolve the issue and enable you to get back to work as we shall explore below.
    
Note: The methods included in this article apply to Windows 10 and 11.
   

Content

Keyboard Shortcuts to Use if Your Mouse Freezes
1. Check Cable Connection 
2. Change USB Ports
3. Change Batteries
4. Check Mouse Distance 
5. Clean the Mouse and Mouse Pad
6. Try a Different Mouse
7. Update Mouse Drivers
8. Uninstall and Reinstall Mouse Drivers
9. Disable Additional Mouse Drivers
10. Rollback to Previous Mouse Drivers
11. Restart File Explorer
12. Turn off Power Saving for USB Ports
13. Disable Mouse Pointer Precision
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Claire Moraa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s Why You Shouldn’t Use Your Phone for Internet Speed Tests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=796894</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/796894/heres-why-you-shouldnt-use-your-phone-for-internet-speed-tests/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most of us use our phones for practically everything, so it just seems natural to grab your phone to run a speed test on your home internet connection. Here’s why you should avoid doing that—and what to do instead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Fitzpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SQUASHFS error?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uuvnnv/squashfs_error/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uuvnnv/squashfs_error/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T20:47:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I typed curl in root and this output prints [ 2320.078325] SQUASHFS error: Unable to read fragment cache entry [7a4af2]
 [ 2320.0783951 SQUASHFS error: Unable to read page, block 7a4af2, size 43bde [ 2320.078695] SQUASHFS error: Unable to read fragment cache entry [7a4af2] [ 2320.078763] SQUASHFS error: Unable to read page, block 7a4af2, size 43bde zsh: Input/output error: curl
 127 root@archiso #_
 i don't know what i have done wrong
    submitted by    /u/JX720  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[makepkg.conf using sccache]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uuv5gn/makepkgconf_using_sccache/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uuv5gn/makepkgconf_using_sccache/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T20:20:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is there option to use sccache instead ccache in makepkg.conf when building something from AUR?
    submitted by    /u/antyhrabia  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LG's Latest 4K Ultra Short Throw Projector Brings the Brightness]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118648/lgs-latest-4k-ultra-short-throw-projector-brings-the-brightness/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118648/lgs-latest-4k-ultra-short-throw-projector-brings-the-brightness/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T20:04:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LG just unveiled its latest flagship 4K CineBeam projector that takes its ultra short throw (UST) lineup to the next level. The LG CineBeam HU915QE packs impressive specs like 3,700 lumens, and you can put it as close as 2.2-inches from the wall and still get a 90-inch screen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Display Owner Information on the Lock Screen on Your Android Phone]]></title>
        <id>http://www.howtogeek.com/?p=194878</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/194878/how-to-display-owner-information-on-the-lock-screen-on-your-android-phone/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you lose your Android device, it’s not likely you’ll get it back. However, there are some kind souls who will want to return it. We’ll show you how to make sure they know how to reach you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RISC-V With Linux 5.19 Preps "COMPAT" Mode For 32-bit Apps On 64-bit Kernels & More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=RISC-V-Linux-5.19</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=RISC-V-Linux-5.19"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T19:49:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Linux 5.18 expected to be released as stable tomorrow and that opening up the Linux 5.19 merge window, feature work aimed for this next kernel should be largely wrapped up. Within the RISC-V architecture's "for-next" branch is several interesting additions...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Change the Language on Google]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=804587</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/804587/how-to-change-language-google/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T19:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google makes its services available in many different languages in addition to English. If you’d like to use Gmail, Drive, and other services in your chosen language, simply set the new language as the default in your account. We’ll show you how to do that on your desktop and your mobile.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Should I - really - care about what I install from the AUR ?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uuthsm/should_i_really_care_about_what_i_install_from/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uuthsm/should_i_really_care_about_what_i_install_from/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T18:53:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Novice Arch user here, I'm installing a lot of aur packages and in most cases they are very downloaded by everyone.
 If I understood right how the AUR works, a dangerous package is one that is not very downloaded and ... that's about it. I think/hope there is moderation done on the AUR packages so the major part of dangerous packages are deleted very early.
 So correct me if I'm wrong but there very few packages out there that are really dangerous for my system ?
 + Another question : How is moderation on the AUR atm ? (sorry for my english btw)
    submitted by    /u/Daitan_  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram Volume always drops to 30-50%. Arch, Pipewire, wireplumber]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uutcqf/telegram_volume_always_drops_to_3050_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uutcqf/telegram_volume_always_drops_to_3050_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T18:46:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/qunetaiar  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No sound at all from any output ?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uusv04/no_sound_at_all_from_any_output/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uusv04/no_sound_at_all_from_any_output/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T18:21:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi,
 A few days ago, I had a weird Bluetooth headset crash, audio stopped and the headset acted like it was connected and turned off at the same time. As I already had this kind of situations, I disabled Bluetooth, turned it back on and reconnected the headset. But this time, upon reconnecting, I had no sound coming out from it.
 The only sound I am able to hear are the notification sounds from GNOME. That's it.
 I tested a BT speaker, a wired headset and even the internal speakers wouldn't work at all, which is very annoying because I use this laptop mostly for entertainment.
 I started running some tests : 
 The laptop speakers do work properly. I tested under Windows 10 (the laptop dual boots) and the speakers and BT speakers do work properly.
 I tried to make it forget the headset that had the crash and pairing it back to no avail.
 speaker-test (from alsa-utils) didn't work so I guess there's the issue ?
 EasyEffects seem to detect audio from apps (I tested with Firefox, Audacious and VLC) but no sound waves are displayed, indicating that the issue must be before PipeWire in the audio software stack. In the case of Audacious, it's internal sound wave display works, indicating that audio is being decoded by the app.
 No, the sound was not muted and the correct output was chosen in the settings. That's the first things I've checked.
 I'm pretty sure the issue lies within ALSA but how can it be persistent after reboot if it was a crash ? Is there a way to put it back to default settings ?
 I'm running pretty much the same audio software stack on my main desktop and I regularly use BT speakers with it and I hadn't encountered this issue (it runs on KDE but that shouldn't affect audio as far as I'm aware of).
    submitted by    /u/lululock  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[httm, 0.10.9: Your favorite ZFS Time Machine just got Arch packages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uuslg1/httm_0109_your_favorite_zfs_time_machine_just_got/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uuslg1/httm_0109_your_favorite_zfs_time_machine_just_got/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T18:07:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[​
 Now with Arch packages!
 Arch packages!
 Follow the links to find a package for Arch-based distributions, and instructions on how to build your own.
 Roast me on on my PKGBUILD! Tell me how to use Cargo.toml metadata to autogenerate!
 If this is your first go around with httm, you might want to swing by the README or the man page for more info on usage
 A taste of the changes since last we met...
  
Allow lookup on multiple alternate replicated datasets by u/kimono-koans in https://github.com/kimono-koans/httm/pull/23
 Display files and directories behind deleted directories by u/kimono-koans in https://github.com/kimono-koans/httm/pull/24
 Use cargo metadata by u/keltia in https://github.com/kimono-koans/httm/pull/26
 Use new Colorable LsColors trait which should reduce stat() syscalls by u/kimono-koans in https://github.com/kimono-koans/httm/pull/28
  
New Contributors
  
u/keltia made their first contribution in https://github.com/kimono-koans/httm/pull/26
  
   submitted by    /u/small_kimono  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel Mode Setting and two monitors: UHD and FullHD]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uush85/kernel_mode_setting_and_two_monitors_uhd_and/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uush85/kernel_mode_setting_and_two_monitors_uhd_and/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T18:01:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I use 2 monitors. Early KMS is enabled.
 Console (vt) size on UHD is 1/4 of the monitor. While on FullHD shows console on a whole surface. Resolution (dpi) is proper, btw.
 If FullHD is disconnected and UHD monitor is the only one connected, it shows console on a full surface as well.
 https://imgur.com/a/6s1S7bg
 Is it possible to fix it?
    submitted by    /u/armodim  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How an SSD Will Improve Your Gaming Experience]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=795221</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/795221/how-an-ssd-will-improve-your-gaming-experience/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T18:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you tired of long boot and loading times whenever you’re trying to game? Upgrading from an outdated HDD to a high-performance SSD will significantly reduce wait times and improve in-game performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Nguyen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['God of War Ragnarok' Is for Every Gamer Now]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118681/god-of-war-ragnarok-is-for-every-gamer-now/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118681/god-of-war-ragnarok-is-for-every-gamer-now/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T18:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Video games can be tons of fun for gamers of all ages, but they aren’t always easy for everyone to play. That’s why Santa Monica Studios just added over 60 accessibility options to the PC version of God of War Ragnarok—to ensure gamers of all abilities can enjoy it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzanne Humphries</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pwn2Own 2022: Windows 11, Ubuntu, Firefox, Safari, Tesla and more hacked]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178696</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/05/21/pwn2own-2022-windows-11-ubuntu-firefox-safari-tesla-and-more-hacked/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T17:52:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The hacking event Pwn2Own took place from May 18 to May 20 of 2022. This year, security researchers managed to hack Windows 11 and Ubuntu, Firefox, Safari, Microsoft Teams, a Tesla and […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Pwn2Own 2022: Windows 11, Ubuntu, Firefox, Safari, Tesla and more hacked appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch Linux Mounts To The Pendrive and goes to rootfs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uurysr/arch_linux_mounts_to_the_pendrive_and_goes_to/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uurysr/arch_linux_mounts_to_the_pendrive_and_goes_to/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T17:36:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It says Mounting /dev/disk/by-label/ARCH 202205' to '/run/archise/bottmnt'
 Mount: /run/archiso/bootant: unknown filesysten type 'ntfs'.
 dnesg (1) may have more information after failed mount system call.
 ERROR: Failed to mount /dev/disk/by-label/ARCH 202205"
 Falling back to interactive prompt You can try to fix the problem manually, log out when you are finished sh: can't access tty: job control turend off [rootfs ]#
 (I copied it from google lens some words might be wrong)
    submitted by    /u/JX720  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ransomware attack exposes data of 500,000 Chicago students]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ransomware-attack-exposes-data-of-500-000-chicago-students/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ransomware-attack-exposes-data-of-500-000-chicago-students/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T17:32:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Chicago Public Schools has suffered a massive data breach that exposed the data of almost 500,000 students and 60,000 employee after their vendor, Battelle for Kids, suffered a ransomware attack in December. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Question About Pacman & Partitions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uur8sh/question_about_pacman_partitions/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uur8sh/question_about_pacman_partitions/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T17:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have been having an issue where pacman is installing to my root partition that is only 30GB so installing things like the cudnn package is filling up my entire drive along with other things that I have only just realized are doing that. I have been looking for a way to make it so that pacman installs in my main LVM partition, but have found that nothing on the wiki that says I can even do that. So with this in mind, my question is this: Is there a way to change where pacman installs so that it's not in my root partition or will I have to reinstall and give my root partition more space keeping in mind the packages I want to install?
 ​
 I have done my best to RTFM for pacman and the closest thing I have found is a reddit post suggesting it would be possible to change the pacman package installation directory. This would be to create a hook which I am assuming means if it hits this directory redirect it to another one. Though I don't know enough to know if this is good solution or something that would bite me later.
    submitted by    /u/cyber-head  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Enable or Disable Bluetooth on Android]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=804664</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/804664/how-to-enable-or-disable-bluetooth-on-android/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you need to connect short-range wireless peripherals to your Android device, Bluetooth has you covered. Also, you might need to turn off Bluetooth at times. Here’s how to do both on Android.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Music Coming to 'Nearly All' Audi Models]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118663/apple-music-coming-to-nearly-all-audi-models/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118663/apple-music-coming-to-nearly-all-audi-models/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T16:34:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many Audi owners are soon to get a nice surprise—integration with Apple Music! The German car manufacturer recently announced that it will be rolling out the service into ‘nearly all’ of its vehicle models.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzanne Humphries</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[budgie has Alzheimer's .... plz belp]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uuqixz/budgie_has_alzheimers_plz_belp/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uuqixz/budgie_has_alzheimers_plz_belp/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T16:23:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I installed a new arch system yesterday , and I decided to go with budgie instead of gnome this time , and it went great I got the theme and layout the worked well for me and it was flawless until I restarted , it remembered my theme and fonts , but but not my applets , they were all removed , it happens every restart/logout.
    submitted by    /u/P65B40  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use “Lockdown Mode” on Android]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=806113</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/806113/how-to-use-lockdown-mode-on-android/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T16:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every Android device has a lock screen with some sort of security. Most of the time, that’s enough— but what if you want a little extra security? That’s where the “Lockdown” feature comes in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Systemd 251 Released With systemd-sysupdate Introduced, Many Other Additions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=systemd-251</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=systemd-251"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T15:51:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Systemd 251 is officially out this Saturday as the first feature update to this Linux init system for 2022...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[17 Funny Internet Memes to Crack You Up this Week]]></title>
        <id>http://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=106070</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/13862415/25-funny-internet-memes"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the world is seemingly full of bad news lately, we can all use something to crack us up. To do that, we’ve scoured the Web and found some of the best funny Internet memes to give us all a very good laugh. Some of the best memes had nothing to do with any of the top trending stories. Here are some of the best memes for you to laugh at this week.
   
Also read:These Android Memes Will Make Your Day
    
1. The Obligatory Will Smith Slap Meme
    
 
Will smith after seeing Jada’s reaction to Chris Rock’s joke. pic.twitter.com/Mc4kZZIivG
— Imported Alhaji ? (@ImportedAlhaji) March 28, 2022
 
    
Of the million or so memes that were made following Will Smith’s infamous slap of Chris Rock at the Academy Awards, this one sums it up wonderfully. This shot of Kanye... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Zak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malicious PyPI package opens backdoors on Windows, Linux, and Macs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/malicious-pypi-package-opens-backdoors-on-windows-linux-and-macs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/malicious-pypi-package-opens-backdoors-on-windows-linux-and-macs/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T15:16:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yet another malicious Python package has been spotted in the PyPI registry performing supply chain attacks to drop Cobalt Strike beacons and backdoors on Windows, Linux, and macOS systems. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[testing: increased file system storage for the efly live system]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uuoxie/testing_increased_file_system_storage_for_the/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uuoxie/testing_increased_file_system_storage_for_the/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T15:02:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[tldr: the previous RAM configuration for the efly system was overly conservative and not aligned with modern hardware capabilities. depending on your available ram, these recent changes can easily increase your virtual file system space by 4000%+.
 modern desktop systems quite often have 64GB of ram or more available. but the efly live system (repo here) had a very conservative restriction of just 256MB for the copy-on-write virtual file system.
 the arch wiki describes a solution. but this solution is manual. and you need to know that it's possible, where to find it and how it works.
 in other words not very practical. so i've been playing around a bit and wrote a script, that runs at boot and adjusts the virtual file system limit (cowspace) according to your available RAM.
 something ver…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Convert Dollars, Text, Percent, and Dates in Google Sheets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=799515</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/799515/convert-dollars-text-percent-dates-in-google-sheets/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T15:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can format the data in your cells a few different ways for currency, dates, percentage, text, and numbers. If you’re working with formulas where you want to format those results, you can use a handful of Google Sheets functions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I got a clone gamepad but I can't make it run as an x360 controller]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uunr67/i_got_a_clone_gamepad_but_i_cant_make_it_run_as/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uunr67/i_got_a_clone_gamepad_but_i_cant_make_it_run_as/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T14:02:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I didn't have the money to get a proper one nor do I I have the money to buy one now. When it is connected to my laptop with a cable lsusb says that its a generic x360 controller but when I use the 2.4ghz USB dongle it came with lsusb says that it's a Nintendo switch pro controller for some odd reason I'm just new to this stuff and want to figure out what I need because the wireless dongle worked properly in Linux mint and Ubuntu.
    submitted by    /u/crippl3r  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 hacked three more times on last day of Pwn2Own contest]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/windows-11-hacked-three-more-times-on-last-day-of-pwn2own-contest/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/windows-11-hacked-three-more-times-on-last-day-of-pwn2own-contest/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On the third and last day of the 2022 Pwn2Own Vancouver hacking contest, security researchers successfully hacked Microsoft's Windows 11 operating system three more times using zero-day exploits. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Portable Monitors of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=757555</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/757555/best-portable-monitor/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you are multitasking or just need a bigger screen, portable monitors can add crucial screen real estate to your setup on the go. But if you aren’t sure which to pick, our recommendations for the best portable monitor can help.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gaurav Shukla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nintendo Switch Won’t Turn On? Here’s What to Do]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=805379</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/805379/nintendo-switch-wont-turn-on/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T13:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Does your Nintendo Switch seem dead to the world? There are a few obvious (and some not-so-obvious) things that could be wrong. Let’s run you through a list of troubleshooting steps to diagnose your console’s issue and potentially fix it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Budget Phones Should Have One Good Camera, Not Four Crappy Cameras]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118264/budget-phones-should-have-one-good-camera-not-four-crappy-cameras/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118264/budget-phones-should-have-one-good-camera-not-four-crappy-cameras/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T13:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can’t work for a site called Review Geek without getting hands-on experience with a ton of smartphones. But every time a new budget phone crosses my path, I get more and more frustrated with a stupid trend. These affordable phones all have three, four, or even five cameras, but they can’t take a half-decent photo.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stop Taking Live Photos on iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=803010</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/803010/stop-taking-live-photos-on-iphone/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By default, modern iPhones capture small videos called “Live Photos” every time you take a picture with the Camera app. These Live Photos take up a lot of expensive storage space, and if you don’t use them, they could be wasting your money. Here’s what you should do instead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung Galaxy vs iPhone: qual è il telefono migliore?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/05/samsung-galaxy-vs-iphone-qual-e-il.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/05/samsung-galaxy-vs-iphone-qual-e-il.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T11:38:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I telefoni Samsung e Apple sono da anni i migliori telefoni in circolazione, ma un utente alle prime armi o che non segue molto il mondo tecnologico potrebbe riscontrare delle difficoltà a scegliere tra i due grandi marchi, anche in seguito a precise scelte dal punto di vista hardware e dal punto di vista estetico. 
Nella guida che segue cercheremo di mostrarvi quali sono i punti di forza (e i...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make Your Facebook Account More Private]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=804161</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/804161/how-to-make-facebook-private/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T11:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Facebook has a shaky reputation when it comes to privacy, but it’s a useful tool for keeping in touch with friends and family. If you’re going to use the social network, there are a few things you can do to lock things down as much as possible.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ubuntu 22.10 Switching To PipeWire For Linux Audio Handling]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Ubuntu-22.10-PipeWire</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Ubuntu-22.10-PipeWire"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An early change made this week to Ubuntu 22.10 in its early development state is replacing the PulseAudio sound server with PipeWire...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Open-Source Firmware Virtual Beer Event Is Happening Next Week]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Spring-vPub-2022-OSFW</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Spring-vPub-2022-OSFW"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The folks from the Polish open-source firmware consulting firmware 3mdeb are hosting another "OSF vPub" where they discuss open-source firmware efforts over beers in this currently-virtual event...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HarfBuzz 4.3 Released With Big Performance Improvements]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=HarfBuzz-4.3</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=HarfBuzz-4.3"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T09:21:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HarfBuzz 4.3 was released on Friday as this open-source library that serves as a text shaping engine used by GNOME/GTK, KDE/Qt, Android, Flutter, Java, all major web browsers, and other software...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KDE Plasma 5.25 Preparing More Bug Fixes, Continued Wayland Fixes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=KDE-Plasma-5.25-Post-Beta</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=KDE-Plasma-5.25-Post-Beta"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T09:05:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following this week's KDE Plasma 5.25 beta release, KDE developers turned their attention to bug fixing and they accomplished a lot...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is there a pdf-reader that shows a list of search results]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uuioqt/is_there_a_pdfreader_that_shows_a_list_of_search/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uuioqt/is_there_a_pdfreader_that_shows_a_list_of_search/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T08:12:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hiii^^, I was wondering if there was a way to get a list of all search results in zathura (e.g. something that displays the result and the page the result is on and maybe a way to quickly navigate there)... n-ing through a large document can take quite a while...
    submitted by    /u/t0terverlierer  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla patches two critical security issues in Firefox and Thunderbird]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178692</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/05/21/mozilla-patches-two-critical-security-issues-in-firefox-and-thunderbird/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T05:08:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla published updates for its Firefox and Firefox ESR web browsers on May 20, 2022. The Thunderbird development team released a patch for the email client as well. The security updates patch […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Mozilla patches two critical security issues in Firefox and Thunderbird appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Golden Drake Linux: Arch for gamers and game developers!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uufm17/golden_drake_linux_arch_for_gamers_and_game/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uufm17/golden_drake_linux_arch_for_gamers_and_game/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T04:28:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been working on a custom Arch Linux installer designed with gamers and game developers in mind, Golden Drake Linux, so if you have a minute to look at the README or try out the latest release, please feel free to share feedback, advice, constructive criticism, gentle insults, etc. :) Thanks!
    submitted by    /u/GoldenDrake  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wine 7.9 Brings Many Fixes For Running Windows Games/Apps On Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Wine-7.9-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Wine-7.9-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wine 7.9 was released on Friday as the latest bi-weekly development release of this open-source software for enjoying Windows games and applications on Linux, macOS, and other platforms...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No audio on fresh install]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uubowt/no_audio_on_fresh_install/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uubowt/no_audio_on_fresh_install/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T00:32:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm setting up Arch for the first time and I'm doing everything in i3 if that helps at all. I don't have any audio however. I went to try and turn on some lofi while I work on setting up and getting surf installed (if anyone can give me pointers on that as well, I'd be appreciative). But I don't have any audio and I've tried updating pulseaudio, installing and updating pulseaudio-alsa, and made sure my keybindings for volume keys are correct. I still haven't had any luck so I'm hoping someone that's better experienced at Arch could give me some pointers. 
 Thank you!
 Quick edit: I skimmed some other posts and updating pulseaudio and pulseaudio-alsa were some of the fixes I've found, but they didn't work for me.
    submitted by    /u/Abstract_9  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Stories on TikTok]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=485220</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15317660/create-stories-tiktok"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Previously popularized by apps such as Instagram and Snapchat, Stories has now made it to TikTok. A new update now allows users of the video-focused social networking service to post images and videos that will stay on the app for 24 hours before being deleted. This article shows how you can get started with your first Story on TikTok.
   

Content

How Are TikTok Stories Different?
How to Create Your First TikTok Story
Story Customization Options on TikTok
Posting and Editing Your Story
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Activate Parental Controls on TikTok
    
How Are TikTok Stories Different?
    
Generally speaking, TikTok Stories work in pretty much the same way as stories on other social media apps. However, there are a few differences worth mentioning.
    
For instance, Stories on TikTok will appear in the “For You” feed just like regular... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexandra Arici</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Week in Ransomware - May 20th 2022 - Another one bites the dust]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/the-week-in-ransomware-may-20th-2022-another-one-bites-the-dust/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/the-week-in-ransomware-may-20th-2022-another-one-bites-the-dust/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-21T00:08:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ransomware attacks continue to slow down, likely due to the invasion of Ukraine, instability in the region, and subsequent worldwide sanctions against Russia. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HP Preparing An AMD-Powered Linux Laptop Powered By Pop!_OS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=HP-Dev-One</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=HP-Dev-One"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T22:12:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To date Pop!_OS has been System76's own Ubuntu derivative pre-loaded onto their various laptops and desktops. Rather interestingly, HP is preparing to launch a new laptop that will make use of Pop!_OS...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Questa settimana su TLI (21 maggio 2022)]]></title>
        <id>3581|20220521000001</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/newsletter-turbolab.it-1349/questa-settimana-tli-21-maggio-2022-3581"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T22:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Non hai tempo di leggerci tutti i giorni? nessun problema! ecco a te il riepilogo di quanto proposto da TurboLab.it nel corso della settimana in conclusione.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Check What Version of Windows You Are Running]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=477404</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15317510/check-windows-version"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Often, it matters little what version of Windows you’re running on your PC. But if you’re trying to troubleshoot a technical problem or upgrade your system, you need to know.
    
This tutorial will show you how to identify most Windows versions at a glance and even get specific details such as the build number using simple commands.
   

Content

How to Identify the Windows Version Visually
Alternative Ways to Check Your Windows Version
1. Using the Winver Command
2. With CMD
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:Your PC Can’t Run Windows 11? Try Changing These Settings
    
How to Identify the Windows Version Visually
    
The fastest way to identify the version of Windows you’re running is through a visual check. After all, the general appearance of each Windows version is the same as long as you’ve... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Kanyoro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Jailbreak an Amazon Fire TV Stick]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=797654</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/797654/jailbreak-firestick/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever dreamed of getting Android apps from outside the official Amazon Appstore on your Fire TV device? You can, in a process often called “jailbreaking.” It’s easy to perform, and it’s not the illegal or hacky process it sounds like.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco urges admins to patch IOS XR zero-day exploited in attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisco-urges-admins-to-patch-ios-xr-zero-day-exploited-in-attacks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisco-urges-admins-to-patch-ios-xr-zero-day-exploited-in-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T20:39:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco has addressed a zero-day vulnerability in its IOS XR router software that allowed unauthenticated attackers to remotely gain access to Redis instances running in NOSi Docker containers. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[help xfce4 screenshot automatically opening+200 tabs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uu6rww/help_xfce4_screenshot_automatically_opening200/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uu6rww/help_xfce4_screenshot_automatically_opening200/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T20:20:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/mainsamayhoon24  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Much Does it Cost to Fix an iPhone Screen?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118647/how-much-does-it-cost-to-fix-an-iphone-screen/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118647/how-much-does-it-cost-to-fix-an-iphone-screen/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T20:11:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking an iPhone screen is never a fun experience. While nearly every electronics repair store will help you fix your iPhone, the job isn’t free, and you could walk out with a much lighter wallet. So, here are all your repair options, plus the prices you can expect to pay for an iPhone screen replacement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Repair Corrupted Windows System Files with the SFC and DISM Commands]]></title>
        <id>http://www.howtogeek.com/?p=222532</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/222532/how-to-repair-corrupted-windows-system-files-with-the-sfc-and-dism-commands/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The System File Checker tool built into Windows can scan your Windows system files for corruption or any other changes. If a file has been modified, it will automatically replace that file with the correct version. Here’s how to use it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to change the "host" name?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uu5y68/how_to_change_the_host_name/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uu5y68/how_to_change_the_host_name/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T19:39:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm not talking about the hostname, but the "host" model name that appears in neofetch. For some reason, my laptop's name is very long - "HP ENVY Pro 4-b0000 ........". How would I go about changing that?
    submitted by    /u/AlpinDale  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save 40% on a Samsung Galaxy Chromebook]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=491077</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15317405/samsung-galaxy-chromebook-professional-laptop"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are many advantages to a Chromebook, and carrying the Samsung Galaxy name is never a bad thing. That’s what makes the Samsung Galaxy Chromebook Professional Laptop so desirable. You can use it just as you would any laptop or tablet. Even better: you can get as much as 40% off the 2020 model.
    
You’ll find a fantastic picture quality with expansive color, contrast, and depth from the 4K AMOLE touchscreen display. This 2-in-1 convertible design will help with your work as well as your leisure time. It’s there when you need it and will start up in just six seconds. Store all your important documents and files with the 256GB SSD as you multitask.
    

    
The built-in pen stylus fits nicely into the slim design of the Samsung Galaxy Chromebook Professional Laptop. It allows you to jot down ideas, edit, and create accurate sketches to help others visualize your plans.
    
Chrome OS just works. It’s simple, secure, and fast, thanks to the 10th Generation Intel Core processor. It’s also... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ranger not showing images with Ueberzug]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uu5h3k/ranger_not_showing_images_with_ueberzug/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uu5h3k/ranger_not_showing_images_with_ueberzug/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T19:17:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, so as the title says I am not able to see images in ranger using ueberzug. I have tried different terminals (currently using kitty) and also tried searching something about this error but I haven't found anything.
 ​
 Screenshot: https://i.imgur.com/vWeJIrI.png
 Can anyone help me? Thanks!
    submitted by    /u/DominiCzech  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Format a USB Drive on Windows 10]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=803514</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/803514/how-to-format-a-usb-drive-on-windows-10/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You don’t need to use any complex tools to format a USB flash drive. You can do it directly in File Explorer. But what do all of the options mean, and which should you choose? Here is what you need to know.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Lewis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Double Notifications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uu4p35/double_notifications/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uu4p35/double_notifications/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T18:40:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[for a while now i've been getting double notifications in Firefox. I really only have Reddit set up for push notifications. not sure if this is a firefox, reddit, arch or xfce issue. 
 I posted over on the xfce forums but no answers. 
 Some of my installed packages related to notifications...
 local/libevent 2.1.12-1 An event notification library local/libnotify 0.7.12-1 Library for sending desktop notifications local/startup-notification 0.12-7 Monitor and display application startup local/xfce4-notifyd 0.6.3-1 (xfce4-goodies) Notification daemon for the Xfce desktop 
    submitted by    /u/callmejoe9  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11’s Android Apps Are About to Get a Lot Better]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=806702</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/806702/windows-11s-android-apps-are-about-to-get-a-lot-better/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T18:39:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Windows Subsystem for Android is an optional feature in Windows 11, which allows you to run Android applications and games alongside your other software. Microsoft is now testing a significant upgrade to the Subsystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[nvidia and nvidia-dkms packages conflict]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uu4iic/nvidia_and_nvidiadkms_packages_conflict/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uu4iic/nvidia_and_nvidiadkms_packages_conflict/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T18:31:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm trying to install nvidia-dkms on my arch install, but pacman says that nvidia (the driver) and nvidia-dkms are in conflict and will uninstall the other. I have installed linux-zen-headers, but still nothing is working. Is there any way to fix this?
    submitted by    /u/Algod2  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux 5.18 Preparing For Release - Especially Heavy With Many Intel & AMD Changes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.18-Nears-Release</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.18-Nears-Release"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T18:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's been a fairly smooth week and Linus Torvalds is expected this Sunday to formally release the Linux 5.18 stable kernel. Unless he has any last minute reservations and decides to stretch it out an extra week, Linux 5.18 will be out as stable and with it comes a great deal of new features -- especially for benefiting AMD and Intel products from CPUs to GPUs...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft disables telemetry in Windows 11 Subsystem for Android by default]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-disables-telemetry-in-windows-11-subsystem-for-android-by-default/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-disables-telemetry-in-windows-11-subsystem-for-android-by-default/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T18:20:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has updated the Windows Subsystem for Android in Windows 11 to make telemetry collection optional and announced an upgrade to Android 12.1. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Backdoor baked into premium school management plugin for WordPress]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/backdoor-baked-into-premium-school-management-plugin-for-wordpress/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/backdoor-baked-into-premium-school-management-plugin-for-wordpress/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T18:02:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security researchers have discovered a backdoor in a premium WordPress plugin built as a complete management solution for schools. The malicious code enables a threat actor to execute PHP code without authenticating. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Touch ID on iPhone, iPad, and Mac?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=804751</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/804751/what-is-touch-id-on-iphone-ipad-and-mac/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T18:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some models of Apple iPhone, iPad, and Mac include an authentication feature called “Touch ID,” which lets you use your fingerprint to verify your identity. We’ll explain why it’s useful and how it works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to check which audio server is used? Pipewire and Pulseaudio are running]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uu3ge8/how_to_check_which_audio_server_is_used_pipewire/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uu3ge8/how_to_check_which_audio_server_is_used_pipewire/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T17:42:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So I played a bit around to get Audiosurf 2 working on Linux (It doesn't work on Pipewire for me) and I somehow managed to end up with both installed and running.
 Firstly, how did I manage to have both without forcing anything?
 How to properly check what audio server is used?
 > systemctl --user status pulseaudio ● pulseaudio.service - Sound Service Loaded: loaded (/usr/lib/systemd/user/pulseaudio.service; disabled; vendor preset: enabled) Active: active (running) since Thu 2022-05-19 22:25:20 CEST; 21h ago TriggeredBy: ● pulseaudio.socket Main PID: 290247 (pulseaudio) Tasks: 3 (limit: 9289) Memory: 10.0M CPU: 26min 39.569s CGroup: /user.slice/user-1000.slice/user@1000.service/session.slice/pulseaudio.service └─ 290247 /usr/bin/pulseaudio --daemonize=no --log-target=journal May 19 22:25:19 Arch-8956 systemd[26967]: Starting Sound Service... May 19 22:25:20 Arch-8956 pulseaudio[290247]: stat('/etc/pulse/default.pa.d'): No such file or directory May 19 22:25:20 Arch-8956 systemd[26967]: Started Sound Service. May 19 23:59:22 Arch-8956 pulseaudio[290247]: org.freedesktop.DBus.Properties.Get /org/bluez/hci0/dev_38_18_4C_19_6D_86/sep1/fd0 Volume failed: org.freedesktop.DBus.Error.InvalidArgs: No such property 'Volume' May 20 06:40:29 Arch-8956 pulseaudio[290247]: Lost I/O connection in module "module-gsettings" 
 ​
 > systemctl --user status pipewire ● pipewire.service - PipeWire Multimedia Service Loaded: loaded (/usr/lib/systemd/user/pipewire.service; disabled; vendor preset: enabled) Active: active (running) since Thu 2022-05-19 22:24:46 CEST; 21h ago TriggeredBy: ● pipewire.socket Main PID: 290075 (pipewire) Tasks: 2 (limit: 9289) Memory: 1.9M CPU: 69ms CGroup: /user.slice/user-1000.slice/user@1000.service/session.slice/pipewire.service └─ 290075 /usr/bin/pipewire May 19 22:24:46 Arch-8956 systemd[26967]: Started PipeWire Multimedia Service. 
    submitted by    /u/ReakDuck  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[Question] Hello everyone, i've never removed orphaned packages and i dont know if it's safe to remove them . I have more than 2gb of orphaned packages and i'm wondering whether its safe or not, and also some of those packages are not actually orphaned so is there a way to "blacklist" some of them?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uu2ke3/question_hello_everyone_ive_never_removed/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uu2ke3/question_hello_everyone_ive_never_removed/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T17:12:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/Mitass  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I am confused by arch's tag line....help here,why arch of all distros.what is the one thing that arch can do that other distros can't?I found many answers but none of them were convincing enough, a newbie here....]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uu2gk7/i_am_confused_by_archs_tag_linehelp_herewhy_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uu2gk7/i_am_confused_by_archs_tag_linehelp_herewhy_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T17:09:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many arch users say they use arch because it is "install only what you want".I can't understand.cant one remove all not required programs and stuff from a distro ? And also I am a newbie linux hobbyist so don't critisize me..but the arch Linux distro itself comes with many stuff that most of us don't know what they are...the only thing we are doing is installing the required softwares on top it.we can do that in other distros too right ?correct me if I am wrong I am a newbie and tried arch...it's hard and thought we can do the same stuff in other distros too...
    submitted by    /u/anonymous_persona_  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Whats the deal with ctrl+backspace/alt+backspace?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uu2de4/whats_the_deal_with_ctrlbackspacealtbackspace/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uu2de4/whats_the_deal_with_ctrlbackspacealtbackspace/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T17:06:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One time, ctrl+bs lets me erase word per bs press, other times it doesn't, but alt+bs lets me. Why is that so?
    submitted by    /u/CTRL1_ALT2_DEL3  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Do Only Some iPhone Spam Messages Have the “Report Junk” Option?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=805853</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/805853/why-do-only-some-iphone-spam-messages-have-the-report-junk-option/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T17:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve been using your iPhone for long enough, you’ve likely noticed very few spam text messages have the “Report Junk” option to help you automatically report and block spam. What gives?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Fitzpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can someone please explain package/aur signing in a simple way? The wiki is too complex for me to understand.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uu247k/can_someone_please_explain_packageaur_signing_in/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uu247k/can_someone_please_explain_packageaur_signing_in/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T16:58:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So they're supposed to be there for the user to verify if the package is authentic or something, as far as i know.
 Can someone please explain to me the principles and the process of doing it properly (in order to avoid downloading malicious packages)? I cant seem to understand what the wiki is trying to say, the terminology is too complex for me. 
 Does pacman-key command also apply to AUR, or is there another command for AUR signing?
    submitted by    /u/CTRL1_ALT2_DEL3  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qualcomm Sets a New Example for AR Glasses Design]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118640/qualcomm-sets-a-new-example-for-ar-glasses-design/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118640/qualcomm-sets-a-new-example-for-ar-glasses-design/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T16:53:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Qualcomm is a leader in mobile technologies, and naturally, its processors are popular in mixed reality headsets like the Meta Quest (formerly Oculus Quest). But what about AR glasses? Well, Qualcomm now confirms that it’s working with three companies to develop Snapdragon-powered smart glasses, and it’s even published a “reference design” to prepare us for the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Questions from a beginner about post-install and backups]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uu1yv9/questions_from_a_beginner_about_postinstall_and/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uu1yv9/questions_from_a_beginner_about_postinstall_and/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T16:53:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey!
 So I’m pretty new to Arch, but I have managed to get it installed and running. Now that is done, there are two questions I was hoping I could get answers for:
  
Once I have it installed, are there any tasks I must do? I’ve seen the ‘General Recommendations’ page on the wiki, but am not sure if that’s something that is optional. Am I good to just start installing apps, or do I need to do some additional configuration first, such as securing my system?
 
Is there any way I could backup my system? Considering how new I am to this I know I’m probably going to break something eventually, and would rather not have to start from scratch each time. On a VM I know I could just take snapshots, but I am not sure how to do something like that outside a VM.
 
On installing AUR packages, I’ve read that I am supposed to manually check the package build (?). Is this what I’m supposed to be checking? If so, what should I be looking for yo make sure it is safe.
 
 Thanks!
 Edit: Added another question
    submitted by    /u/FreeBeachFortune  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Go Download Tesla's Free Service Manuals While You Can]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118641/go-download-teslas-free-service-manuals-while-you-can/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118641/go-download-teslas-free-service-manuals-while-you-can/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T16:45:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, Tesla opened up access to let users download its service manuals, parts manuals, and repair guides for free, which is a pretty big deal, especially if you’re a DIY type of person. However, we’ve seen this happen before, and it didn’t last long, so download them while you can.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Programmi per registrare musica e canzoni online]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2017/08/programmi-per-registrare-musica-e.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2017/08/programmi-per-registrare-musica-e.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T16:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gli appassionati di musica sanno quando fosse facile registrare le proprie canzoni preferite, specie per chi è vissuto negli anni '80 e '90: bastava sintonizzarsi su una qualsiasi radio FM, inserire una musicassetta e premere sul tasto Rec, senza necessità di avere una conoscenza tecnica approfondita.

 Il mondo è andato avanti e si è passati al digitale, ma gli appassionati possono registrare la...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[openSUSE Tumbleweed's GCC 12 Upgrade Helping Performance In Some Areas]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31133</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31133"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T16:18:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week the rolling-release openSUSE Tumbleweed switched to the new GCC 12 as the default system compiler and rebuilt its package set under this annual feature upgrade to the GNU Compiler Collection. For those curious here are some benchmarks before and after that GCC 12 transition for openSUSE Tumbleweed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Link an Android Phone to a Windows 11 PC With Microsoft Phone Link]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=804405</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/804405/how-to-link-an-android-phone-to-a-windows-11-pc-with-microsoft-phone-link/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Phone Link—formerly known as “Your Phone”—is an essential app for Windows 11 users with Android phones. It gives you access to your phone’s notifications, messages, and photos right on your PC. We’ll help you set it up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Encrypt existing partition?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uu0blq/encrypt_existing_partition/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uu0blq/encrypt_existing_partition/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T15:58:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have an 8TB drive I want to encrypt with LUKS. It seems to be impossible to just encrypt it, but I have seen some people to shrink the existing partition, make an encrypted one, move the files, and delete the unencrypted one. Does this work? Do LUKS partitions allow for resizing? What would be the risk of data loss? Thanks.
    submitted by    /u/MaleficentAd3284  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save Up to 23% On Roborock’s New Q Series Robot Vacuums]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=805194</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/805194/early-bird-sale-roborocks-new-allergy-busting-vacuums-are-here/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T15:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While you’d expect allergens to run rampant outside your home during spring and summer, plenty of dust mites, pollen grains, pet dander, and other irritants also make it into your hallowed halls. Your home’s air filtration system gets a lot of these out of the air, but what about all the debris that gets left behind in your carpet? Roborock has the solution with its new Q series robot vacuums, which go on sale starting today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zach Laidlaw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Launcher Android: quali sono i migliori]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Launcher-Android-quali-sono-i-migliori_24545</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Launcher-Android-quali-sono-i-migliori_24545"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T15:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A meno che non si acquisti uno smartphone Google Pixel non sono tanti i dispositivi mobili che installano Android stock. Tant'è vero che sono nate ROM alternative come Pixelexperience che si sostituiscono al firmware preinstallato dai vari produttori garantendo all'utente un'esperienza d'uso molto simile a quella di Android stock.Che si chiami One UI nel caso di Samsung, MIUI per Xiaomi, ColorOS per Oppo e così via, ogni produttore di smartphone sviluppa e aggiorna continuamente la sua interfaccia Android personalizzata sopra al basecode del sistema operativo Google.Non è questione di rendere lo smartphone più in linea con il proprio 'gusto estetico': in alcuni casi gli utenti mal tollerano la disposizione delle funzioni nelle varie versioni di Android.I launcher Android sono componenti software che offrono un'impostazione alternativa rispetto alla soluzione scelta dall'azienda di Mountain View o all'interfaccia personalizzata dal singolo produttore.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qualcomm’s New Snapdragon Chips Will Speed Up Android Phones]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=806568</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/806568/qualcomms-new-snapdragon-chips-will-speed-up-android-phones/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T15:49:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many of the best Android phones and tablets use a System-on-a-Chip (SoC) from Qualcomm, and now the company has revealed its fastest mobile chip yet: the Snapdragon 8+ Gen 1. There’s also a new Snapdragon 7 chip, intended for upper mid-range phones.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox Presents: A YouTube creator blending femininity and engineering]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.mozilla.org/?p=68990</id>
        <link href="https://blog.mozilla.org/en/products/firefox/xyla-foxlin-youtube-engineering/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T15:44:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Being feminine and having technical skills are not mutually exclusive. This should be obvious, but Xyla Foxlin has had to work hard to prove femininity and engineering can go hand in hand. While in college, she started a YouTube channel called Beauty and the Bolt, where she co-produced tutorials on STEM topics like electronics, math […]
The post Firefox Presents: A YouTube creator blending femininity and engineering appeared first on The Mozilla Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kristina Bravo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Missing Pixel 6a Feature Doesn't Matter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118600/this-missing-pixel-6a-feature-doesnt-matter/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118600/this-missing-pixel-6a-feature-doesnt-matter/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T15:38:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The upcoming Pixel 6a costs just $450 and offers some of Google’s flagship features, including the Tensor processor and Live Translate. But there’s a bit of controversy surrounding one missing spec—a high refresh rate. And to be honest, the controversy is unwarranted.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Install macOS in VirtualBox]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=post-ideas&amp;p=302574</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/11651718/install-macos-virtualbox"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple has always made it hard to install its operating system on non-Apple hardware, making it hard to take advantage of the benefits of this refined OS. Here we will show you how to install macOS in a virtual machine. You will need a compatible set of hardware, along with a system with powerful enough components to run both Windows and macOS. 
   

Content

What You’ll Need
How to Create Your macOS Virtual Machine
Final Configuration
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Fix Ubuntu Freezing in VirtualBox
    
What You’ll Need
    
First, you’ll need to download a copy of Oracle VM VirtualBox. You’ll also need an ISO image of the macOS version you want to install.
    
Getting hold of an ISO is actually more difficult than you might expect. Even if you have access to a Mac, you won’t be... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ojash Yadav</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here's Why Your iPhone May Have Deactivated iMessage]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118621/heres-why-your-iphone-may-have-deactivated-imessage/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118621/heres-why-your-iphone-may-have-deactivated-imessage/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T15:23:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An unusual new iPhone bug is apparently deactivating iMessage and Facetime for some users. The leading solution requires owners to go down to a physical retail store and get a new SIM card.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emergency Windows 10 updates fix Microsoft Store app issues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/emergency-windows-10-updates-fix-microsoft-store-app-issues/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/emergency-windows-10-updates-fix-microsoft-store-app-issues/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T15:21:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has released out-of-band (OOB) updates on Thursday evening to address a newly acknowledged issue impacting Microsoft Store apps. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Hyundai and Kia EVs Recalled Over Parking Hazard]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118610/new-hyundai-and-kia-evs-recalled-over-parking-hazard/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118610/new-hyundai-and-kia-evs-recalled-over-parking-hazard/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T15:16:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bad news for some Kia and Hyundai EV owners! Both brands are recalling approximately 20,000 electric vehicles—the Kia EV6 and the Hyundai Ioniq 5—over a dangerous issue with the parking brake function.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzanne Humphries</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Wrap Text Around an Image in Microsoft PowerPoint]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=804362</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/804362/how-to-wrap-text-around-an-image-in-microsoft-powerpoint/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T15:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Placing text around an image brings a professional appearance to your presentation and makes the most of the space on your slide. Even though PowerPoint doesn’t offer the same feature as Word for wrapping your text, there are a couple of ways to make it happen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migliori App per fare fitness divertendosi su Android e iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/05/migliori-app-per-fare-fitness.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/05/migliori-app-per-fare-fitness.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T14:55:00.005Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Il fitness è una cosa molto importante per mantenere un buono stato di salute: almeno una volta al giorno tutti noi dobbiamo percorrere almeno 7.000 o 8.000 passi per mantenerci in forma ed evitare di mettere su peso. Le app di fitness per telefono spesso sono così serie e noiose da scoraggiare i più giovani e i pigri ad allenarsi; per fortuna possiamo sacrificare anche delle app di fitness...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arcade1Up Pinball Cabinet Review: A Great Start]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118385/arcade1up-pinball-cabinet-review-a-great-start/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118385/arcade1up-pinball-cabinet-review-a-great-start/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T14:24:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a child of the ’80s and ’90s, owning a pinball machine wasn’t something I could fathom when I was young. But if it had occurred to me, I would have loved it. With Arcade1Up’s pinball cabinets, the company tries to thread the needle between accessibility and realism. And it gets pretty darn close.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Hendrickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Speakers of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=798359</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/798359/best-speaker/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T14:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Speakers have come a long way and can suit a variety of needs, which makes shopping for one a tricky process. Need a little help? Just take a look at a few of our favorites to get you pointed in the right direction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kris Wouk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>