<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-04-29T02:00:05.833Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hands on with Microsoft Edge's new built-in VPN feature]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/hands-on-with-microsoft-edges-new-built-in-vpn-feature/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/hands-on-with-microsoft-edges-new-built-in-vpn-feature/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T23:25:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Edge's Secure Network is powered by Cloudflare - one of the most trusted DNS hosts in the industry - and it aims to protect your device and sensitive data as you browse. The feature is in the early stage of development available to select users in Edge Canary and it's not a full-fledged VPN service offered in browsers like Opera. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mayank Parmar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I just got Arch installed on a pen drive, anything important I need to know?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ue80cp/i_just_got_arch_installed_on_a_pen_drive_anything/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ue80cp/i_just_got_arch_installed_on_a_pen_drive_anything/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T23:15:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/manggohstt  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch is unavailable after crash]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ue7dwc/arch_is_unavailable_after_crash/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ue7dwc/arch_is_unavailable_after_crash/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T22:44:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was transitioning from Plasma to i3 and in middle of configuring fish while my laptop ran out of battery power
 After rebooting I cannot access my arch anymore and grub is unavailable in boot order in UEFI (and in EFI shell), also wanted to configure new grub, but I cannot see neither Arch or Windows drives (both being NVME SSDs)
 I don't know what to do now, did anyone struggled with something like that in past? Is there any way to solve it?
    submitted by    /u/ModerNew  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Issues installing Arch in a VM but I thought I figured it out...]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ue7b66/issues_installing_arch_in_a_vm_but_i_thought_i/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ue7b66/issues_installing_arch_in_a_vm_but_i_thought_i/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T22:41:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So, I've installed Arch at least 2 dozen times now in VMs and a couple times on real machines. Never had any issues.
 But today and last night, I am having a heck of a time booting into a freshly installed VM using EFI. I installed everything and it all configured nicely for me. I even rebooted and it loaded refind and booted me into the command prompt just fine. I shut it down with the shutdown now command, powered it back up again and I keep getting what you see here. Does anyone know how to fix this?
 I know I've ran Arch in an EFI in Proxmox before. I can't seem to figure out why this isn't working. I tried doing a mkinitcpio -p linux and when I rebooted the first time it finally logged me in... Now when I reboot it just goes to a EFI shell after I get that error screen.
 Server Specs:
 Dell R720
 2 300GB SAS drives RAID1 (boot)
 2 640GB SATA drives RAID1 (ISOs)
 2 4TB SAS drives RAID1 (VMs)
 96gb RAM
    submitted by    /u/Phydoux  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubuntu Focus M2 Gen4 Announced With Intel Alder Lake, RTX 30 Graphics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Kubuntu-Focus-M2-Gen4</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Kubuntu-Focus-M2-Gen4"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T22:32:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While most of the Linux pre-loaded laptops these days ship with GNOME or a desktop derived from GNOME components, the Kubuntu Focus has been one of the most notable exceptions for using KDE Plasma and also ptimized for workflows around deep learning, programming, dev ops, and more. Today the company announced the Kubuntu Focus M2 Gen4 laptop with upgraded hardware...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creare una barra multifunzione in Linux Mint Cinnamon sfruttando le potenzialità di Xfce]]></title>
        <id>3554|20220429000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/linux-27/creare-barra-multifunzione-linux-mint-cinnamon-sfruttando-potenzialita-xfce-3554"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Obiettivo di questo articolo è quello di provare a illustrare come sfruttare le potenzialità e la versatilità del pannello (e suoi componenti) tipico dell'ambiente desktop (desktop environment) Xfce all'interno di Linux Mint Cinnamon (versione 20.3 "Una", in questo caso), senza la necessità di abbandonare il nostro milieu Cinnamon o di installare altri ambienti.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WhatsApp is currently down with users reporting connection issues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/whatsapp-is-currently-down-with-users-reporting-connection-issues/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/whatsapp-is-currently-down-with-users-reporting-connection-issues/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T21:25:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WhatsApp is down according to user reports mentioning issues connecting to the messaging platform and the inability to send messages although still connected. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 12 Best UC Browser Alternatives for Android]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=296362</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/11237040/uc-browser-alternatives-android"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you a UC browser fan? Its user-friendly app is one of the best you can download on your Android device. And in terms of usage statistics, the Alibaba-owned browser is easily the most popular in the Android market after Google Chrome. In the last few years, though, there have been numerous privacy concerns with the UC browser app. If you’re looking to make a change, or if the app is been banned in your country, check out this list of UC browser alternatives. 
   

Content

Why the UC Browser Is Popular
1. Opera Mini Browser 
2. Samsung Internet Browser
3. DuckDuckGo Browser 
4. Brave Browser
5. Puffin Web Browser
6. Dolphin Web Browser
7. Firefox Focus
8. Via Browser
9. Opera Touch
10. Microsoft Edge Browser 
11. Opera Crypto Browser
12. Tor Browser Alpha

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:5 Best Privacy-Focused Browsers for Android and iOS
... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sayak Boral</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EmoCheck now detects new 64-bit versions of Emotet malware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/emocheck-now-detects-new-64-bit-versions-of-emotet-malware/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/emocheck-now-detects-new-64-bit-versions-of-emotet-malware/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T21:01:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Japan CERT has released a new version of their EmoCheck utility to detect new 64-bit versions of the Emotet malware that began infecting users this month. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wired vs. Wireless Keyboards: Which Is Better for Gaming?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=794904</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/794904/wired-vs-wireless-keyboards-for-gaming/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T21:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Besides the cable, you may find wireless keyboards don’t provide nearly as much value as their wired counterparts. Let’s find out why and discuss why you might benefit more from using a wired gaming keyboard.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Nguyen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best packages for non-ASCII characters?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ue4rrm/best_packages_for_nonascii_characters/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ue4rrm/best_packages_for_nonascii_characters/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T20:45:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently saw this post asking what the best go-to packages are for a minimal install like Arch, and it got me wondering if there was anything similar for characters and text that are outside of the ASCII format (e.g: Japanese text, Chinese text, etc). Any suggestions?
    submitted by    /u/4xTB  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Watch Not Connecting to Your Phone? Here’s the Fix]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=796472</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/796472/apple-watch-not-connecting-to-phone/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T20:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple gadgets are supposed to “just work” but most iPhone owners will tell you that’s not always the case. This can be true of the Apple Watch, which occasionally may stop syncing with your iPhone altogether. Fortunately, the fix is pretty easy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch feels laggy and font looks sharp]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ue3fpa/arch_feels_laggy_and_font_looks_sharp/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ue3fpa/arch_feels_laggy_and_font_looks_sharp/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T19:45:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello,
 I am new to arch and linux in general and have some troubles with it. The things that bug me the most are that it feels really laggy on my 144hz monitor. It all feels like its running at 60fps. I've tried the vsync test online but something is still off. Also something happened to the font. It is not as smooth as before.
 I tried to reinstall the nvidia drivers with:
 pacman -S nvdia-lts
 but this didn't seem to work so I decided to turn to reddit.
    submitted by    /u/IIKrisII  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get an HP Chromebook 14″ Laptop for Under $180]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=335545</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/14675906/deal-hp-chromebook-14-laptop"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you exhausted your old laptop while working from home and are looking for something new, you may want to consider a new laptop. It can be affordable and doesn’t have to exhaust your entire budget. You can get an HP Chromebook 14″ Laptop with 4GB RAM, 32 GB eMMC storage, Google Chrome OS, and more.
    
This Chromebook has a dual-core Intel Celeron processor N4020. It includes a 14-inch display with an 88º wide-angle field of view for conducting video chats and viewing your photos, YouTube videos, and streamed media. It has a 32 GB eMMC hard drive with 4 GB DDR4-2400 SDRAM, Wi-Fi 5, and Bluetooth 5.0. The battery can last up to 13-1/2 hours, and you can use the Fast Charge technology to charge it up to 50% from 0 in just 45 minutes.
    

    
All of this will give you the power you need to use it throughout the day for both work and play. It will allow you to stay productive during the day, then relax later and take... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Twitter Alternative: How Does Mastodon Work?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=801927</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/801927/a-twitter-alternative-how-does-mastodon-work/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T19:15:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to keep an eye on the world’s events beyond the corporate eye of Twitter? Then the microblogging platform Mastodon might just be for you. Here’s a look at what it is, how it works, and how it compares to Twitter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Before You Buy Snapchat's Selfie Drone, Check the Specs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/116416/before-you-buy-snapchats-selfie-drone-check-the-specs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/116416/before-you-buy-snapchats-selfie-drone-check-the-specs/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T19:14:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The team at Snap just launched Pixy, a selfie drone that costs just $230. It’s a pretty interesting product—Pixy is about the size of your hand, has fully automated flight paths (no controller), and captures video with a 2.7k resolution. But before buying Pixy, you’d better check the detailed specs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA)?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=794722</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/794722/what-is-multi-factor-authentication-mfa/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T19:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ve heard of two-factor authentication (2FA) and its many benefits, but what about multi-factor authentication (MFA)? MFA can go beyond a simple text or authentication app, and might even happen without you knowing it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sydney Butler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Synology warns of critical Netatalk bugs in multiple products]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/synology-warns-of-critical-netatalk-bugs-in-multiple-products/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/synology-warns-of-critical-netatalk-bugs-in-multiple-products/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T18:55:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Synology has warned customers that some of its network-attached storage (NAS) appliances are exposed to attacks exploiting multiple critical Netatalk vulnerabilities. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GCC 12 Branched, Possible GCC 12.1 Stable Release Next Week]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=GCC-12-Branched</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=GCC-12-Branched"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T18:37:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The GCC 12 compiler code-base has reached zero P1 regressions (the highest priority) and thus the GCC 12 compiler code has been branched from mainline, a release candidate is imminent, and if all goes well GCC 12.1.0 as the stable release could be out as soon as the end of next week...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add To or Edit a Drop-Down List in Google Sheets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=796013</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/796013/how-to-add-to-or-edit-a-drop-down-list-in-google-sheets/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T18:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Sheets makes it easy to add and remove items from the existing drop-down menus in your spreadsheets. You can also change your drop-down settings, and even completely remove them if you want. Here’s how to do that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 Amazing Rivian R1T Electric Truck Features]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/115949/8-amazing-rivian-r1t-electric-truck-features/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/115949/8-amazing-rivian-r1t-electric-truck-features/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T17:46:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year, a new American auto manufacturer named Rivian released the first electric truck, the exciting Rivian R1T. It’s an adventure vehicle with a unique design, plenty of power, and a lot to love.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft fixes ExtraReplica Azure bugs that exposed user databases]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-fixes-extrareplica-azure-bugs-that-exposed-user-databases/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-fixes-extrareplica-azure-bugs-that-exposed-user-databases/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T17:34:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has addressed a chain of critical vulnerabilities found in the Azure Database for PostgreSQL Flexible Server that could let malicious users escalate privileges and gain access to other customers' databases after bypassing authentication. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EaseUS Video Downloader Review]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=479138</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15256265/easeus-video-downloader-review"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T17:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are many reasons you might want to secure an online video and have it offline for later use. Perhaps you are doing some research and you don’t want to risk the videos you are using as reference becoming unavailable. Maybe you want to keep all the videos in one place so that you can go through them all without searching or waiting. 
    
In another scenario, for example, you uploaded a video to a streaming site and no longer have the original but would like to recover it. If you have it saved offline, at least you can have a backup of it. Perhaps you are going away somewhere remote with no Wi-Fi for a month. You can line up a bunch of videos to keep you entertained. This review takes a look at EaseUS Video Downloader to see how it could help you out in these scenarios.
    
This is a sponsored article and was made possible by EaseUS. The actual contents and opinions are the sole views of the author who maintains editorial independence even when a post is sponsored.
    
Going Offline
    
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phil South</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Black screen with blinking line after incomplete install]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ue084i/black_screen_with_blinking_line_after_incomplete/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ue084i/black_screen_with_blinking_line_after_incomplete/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T17:22:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After going through most of the installation process I realised I did not enable efi boot options in bios pre-install and it gave me an error message. While I was then researching how to sort that out my power went out and the desktop PC I was installing on powered down. Now when i attempt to boot it I get absolutely nothing except a black screen and a blinking line similar to a command line. No grub nothing. If I try to press any keys nothing happens and an error sound is emitted. No mouse either. I am not sure what to do please help.
 edit: i can’t just start again because there is no boot menu. the pc literally turns on and it’s just a black screen with a line cursor that doesn’t let me type or do anything.
    submitted by    /u/kidders_mxj  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Facebook's Next VR Headset Is Built For Work (And Maybe Play)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/116380/facebooks-next-vr-headset-is-built-for-work-and-maybe-play/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/116380/facebooks-next-vr-headset-is-built-for-work-and-maybe-play/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T17:11:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During a Q1 earnings call, Facebook (now Meta) CEO Mark Zuckerberg announced that the upcoming Project Cambria headset “will be more work focused,” with features and ergonomics suited for a mixed reality office environment. But these features should appeal to gamers, assuming that Zuckerberg isn’t holding back any unpleasant details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Configurare un access point Wi-Fi come ripetitore del router primario]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2015/07/configurare-un-access-point-wifi-come.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2015/07/configurare-un-access-point-wifi-come.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T17:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Abbiamo mostrato in diversi articoli come sia possibile ed anche semplice estendere una rete wireless in casa o in ufficio. Se abbiamo un problema a coprire alcune zone dela casa o dell'ufficio, possiamo aumentare il segnale wireless connettendo un secondo router al modem principale, configurando il nuovo dispositivo solo come Access Point (senza nessun'altra funzione di router).

 Nella guida...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Draw on Google Docs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=779084</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/779084/how-to-draw-on-google-docs/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Docs is well-known for being a comprehensive text editor, but it also provides some basic, built-in drawing tools that allow users to create basic designs in their documents and give them that special touch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marshall Gunnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Edge Will Test a Built-In VPN Feature]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/116392/microsoft-edge-will-test-a-built-in-vpn-feature/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/116392/microsoft-edge-will-test-a-built-in-vpn-feature/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T16:57:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Believe it or not, Microsoft Edge is actually a pretty decent browser these days. Admittedly that’s because, under the hood, it’s powered by Chromium, but facts are facts. And here and there, Microsoft continues to add useful features—including a test for a new (and free) VPN.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Hendrickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come installare Ubuntu in Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Come-installare-Ubuntu-in-Windows_24448</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Come-installare-Ubuntu-in-Windows_24448"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T16:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ad aprile 2022 Canonical ha rilasciato Ubuntu 22.04 LTS, la nuova e più recente versione della distribuzione Linux con supporto a lungo  termine: il rilascio degli aggiornamenti di sicurezza è assicurato fino ad aprile 2032.Al solito sul sito ufficiale del progetto si possono trovare tutti i download di Ubuntu, comprese le versioni desktop, server, per i dispositivi IoT e così via.Il modo tradizionale per installare Ubuntu consiste nello scaricare l'immagine ISO aggiornata, salvarla su una chiavetta USB avviabile con Rufus oppure su un dispositivo esterno multi-boot con Ventoy ed effettuare l'avvio del sistema da questo supporto, previa modifica della configurazione del BIOS/UEFI (la sequenza di boot deve prevedere l'avvio dall'unità USB).Il file ISO di Ubuntu permette di provare il sistema operativo senza installarlo (modalità live) oppure avviare il setup vero e proprio.
Installare ed eseguire Ubuntu in Windows
 Grazie alle tante soluzioni per la virtualizzazione delle quali possiamo disporre oggi, è molto semplice installare ed eseguire Ubuntu in Windows.
Installazione di Ubuntu come macchina virtuale in Windows
 Per installare Ubuntu in Windows si possono utilizzare varie soluzioni per la virtualizzazione ma Microsoft Hyper-V risulta immediatamente fruibile dagli utenti di tutte le edizioni di Windows 10 e 11.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Medical software firm fined €1.5M for leaking data of 490k patients]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/medical-software-firm-fined-15m-for-leaking-data-of-490k-patients/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/medical-software-firm-fined-15m-for-leaking-data-of-490k-patients/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T16:17:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The French data protection authority (CNIL) fined medical software vendor Dedalus Biology with EUR 1.5 million for violating three articles of the GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation). [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Change the Default Phone App on Android]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=798736</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/798736/how-to-change-the-default-phone-app-on-android/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With everything that phones can do, it’s easy to forget they are phones at the core. On Android, you have the choice to swap your phone (dialer) apps with something else from the Play Store. We’ll show you how to do it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get a Taste of Nothing's First Phone with This Android Launcher]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/116369/get-a-taste-of-nothings-first-phone-with-this-android-launcher/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/116369/get-a-taste-of-nothings-first-phone-with-this-android-launcher/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T15:41:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Those who are patiently waiting for Nothing’s first smartphone can now test the Nothing Launcher. As promised, this launcher features some of the unique design language (mainly fonts and widgets) of the upcoming “Nothing OS.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ukraine targeted by DDoS attacks from compromised WordPress sites]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ukraine-targeted-by-ddos-attacks-from-compromised-wordpress-sites/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ukraine-targeted-by-ddos-attacks-from-compromised-wordpress-sites/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T15:38:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ukraine's computer emergency response team (CERT-UA) has published an announcement warning of ongoing DDoS (distributed denial of service) attacks targeting pro-Ukraine sites and the government web portal. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fwupd 1.8 Released With New Capabilities, Expanded Hardware Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Fwupd-1.8-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Fwupd-1.8-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T15:32:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In addition to "Fwupd Friendly Firmware" getting off the ground, this week also marks Fwupd 1.8 as the newest version of this open-source solution paired with the Linux Vendor Firmware Service (LVFS) for easy system and component firmware updating on Linux and other platforms...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 of the Best Photo-Editing Apps You Can Get for Free]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=post-ideas&amp;p=214931</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/6936807/best-photo-editing-apps"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T15:25:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks to smartphones, most of us now carry high-quality cameras around in our pockets. But what happens when the pictures you take are less than ideal and need edits or color adjustments? Well, that’s where photo-editing apps come in — they let you turn decent photos into digital masterpieces you can share across social media.  However, you don’t have to shell out big bucks for programs like Adobe Photoshop to edit your favorite photos. Instead, use any of the amazing free photo-editing apps we’ve rounded up below.
   

Content

1. GIMP
2. Canva
3. Fotor
4. Adobe Photoshop Express
5. Darktable
6. Pixlr X
7. RawTherapee
8. PhotoDirector
9. Fotoxx
10. PhotoScape X
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Use Lightroom Presets to Edit Photos Faster
    
1. GIMP
    
GIMP is one of the most widely used open-source... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Megan Glosson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[nvidia 2070 fans not showing in lm-sensors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/udxiaz/nvidia_2070_fans_not_showing_in_lmsensors/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/udxiaz/nvidia_2070_fans_not_showing_in_lmsensors/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T15:22:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi,
 I've got a relatively new arch install and am not seeing any fan speeds for my nvidia GPU showing in lm-sensors. I ran sensors-detect and said yes to everything, which seems to have gotten the GPU temp to show up, but I can't seem to get output for fan speeds. I'm assuming there's some kernel module I've forgotten to load or something.
 I can see the fan speed with nvidia-smi, and set the speed with nvidia-settings, but they don't show up in lm-sensors.
 My end goal is to get the fans added to my plasma-systemmonitor layout, but the only sensors that show up as options to add to my graph are ones found with lm-sensors. And I can't figure out how to make a custom sensor for plasma-systemmonitor that can be imported into the list of available sensors - If I could, I could just make a simple script to pull fanspeed with nvidia-settings every second.
 Any idea how to get the GPU fan sensors to show up?
    submitted by    /u/bitwaba  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dell's Controversial New XPS Laptop Finally Goes on Sale]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/116360/dells-controversial-new-xps-laptop-finally-goes-on-sale/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/116360/dells-controversial-new-xps-laptop-finally-goes-on-sale/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T15:18:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dell revealed its unique new XPS 13 Plus laptop earlier this year at CES, and now the company confirmed it’s finally available for purchase. So, if you want a sleek laptop without a trackpad, this is for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sharing YouTube TV with Your Family Will Soon Become Tolerable]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/116361/sharing-youtube-tv-with-your-family-will-soon-become-tolerable/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/116361/sharing-youtube-tv-with-your-family-will-soon-become-tolerable/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T15:06:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The good news: YouTube TV is getting a long-awaited feature that’ll make sharing the service with your family much more tolerable. The bad news: that feature should also become available for Chromecast with Google TV users at the same time, and it probably won’t.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzanne Humphries</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migliori app per il benessere digitale su Android e iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/04/migliori-app-per-il-benessere-digitale.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/04/migliori-app-per-il-benessere-digitale.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T15:06:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Il benessere digitale è diventata una cosa da non trascurare quando utilizziamo il telefono: ormai siamo talmente assuefatti dall'uso del dispositivo mobile da non guardare più chi abbiamo davanti, rimanendo ore ed ore incollati nella nostra vita digitale proiettata sul piccolo schermo del nostro telefono. Questo può portare a cali della concentrazione, periodi di stanchezza cronica fino ad...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monitor portatile wireless: ASUS ZenScreen Go MB16AWP]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Monitor-portatile-wireless-ASUS-ZenScreen-Go-MB16AWP_24447</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Monitor-portatile-wireless-ASUS-ZenScreen-Go-MB16AWP_24447"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T15:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[L'utilità dei monitor portatili è ben nota: si possono utilizzare per estendere lo schermo di un notebook o di un convertibile di più piccole dimensioni oppure per duplicare il display e presentare a terzi ciò che si è elaborato.Il nuovo ASUS ZenScreen Go MB16AWP è un monitor portatile wireless da 15,6 pollici con pannello FHD antiriflesso e batteria integrata da 7.800 mAh che assicura fino a 3,5 ore di autonomia tra una ricarica e l'altra.La qualità visiva è assicurata grazie ad un pannello IPS antiriflesso che regala una visualizzazione a 180° e alle tecnologie Flicker Free e Blue Light Filter. Queste ultime sono progettate per ridurre al minimo l'affaticamento degli occhi anche in caso di utilizzi prolungati.Il G-Sensor che equipaggia il monitor ASUS si occupa di rilevare l'orientamento…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nanoleaf Announces a Super Fancy Light for Secretlab's Super Fancy Desk]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/115682/nanoleaf-announces-a-super-fancy-light-for-secretlabs-super-fancy-desk/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/115682/nanoleaf-announces-a-super-fancy-light-for-secretlabs-super-fancy-desk/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T15:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nanoleaf fans better prepare to pony up, because the brand’s latest product is specially made for a Secretlabs desk. The new MAGRGB light strip adds colorful, customizable lighting to the MAGNUS Metal Desk, a $550 monster that pairs with oodles of magnetic accessories.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Basics of Structuring Formulas in Microsoft Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=798325</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/798325/excel-formula-structure-basics/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T15:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re not all mathematicians, but some tasks in Microsoft Excel are best done using formulas. Maybe you’re new to writing formulas or are trying but keep getting confusing errors. Here, we’ll cover the basics of structuring formulas in Excel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pixel 6 Pro Gets Face Unlock Settings in Android 13 Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/116349/pixel-6-pro-gets-face-unlock-settings-in-android-13-beta/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/116349/pixel-6-pro-gets-face-unlock-settings-in-android-13-beta/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T14:52:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As discovered by M. Brandon Lee, the new Android 13 Beta adds Face Unlock settings to the Pixel 6 Pro. These settings aren’t functional, though they seem to verify rumors that Face Unlock will come to the Pixel 6 Pro this June.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch Repos and Gnome Software]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/udwkp9/arch_repos_and_gnome_software/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/udwkp9/arch_repos_and_gnome_software/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T14:41:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi..I've seen that in gnome software, I can't disable the repos if I want, like debian or fedora. I think gnome-software-packagekit-plugin need that support. Also in past I've seen that in fedora, gnome software nicely lists the updates with old and new version numbers but in arch it's not the case...So is it resolved? I deleted the software app 2 months earlier and using terminal for package management ever since. the checkupdates utility from pacman-contrib package does that version thing that I've told.
    submitted by    /u/abhirupbakshi  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Macchina per incisione laser LC400 PRO 50W: offerta a circa 185 euro]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Macchina-per-incisione-laser-LC400-PRO-50W-offerta-a-circa-185-euro_24446</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Macchina-per-incisione-laser-LC400-PRO-50W-offerta-a-circa-185-euro_24446"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T14:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Il mercato offre una vasta scelta di macchine per incisione laser. Il modello LC400 PRO 50W è uno dei più interessanti perché sa coniugare buon design, risultati di qualità e prezzo aggressivo.L'area di incisione è pari a 400 x 400 mm mentre la tecnologia per la regolazione automatica dell'altezza della testina laser permette di ottenere risultati all'altezza delle aspettative praticamente con qualunque tipologia di supporto: legno, materiali plastici, gomma, carta, pelle e così via.

Il design interamente in metallo rende la macchina più solida e durevole migliorando la precisione dell'incisione grazie alla maggiore stabilità rispetto ad altri modelli.Si tratta inoltre di un dispositivo ad assemblaggio rapido che può essere completato in appena 15-20 minuti.Compatibile con tutti i princip…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ransomware payments are marginal when compared to the overall costs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178296</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/04/28/ransomware-payments-are-marginal-when-compared-to-the-overall-costs/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T14:23:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ransomware payments by organizations made up about a seventh of the overall costs of ransomware attacks in 2020 according to a new study by Check Point Research and Kovrr. While ransom payments […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Ransomware payments are marginal when compared to the overall costs appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is There a Difference Between Tin Foil and Aluminum Foil?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lifesavvy.com/126827/is-there-a-difference-between-tin-foil-and-aluminum-foil/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lifesavvy.com/126827/is-there-a-difference-between-tin-foil-and-aluminum-foil/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re anything like me, you often use tin foil and aluminum foil interchangeably. Personally, I’ve always assumed they’re the same thing. Turns out, though, I’ve been confusing two completely different products.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shea Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Attack Your Own Company's Service Desk to spot risks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/how-to-attack-your-own-companys-service-desk-to-spot-risks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/how-to-attack-your-own-companys-service-desk-to-spot-risks/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Specops Secure Service Desk is an excellent tool for keeping a help desk safe from social engineering attacks. Although Specops Secure Service Desk offers numerous features, there are three capabilities that are especially useful for thwarting social engineering attacks. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sponsored by Specops</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best iPad Cases of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=758054</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/758054/best-ipad-case/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your iPad’s 10.2-inch display is great for watching movies and playing games, but you’ll want a case to protect that glass screen from scratches and cracks. These are the best cases for the 2021 iPad, also known as the 9th-generation iPad, as well as the 8th-gen iPad released in 2020.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kris Wouk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Pay: bufera sull'impossibilità di accedere al sistema di pagamento da parte di terzi]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Apple-Pay-bufera-sull-impossibilita-di-accedere-al-sistema-di-pagamento-da-parte-di-terzi_24445</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Apple-Pay-bufera-sull-impossibilita-di-accedere-al-sistema-di-pagamento-da-parte-di-terzi_24445"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T13:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nuvoloni neri si addensano su Apple Pay, lo strumento di pagamento in mobilità che consente di effettuare transazioni contactless utilizzando un iPhone 6 e successivi o un Apple Watch di qualsiasi generazione presso i negozi fisici grazie al chip NFC integrato.Stando a quanto rivela in anteprima il Financial Times, la Commissione Europea starebbe per avviare una verifica nei confronti di Apple incentrata proprio sul funzionamento di Pay.La Mela impedisce ai soggetti terzi e ai concorrenti di accedere al suo sistema di pagamento via NFC: tra gli esclusi vi sono ad esempio PayPal e i principali istituti di credito.La tecnologia NFC permette a ciascun utente di pagare avvicinando lo smartphone al terminale di pagamento o POS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When to Replace Your Old Mouse Pad]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=794982</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/794982/when-to-replace-your-old-mouse-pad/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T13:30:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using a good mouse pad makes your time on the computer much more enjoyable. Look out for the signs we’ll go over when your pad no longer provides the comfort and control you need. Here’s what to look out for.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Nguyen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a Rug Pull in Crypto and NFTs?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/?p=59538</id>
        <link href="https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/rugpull-explained/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T13:01:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You are taking your daily cup of coffee as you browse the internet when you notice some newly minted NFTs and cryptos going viral. You wonder what the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rean</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is a Mobile Hotspot?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=795007</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/795007/what-is-a-mobile-hotspot/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T13:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mobile hotspots offer a convenient way to share internet access with multiple devices. But how do they work, and do you need to pay for them? Here’s everything you need to know about a mobile hotspot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gaurav Shukla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JIRENO CUBE4 Projector Review: Great, but Not Fully Portable]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/115984/jireno-cube4-review/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/115984/jireno-cube4-review/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The JIRENO CUBE 4 is a powerhouse of a projector that is well worth the price of admission. With its 1080p FHD Resolution, Full 4K Decoding, dual 5-watt speakers, and built-in Android TV, the JIRENO CUBE4 has everything you want in a portable projector. The only problem: it’s not that portable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chazz Mair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rimuovere numeri di telefono, indirizzi personali e documenti da Google si può]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Rimuovere-numeri-di-telefono-indirizzi-personali-e-documenti-da-Google-si-puo_24444</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Rimuovere-numeri-di-telefono-indirizzi-personali-e-documenti-da-Google-si-puo_24444"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T12:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I crawler del motore di ricerca Google sono costantemente al lavoro per individuare e indicizzare i contenuti pubblicati sul Web.Può accadere che alcune informazioni personali compaiano tra i risultati di specifiche ricerche costituendo una potenziale minaccia per il soggetto cui i dati si riferiscono.Conosciamo già le norme sul diritto all'oblio: esse permettono agli aventi titolo di richiedere la rimozione di contenuti dal motore di ricerca di Google anche se il sito che li pubblica continua a ospitarli sulle sue pagine.Sentenze passate ormai in giudicato, fatti di cronaca, eventi che riguardano un cittadino possono spesso rappresentare un 'marchio a vita' per quella persona: il diritto all'oblio consente di evitare che nelle SERP di Google continuino a comparire informazioni che riguardano un soggetto.C'è poi il pericolo doxxing ovvero gli attacchi che mirano a diffondere online informazioni personali e dati sensibili di altre persone.Compilando il modulo per la richiesta di rimozione dei contenuti dal motore di ricerca Google da oggi è possibile de-indicizzare pagine che contengono indizzi fisici, numero di telefono e indirizzi email, credenziali di accesso e copie di documenti di riconoscimento.La decisione deriva dal fatto che un volume sempre più imponente di informazioni personali viene pubblicato online senza l'autorizzazione dei diretti interessati e quindi in spregio di tutte le norme vigenti.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the sar Command on Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=793513</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/793513/how-to-use-the-sar-command-on-linux/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T12:30:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The sar command lets you see performance statistics for different elements of your Linux computer, for both real-time and historical data. We show you how to use this great resource.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKay</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tutti i modi di Ingrandire lo schermo del PC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2016/06/ingrandire-lo-schermo-del-pc-tutti-i.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2016/06/ingrandire-lo-schermo-del-pc-tutti-i.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T12:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quando acquistiamo un nuovo computer con schermo FullHD, 2K o 4K nasce inevitabilmente l'esigenza di ingrandire lo schermo del PC, visto che le icone, le barre e gli elementi delle applicazioni possono mostrarsi troppo piccoli rispetto ai vecchi schermi HD.

 Qualsiasi sia la nostra esigenza di ingrandimento nella guida che segue vi mostreremo come ingrandire lo schermo del PC in maniera semplice...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Do “Cap” and “No Cap” Mean on the Internet?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=795210</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/795210/what-do-cap-and-no-cap-mean/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T12:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No, we’re not talking about baseball caps. Here’s what this unusual internet slang term means and why you’re seeing it all over Tweets and song lyrics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vann Vicente</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Bumblebee malware replaces Conti's BazarLoader in cyberattacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-bumblebee-malware-replaces-contis-bazarloader-in-cyberattacks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-bumblebee-malware-replaces-contis-bazarloader-in-cyberattacks/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T11:45:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A newly discovered malware loader called Bumblebee is likely the latest development of the Conti syndicate, designed to replace the BazarLoader backdoor used to deliver ransomware payloads. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Ilascu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD Radeon RX 6400 On Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31080</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31080"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T11:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week AMD quietly launched the Radeon RX 6400 series as the new low-end RDNA2 graphics. With Radeon RX 6400 there are finally low-profile, single-slot PCIe RDNA2 graphics cards whether they be for 2U servers, mini ITX builds, or other interesting use-cases. Up for testing today is an XFX Radeon RX 6400 4GB low-profile graphics card for Linux benchmarking.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[is there a reason polybar is still in the aur and not in community?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/udsq4k/is_there_a_reason_polybar_is_still_in_the_aur_and/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/udsq4k/is_there_a_reason_polybar_is_still_in_the_aur_and/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T11:22:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/sam1090x  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NPM flaw let attackers add anyone as maintainer to malicious packages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/npm-flaw-let-attackers-add-anyone-as-maintainer-to-malicious-packages/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/npm-flaw-let-attackers-add-anyone-as-maintainer-to-malicious-packages/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T11:19:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A logical flaw in the npm registry, dubbed 'package planting' let authors of malicious packages quietly add anyone and any number of users as 'maintainers' to their packages in an attempt to boost the trust in their package. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ax Sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linus Torvalds Comments On The NTFS Linux Driver Situation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linus-Torvalds-NTFS3-Comments</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linus-Torvalds-NTFS3-Comments"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T11:11:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As written about earlier this week, concerns have been raised over the "new" NTFS Linux driver that it's effectively unmaintained already less than one year after being mainlined. Linus Torvalds has since commented on the matter and opens up the door for other developers to maintain it...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Buy a New CPU for Your Motherboard]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=792121</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/792121/how-to-buy-a-new-cpu-for-your-motherboard/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The central processing unit (CPU) is an integral part of any PC. But how do you choose the best CPU that’s compatible with your motherboard? Do you opt for AMD or Intel? Budget-friendly or power-hungry?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Georgie Peru</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Token OAuth possono essere rubati per i furti d'identità: il caso GitHub]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Token-OAuth-possono-essere-rubati-per-i-furti-d-identita-il-caso-GitHub_24443</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Token-OAuth-possono-essere-rubati-per-i-furti-d-identita-il-caso-GitHub_24443"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T10:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[La nota piattaforma di hosting per progetti software GitHub sta indagando da giorni su un problema di sicurezza che ha interessato decine di organizzazioni.Un gruppo di criminali informatici al momento sconosciuto sarebbe riuscito a rubare token OAuth altrui per guadagnare l'accesso al contenuto di una serie di repository GitHub privati, sottraendo dati sensibili e informazioni riservate.Stando alle prime analisi, come spiega GitHub in un resoconto che viene continuamente aggiornato, i token OAuth non sarebbero stati sottratti sui server dell'azienda (anche perché non sono memorizzati in un formato sfruttabile da eventuali aggressori) ma su altri host.I token OAuth in questione sono stati rilasciati da GitHub a due conosciutissimi servizi di i integrazione come Heroku e Travis-CI, entrambi utilizzati dagli sviluppatori software per creare e testare progetti ospitati su GitHub.I portavoce di GitHub spiegano che gli aggressori hanno utilizzato le API della piattaforma autenticandosi con i token OAuth rilasciati a Heroku e Travis-CI quindi sono risaliti alla lista delle organizzazioni che hanno autorizzato le app Heroku e Travis-CI nei rispettivi account GitHub.A questo punto l'attacco è proseguito selezionando gli obiettivi di maggior interesse per gli aggressori, con l'accesso al contenuto dei repository privati e con la successiva sottrazione di dati riservati.
I token OAuth possono essere rubati
 In un altro articolo abbiamo visto cos'è il protocollo OAuth e di come molti di noi lo utilizzino ogni giorno per autenticarsi sui siti Web di terze parti usando ad esempio Google, Microsoft, Facebook od Apple come 'intermediari', senza la necessità di effettuare alcuna nuova registrazione.Tutto molto comodo.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Now Allows You to Remove Personal Information from Search]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=484185</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15255398/google-remove-personal-information-from-search"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T10:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While it can be too easy to just search on Google for someone’s profile, that also means it’s that easy to find information on you. If you’ve always wanted to remove your personal information from Google Search, now you’ll be able to make an official request.
   
Also read:How to Disable or Automatically Delete Google Location History
    
Remove Personal Information from Google Search
    
I’ll admit that if I need someone’s address for some reason, Google Search is my first option: it’s just easier than messaging and asking for it. But I won’t always have the Google Search option to find someone’s personal information – and neither will you. Google will now offer everyone the option to have their personal information removed from Search.
    
It’s not a completely new concept. Google already allows you to have more troubling data removed, like banking information or an account number that could cause you harm if someone stumbled... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Edge Secure Network: non è una VPN ma un proxy sicuro]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Microsoft-Edge-Secure-Network-non-e-una-VPN-ma-un-proxy-sicuro_24442</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Microsoft-Edge-Secure-Network-non-e-una-VPN-ma-un-proxy-sicuro_24442"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T10:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Un po’ come hanno fatto molti browser concorrenti, Edge si arricchirà a breve di una nuova funzione chiamata Secure Network, attivabile dal menu principale in alto a destra.L'obiettivo è quello di rendere più sicura la navigazione sul Web, soprattutto quando si utilizzassero reti altrui.La nuova funzione Secure Network di Edge provvede a creare un tunnel cifrato tra il browser dell'utente e un sistema remoto: tutto ciò che transita attraverso questo canale di comunicazione viene automaticamente protetto e reso inaccessibile da parte di terzi.Si ipotizzi di utilizzare HTTP o un qualunque altro protocollo di livello applicativo che non applica la cifratura dei dati: attivando Secure Network tutti i dati in transito verranno crittografati e quindi sarà scongiurato l'accesso da parte di qualunque soggetto volesse sottrarli, modificarli o danneggiarli.Crittografando il traffico Web direttamente da Edge, come spiega Microsoft, si evita che il provider Internet o qualunque altro soggetto raccolgano i dati di navigazione ovvero l'elenco dei siti Web visitati.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the Whatis Command in Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/?p=59117</id>
        <link href="https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/linux-command-whatis/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T10:01:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's quite similar to "man" except this command only prints the one line description of the given command. It's handy to get what's the command is for]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hongkiat.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Razer Basilisk V3 Review: High-Quality Comfort]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=799114</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/799114/razer-basilisk-v3-review/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T10:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Any fan of FPS games knows how important it is to have a responsive mouse. The Razer Basilisk V3 is the fast, consistent, affordable mouse that you won’t regret adding to your setup. It has every feature competitive gamers want and, in my opinion, stands with the best mice on the market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chazz Mair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ransom payment is roughly 15% of the total cost of ransomware attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ransom-payment-is-roughly-15-percent-of-the-total-cost-of-ransomware-attacks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ransom-payment-is-roughly-15-percent-of-the-total-cost-of-ransomware-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers analyzing the collateral consequences of a ransomware attack include costs that are roughly seven times higher than the ransom demanded by the threat actors. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best windows manager for beginner?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/udrg63/best_windows_manager_for_beginner/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/udrg63/best_windows_manager_for_beginner/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T09:57:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Graphics Card: Nvidia RTX 3060
 Objectives: To play games thru steam and lutris, run gtk applications, dynamic tiling, dont really care about wayland or xorg (whichever works the best with minimal issues) and beginner friendly.
 WMs ive heard are good: i3 and sway
 Thanks for anyone's feedback!
    submitted by    /u/Neo_Nethshan  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Locale messed up in KDE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/udr95x/locale_messed_up_in_kde/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/udr95x/locale_messed_up_in_kde/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T09:42:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've recently installed Arch on a new machine and LC_ALL seems to be messed up.
 locale  locale: Cannot set LC_ALL to default locale: No such file or directory LANG=en_US.UTF-8 LC_CTYPE="en_US.UTF-8" LC_NUMERIC=en_US.UTF-8 LC_TIME=en_GB.UTF-8 LC_COLLATE="en_US.UTF-8" LC_MONETARY=Default.UTF-8 LC_MESSAGES="en_US.UTF-8" LC_PAPER="en_US.UTF-8" LC_NAME="en_US.UTF-8" LC_ADDRESS="en_US.UTF-8" LC_TELEPHONE="en_US.UTF-8" LC_MEASUREMENT=nl_NL.UTF-8 LC_IDENTIFICATION="en_US.UTF-8" LC_ALL= 
 locale -a  C en_GB.utf8 en_US.utf8 nl_NL.utf8 POSIX ro_RO.utf8 
 grep -v "^#" /etc/locale.gen  en_GB.UTF-8 UTF-8 en_US.UTF-8 UTF-8 nl_NL.UTF-8 UTF-8 ro_RO.UTF-8 UTF-8 
 /etc/locale.conf  LANG=en_US.UTF-8 
 ~/.config/plasma-localerc  [Formats] LANG=en_US.UTF-8 LC_MEASUREMENT=nl_NL.UTF-8 LC_MONETARY=Default.UTF-8 LC_NUMERIC=en_US.UTF-8 LC_TIME=en_GB.UTF-8 
 I have re-ran locale-gen with sudo and still the problem persists. I have also tried many solutions such as setting LC_ALL manually in locale.conf with no success
    submitted by    /u/Link512  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD Sends Out New Linux Patches As Part Of Their Next-Gen GPU Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMDGPU-More-IP-Blocks-April-22</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMDGPU-More-IP-Blocks-April-22"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T09:26:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few patch series were fired off yesterday for enabling new IP blocks on upcoming Radeon graphics processors...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11: estendere schermo, anche in modalità wireless]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-11-estendere-schermo-anche-in-modalita-wireless_24441</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-11-estendere-schermo-anche-in-modalita-wireless_24441"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T09:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Capita spesso di avere la necessità di utilizzare più schermi collegati con lo stesso PC. Lo spazio sul desktop non basta mai: certo, esiste la possibilità di usare i desktop virtuali, ma volete mettere la comodità e la praticità di affiancare più monitor approfittando di un'area molto più ampia per il desktop?Abbiamo visto a suo tempo come collegare due monitor al PC tramite cavo: è sufficiente avere a disposizione una o più porte HDMI o DisplayPort.Utilizzando il protocollo Miracast, considerato come l'equivalente wireless di un cavo HDMI, è tuttavia possibile estendere lo schermo di Windows 11 su un altro monitor o su un altro dispositivo compatibile in modalità senza fili: è sufficiente disporre di un display o di un TV compatibile Miracast.Così come Windows 10, anche Windows 11 dispone di tutto il necessario per proiettare lo schermo via Miracast duplicandone il contenuto (utile durante le presentazioni) oppure estendendolo.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bethesda Launcher is being shuttered, and here's how to transfer your games to Steam for free]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178278</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/04/28/bethesda-launcher-is-being-shuttered-and-heres-how-to-transfer-your-games-to-steam-for-free/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T09:11:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bethesda Softworks is sunsetting its game launcher. Don't worry, you aren't going to lose the games that you paid for. Bethesda is allowing players to transfer the games they own on its […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Bethesda Launcher is being shuttered, and here's how to transfer your games to Steam for free appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Edge Secure Network: browser VPN with 1GB free data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178290</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/04/28/microsoft-edge-secure-network-browser-vpn-with-1gb-free-data/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T09:06:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft is testing a new feature in the Microsoft Edge web browser, that is bringing a browser VPN free of charge to all users who are signed-in with a Microsoft Account. Microsoft […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Microsoft Edge Secure Network: browser VPN with 1GB free data appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Austin Peay State University resumes after ransomware cyber attack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/austin-peay-state-university-resumes-after-ransomware-cyber-attack/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/austin-peay-state-university-resumes-after-ransomware-cyber-attack/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T09:04:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Austin Peay State University (APSU) confirmed yesterday that it had been a victim of a ransomware attack. The university, located in Clarksville, Tennessee advised students, staff, and faculty to disconnect their computers and devices from the university network immediately as a precaution. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ax Sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SteamOS 3.2 Beta Brings Improved Fan Control, Experimental Refresh Rate Switching]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=SteamOS-3.2-Beta</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=SteamOS-3.2-Beta"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T09:03:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Valve overnight released a beta of SteamOS 3.2 with some notable improvements for Steam Deck users...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Etnaviv Open-Source Driver Adds GC7000 r6204 GPU Support For The NXP i.MX 8M Plus]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Etnaviv-iMX8MP-Support</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Etnaviv-iMX8MP-Support"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T08:43:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of Mesa's smaller drivers that continues advancing but not receiving as much attention as the big names is Etnaviv for providing open-source, reverse-engineered graphics support for Vivante graphics IP used across different SoCs...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Key error in the installation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/udq9ry/key_error_in_the_installation/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/udq9ry/key_error_in_the_installation/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T08:27:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://recetasbellas.files.wordpress.com/2022/04/20220427_075313.jpg
 It happens to me with different ISO images that I burn to USB. I always get a key error and it doesn't let me continue. 
 I try to update the certificates with pacman-key --refresh-keys, but I get a lot of errors. Until a few days ago I had no problems installing Arch, but now I find it impossible. 
 Any solution? 
 Thank you very much. 
 Regards, Juan.
    submitted by    /u/jbellas  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel module is exist but unloadable and causes multimedia keys become unusable.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/udpm64/kernel_module_is_exist_but_unloadable_and_causes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/udpm64/kernel_module_is_exist_but_unloadable_and_causes/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T07:38:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After upgrade to kernel 5.17, I notice my multimedia keys (fn+F10/F11/F12) is unusable. Checking into log, asus_nb_wmi module is failed to load. I have dualboot with fedora (has a same problem before) which same module is loaded successfully and the multimedia keys is working fine. I'm trying to load the kernel module but it gives me warning like "no such device". The kernel module is exist BTW. The kernel 5.15 LTS works fine, I can assume that there is something wrong with 5.17. Any clue to fix this issue ? Thanks
 it's really similiar with this https://bugzilla.redhat.com/show_bug.cgi?id=2079125
    submitted by    /u/tiny_humble_guy  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fan speed control Acer Nitro 515-45.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/udoura/fan_speed_control_acer_nitro_51545/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/udoura/fan_speed_control_acer_nitro_51545/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T06:45:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am using Arch linux on my Acer Nitro AN515-45 laptop 
 $ neofetch OS: Arch Linux x86_64 Host: Nitro AN515-45 V1.06 Kernel: 5.17.4-arch1-1 Uptime: 41 mins Packages: 1038 (pacman) Shell: bash 5.1.16 Resolution: 1920x1080 WM: i3 Theme: Material-Black-Cherry-4.0 [GTK2/3] Icons: Oranchelo [GTK2/3] Terminal: alacritty CPU: AMD Ryzen 5 5600H with Radeon Graphics (12) @ 3.300GHz GPU: AMD ATI 05:00.0 Cezanne GPU: NVIDIA GeForce GTX 1650 Mobile / Max-Q Memory: 1582MiB / 7359MiB 
 and while playing game like Apex Legends my CPU is constantly at 90C during gameplay. I am not sure if the fan is ramping up to 100% so i wanted to control the fan speed.
 I looked on the Fan speed control page in Arch Wiki and followed it.
 Fancontrol (lm-sensors): Running
 # sensors-detect 
 returns this . TL;DR it says…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brave 1.38 launches with improved Shields panel and De-AMP privacy feature]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178277</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/04/28/brave-1-38-launches-with-improved-shields-panel-and-de-amp-privacy-feature/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T05:18:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brave Software released Brave 1.38, a new stable version of the company's Chromium-based browser, on April 27, 2022. The new version of Brave introduces De-AMP, a technology to redirect Google AMP pages […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Brave 1.38 launches with improved Shields panel and De-AMP privacy feature appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Issue with external monitor through docking station]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/udl9wv/issue_with_external_monitor_through_docking/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/udl9wv/issue_with_external_monitor_through_docking/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T03:08:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi! I have a laptop installed with arch linux. I am using bspwm on it. When I login with my external monitor plugged in (display port through a docking station), everything is well. Then if I disconnect the docking station and reconnect it, my external monitor stays black and goes to sleep. However, if I start a tty at that point it wakes up the monitor and then i can go back to my bspwm session without any issues. I check the xrandr output before and after the disconnection/connection step and I do not see any difference. I am not sure where to go from there... it really looks like something is missing to wake up the monitor but I really don't know where to look.
 Thanks,
    submitted by    /u/TechIssueSorry  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[28 Best Chromebook Tips and Tricks for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=457448</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15254019/best-chromebook-tips-tricks-beginners"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re new to Chrome OS, you might feel a little overwhelmed in the beginning. The reason for this is that a Chromebook differs from a traditional laptop. However, once you’ve figured out how to use your Chromebook it’ll be just like using your Android phone on a larger screen, but with more capabilities. This guide will help you get started by sharing a list of Chromebook tips, tricks, and hidden features.
   

Content

1. Right-click on Chromebook
2. Use Touchpad in the Right Manner
3. Make Use of Touchpad Gestures
4. Zoom In and Out
5. View Clipboard Items
6. Use Chromebook Search for Quick Tasks
7. Use Google Assistant
8. Take a Screenshot
9. Enable Caps Lock
10. Remap Keyboard Keys
11. Check Chromebook’s Storage
12. Preview Files Quickly
13. Open Task Manager
14. Pin Apps to Taskbar
15. Create Folders in Launcher
16. Use App Shortcuts
17. Use Apps in Split Screen
18. View and Switch Between Open Apps
19. Install Android Apps
20. Turn Web Pages into Chrome Apps
21. Install Chrome Extensions
22. Silence Select Notifications
23. Silence All Notifications
24. Connect Phone to Chromebook
25.... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mehvish Mushtaq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beware: Onyx ransomware destroys files instead of encrypting them]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/beware-onyx-ransomware-destroys-files-instead-of-encrypting-them/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/beware-onyx-ransomware-destroys-files-instead-of-encrypting-them/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T00:16:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new Onyx ransomware operation is destroying large files instead of encrypting them, preventing those files from being decrypted even if a ransom is paid. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PSA: Onyx ransomware destroys large files instead of encrypting them]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/psa-onyx-ransomware-destroys-large-files-instead-of-encrypting-them/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/psa-onyx-ransomware-destroys-large-files-instead-of-encrypting-them/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T00:16:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new Onyx ransomware operation is destroying large files instead of encrypting them, preventing those files from being decrypted even if a ransom is paid. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mesa 22.1-rc3 Released With Backports For Intel Raptor Lake P, Zink/Kopper On Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Mesa-22.1-rc3</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Mesa-22.1-rc3"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T23:38:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mesa 22.1 is gearing up for release in early to mid May while out today is the third weekly release candidate. Mesa 22.1-rc3 continues in back-porting many fixes and improvements from the feature code building up for next quarter's Mesa 22.2...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sharing Screen with Arch (EndeavourOS) + Gnome w/ Wayland in Chromium not working]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/udga8w/sharing_screen_with_arch_endeavouros_gnome_w/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/udga8w/sharing_screen_with_arch_endeavouros_gnome_w/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T22:55:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello /r/archlinux,
 I am pretty happy with wayland and gnome 42. The only Issue I have is that Firefox is working with screen sharing but Chromium results in Black Screen..
 ​
 Does someone know this Issue and can help me out?
 ​
 Known Issue? https://github.com/NixOS/nixpkgs/issues/91218
 ​
 Details:
   ~ ❯ pacman -Qs pipewire ✘ INT   00:51:42 local/gst-plugin-pipewire 1:0.3.50-1 Multimedia graph framework - pipewire plugin local/libpipewire02 0.2.7-2 Low-latency audio/video router and processor - legacy client library local/pipewire 1:0.3.50-1 Low-latency audio/video router and processor local/pipewire-alsa 1:0.3.50-1 Low-latency audio/video router and processor - ALSA configuration local/pipewire-jack 1:0.3.50-1 Low-latency audio/video router and processor - JACK support local/pipe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla Firefox e il "Tab Unloading" delle schede inattive]]></title>
        <id>3548|20220428000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/browser-455/mozilla-firefox-tab-unloading-schede-inattive-3548"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Negli ultimi tempi, in un vecchio elaboratore dotato di poca RAM (soltanto 3 GB), in cui ho installato Linux Mint, avevo notato che le schede (o tab) temporaneamente inattive, quando venivano da me richiamate, ricaricavano da zero la pagina internet da ultimo visitata, come se avessi ricercato quel determinato indirizzo per la prima volta.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Black Basta ransomware springs into action with a dozen breaches]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-black-basta-ransomware-springs-into-action-with-a-dozen-breaches/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-black-basta-ransomware-springs-into-action-with-a-dozen-breaches/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T21:46:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new ransomware gang known as Black Basta has quickly catapulted into operation this month, claiming to have breached over twelve companies in just a few weeks. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create and Manage a Telegram Channel]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=477615</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15253801/create-manage-telegram-channel"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram is a WhatsApp alternative that offers a wide range of interesting features. For instance, the app allows you to go beyond the scope of communicating with your immediate contacts by enabling you to reach people beyond these limits. This can be done via channels. In this article we’re going to show you how you can create and manage a channel on Telegram.
   

Content

What Are Telegram Channels?
How to Create a Channel in Telegram
How to Manage Your Telegram Channel
How to Enable Conversations in Your Telegram Channel
How to Delete a Telegram Channel
How to Find Channels to Subscribe to on Telegram
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Set Up Passcode Lock in Telegram
    
What Are Telegram Channels?
    
Telegram channels allow the broadcasting public messages to large audiences. They can be powerful tools especially for brands that... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexandra Arici</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A stop job is running everytime I halt my system!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ude580/a_stop_job_is_running_everytime_i_halt_my_system/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ude580/a_stop_job_is_running_everytime_i_halt_my_system/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T21:16:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've had my arch system for awhile and I have had this issue for as long as I can remember, but I do know it didn't happen straight after installation, it happened a couple of days later.
 Everytime I'm trying to shutdown or reboot my system, this with reboot, halt or shutdown now, it waits for a stop job and it takes the full two minutes or so for it to end in a timeout, same everytime. Journalctl tells me kwin_x11 and some other processes are causing this but I don't know why. The relevant logs from journalctl -p5 gives me
 Feb 26 00:55:55 Arch systemd[1]: session-2.scope: Stopping timed out. Killing. Feb 26 00:55:55 Arch systemd[1]: session-2.scope: Killing process 900 (kwin_x11) with signal SIGKILL. Feb 26 00:55:55 Arch systemd[1]: session-2.scope: Killing process 24491 (QSGRenderThrea…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Hate Bluetooth Audio: Here's Why]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/116275/i-hate-bluetooth-audio-heres-why/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/116275/i-hate-bluetooth-audio-heres-why/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T21:14:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re knee-deep in the world of Bluetooth, and the average customer has absolutely zero interest in wired headphones or speakers. Still, they complain about Bluetooth, and I happily complain with them. Bluetooth audio is one of the biggest downgrades in tech history—outside of a few situations, it’s the worst possible alternative to a messy wad of headphone cables.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub: How stolen OAuth tokens helped breach dozens of orgs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/github-how-stolen-oauth-tokens-helped-breach-dozens-of-orgs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/github-how-stolen-oauth-tokens-helped-breach-dozens-of-orgs/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T21:04:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub has shared a timeline of this month's security breach when a threat actor gained access to and stole private repositories belonging to dozens of organizations. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Download Images From Google Image Search]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=793566</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/793566/how-to-download-images-from-google/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s Image Search results are sometimes so beautiful that you want to save some of those images to your device. If you’ve found yourself in this situation, here’s how to download photos from your search results on desktop and mobile.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CPU temperature and battery life]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/udcytp/cpu_temperature_and_battery_life/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/udcytp/cpu_temperature_and_battery_life/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T20:25:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I should preface this by saying that I'm still pretty new to all this, and feeling somewhat overwhelmed by what is a pretty big black box to me.
 Up until just recently, my laptop's cpu temperature was running up to the mid 60s on idle and I'm not entirely sure why. I've done powertop --auto-tune as outlined in the wiki and it somehow managed to make the temperature worse (over 70C), which I can assume leads to a worse battery life.
 On top of all this, the temperature control seems to sometimes work well on power supply. The fan kicks on around 55C and runs until the temperature hits 50C, which I think is pretty ideal (similar to what I'm seeing on Windows at least). That only appears to be true on power supply though, because when I just unplugged it, the temperature shot up to 65C and remains there. I'm not hearing the fan speed up to compensate the rising temperature either.
 The power drain is still horrible.
 I assume there is some information I can provide that would help diagnose whatever is going on here. Please let me know what that is.
 At the very least, I can tell you some system info:
 OS: Arch Linux x86_64
 Host: XENIA 15 M37957-404
 Kernel: 5.17.4-arch1-1
 CPU: 11th Gen Intel i7-11800H (16) @ 4.600GHz
 GPU: NVIDIA GeForce RTX 3070 Mobile / Max-Q 
 GPU: Intel TigerLake-H GT1 [UHD Graphics]
 Right now I'm on the Intel GPU.
 Edit: Okay, so I thought about it makes sense that the fan is less aggressive on battery. The heat produced by the cpu is still there; the fan just pushes it elsewhere. In other words, it's sucking power either way. Saying that, the underlying issue is to figure out what's turned on that doesn't need to be, maybe?
 Thank you for any advice anyone can offer. I'm incredibly confused.
    submitted by    /u/-_H_-_E_-_L_-_P_-  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QNAP warns users to disable AFP until it fixes critical bugs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/qnap-warns-users-to-disable-afp-until-it-fixes-critical-bugs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/qnap-warns-users-to-disable-afp-until-it-fixes-critical-bugs/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T20:21:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Taiwanese corporation QNAP has asked customers this week to disable the AFP file service protocol on their network-attached storage (NAS) appliances until it fixes multiple critical Netatalk vulnerabilities. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[vagrant up --provider=libvirt takes ages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/udcp90/vagrant_up_providerlibvirt_takes_ages/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/udcp90/vagrant_up_providerlibvirt_takes_ages/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T20:13:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trying archlinux/archlinux vagrant image but it's stuck on:
  ==> default: Waiting for domain to get an IP address... 
 Sometimes it starts. But mostly is failing for minutes. Using libvirt provider. virsh list shows running.
 Can I debug that somehow? Only default configuration is used (changed nr of CPUs and memory size, nothing else).
 Thank you.
    submitted by    /u/Original_Two9716  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Boost Bass on Windows 10 or 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=797648</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/797648/how-to-boost-bass-on-windows/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T20:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Disappointed that the rafters aren’t shaking when you play your music? Both Windows 10 and Windows 11 offer an option to enhance your current bass levels. We’ll show you how to enable this option on your PC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save $20 on a Corsair Void RGB Elite USB Gaming Headset]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=483939</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15253562/corsair-void-rgb-elite-usb-gaming-headset"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking to get the maximum sound with your gaming? Instead of relying on a wireless set of earbuds, try a Corsair Void RGB Elite USB Gaming Headset. You need the right tools for the job. Along with the sound, you’ll have total comfort and customization.
    
Don’t miss a single sound in your game with this headset due to the custom-tuned 50-millimeter high-density neodymium audio drivers and 20Hz – 30,000Hz frequency range. A microphone will pick up your voice with great clarity from any direction and features a flip-up mute function and built-in LED light to indicate when you’re on mute.
    

    
Breathable microfiber mesh fabric and plush memory foam earpads are used in the Corsair Void RGB Elite USB Gaming Headset for lasting comfort through your long gaming sessions. It’s built to last you for years with the aluminum yokes. Customize the look of the headset with a wide array of colors and effects with RGB lighting in both ear cups.
    
Completely immerse yourself in 7.1 surround sound when... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Change the Tor Browser Language]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=799216</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/799216/change-tor-browser-language/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T19:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you use the Tor browser and you don’t like the default language, it’s easy to switch between various languages available in the browser. We’ll show you how to do that on both your desktop and your Android phone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nuovo POCO F4 GT: componenti flagship, prezzo budget - specifiche tecniche e link per acquisto scontato]]></title>
        <id>3559|20220427203318</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/smartphone-tablet-phablet-6/nuovo-poco-f4-gt-componenti-flagship-prezzo-budget-specifiche-tecniche-link-acquisto-scontato-3559"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T18:33:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Il nuovo POCO F4 GT di Xiaomi rappresenta la scelta ideale per chi cerchi il miglior rapporto prezzo/prestazioni in assoluto, in abbinata ad alcune funzionalità rivolte agli appassionati di gaming in mobilità. Sotto allo schermo AMOLED a 120 Hz troviamo lo Snapdragon 8 Gen 1, cioè il modello di punta di Qualcomm, i grilletti a levitazione magnetica e molte altre caratteristiche da "flagship" veicolate ad un prezzo davvero ridotto, per uno smartphone che si qualifica a tutti gli effetti come il "best buy" del momento
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yocto 4.0 Released For Embedded/IoT Linux Software Stack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Yocto-4.0-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Yocto-4.0-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T18:19:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Linux Foundation based Yocto Project for making it easy to create Linux-based IoT/embedded operating system software builds is out today with Yocto 4.0...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel Masquerade]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ud9zim/kernel_masquerade/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ud9zim/kernel_masquerade/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T18:13:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am setting up my server as i have previously with trials and am having issues with Masquerade on a nat setup. I have used several times before but cannot get it to work. Research suggests it requires modules in the kernel. 
 Does anyone know if this is right and has something changed?
 Turned out to be firewall once I worked it out. For some reason then interface name is not matching and as a result the default policy drop was kicking in. No idea why it was not a match as all is correct.
    submitted by    /u/UnusualBot1101  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft says Russia hit Ukraine with hundreds of cyberattacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-says-russia-hit-ukraine-with-hundreds-of-cyberattacks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-says-russia-hit-ukraine-with-hundreds-of-cyberattacks/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T18:09:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has revealed the true scale of Russian-backed cyberattacks against Ukraine since the invasion, with hundreds of attempts from multiple Russian hacking groups targeting the country's infrastructure and Ukrainian citizens. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weird sound fade with pipewire]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ud9tsx/weird_sound_fade_with_pipewire/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ud9tsx/weird_sound_fade_with_pipewire/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T18:06:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone, I just got arch on my asus ux433 and i haven't been able to make sound work out of the box. It's currently using pipewire with the necessary pipewire-* packages installed but i'm running in a weird bug where sound fades out after a couple of seconds of playback (like cutting the low frequencies and then there's nothing left at all). Sound is back after a few seconds but the bug comes back again and so on. Do you guys have any ideas? I have a realtek alc294 audio card, I tried a bunch of fixes but nothing is working.
    submitted by    /u/imjaacked  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Made It Easier to Hide Yourself from Google Search]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/116284/google-made-it-easier-to-hide-yourself-from-google-search/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/116284/google-made-it-easier-to-hide-yourself-from-google-search/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T18:02:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re looking to get back some of your privacy, Google recently introduced new policies that’ll let users protect themselves from Google Search. By that, we mean giving people control over what personally-identifiable information shows up in search results.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Substitute Text in Google Sheets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=795796</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/795796/substitute-text-in-google-sheets/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T18:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Important to managing data is updating it if things change. When you’re working with a text string in Google Sheets, you have a few ways to substitute that text without manually changing the string.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux Disabling Raw Access To Floppy Disks "FDRAWCMD" By Default]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-Disable-FDRAWCMD</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-Disable-FDRAWCMD"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T17:49:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's been a rough year for floppy disk support on Linux and goes to show the state of seldom maintained to unmaintained code...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to stop systemd automatically mounting usb drive]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ud98cs/how_to_stop_systemd_automatically_mounting_usb/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ud98cs/how_to_stop_systemd_automatically_mounting_usb/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T17:40:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, I have a usb stick which i once mounted with 'systemd-mount /dev/sdcX'. The problem is though, everytime i plug it in or restart my pc it gets automounted. I have no idea how to stop this i've tried unmounting it and remounting it with --automount=no but i dont know how to stop it doing this. i cant find any answers online or in the documentation
    submitted by    /u/Turbulent_Basil4934  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GRUB does not detect Windows 10, MBR with bios boot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ud8p74/grub_does_not_detect_windows_10_mbr_with_bios_boot/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ud8p74/grub_does_not_detect_windows_10_mbr_with_bios_boot/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T17:15:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, so I tried helping a friend dualbooting arch with windows 10, and we installed arch in bios mode because he had an MBR disk, and now GRUB does not detect Windows 10. GRUB_DISABLE_OS_PROBER=false is uncommented, and the grub.cfg has been regenerated. os-prober does not seem to generate any output, and I would like to know how we can fix this issue.
    submitted by    /u/samemessagewarnbot  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get Samsung’s Galaxy S22 Ultra for Its Lowest Price Ever]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=800602</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/800602/get-samsungs-galaxy-s22-ultra-for-its-lowest-price-ever/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T17:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s hard to believe that another month has come and gone, but here we are, closing out April in a big way. This week, you’ll find the best discounts so far on Samsung’s Galaxy S22 Ultra and S22+. You can also save big on a base Galaxy S22, a pair of Jabra earbuds, and a Withings hybrid smartwatch. Let’s get into it!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zach Laidlaw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Move a Window to Another Monitor on Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=797812</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/797812/how-to-move-a-window-to-another-monitor-on-windows-11/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re running multiple monitors on Windows 11, it’s easy to move an existing app window between two or more displays. We’ll show you how to do it using the mouse or a keyboard shortcut.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Classic 'Elder Scrolls' Games Arrive on Steam for Free]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/116239/classic-elder-scrolls-games-arrive-on-steam-for-free/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/116239/classic-elder-scrolls-games-arrive-on-steam-for-free/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T16:45:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ll spend the next few years waiting for Elder Scrolls VI, the upcoming sequel to Skyrim. But in the meantime, maybe we should enjoy some classic Elder Scrolls games. Bethesda just added five of its old titles to Steam, and three of them are free.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Auto HDR: supporto migliorato in Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Auto-HDR-supporto-migliorato-in-Windows-11_24440</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Auto-HDR-supporto-migliorato-in-Windows-11_24440"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T16:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Con la tecnica HDR (high dynamic range) è possibile migliorare la 'qualità dei pixel' permettendo di godere di immagini molto più realistiche e maggiormente aderenti alla realtà. HDR consente di avere immagini con una più ricca gamma di colori, bianchi più luminosi e neri più profondi.Abbiamo visto cos'è e come funziona HDR parlando anche delle differenze tra monitor HDR10, HDR10+ e Dolby Vision descrivendone le principali differenze.Per attivare HDR in Windows e la modalità Auto HDR, pensata per ottimizzare la resa dei contenuti SDR o a 'intervallo dinamico standard' basta agire sulle impostazioni del monitor. Abbiamo già visto come migliorare la resa del monitor o del display in Windows.Per apprezzare le migliorie introdotte nella resa delle immagini con HDR è possibile servirsi della funzione nascosta Split screen presentata da Microsoft e disponibile per tutti gli utenti avanzati.Basta aprire il prompt dei comandi con i diritti amministrativi e digitare:reg add HKLM\SYSTEM\CurrentControlSet\Control\GraphicsDrivers /v AutoHDR.ScreenSplit /t REG_DWORD /d 1Per disattivare la modalità Split screen basta usare il comando che segue:reg delete HKLM\SYSTEM\CurrentControlSet\Control\GraphicsDrivers /v AutoHDR.ScreenSplit /fLa novità riservata agli utenti di Windows 11 è che adesso, premendo Windows+G, facendo clic sull'icona dell'ingranaggio in alto, scegliendo Funzionalità di gioco e infine Modifica intensità HDR si può agire su una barra che aiuta a definire quanto i colori debbano essere più o meno vividi.La novità arriverà attraverso un aggiornamento della Xbox Game Bar distribuito attraverso il Microsoft Store.Gli utenti di Windows 11 potranno inoltre beneficiare presto del supporto multi-GPU per più schede video dedicate in configurazione Nvidia Scalable Link Interface (SLI) e AMD CrossFire.Maggiori informazioni sono reperibili nell'annuncio pubblicato da Microsoft..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grub/os-prober not detecting Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ud7dao/grubosprober_not_detecting_windows/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ud7dao/grubosprober_not_detecting_windows/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T16:18:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve been trying to dual-boot Arch and Windows 11 for a while now with GRUB but can’t seem to get GRUB to find Windows, from what I’ve found online, I hope this helps in understanding my problem:
 EFI partition is mounted to /boot Windows data partition is mounted to /win11
 grub-install —target=x86_64-efi —efi-directory=/boot —bootloader-id=GRUB
 grub-mkconfig -o /boot/grub/grub.cfg
 Found linux image… Found initrd image… Found fallback initrd image(s) in /boot… Warning: os-prober will be executed to detect other bootable partitions Its output will be used… Adding boot menu entry for UEFI Firmware Settings done
 efibootmgr -v BootCurrent: 0000 Timeout: 5 seconds BootOrder: 0001,0000 Boot0000* UEFI USB SanDisk… Boot0001* GRUB HD…
 /etc/fstab /dev/nvme0n1p6 UUID=… / ext4 rw.relatime 0 1
 /dev/nvme0n1p2 LABEL=SYSTEM UUID=… /boot vfat rw,relatime,fmask=0022,dmask=0022,codepage=437,iocharset=ascii,shortname=mixed,utf8,errors=remount-ro 0 2
 /dev/nvme0n1p4 LABEL=Windows UUID=… /win11 ntfs3 rw,relatime,uid=0,gid=0,iocharset=utf8 0 0
 /dev/nvme0n1p5 UUID=… none swap defaults 0 0
 I think I screwed something up because Windows doesn’t even show up in efibootmgr, but I have no idea. As always, thanks
    submitted by    /u/Zeno371  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[System error " Dependency failed /home"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ud71vp/system_error_dependency_failed_home/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ud71vp/system_error_dependency_failed_home/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T16:04:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[error
 My laptop was lagging so I restarted the pc by holding the power button. And then I got booted into this emergency mode. help needed
    submitted by    /u/GuyKage8  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Enable Secure Private DNS on Android]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=795644</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/795644/how-to-enable-secure-private-dns-on-android/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T16:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Almost everything you do on the internet starts with a DNS query, so having secure communication with a DNS provider is essential. This is where Android’s Private DNS feature comes into play.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gaurav Shukla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel Preps Some Big Graphics Driver Improvements For Linux 5.19]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=drm-intel-gt-next-5.19</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=drm-intel-gt-next-5.19"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intel open-source engineers sent in their initial batch of "drm-intel-gt-next" updates to DRM-Next today destined for the Linux 5.19 merge window...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accedere le app con due account diversi su Android (anche Whatsapp e Facebook)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2016/06/usare-unapp-con-due-account-insieme-su.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2016/06/usare-unapp-con-due-account-insieme-su.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T15:56:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grazie a una magica applicazione piuttosto recente e che funziona a meraviglia è possibile, per chiunque ne abbia l'esigenza, utilizzare una stessa applicazione anche con due account differenti, simultaneamente. Per esempio si possono separare gli account personali da quelli professionali di lavoro oppure tenere attività segrete e nascoste con un secondo account.

Esempi di applicazioni che può...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple's Repair Program Will Help The Company Double Down On Its Worst Practices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/116176/apples-repair-program-will-help-the-company-double-down-on-its-worst-practices/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/116176/apples-repair-program-will-help-the-company-double-down-on-its-worst-practices/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T15:54:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After half a year of silence, Apple has finally launched its Self Service Repair program. It’s a huge step for the company—customers can now buy authentic Apple parts and access official repair manuals. But Self Service Repair isn’t ideal for customers, and it gives Apple an excuse to double down on its worst practices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bug di sicurezza più pericolosi secondo chi si occupa di cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Bug-di-sicurezza-piu-pericolosi-secondo-chi-si-occupa-di-cybersecurity_24439</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Bug-di-sicurezza-piu-pericolosi-secondo-chi-si-occupa-di-cybersecurity_24439"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T15:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Le Autorità statunitensi, britanniche, canadesi, australiane e neozelandesi che si occupano di cybersecurity hanno pubblicato oggi la lista delle vulnerabilità software più pericolose perché ancora oggi attivamente sfruttate dai criminali informatici per aggredire i sistemi altrui.Si tratta delle vulnerabilità che hanno maggiormente colpito gli utenti e in particolar modo le realtà aziendali nel corso del 2021.Nelle due tabelle pubblicate all'interno del documento 2021 Top Routinely Exploited Vulnerabilities, si possono riconoscere anche riferimenti a bug di sicurezza non proprio recenti: ciò significa che molte aziende rimandano per troppo tempo l'installazione di patch cruciali per la protezione delle proprie infrastrutture informatiche.Gli esperti fanno notare che per tutte le vulnerabi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Wake on Lan" not possible?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ud6qic/wake_on_lan_not_possible/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ud6qic/wake_on_lan_not_possible/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T15:51:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, I'm trying to enable Wol by following the arch wiki article.
 Now if I do sudo ethtool eno1 (my PC is connected through a LAN-Cable to the internet), I'm getting the following output:
  Settings for eno1: Supported ports: [ TP ] Supported link modes: 10baseT/Half 10baseT/Full 100baseT/Half 100baseT/Full 1000baseT/Full Supported pause frame use: Symmetric Receive-only Supports auto-negotiation: Yes Supported FEC modes: Not reported Advertised link modes: 10baseT/Half 10baseT/Full 100baseT/Half 100baseT/Full 1000baseT/Full Advertised pause frame use: Symmetric Advertised auto-negotiation: Yes Advertised FEC modes: Not reported Speed: 1000Mb/s Duplex: Full Auto-negotiation: on Port: Twisted Pair PHYAD: 0 Transceiver: internal MDI-X: Unknown Current message level: 0x000060e4 (24804) link ifup rx_err tx_err hw wol Link detected: yes 
 The two lines are missing:
  Supports Wake-on: <value> Wake-on: <value> 
 so does that mean, that my network adapter doesn't support Wol?
    submitted by    /u/TornaxO7  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Subaru Just Revealed the Pricing for Its Solterra EV]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/116197/subaru-just-revealed-the-pricing-for-its-solterra-ev/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/116197/subaru-just-revealed-the-pricing-for-its-solterra-ev/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T15:39:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Subaru initially teased the Solterra, its first all-electric SUV, about a year ago. And now that the company has announced pricing for the EV, we happily move another step closer to finally being able to purchase one. The highly-anticipated 2023 Solterra starts at $44,995.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzanne Humphries</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VW's New Electric Microbus "Documentary" Is All About Good Vibes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/116192/vws-new-electric-microbus-documentary-is-all-about-good-vibes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/116192/vws-new-electric-microbus-documentary-is-all-about-good-vibes/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T15:36:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve seen hints and teasers of Volkswagen’s new Microbus for nearly five years, but the company finally made it official in March. The VW ID. Buzz electric bus will hit the streets later this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russian govt impersonators target telcos in phishing attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/russian-govt-impersonators-target-telcos-in-phishing-attacks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/russian-govt-impersonators-target-telcos-in-phishing-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T15:32:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A previously unknown and financially motivated hacking group is impersonating a Russian agency in a phishing campaign targeting entities in Eastern European countries. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Try Windows 11 Without Nuking Windows 10]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=477521</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15253286/try-latest-windows"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 packs a lot of improvements over Windows 10. Unfortunately, to do a full Windows 11 install, you have to renounce your stable Windows 10.
    
The good news is that you can try Windows 11 on your primary machine without messing with Windows 10. You have three options: use a virtual machine, dual booting or a Windows 11 simulator. You can pick the method that works best for you, and we’ll show you how to set each up in what follows.
   

Content

Use a Virtual Machine
Dual Boot Windows 11 With Windows 10
Try the Windows 11 Simulator

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Use Windows 11 without a Microsoft Account
    
Use a Virtual Machine
    
A virtual machine (VM) allows you to install Windows 11 on top of your Windows 10 OS. In short, you’ll have... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Kanyoro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity agencies reveal top exploited vulnerabilities of 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cybersecurity-agencies-reveal-top-exploited-vulnerabilities-of-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cybersecurity-agencies-reveal-top-exploited-vulnerabilities-of-2021/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T15:08:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In partnership with the NSA and the FBI, cybersecurity authorities worldwide have released today a list of the top 15 vulnerabilities routinely exploited by threat actors during 2021. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come riconoscere le recensioni false su Amazon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/04/come-riconoscere-le-recensioni-false-su.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/04/come-riconoscere-le-recensioni-false-su.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T15:06:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon deve una buona fetta del suo successo alle recensioni dei prodotti: tutti gli utenti che acquistato un determinato prodotto possono lasciare una semplice recensione valutativa (indicando da 1 a 5 stelle) e abbellirla con da una recensione scritta, spesso correlata anche da foto e da video. Purtroppo anche nel campo delle recensioni troviamo i disonesti: alcuni venditori infatti fanno uso...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How worried should I be about a few out of date packages in a AUR?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ud5ph4/how_worried_should_i_be_about_a_few_out_of_date/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ud5ph4/how_worried_should_i_be_about_a_few_out_of_date/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T15:05:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most of these packages I rarely use:
 Brave-bin, pamac-all, snapd_glib, ttf-ms-win10-auto
 I might be able to delete all of the above but occassionally use them.
 I do use virtio-win fairly often with qemu VM's
 ​
 I just did a "oh crap" I forgot that for a while update and all is working fine other than the fact that pamac didn't build. . . .I mostly don't use it.
    submitted by    /u/Im-Mostly-Confused  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Insert and Animate 3D Models in Microsoft PowerPoint]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=797075</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/797075/insert-and-animate-3d-models-shapes-powerpoint/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T15:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re looking for a unique way to spruce up your slideshow, check out the 3D model feature in Microsoft PowerPoint. You can insert a 3D image then resize it, rotate it, and even animate it with a nifty effect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Differenza Windows Subsystem for Linux WSL e Hyper-V]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Differenza-Windows-Subsystem-for-Linux-WSL-e-Hyper-V_24438</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Differenza-Windows-Subsystem-for-Linux-WSL-e-Hyper-V_24438"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T14:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Si parla sempre più spesso di Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSL), la soluzione software integrata in Windows 10 e Windows 11 che permette di eseguire Linux in Windows avviando le applicazioni anche con interfaccia grafica.Con l'introduzione, da parte di Microsoft, del componente chiamato WSLg è infatti possibile eseguire programmi Linux in Windows con interfaccia grafica richiamandoli dal menu Start, dal desktop, dalla barra delle applicazioni del sistema operativo o da qualunque altra locazione di memoria.
Cos'è Windows Subsystem for Linux o WSL
 Microsoft ha rilasciato nel tempo due versioni di WSL: la prima, presentata ad agosto 2016 per gli utenti di Windows 10, era un layer di compatibilità.Inizialmente permetteva soltanto il caricamento da una finestra del terminale una bash di Ubuntu e SUSE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How do I bind a keyboard button to mouse?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ud57ay/how_do_i_bind_a_keyboard_button_to_mouse/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ud57ay/how_do_i_bind_a_keyboard_button_to_mouse/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T14:43:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[xte 'mouseclick 2' Menu 
 in ~/.xbindkeysrc from https://wiki.archlinux.org/title/Mouse_buttons#Binding_mouse_buttons_to_keyboard_functions Results in only clicking the mouse button, holding keyboard key does not hold down the mouse button, I also tried xdotool xdotool click 2 but its also same.
    submitted by    /u/Zaiden_J  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FreeBSD/riscv64 on QEMU with Arch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ud4idl/freebsdriscv64_on_qemu_with_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ud4idl/freebsdriscv64_on_qemu_with_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T14:11:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey everyone, if this question is off-topic I apologize in advance and if you can redirect me into correct channel or any other source where I can ask question I would happily do, for now I think this is the best place to ask. I daily drive arch and wanted to run freeBSD/riscv64 image on qemu following this https://wiki.freebsd.org/riscv#QEMU_Emulator and u-boot guide: https://github.com/u-boot/u-boot/blob/master/doc/board/emulation/qemu-riscv.rst However it seems I'm doing something wrong and compilation results in error here is all additional info: https://pastebin.com/72shccGa
 ​
 EDIT: Solved by following guide exactly.. I needed to use export CROSS_COMPILE= instead of cross_toolchain
    submitted by    /u/Daxsis  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LEGO Succulents: The Perfect Plants for People Who Kill Plants]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lifesavvy.com/126456/lego-succulents-the-perfect-plants-for-people-who-kill-plants/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lifesavvy.com/126456/lego-succulents-the-perfect-plants-for-people-who-kill-plants/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T14:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t have much of a green thumb? LEGO is about to help you out with its brand-new Botanical Collection.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shea Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Bluetooth Headphones for Nintendo Switch of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=759871</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/759871/best-bluetooth-headphones-for-nintendo-switch/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The best Bluetooth headphones for the Nintendo Switch produce outstanding audio quality, have good noise cancellation, and stay powered for hours. Here are the best options to pick up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Colp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>