<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-07-19T02:22:23.367Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anybody in here a fan of Blackarch linux?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w2h46h/anybody_in_here_a_fan_of_blackarch_linux/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w2h46h/anybody_in_here_a_fan_of_blackarch_linux/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T02:19:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/frozengrim1331  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Removing multilib and multilib testing repositories from pacman]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w2ftcf/removing_multilib_and_multilib_testing/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w2ftcf/removing_multilib_and_multilib_testing/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T01:17:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone, I encountered a weird bug in that I am trying to remove the multilib and multilib testing repositories. I followed the Wiki's instructions to remove the already installed packages
 (with # pacman -R $(comm -12 <(pacman -Qq | sort) <(pacman -Slq multilib | sort)))
 ,then comment out the Include = /etc/pacman.d/mirrorlist line for both of them in /etc/pacman.conf and to upgrade my system.However, after commenting, a pacman -Syu gave me the error:
 error: failed to synchronize all databases (no servers configured for repository)
 However, when I uncommented the lines and ran a pacman -Syu, it worked as normal.
 When I neofetch, I do see that all multilib packages have been removed. Here is my pacman.conf.
 Thank you very much for the help
 ​
 1 # 2 # /etc/pacman.conf 3 # 4 # S…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Regarding Xwaylands fractionalscaling]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w2fi9o/regarding_xwaylands_fractionalscaling/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w2fi9o/regarding_xwaylands_fractionalscaling/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T01:02:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This attempt at solving the problem for Xwaylands blurry apps seems interesting.
 My general understanding of the problem is that xorg apps running over the xwayland interface use a lower resolution which is then scaled up resulting in blurryness. Reading the above post it seems to be fixable on fedora35 through a gnomesetting? Can someone educate me on 1. If this is actually a fix to the blurryness problem of xwayland? 2. If yes: can asimilar thing be achieved for other desktopenvironments?
 Sorry for long responstimes Europe/Berlin timezone here.
    submitted by    /u/tristan_rw  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stop Your PC from Making Random USB Noises]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=168487</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/4771704/stop-random-usb-connect-noises-windows"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re all familiar with the Connect/Disconnect noise Windows makes when you connect and disconnect USB devices. But things get a little spooky when you hear the random USB noises for no reason. You’re just working on your computer when suddenly and inexplicably, the USB noises go haywire for a few seconds, connecting and reconnecting, while you wonder what demons possessed your computer. This tutorial includes tips that can help you exorcise these phantom USB noises.
   

Content

Using Device Manager
USBDeview
Turn Off USB Notification Sounds
Try a New USB Port
Avoid USB Hubs
Try System Restore
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:SSD vs. HDD vs. USB Flash Drive: Everything You Need to Know
    
Using Device Manager
    
This is the quick-and-easy method (though not as robust as the tool mentioned later). If it does... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Crystal Crowder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to enable foot's systemd service?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w2e05x/how_to_enable_foots_systemd_service/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w2e05x/how_to_enable_foots_systemd_service/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T23:51:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Foot terminal ships with a systemd unit. But I don't see any information on how to use it. I see that there's a socket and a service. If I try to enable the service with --user, I get a message that it,
  
is added as a dependency to a non-existent unit wayland-instance@.target
  
Is this working as expected? If not, how should we enable it?
    submitted by    /u/Pound_Hash  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New GPU, got the drivers working, now it won't do dual monitors. Help!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w2dlss/new_gpu_got_the_drivers_working_now_it_wont_do/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w2dlss/new_gpu_got_the_drivers_working_now_it_wont_do/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T23:31:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello again!
 After I got my GPU drivers to work a few days ago, my PC has refused to output to more than one monitor at a time. I have a monitor-sized 1080p TV hooked up to an HDMI port, and an old Dell monitor plugged in to one of the DisplayPort sockets (cable is DVI on the monitor end)
 When the machine boots, the BIOS and GRUB appear on the Dell monitor. Once the driver and X load, it switches the Dell monitor off and displays on the TV (which is my primary display anyway). Opening ARandR, it only seems to detect the TV. Even unplugging the HDMI cable from the card, both while the PC is running and before boot, it never switches back to the Dell monitor. Only ever uses it during boot.
 Specs, in case you need them:
 AMD Ryzen 5 2600
 16GB DDR4
 PowerColor Radeon RX 6600
 Gigabyte B450…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMDGPU LLVM Backend Prepares FP8 Instructions For GFX940 / Next-Gen CDNA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMDGPU-GFX940-FP8-Instructions</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMDGPU-GFX940-FP8-Instructions"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T22:27:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In addition to AMD engineers being busy working on RDNA3 graphics support for their open-source Linux graphics driver stack, concurrently they have also been working on enabling GFX940 as their next-gen CDNA part, presumably to launch as the AMD Instinct MI300 if traditions hold...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[O&O DeskInfo mostra le informazioni del sistema direttamente sul desktop]]></title>
        <id>3620|20220719000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/windows-10/amp-deskinfo-mostra-informazioni-sistema-direttamente-desktop-3620"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[O&O DeskInfo è una piccola applicazione portable che permette di visualizzare sul desktop tutte le più importanti informazioni sul sistema operativo, come utilizzo della CPU, della RAM o il traffico della scheda di rete. Già al primo avvio si può scegliere di farlo partire con il sistema operativo in modo da avere un monitoraggio continuo oppure richiamarlo solo nel momento del bisogno.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How many times have you installed Arch Linux .]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w2bdao/how_many_times_have_you_installed_arch_linux/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w2bdao/how_many_times_have_you_installed_arch_linux/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T21:54:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I reflect most Arch users have installed the system at least 2 times; the first, to try the system and have a first contact; and the second, because the system broke, you did something wrong the first time, you wanted to improve your installation, etc. Personally, I have installed Arch between 5 and 7 times on 3 different computers, how many times have you installed the system? And‏‏‎‏‏‎‏‏‎‏‏‎­most importantly, why? Quick survey, don't overthink it, it's just curiosity. View Poll
    submitted by    /u/theylick  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fix “Something Went Wrong Try Again” Issue in Google Play]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=504111</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15438422/fix-something-went-wrong-try-again-google-play"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While downloading certain apps from Google Play, you might come across a  “Something went wrong. Try again” error. Even though you have reliable Wi-Fi/mobile data Internet, the problem doesn’t go away. This is a significant issue affecting Android devices as it prevents you from downloading select apps when you need them urgently. We will discuss the best possible ways to mitigate the issue.
   

Content

Why Does It Say "Something Went Wrong Try Again?"
What Causes the Error?
How to Resolve "Something Went Wrong Try Again" Error in Google Play Store
1. Fix Your Google Account(s) Associated with Google Play
2. Remove and Re-Add Google Account 
3. Clear Google Play Services and Other Apps Cache 
4. Force Stop Google Play 
5. Check If Automatic Date and Time is Enabled
6. Reset Network Settings
7. Reset All Settings
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sayak Boral</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[View your Android phone notifications on your Linux desktop]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w2aojh/view_your_android_phone_notifications_on_your/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w2aojh/view_your_android_phone_notifications_on_your/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T21:24:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I want to share a little project I created - as an alternative to KDEConnect - which displays your Android phone notifications on your Linux desktop. It is called Android 2 Linux Notifications.
 It basically consists of a simple Android app (available on Google Play and F-Droid) and a server which runs on your computer written in Python. They communicate over LAN (including encryption and authentication of course). It is very easy to set-up and doesn't contain unnecessary features in my opinion.
 Here are some links in case you are interested:
  
GitHub repositories (contributions are welcome!): 
 Server
 App
 
 App Download 
 Google Play
 F-Droid (don't wonder, the screenshots are broken there)
 
 Server is available on the AUR
 Basically everything you need to know including how to set it up and install everything
  
I really hope you like it! In case you have a question, just write a comment here or create an issue on GitHub.
    submitted by    /u/patri9ck  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Amazon Kindle Unlimited Worth It?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/123380/is-amazon-kindle-unlimited-worth-it/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/123380/is-amazon-kindle-unlimited-worth-it/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T21:09:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With over a million titles in its collection, Kindle Unlimited is by far the best-known eBook subscription service. But it isn’t included with Amazon Prime and costs $10 a month—a hefty fee for a service that mainly relies on self-published authors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 Useful Tools Microsoft Edge Has That Google Chrome Doesn’t]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=800544</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/800544/6-useful-tools-microsoft-edge-has-that-google-chrome-doesnt/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Edge may have come on in leaps and bounds in the last few years, but does it now have enough useful and unique features to replace Chrome as the world’s favorite browser? A few features may have you convinced.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Russ Ware</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to install Windows 10 on archlinux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w297z8/how_to_install_windows_10_on_archlinux/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w297z8/how_to_install_windows_10_on_archlinux/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T20:23:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I first installed Endeavor OS because I wanted to get into cybersecurity and I had heard that Linux was the best bet. But due to incompatibility reasons I want to switch back to windows and either dual boot or just boot from a USB. The only tools I have at my disposal are the archlinux laptop and a 8gb USB im not sure if its important but its running something Kde.
 PS: I know practically nothing about how to use Linux other than gitclone, ls, cd and stuff like that the only reason I was able to install this was by a friend but hes busy for a couple of weeks and i would like to switch back asap
    submitted by    /u/9bow57  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unable to get xorg/desktop environment working on an old 2005 computer running arch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w28spu/unable_to_get_xorgdesktop_environment_working_on/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w28spu/unable_to_get_xorgdesktop_environment_working_on/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T20:05:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Im relatively new to and not good with configuring linux and I’ve just installed arch linux on some old 2005 computer using a YouTube tutorial. Whenever I try to get a desktop environment working, I get a blinking cursor upon boot. Does anyone have any idea how to solve this? I just wanna get xfce or a window manager working on here and actually have a functional old desktop computer
 I suspect its Xorg as whenever I try to run startx it comes back with this error, and my .xinitrc file is completely empty. The error: Server terminated with error xinit: giving up xinit: unable to connect to X server: Connection refused xinit: server error 
 Specs:
 OS: Arch Linux ×86_64 Kernel: 5.18.12-arch1-1 Packages: 320 Shell: bash 5.1.16 CPU: AMD Athlon 64 3200+ 2.200GHZ GPU: 01:00.0 Silicon Integrated Systems [SiS] 661/741/760 PCI/AGP or 662/7616x PCIE VGA Display Adapter Memory:654MiB
    submitted by    /u/Valxb70  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can I Use an Apple Watch Without an iPhone?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=802150</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/802150/can-i-use-an-apple-watch-without-an-iphone/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple sells the world’s most popular smartwatch, but it’s not a standalone product. If you don’t have an iPhone, you might be wondering what you can do with an Apple Watch or if you can use one at all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Login Prompts on Gnome accounts and Lutris don't work]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w2817d/login_prompts_on_gnome_accounts_and_lutris_dont/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w2817d/login_prompts_on_gnome_accounts_and_lutris_dont/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T19:33:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I asked about this just three days ago on the easy questions megathread. Turns out it might not just be an easy question. Here's what I said back on the 15th.
  
I just noticed that anytime I click on a login button for apps that pull up a web page displayed on the app itself instead of opening a tab on my default browser (Firefox), the app will either just close the page or just kill the app. Here's an error I get for trying to login to Google through Gnome Accounts: 
 03:24:49.0736 online-accounts-cc-panel: WARNING: Error showing account: Child process killed by signal 11 
 And here's an error I get trying to login to Epic Games through Lutris: 
 DEBUG 2022-07-15 03:26:41,829 [base.login:285]:Connecting to Epic Games Store 
 Segmentation fault (core dumped) 
 Am I missing a package or something?
  
I also have some videos of what's going on here.
 https://streamable.com/gvzlpj
 One thing I found out is that it doesn't work on Wayland. On X11, the webpages open up.
 https://streamable.com/cs1r1s
 Again, am I missing a package?
    submitted by    /u/SomeAwesomeGuyDa69th  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save $900 on an LG OLED C1 Series 65″ Smart TV]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=507298</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15438294/lg-oled-c1-series-65-smart-tv"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T19:25:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even a week later, there are still a few stray Amazon Prime Days deals to be found. You can get an LG OLED C1 Series 65″ Smart TV for an amazing $900 off! With that great price, you still have Alexa, 4K, AI, Dolby Vision IQ, Dolby Atmos, and a gaming mode.
    
The OLED display has over 8 million pixels that each turn on independently, leaving you with perfect black, more than a billion rich colors, and endless contrast. You’ll feel like you’re watching movies in the theater with Cinema HDR, Dolby Vision IQ, and Dolby Atmos. Filmmaker Mode allows you to see movies the way they are intended to be seen. Netflix, Prime Video, Apple TV+, Disney+, and LG channels are built in to make watching even easier.
   
 
   
The α9 Gen 4 AI processor 4K in the LG C1 Series Smart TV adjusts the picture and sound using deep-learning algorithms to make everything look its best, regardless of whether you’re watching the latest blockbuster or binge-worthy TV shows. You’ll also have... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Ranger as default file explorer; ie firefox download prompt, LibreOffice download prompt, etc.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w27h2p/using_ranger_as_default_file_explorer_ie_firefox/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w27h2p/using_ranger_as_default_file_explorer_ie_firefox/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T19:10:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How can I use Ranger for all of my upload download needs when a prompt asks me for a location? Eg when firefox requests a location for a download or an upload. I'm currently using mimeo as a mime handler.
 Thanks!
    submitted by    /u/Frederic-Henry  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SuperTux's package ships Discord Rich Presence now?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w27e8b/supertuxs_package_ships_discord_rich_presence_now/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w27e8b/supertuxs_package_ships_discord_rich_presence_now/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T19:07:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So I tried updating today. Suddenly, this:
 error: failed to commit transaction (conflicting files) supertux: /usr/include/discord_register.h exists in filesystem (owned by discord-rpc-git) supertux: /usr/include/discord_rpc.h exists in filesystem (owned by discord-rpc-git) Errors occurred, no packages were upgraded. 
 The discord-rpc-git package is from AUR, and provides Discord's rich presence stuff by itself as its own package, and another game installed from AUR on my system depends on discord-rpc.
 I figured I should report this somewhere, but I'm not sure where's best to; the bug reporting form does not have a category for community repo packages lol
 EDIT: Posted it on the bug tracker: https://bugs.archlinux.org/task/75368
    submitted by    /u/Architector4  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Check Your Phone: Google Pay Is Now Google Wallet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=819018</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/819018/check-your-phone-google-wallet-is-now-google-pay/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T19:01:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google announced back in May that the Google Pay app would be renamed to Google Wallet, complete with a fresh modern design. The update is now starting to roll out to Android phones.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Save a Picture as a PDF]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=816979</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/816979/save-picture-as-pdf/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes, you may want to save a picture (often a document image) as a PDF on your device. Luckily, Windows, Mac, Android, iPhone, and iPad offer the feature of downloading images from the internet as PDFs. We’ll show you how to use those options.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pipewire-pulse Auto-switch input device to wired headset mic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w27040/pipewirepulse_autoswitch_input_device_to_wired/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w27040/pipewirepulse_autoswitch_input_device_to_wired/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T18:50:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I tried enabling the module-switch-on-port-available module in pipewire-pulse but I cannot get the default microphone device to switch to headset mic. The headset audio switches fine but not the mic. Amy I missing a configuration to enable the wired headset plugin to auto switch the microphone device?
    submitted by    /u/j6jr85ehb7  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel Working On New Hardware-Based Prevention For Spectre-BHI Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-Spectre-BHI-BHI_DIS</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-Spectre-BHI-BHI_DIS"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T18:30:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While Retbleed was grabbing the headlines last week and attention of kernel developers, an Intel engineer sent out a new patch series adding Linux kernel support for "BHI_DIS" as a new hardware-based mitigation that appears to be coming with future Intel CPUs for better fending off Spectre-BHI (Branch History Injection) that was disclosed back in March. But initial indications are this new hardware-based prevention may be even more costly for performance and is not being enabled by default...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make a Song Your Ringtone on Android]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=816675</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/816675/how-to-make-a-song-a-ringtone-on-android/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T18:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want your Android phone to play your favorite song when you get a call? If so, set your song as the default ringtone for all callers or specific ones. We’ll show you how to do that on your phone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ubuntu Working On GNOME Wayland Support For The AMD Xilinx Kria KR260]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=GNOME-Wayland-WIP-KR260</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=GNOME-Wayland-WIP-KR260"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Canonical engineer Daniel van Vugt who is known for his work on enhancing the upstream GNOME desktop stack to improve the experience for Ubuntu has recently taken up interest in getting the AMD-Xilinx Kria KR260 working with the GNOME Wayland session. The Kria KR260 is for the recently-announced AMD/Xilinx Robotics Starter Kit...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russia fines Google $358 million for not removing banned info]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/russia-fines-google-358-million-for-not-removing-banned-info/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/russia-fines-google-358-million-for-not-removing-banned-info/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T17:51:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A court in Moscow has imposed a fine of $358 million (21 billion rubles) on Google LLC for failing to restrict access to information considered prohibited in the country. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FBI warns of fake cryptocurrency apps used to defraud investors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fbi-warns-of-fake-cryptocurrency-apps-used-to-defraud-investors/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fbi-warns-of-fake-cryptocurrency-apps-used-to-defraud-investors/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T17:36:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The FBI warned that cybercriminals are creating and using fraudulent cryptocurrency investment applications to steal funds from US cryptocurrency investors. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[/dev/sda2 is apparently in use by the system; will not make a filesystem here!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w253wu/devsda2_is_apparently_in_use_by_the_system_will/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w253wu/devsda2_is_apparently_in_use_by_the_system_will/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T17:30:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm trying to install Arch, and when I try formatting the /dev/sda2 partition, to be 'mkfs.ext4 /dev/sda2' the message "/dev/sda2 is currently in use by the system; will not make a filesystem here!" pops up. I've searched for the message in the Arch Wiki to no avail. So I'm asking you all for help- thanks :)
    submitted by    /u/Osinacho  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trifo Ollie Pet AI Smart Robot Vacuum Review]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=501888</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15438120/trifo-ollie-pet-ai-smart-robot-vacuum"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T17:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you have pets, you also have to vacuum often to clean up all the hair and dander that accumulates. It’s a daunting task but necessary. The Trifo Ollie Pet AI Smart Robot Vacuum helps make the task is as easy as setting a schedule on your phone or even telling Alexa or Google Assistant a room needs cleaning. With a focus specifically on pet owners, I was thrilled to give this vacuum a test drive in my own home.
    
This is a sponsored article and was made possible by Trifo. The actual contents and opinions are the sole views of the author who maintains editorial independence even when a post is sponsored.
    
Overview of Features
    
The Trifo Ollie Pet AI Smart Robot Vacuum offers some unique features over most robot vacuums. Not only does it clean your floors, but it provides ways to interact with your pet. After all, vacuums and pets don’t always get along so well, so a more pet-friendly option may just make your fur baby less afraid of the vacuum.
   
 Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Crystal Crowder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Verizon’s C-Band 5G Is About to Get Much Faster]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=818904</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/818904/verizons-c-band-5g-is-about-to-get-much-faster/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T17:23:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier this year, Verizon and T-Mobile started deploying 5G service on C-Band, a mid-band frequency that offers faster speeds at farther distances. Verizon is now preparing an upgrade that could make C-Band even better.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fitbit Charge 5 Update Addresses Battery Drain Bug]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/123374/fitbit-charge-5-update-addresses-battery-drain-bug/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/123374/fitbit-charge-5-update-addresses-battery-drain-bug/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T17:19:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly a full year after its launch, the Fitbit Charge 5 suffers from some odd and annoying bugs. And many of these problems, particularly battery drain and Bluetooth connection dropouts, were first reported in 2021. Now, it seems that Fitbit is addressing these two complaints with a firmware update.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Documenti Google: come condividere, usare segnalibri, link e commenti]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Documenti-Google-come-condividere-usare-segnalibri-link-e-commenti_22929</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Documenti-Google-come-condividere-usare-segnalibri-link-e-commenti_22929"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T17:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Documenti Google è probabilmente uno degli strumenti migliori per collaborare su un progetto a più mani lasciando che i collaboratori possano inserire aggiunte e applicare modifiche in tempo reale.Conosciuta anche come Google Docs la soluzione di Google per l'elaborazione di documenti di testo è collaborativa: chi decide di utilizzarla non deve installare nulla in locale perché tutte le funzionalità del wordprocessor sono interamente fruibili da browser web e gli interventi apportati dai collaboratori su uno stesso documento compariranno in tempo reale.Per creare un nuovo documento basta accedere alla home page di Documenti Google quindi fare clic su Vuoto oppure digitare doc.new nella barra degli indirizzi del browser e premere Invio.In alto a destra, accanto al pulsante Condividi, appariranno dei circoletti ciascuno contenente l'icona scelta come foto da ogni collaboratore nella sezione Informazioni personali dell'account Google.Nel caso degli utenti che accedono senza disporre di un account utente Google oppure senza aver preventivamente effettuato il login, appaiono icone raffiguranti animali stilizzati e l'indicazione Utente anonimo.


Condividere i documenti Google
 Spostando il puntatore del mouse sul pulsante Condividi in alto a destra si leggerà Privato solo per me: ciò significa che per impostazione predefinita il documento Google sul quale si sta lavorando è accessibile e modificabile solo dall'utente che lo ha creato e che è attualmente collegato.

Cliccando sul pulsante Condividi è possibile inserire gli account Google degli utenti con cui si desidera condividere il documento specificando se possano soltanto visualizzarlo, commentarlo o anche modificarlo (Editor).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Move a Table in Microsoft Word]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=810690</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/810690/how-to-move-a-table-in-word/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T17:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Although you probably strive to format your Word document as you compose it, there may be a time when you need to rearrange items. This is common if you use images, objects, and for this guide, tables.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to clone files owned by root between 2 machines]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w245ui/how_to_clone_files_owned_by_root_between_2/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w245ui/how_to_clone_files_owned_by_root_between_2/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T16:51:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I want to clone the contents of a local directory /foo/ into /foo/ on a remote machine. The directory /foo/ and contents are owned by root:homestar with permissions 640. The remote machine is running an ssh server with both password authentication and root login disabled. The local machine is not running an ssh server. I have root access on both machines and my user has sudo permissions on both machines, the ability to ssh into the remote machine, and is in group homestar. I have tried to do the cloning with
 $ sudo sshfs strongbad@poopsmith:// tmp -o Identityfile=strongbad_rsa -o allow_root
 $ sudo rsync -vaH --delete --force --chmod=D0750,F0640 --usermap=*:root --groupmap=*:homestar /foo/ tmp/foo
 but get a "permission denied" error. I think the error is because the allow_root option only affects the local machine and not the remote machine. How do I clone a local directory owned by root onto a remote machine?
    submitted by    /u/AppointmentNearby161  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come rintracciare pacchi provenienti da Cina, USA o altri paesi]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2019/02/come-rintracciare-pacchi-provenienti-da.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2019/02/come-rintracciare-pacchi-provenienti-da.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T16:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sempre più prodotti vengono spediti dalla Cina o da altri nazioni estere quando acquistiamo su Amazon o su eBay, senza dimenticare i siti specializzati nella vendita di prodotti cinesi come Wish e AliExpress. Se al momento dell'acquisto scegliamo la spedizione tracciata otterremo un codice di tracking molto diverso rispetto a quelli ottenibili dai corrieri italiani, visto che difficilmente possono essere tracciati sui siti che siamo abituati ad utilizzare sul territorio italiano.
 In questa guida vi mostreremo come rintracciare i pacchi provenienti dall'estero e in particolare dalla Cina, indirizzandovi perso i siti Web in grado di tracciare qualsiasi spedizione internazionale. Riusciremo così a capire dov'è il nostro pacco anche in caso di spedizioni molto lunghe e laboriose, scoprire se …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnerabilità Windows più pericolose del mese di luglio 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Vulnerabilita-Windows-piu-pericolose-del-mese-di-luglio-2022_24785</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Vulnerabilita-Windows-piu-pericolose-del-mese-di-luglio-2022_24785"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T16:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[È ormai già passata una settimana da quando Microsoft ha rilasciato gli aggiornamenti di sicurezza di luglio 2022. Sebbene alcuni esperti consiglino di aspettare ancora qualche giorno prima di procedere con l'installazione delle patch di questo mese, la presenza di alcune vulnerabilità piuttosto pericolose suggerisce di 'giocare d'anticipo'.E neanche tanto d'anticipo visto che una delle falle di sicurezza più pericolose di questo mese, contraddistinta dall'identificativo CVE-2022-22047 è già utilizzata dai criminali informatici per condurre attacchi più o meno mirati.CISA (Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency), agenzia governativa statunitense che si occupa di contribuire alla riduzione delle minacce che possono causare problemi ad infrastrutture critiche utilizzate a livello nazionale, ha lanciato l'allerta proprio sulla vulnerabilità CVE-2022-22047 esortando gli enti pubblici ad aggiornare i rispettivi sistemi informatici entro e non oltre il 2 agosto prossimo.Pur non assegnando un punteggio particolarmente elevato in termini di gravità, Microsoft conferma che la falla CVE-2022-22047 può essere sfruttata per acquisire privilegi SYSTEM su qualunque sistema Windows vulnerabile (leggasi, ove non sia stata applicata la patch correttiva già disponibile).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hyundai's Concept Car Blends Hydrogen and Electric for Impressive Results]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/123359/hyundais-concept-car-blends-hydrogen-and-electric-for-impressive-results/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/123359/hyundais-concept-car-blends-hydrogen-and-electric-for-impressive-results/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T16:13:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Between the Hyundai Ioniq 5 and the newly announced Ioniq 6, Hyundai is on a roll right now. And to keep the momentum going, we’re now getting our first look at the Hyundai N Vision 74, a high-performance hybrid-electric hydrogen sports car.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Important Note On The Alder Lake Mobile Power/Performance With Linux 5.19]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=article&amp;item=linux-519-alderlakep&amp;num=1</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=article&amp;item=linux-519-alderlakep&amp;num=1"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T16:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After dealing with the Intel Alder Lake P GuC firmware breakage around Linux 5.19 Git that is now to be addressed by the upstream Intel developers, it was on to performance testing the shiny new Core i7 1280P with this kernel due to be released as stable within the next two weeks... For those concerned about maximum performance, there was a glaring performance regression for this Alder Lake P on the new kernel being released as stable later this month. Well, a default change in performance/behavior at least but the power efficiency / performance-per-Watt tended to be better on this new kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to List the Installed Packages on Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=810903</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/810903/linux-list-installed-packages/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T16:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With thousands of free Linux applications, it’s easy to lose track of what you once installed but no longer use. Here’s how to list the installed applications on the major Linux families.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKay</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMDVLK 2022.Q3.1 Released With Fixes, Minor Enhancements]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMDVLK-2022.Q3.1-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMDVLK-2022.Q3.1-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AMD today published AMDVLK 2022.Q3.1 as their latest snapshot of this open-source Radeon Vulkan driver for Linux systems...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You'll Never Own This Plastic Surface Duo Prototype]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/123351/youll-never-own-this-plastic-surface-duo-prototype/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/123351/youll-never-own-this-plastic-surface-duo-prototype/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T15:58:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks to a deleted eBay listing, we now have images of a Surface Duo with a plastic outer shell and a dual-camera system. The seller indicates that this is a Surface Duo 2 “dev unit,” though it’s probably a canceled prototype for an “affordable” Surface Duo 2.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up WordPress Using Docker in Ubuntu]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=504604</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15437700/set-up-wordpress-docker"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress is the world’s most popular content management system (CMS). More than 40% of the web runs on WordPress. Docker is a containerizing system used to run your software in an isolated environment. The concept of containerization is not new in the software development world. But Docker makes it very developer friendly.
    
In this article, we are going to show you how to install WordPress site in a Docker container.
   

Content

Why Docker?
Docker Installation
Services We Need for WordPress
Using a Docker-Compose File
Running WordPress Inside Docker
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}    
Why Docker?
    
Why Docker, you may ask?
    
The answer is simplicity. In Docker, your application is containerized within one image. There is no need to do complicated installation and configuration to get it running.
   
 Image source: Wikimedia creative commons
   
Not to mention, it is also faster and easier for you to migrate/upgrade to another server. Say your WordPress becomes very popular... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hrishikesh Pathak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Axerve POS Easy, la soluzione conveniente che abbatte le commissioni: cos'è e come funziona]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Axerve-POS-Easy-la-soluzione-conveniente-che-abbatte-le-commissioni-cos-e-e-come-funziona_24732</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Axerve-POS-Easy-la-soluzione-conveniente-che-abbatte-le-commissioni-cos-e-e-come-funziona_24732"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T15:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A partire dal 30 giugno 2022 la platea delle figure che devono accettare pagamenti delle prestazioni tramite POS è stata estesa e se fino a un periodo recente era possibile sottrarsi all'obbligo di accettazione dei pagamenti elettronici mediante carta di credito o di debito oggi questo non è più possibile. Le categorie di esercenti in possesso di partita IVA che negano il pagamento da parte del cliente mediante transazione elettronica sono quindi passibili di sanzione: 30 euro più una quota variabile pari al 4% del controvalore complessivo della spesa. Ovviamente sono escluse multe nel caso in cui la transazione elettronica non possa avvenire per 'oggettiva impossibilità tecnica'. Con il preciso obiettivo di contrastare il fenomeno dell'evasione fiscale il legislatore ha previsto l'obbligo di attrezzarsi al fine di gestire i pagamenti elettronici. Per i professionisti, i negozianti, gli artigiani e in generale per tanti esercenti, dotarsi di un POS per gestire i pagamenti elettronici veniva considerata una spesa superflua, comunque rimandabile, soprattutto per via delle commissioni elevate. 
Cos'è Axerve POS Easy e come funziona
 Axerve POS Easy è una soluzione pratica ed economica che viene incontro alle specifiche esigenze proponendo soluzioni sia senza commissioni come Smart POS Easy a canone che a basse commissioni come Smart POS Easy a commissioni.

Entrambe le offerte, prevedono un POS intelligente che si connette sia in 4G che tramite WiFi in modo da poterlo utilizzare in qualunque situazione, all'interno delle mura della propria attività come all'esterno, ad esempio quando si dovesse raggiungere l'utente per un servizio in loco.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Opera Software fixes Windows Reliability Monitor in browser]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179796</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/07/18/opera-software-fixes-windows-reliability-monitor-in-browser/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T15:22:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Opera Software has fixed the Windows Reliability Monitor issue in the company's Opera web browser. Last week, we reported that the Opera web browser was causing seemingly unrelated entries in the Windows […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Opera Software fixes Windows Reliability Monitor in browser appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Outlook Is Down for Some People Right Now]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=818890</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/818890/outlook-is-down-for-some-people-right-now/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T15:01:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you having email problems with an Outlook.com account? Don’t worry, you’re not alone — it’s a widespread problem, and Microsoft is trying to fix it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Google Sheets Features to Boost Your Productivity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=811228</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/811228/google-sheets-features-to-boost-productivity/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T15:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Saving time, performing tasks easily, working efficiently, and maximizing output are all parts of productivity. With these several Google Sheets features, you can boost your productivity and work more effectively on your spreadsheets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tutela del diritto d'autore: Cloudflare obbligata a modificare record DNS pubblici]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Tutela-del-diritto-d-autore-Cloudflare-obbligata-a-modificare-record-DNS-pubblici_24784</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Tutela-del-diritto-d-autore-Cloudflare-obbligata-a-modificare-record-DNS-pubblici_24784"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T14:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Un'azienda come Cloudflare non ha certo bisogno di presentazioni: offre strumenti per velocizzare il caricamento delle pagine Web riducendo significativamente i workload dei server Web grazie all'utilizzo di efficaci sistemi di caching.La società, con sede a San Francisco (Stati Uniti), offre anche strumenti per proteggere le applicazioni Web dagli attacchi informatici (Web Application Firewall), da attacchi DDoS e mette a disposizione servizi CDN (Content Delivery Network).Nell'offerta di Cloudflare ci sono anche server DNS pubblici che chiunque può utilizzare per risolvere i nomi a dominio al posto di quelli dell'operatore di telecomunicazioni italiano. Abbiamo visto come funziona il DNS e quali sono i migliori DNS per navigare.I server DNS Cloudflare che tutti possono utilizzare sono 1.1.1.1, 1.0.0.1 (IPv4); 2606:4700:4700::1111 e 2606:4700:4700::1001 (IPv6).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung's Next-Gen Foldables Get a Leaked Launch Date]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/123340/samsungs-next-gen-foldables-get-a-leaked-launch-date/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/123340/samsungs-next-gen-foldables-get-a-leaked-launch-date/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T14:51:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It seems that Samsung is sticking with its annual launch schedule this year. A leaked promotional image from Evan Blass indicates that Samsung will reveal the Galaxy Z Fold 4, Galaxy Z Flip 4, and Galaxy Watch 5 during a live event on August 10th.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roaming Mantis hits Android and iOS users in malware, phishing attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/roaming-mantis-hits-android-and-ios-users-in-malware-phishing-attacks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/roaming-mantis-hits-android-and-ios-users-in-malware-phishing-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T14:42:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After hitting Germany, Taiwan, South Korea, Japan, the US, and the U.K. the Roaming Mantis operation moved to targeting Android and iOS users in France, likely compromising tens of thousands of devices. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Snapchat Wants to Be the Next Facebook Messenger]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=818860</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/818860/snapchat-wants-to-be-the-next-facebook-messenger/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T14:32:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Snapchat started off as a simple app for sending temporary photos to others, but it has slowly evolved into a full-blown messaging service (and video platform). Today, Snapchat revealed a major new feature: a desktop web app.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did anyone had this issue?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w20s1e/did_anyone_had_this_issue/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w20s1e/did_anyone_had_this_issue/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T14:30:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello,i have a lenovo legion 5 15ARH05,and when i was unblocking & connecting to wifi via rfkill for unblocking and iwctl for wifi,i noticed that when i tried to ping google.com to test the internet connection it says a error and when i tried to pacman -Syu it makes me think that it doesnt connect i never had this feature before but i see this for the first time
    submitted by    /u/HazelReko  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does pacman have an auto-update feature?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w20rk5/does_pacman_have_an_autoupdate_feature/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w20rk5/does_pacman_have_an_autoupdate_feature/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T14:29:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm looking to create a tor relay that will run 24/7 on an old laptop. It'll be a very miminal install, will only have the absolute minimum number of packages to successfully run a tor middle relay. I'm aware of the risks of automatically updating all the packages in arch, but I want my tor package to be updated on a regular basis, as soon as they're released, at the very least.
 Is my only choice creating a shell script that executes once in a while or is there a more refined option?
    submitted by    /u/IcyEvening2484  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft investigates ongoing Exchange Online, Outlook outage]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-investigates-ongoing-exchange-online-outlook-outage/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-investigates-ongoing-exchange-online-outlook-outage/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T14:26:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft is investigating an ongoing outage impacting Microsoft 365 services after customers have reported experiencing issues while trying to sign into, access, and receive emails on the outlook.com portal and via Exchange Online. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reinstalled keyring, upon refresh im receiving an error]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w20k64/reinstalled_keyring_upon_refresh_im_receiving_an/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w20k64/reinstalled_keyring_upon_refresh_im_receiving_an/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T14:20:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After booting up my arch linux install after a year of neglect, im trying to do some cleanup before I try and update the system. First, I reinstalled the keyring with the command
 sudo pacman -S archlinux-keyring
 After this I refreshed the keyring with the command
 sudo pacman-key --refresh-keys
 However, upon doing this, I am receiving an error that says
 gpg: refreshing 124 keys from hkps://hkps.pool.sks-keyservers.net
 gpg: keyserver refresh failed: Server indicated a failure
 ==> ERROR: A specified local key could not be updated from a keyserver.
 I have tried changing the keyserver in /etc/pacman.d/gnupg/gpg.conf to https://keyserver.ubuntu.com, but this doesn't seem to work either.
 Any help would be appreciated.
    submitted by    /u/Ziiinx  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Per ridurre l'utilizzo della CPU su Windows 11 e 10]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/07/come-ridurre-lutilizzo-della-cpu-su.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/07/come-ridurre-lutilizzo-della-cpu-su.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T14:14:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Non appena notiamo che il compute apre i programmi troppo lentamente, il primo controllo che possiamo fare è aprire Gestione attività e controllare quale processo sta saturando le risorse di sistema, in particolare il processore. Dopo aver aperto Gestione attività possiamo infatti premere direttamente sulla colonna CPU per ordinare i processi in base al carico del processore: il processo che supera il 50% delle capacità della CPU è in grado di far rallentare pesantemente qualsiasi altra attività al computer.
 Se il nostro computer è davvero troppo lento e non sappiamo come recuperare le vecchie performance, nella guida che segue vi mostreremo come ridurre l'utilizzo elevato della CPU su Windows 11 e Windows 10, recuperando le prestazioni perdute seguendo alcuni semplici consigli.
  
LEGGI …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enforcing Password History in Your Windows AD to Curb Password Reuse]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/enforcing-password-history-in-your-windows-ad-to-curb-password-reuse/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/enforcing-password-history-in-your-windows-ad-to-curb-password-reuse/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T14:04:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[65% of end-users openly admit to reusing the same password for one or more (or all!) of their accounts. Password history requirements discourage this behavior by making it more difficult for a user to reuse their old password. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sponsored by Specops</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 5 Best Password Managers of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=780233</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/780233/best-password-manager/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the increasing number of services that need accounts, the pile-up of passwords has become frustrating. Thankfully, password managers can help untangle the modern mess of technology and keep your accounts secure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Albert Bassili</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VRChat Is a Universe of Virtual Worlds: Here’s What It’s Like]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=798868</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/798868/vrchat-is-a-universe-of-virtual-worlds-heres-what-its-like/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T13:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s hard to imagine that you can leave this world behind with a $300 electronic gadget, but that’s the promise of VRChat. All you need is an Oculus Quest 2 to socialize in VR and get a glimpse of the promised “metaverse.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sydney Butler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Edifier Stax Spirit S3 Headphones Review: Planar Magnetic Drivers For the Win]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/122838/edifier-stax-spirit-s3-headphones-review-planar-magnetic-drivers-for-the-win/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/122838/edifier-stax-spirit-s3-headphones-review-planar-magnetic-drivers-for-the-win/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T13:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Headphones with planar magnetic drivers are typically (but not always) super expensive, but Edifier’s Stax Spirit S3 cans offer a relatively affordable, compact alternative. These headphones boast quite a bit, and I’m happy to say they live up to the hype.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Chaney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telefono Google: come funziona l'app per gestire le chiamate]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Telefono-Google-come-funziona-l-app-per-gestire-le-chiamate_24783</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Telefono-Google-come-funziona-l-app-per-gestire-le-chiamate_24783"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T12:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sebbene i moderni smartphone siano assimilabili ormai a dei computer nei quali è conservato e tenuto a portata di mano ogni tipo di dato, la parte telefonica resta sempre il cuore centrale del dispositivo.L'app Telefono Google è stata sviluppata dall'azienda di Mountain View per i dispositivi Android e consente, grazie al dialer integrato, non soltanto di comporre i numeri telefonici mediante la tastiera virtuale ma anche di gestire i contatti in modo diretto.Nella parte superiore è presente una casella di ricerca che aiuta a individuare rapidamente i contatti da raggiungere mentre nella parte inferiore ci sono tre icone: Preferiti, Recenti e Contatti. La prima consente di avere in un'unica schermata i contatti ai quali si telefona più spesso, si inviano messaggi o si effettuano videochiamate.La seconda icona mostra i contatti recenti (ad esempio le chiamate ricevute o effettuate) mentre la terza consente di accedere alla rubrica dei contatti.Toccando sul nome di un contatto si può effettuare una chiamata telefonica (anche via VoIP sulle versioni di Android meno recenti), inviare un messaggio (un SMS oppure un contenuto 'ricco' usando Google Messaggi e protocollo RCS) o effettuare una videochiamata con app come Google Duo e Meet che presto si uniranno.
Cercare attività locali non presenti tra i contatti
 Uno dei punti di forza di Google Telefono consiste nel riconoscimento delle attività commerciali che effettuano una chiamata.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here's Everything Coming to Netflix the Week of July 18, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lifesavvy.com/137211/heres-everything-coming-to-netflix-the-week-of-july-18-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lifesavvy.com/137211/heres-everything-coming-to-netflix-the-week-of-july-18-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T12:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another week, another major Netflix launch. The streaming service might have hit a home run releasing Stranger Things over the Fourth of July holiday, but it’s not done yet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shea Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Do Streaming Services Know You’re Using a VPN?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=817615</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/817615/how-do-streaming-services-know-youre-using-a-vpn/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T12:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve ever tried watching Netflix using a VPN, you’re likely familiar with some of the issues surrounding VPNs and streaming. Netflix, Hulu, Amazon Prime, and many other streaming services don’t want you to access their content with a VPN and will either restrict what you can watch or block you entirely. So how do they even know that you’re using a VPN?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fergus O'Sullivan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[App per cambiare la schermata di blocco di Android]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2014/02/cambiare-schermata-di-blocco-su-android.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2014/02/cambiare-schermata-di-blocco-su-android.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T11:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sui telefoni Android si può modificare quasi tutto inclusa la schermata di blocco, ossia la schermata che si vede quando il telefono è in standby e che protegge il telefono da sguardi indiscreti.
 Come vedremo, ci sono diverse applicazioni gratuite per cambiare aspetto e aggiungere anche diverse funzionalità alla schermata di blocco, facendola diventare più utile, più bella e più interattiva e soprattutto più sicura (senza notifiche visibili).
 Vediamo insieme come sostituire la schermata di blocco di Android, puntando solo su app sicure e affidabili vista la pericolosità della modifica (la schermata di blocco protegge anche i pagamenti NFC e le notifiche personali, quindi meglio andarci cauti con questo tipo di modifiche).
 LEGGI ANCHE: Migliorare le notifiche su Android sul blocco-scherm…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All of my packages are newer than when I upgrade]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w1xcmw/all_of_my_packages_are_newer_than_when_i_upgrade/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w1xcmw/all_of_my_packages_are_newer_than_when_i_upgrade/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T11:49:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[:: Starting full system upgrade...
 warning: asciidoc: local (10.2.0-1) is newer than community (10.1.4-1)
 warning: boost-libs: local (1.78.0-3) is newer than extra (1.78.0-2)
 warning: btrfs-progs: local (5.18.1-1) is newer than core (5.17-1)
 warning: ca-certificates-mozilla: local (3.79-1) is newer than core (3.78-1)
 warning: cups: local (1:2.4.2-1) is newer than extra (1:2.4.1-1)
 warning: edk2-armvirt: local (202205-1) is newer than extra (202202-2)
 warning: exo: local (4.16.3-2) is newer than extra (4.16.3-1)
 warning: fakeroot: local (1.29-1) is newer than core (1.28-1)
 warning: glib2: local (2.72.2-1) is newer than core (2.72.1-1)
 warning: glib2-docs: local (2.72.2-1) is newer than core (2.72.1-1)
 warning: glibc: local (2.35-6) is newer than core (2.35-5)
 warning: gnutls: lo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Every Game Microsoft Ever Included in Windows, Ranked]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=803643</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/803643/every-game-microsoft-ever-included-in-windows-ranked/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T11:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past 36 years, Microsoft has included over a dozen different games with its Windows releases (depending on how you count.) We took a look through history and ranked them, worst-to-best. Which game would you rank as number one?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Asahi Linux Update Brings Experimental Apple M2 Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Asahi-Linux-Apple-M2-Initial</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Asahi-Linux-Apple-M2-Initial"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T10:30:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Asahi Linux has issued an update with initial support for the Mac Studio powered by the M1 Ultra SoC as well as having initial (experimental) suppoirt for the new Apple M2 hardware...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Internal Roblox Documents Hacked and Posted Online]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=507043</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15437263/internal-roblox-documents-hacked"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T10:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It seems like if you’re a company with a popular online presence that you
should expect to be hacked at some point. The latest to be hacked is the gaming platform Roblox. A cybercriminal connected with the right person in Roblox and posted internal employee documents online in what appears to be an extortion attempt.
   
Also read:How to Fix Roblox Not Updating or Downloading on Your Mac
    
Roblox Employee Documents Stolen
    
The hacked documents appear to be stolen from a Roblox employee. These documents have inform­ation that appears to be related to Roblox games and their creators. There is also information about several people, assumably employees, included.
    
Roblox said in a statement, “These stolen documents were illegally obtained as part of an extortion scheme that we refused to cooperate with. We acted quickly upon learning of the incident, engaged independent experts to complement our information security team, and have... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Account Microsoft, rilevata un'attività insolita. Non sempre c'è un problema]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Account-Microsoft-rilevata-un-attivita-insolita-Non-sempre-c-e-un-problema_24782</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Account-Microsoft-rilevata-un-attivita-insolita-Non-sempre-c-e-un-problema_24782"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T10:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nei giorni scorsi ci è capitata una cosa strana. Un account Microsoft non risultava più accessibile via IMAP da client di posta. In questi casi la prima operazione da fare consiste nel controllare, previo login da browser Web, il contenuto della pagina Guarda quando e dove hai usato il tuo account: in questo modo si possono verificare gli accessi effettuati da qualunque dispositivo e con qualsiasi connessione.Come altri fornitori anche Microsoft controlla da quali dispositivi e da quali segmenti di indirizzi IP l'utente usa tipicamente collegarsi al suo account. Tant'è vero che la pagina citata in precedenza mostra il device utilizzato, l'indirizzo IP pubblico assegnato al dispositivo o comunque al router, la locazione geografica approssimativa e altre informazioni utili. Tra di esse spicca anche Tipo di sessione: nella colonna corrispondente Microsoft indica le operazioni che sono state effettuate sull'account.Nel caso dell'account citato in apertura, la pagina Guarda quando e dove hai usato il tuo account riportava molteplici operazioni di Sincronizzazione automatica da un indirizzo IP statunitense.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux Laying Out Guidelines To Avoid Kernel Updates Breaking Firmware Compatibility]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-No-Firmware-Breakage</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-No-Firmware-Breakage"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T10:01:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stemming from my article last week noting how Linux 5.19 Git broke Intel Alder Lake P graphics support due to requiring new firmware while not retaining backwards compatibility with the existing Intel GuC firmware, a solution is still being worked on prior to Linux 5.19 final whether it be a revert or the proposed patch working on GuC v69/70 firmware compatibility. Linux firmware guidelines are also being proposed to ensure kernel developers in the future don't try to break firmware support guarantees...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel's entire Arc A-Series Desktop Graphics Card lineup leaks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179791</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/07/18/intels-entire-arc-a-series-desktop-graphics-card-lineup-leaks/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T09:50:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just yesterday, Intel gave us some insight on one of its upcoming Arc A-Series desktop graphics card. The company said that its Intel Arc A750 GPU performs similar to Nvidia's RTX 3060 […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Intel's entire Arc A-Series Desktop Graphics Card lineup leaks appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XFS Improvement For Linux 5.20 Enhances Scalability For Large Core Count Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.20-XFS-Scalability</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.20-XFS-Scalability"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T09:45:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of several improvements being prepared for the XFS file-system with the upcoming Linux 5.20 cycle is focused on improving the CIL scalability for systems with many CPU cores...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More ASUS Motherboards Will Have Working Sensor Support With Linux 5.20]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.20-ASUS-EC-Sensors</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.20-ASUS-EC-Sensors"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T09:32:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ASUS-EC-Sensors driver that provides better and faster hardware sensor reading for ASUS motherboards on Linux and premiered earlier this year in Linux 5.18 is continuing to broaden its list of supported ASUS motherboards...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another Longtime Intel Linux Engineer Joins Google]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Ben-Widawsky-Leaves-Intel</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Ben-Widawsky-Leaves-Intel"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T09:19:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ben Widawsky who had been at Intel for the past seventeen years, most of which were spent improving their open-source Linux graphics driver as well as other Linux kernel contributions, has joined Google...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Proton explains the technical issues that caused the recent ProtonMail outages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179787</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/07/18/proton-explains-the-technical-issues-that-caused-the-recent-protonmail-outages/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T09:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week was a tough one for Proton users, the company experienced multiple outages spread across 3 days. Yesterday, Proton sent out an email to its users to explain the issues behind […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Proton explains the technical issues that caused the recent ProtonMail outages appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stalld 1.17 Brings LoongArch Support, Bug Fixes For Thread Stall Detection & Boosting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Stalld-1.17-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Stalld-1.17-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T09:03:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat released Stalld 1.17 this past week as the newest version of this open-source daemon used for thread stall detection and boosting on Linux...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Permessi app Android non più visualizzati nel Google Play Store: brutta mossa]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Permessi-app-Android-non-piu-visualizzati-nel-Google-Play-Store-brutta-mossa_24781</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Permessi-app-Android-non-piu-visualizzati-nel-Google-Play-Store-brutta-mossa_24781"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T08:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google ha presentato di recente anche in Italia il suo nuovo Play Store. Oltre a un design più accattivante e a un'interfaccia notevolmente più chiara, il Google Play Store visualizza adesso un insieme differente di informazioni per ciascuna app pubblicata.Particolare attenzione è riposta sugli aspetti legati alla privacy ovvero, per esempio, sulle informazioni che vengono condivise con terze parti, sui dati raccolti, sulle misure di sicurezza implementate dallo sviluppatore.È certamente una buona cosa perché abbiamo visto più volte in passato come la presenza di tracker Android sia diffusissima.Incredibilmente, tuttavia, Google ha deciso di rimuovere le indicazioni sui permessi usati da ogni app Android ospitata sul Play Store. È una mossa che va, a nostro avviso, nella direzione sbagliata: è infatti essenziale che gli utenti sappiano da subito quali autorizzazioni usa un'app Android.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 7 sistema operativo sempre più immortale. Supporto esteso fino al 2026?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-7-sistema-operativo-sempre-piu-immortale-Supporto-esteso-fino-al-2026_24780</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-7-sistema-operativo-sempre-piu-immortale-Supporto-esteso-fino-al-2026_24780"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T08:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft non l'ha ancora confermato in via ufficiale ma Windows 7, sistema operativo ritirato 'per la maggior parte degli utenti' il 14 gennaio 2020 potrebbe essere supportato fino al 2026 nell'ambito del programma ESU.ESU è acronimo di Extended Security Updates: si tratta del programma a pagamento riservato alle aziende che permette di ricevere aggiornamenti per Windows 7 fino a metà gennaio 2023. Abbiamo visto che per il supporto esteso ESU di Windows 7 sono stati applicati costi crescenti di anno in anno.A distanza di 6 mesi dalla data di abbandono di Windows 7 anche nell'ambito del programma ESU, arriva la notizia che Microsoft sarebbe intenzionata ad estendere il supporto per ulteriori tre anni: durante questo periodo di tempo, che terminerebbe a gennaio 2026, gli utenti aziendali di Windows 7 continuerebbero a ricevere gli aggiornamenti di sicurezza.Microsoft non ha confermato ufficialmente la novità ma l'analisi del contenuto degli aggiornamenti KB5015861 e KB5015862 rilasciati questa settimana ha messo in evidenza degli indizi davvero interessanti.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Print the First Match and Stop With Grep]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?post_type=devops&amp;p=800695</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/devops/how-to-print-the-first-match-and-stop-with-grep/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T06:02:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[grep is a search utility in Linux used for matching content. By default, it will print out any line that matches, which might include a lot of output. If you only care about the first match, you can limit the output to just the first line.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Heddings</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[App Permissions are no longer displayed on Google Play]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179784</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/07/18/app-permissions-are-no-longer-displayed-on-google-play/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T05:01:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Play is the default store on most Android devices. Most Android users use the store to download new apps and games, and to update them. Up until now, Google Play displayed […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post App Permissions are no longer displayed on Google Play appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I read the wiki but...]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w1qqem/i_read_the_wiki_but/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w1qqem/i_read_the_wiki_but/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T04:49:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I need to know if i need anything else more than : pipewire pipewire-pulse pipewire-alsa lib32-pipewire
 for listening audio through my sound card and control the volume with GUI.
 (i dont need to remap anything)
 Anyone know ?
    submitted by    /u/Geomian  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I keep getting an error when doing archinstall]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w1pmlz/i_keep_getting_an_error_when_doing_archinstall/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w1pmlz/i_keep_getting_an_error_when_doing_archinstall/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T03:46:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Traceback (most recent call last): File "/usr/bin/archinstall", line 8, in <module> sys.exit(runas_a_module()) File "/usr/lib/python3.10/site-packages/archinstall/init.py", line 281, in run_as_a_module File "/usr/lib/python3.10/site-packages/archinstall/lib/profiles.py", line 195, in execute script.execute() self.spec.loader.exec_module(sys.modules[self.namespace]) File "<frozen importlib._bootstrap_external>", line 883, in exec_module File "<frozen importlib._bootstrap>", line 241, in _call_with_frames_removed File "/usr/lib/python3.10/site-packages/archinstall/examples/guided.py", line 286, in <module> if not archinstall.update_keyring(): line 46, in update_keyring File "/usr/lib/python3.18/site-packages/archinstall/lib/networking.py", if run_pacman ("-Sy --noconfirm archlinux-keyring").…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Problems with Unity Editor on Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w1nhov/problems_with_unity_editor_on_linux/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w1nhov/problems_with_unity_editor_on_linux/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T01:54:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/Snoo_44353  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Things randomly crashing on my install]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w1n52a/things_randomly_crashing_on_my_install/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w1n52a/things_randomly_crashing_on_my_install/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T01:36:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, for about a week or two I have noticed that things have randomly been crashing on my install for no apparent reason. Whether it be Firefox, Discord, games, or my entire system, things are just randomly crashing. I have looked through my system logs but have not had any luck finding anything. I do find the core dumps of programs that crashed, but with no hint to what caused it. Has anyone else been experiencing anything similar over the past few weeks, and if so have you found a solution?
 Specs:
 R5 2600x
 RX 5600 XT
 32 gb ddr4 3600 cl18
 B450 Tomahawk
    submitted by    /u/smi1eybone  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come continuare ad utilizzare Internet Explorer 11 su Windows 10 e 11]]></title>
        <id>3510|20220718000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/internet-explorer-147/come-continuare-utilizzare-internet-explorer-11-windows-10-11-3510"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Per quanto Internet Explorer 11 sia ormai un browser obsoleto, e abbandonato da Microsoft che lo ha sostituito con Microsoft Edge, rimangono sempre alcuni siti, in particolare aziendali, che lo richiedono perché non sono mai stati aggiornati. Con i computer che hanno Windows 11 come sistema operativo, e Windows 10 con tutti gli aggiornamenti, l’uso di Internet Explorer 11 è stato proprio disabilitato e succede che Internet Explorer “sparisce” e si apre Edge al suo posto.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How do I install Arch w/ OpenRC/S6?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w1hyum/how_do_i_install_arch_w_openrcs6/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w1hyum/how_do_i_install_arch_w_openrcs6/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T21:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are like no tutorials on this and I just wanna know. Not really very many noticeable issues with systemD, I just wanna try other options. Seems fun.
 Thank you!
    submitted by    /u/the_maggie  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux 5.19-rc7 Released Following A Tough Week With Retbleed, Intel GPU Firmware Snafu]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-rc7-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-rc7-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T21:18:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linus Torvalds just released Linux 5.19-rc7 following a busy week due to the Retbleed security mitigation and not only the CPU overhead performance impact it puts on users but the mess it has on kernel development especially when it comes to embargoed issues that make the patches difficult to review/test well prior to embargo lift...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pacman stdout and stderr redirection via Script]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w1hhwq/pacman_stdout_and_stderr_redirection_via_script/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w1hhwq/pacman_stdout_and_stderr_redirection_via_script/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T21:07:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've wondering whether it's possible, and wise to redirect the output of pacman to a logfile or /dev/null. I want to create a script that send the least amount of information to the Screen, however, I'd like the information to be useful as well.
 I also want to avoid removing pacman prompts from the user's view.
 Is there a pacman option for a quieter less verbose mode? or could I do something like
 sudo pacman -Syu 2>&1 SomeLogFile.txt
 Why might that be a good or bad idea? Are there better alternatives?
 Thanks.
 EDIT:
 Thanks to u/lucasrizzini for providing some sane pacman and terminal commands for dealing with pacman's output. This is looking quite promising for a script usage.
    submitted by    /u/RandomXUsr  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is my iq too used archlinux?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w1hh8l/is_my_iq_too_used_archlinux/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w1hh8l/is_my_iq_too_used_archlinux/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T21:07:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi I have a windows 11 laptop and want to know how to get rid of it? I meant if my iq is too low to use Linux.
    submitted by    /u/alt_right98  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is the Line Under the Battery on the iPhone Lock Screen?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=802975</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/802975/what-is-the-line-under-the-battery-on-the-iphone-lock-screen/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The iPhone has a pretty simple and intuitive interface, but there are still some things that appear with no explanation. One such thing is the line under the cell signal, Wi-Fi, and battery icons on the lock screen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Reasons You Should Switch to Google Phone on Android]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=800390</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/800390/5-reasons-you-should-switch-to-google-phone-on-android/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Android phones are, well, phones at the core. You may not think much about the phone app that came pre-installed, but like many things in Android, it can be changed. You should try the Google Phone app.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gnomes login manager keeps freezing when I resume in a specific way.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w1fmsm/gnomes_login_manager_keeps_freezing_when_i_resume/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w1fmsm/gnomes_login_manager_keeps_freezing_when_i_resume/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T19:44:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If I resume from hybrid-sleep by opening my lid gnomes login manager works fine, but if I leave my laptop open and it goes into hybrid-sleep after 20 minutes and I resume by pressing the power button the login manager just freezes.
    submitted by    /u/LarryIsTheBestEver  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Houseplants Get Addicted to Texting with the Raspberry Pi Pico W]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/123311/houseplants-get-addicted-to-texting-with-the-raspberry-pi-pico-w/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/123311/houseplants-get-addicted-to-texting-with-the-raspberry-pi-pico-w/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T19:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you knew what your houseplants were thinking, they probably wouldn’t die. Or is that just an excuse? A new Raspberry Pi Pico W project that turns houseplants into texting addicts, providing the perfect way to test your green thumb and moral fortitude.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Download a Discord Profile Picture]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=816002</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/816002/how-to-download-discord-profile-picture/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T19:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[See someone using cool art or a funny meme as their profile picture on Discord? While there’s no official way to download someone’s profile picture to your device, there are workarounds. We’ll show you what those workarounds are.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenDoas - How to make it NOT to ask for password for the second time?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w1dg0m/opendoas_how_to_make_it_not_to_ask_for_password/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w1dg0m/opendoas_how_to_make_it_not_to_ask_for_password/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T18:08:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, so I may explained it wrong in the title so I want to explain it here:
 With sudo, when you enter a shell for the first time and then enter some command with sudo, it asks you for a password, but when you enter some command with sudo the second time (in the same shell) it does not. How do I make something similar with (Open)Doas?
    submitted by    /u/DominiCzech  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Take a Break From Someone on Facebook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=815843</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/815843/how-to-take-a-break-from-someone-on-facebook/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T18:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Facebook’s “Take a Break” feature, you can make it so you see less of someone’s posts in your feed, control what the other person can see in your profile, as well as change who can see the posts between you and that person. We’ll show you how to configure this option.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your Favorite 'Metal Gear' Games Return to Consoles Later This Year]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/123320/your-favorite-metal-gear-games-return-to-consoles-later-this-year/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/123320/your-favorite-metal-gear-games-return-to-consoles-later-this-year/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T17:13:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Late last year, several Metal Gear titles were removed from digital storefronts after Konami failed to renew licenses for real-world footage included in the games. But it seems that these fan-favorites are about to return to consoles.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Delete Messages on iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=816933</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/816933/deleting-messages-on-iphone/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T17:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your iPhone makes it super easy to remove individual text messages as well as entire conversations from the Messages app. We’ll show you how to get rid of unwanted messages from your phone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Current Retbleed Performance Costs With An AMD Ryzen 7 4800U]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Retbleed-Ryzen-7-4800U</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Retbleed-Ryzen-7-4800U"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T16:50:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following some weekend benchmarks here are more complementary numbers on the Retbleed mitigation performance benchmark costs. These additional numbers are on a Zen 2 based AMD Ryzen 7 4800U APU that has been common both to laptops as well as embedded/low-profile devices for thin client computing, IoT / edge use-cases, and more...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Office Phishing Attack circumvents multi-factor authentication]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=179779</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/07/17/office-phishing-attack-circumvents-multi-factor-authentication/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T16:43:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft security researchers and engineers discovered a massive phishing attack that has been targeting more than 10,000 organizations since September 2021. The malicious actors used adversary-in-the-middle (AiTM) phishing sites to steal passwords […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Office Phishing Attack circumvents multi-factor authentication appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Roku, and How Does it Work?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=817495</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/817495/what-is-roku-and-how-does-it-work/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T16:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roku is one of the most popular names in the streaming device category. You’ve probably seen it on Amazon and at Best Buy. What does this strange name and purple color scheme bring to your TV? Let’s find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wireless connection disabled when opening laptop lid]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w1aa1o/wireless_connection_disabled_when_opening_laptop/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/w1aa1o/wireless_connection_disabled_when_opening_laptop/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T15:43:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've had this problem for a while now, and unfortunately I can't pinpoint when it started occuring. I do however know that it wasn't an issue until at most 6 months ago.
 When opening the lid of my laptop, the wireless connection is disabled and I have to manually enable it again. journalctl -f shows
 kernel: wlo1: deauthenticating from [MAC address] by local choice (Reason: 3=DEAUTH_LEAVING)
 right before Lid opened. When the lid is closed, the connection remains on as usual.
 The strangest thing is that this doesn't always happen. Upon reboots, it's possible that during that session this issue does not occur. However, if it does occur, it always occurs when opening the lid during that session.
 My laptop has an Intel 7265 wireless controller using the iwlwifi firmware. I use NetworkManager, and if it matters, its plasma-nm frontend for KDE Plasma. I've disabled MAC randomization using the method in the wiki.
    submitted by    /u/pryingmantis89  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shopifiy's Test App Can Delete All Your Furniture]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/123314/shopifiys-test-app-can-delete-all-your-furniture/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/123314/shopifiys-test-app-can-delete-all-your-furniture/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T15:23:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier this year at WWDC, Apple released its RoomPlan API for developers to tap into AR features on iOS devices. Now, we’re seeing an incredible use of the technology thanks to a new demo video released by the Canadian e-commerce brand Shopify.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Search for a Word on a Web Page]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=815839</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/815839/how-to-search-for-a-word-on-a-page/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T15:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you looking for a specific word on a web page? If so, ease your task by using your browser’s find function to locate specific terms on the current web page. Another way to do this is to use Google Search with a custom parameter. We’ll show you both ways.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>