<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-05-07T01:43:10.413Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[unable to run pacstrap successfully during arch installation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uk1q8m/unable_to_run_pacstrap_successfully_during_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uk1q8m/unable_to_run_pacstrap_successfully_during_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-07T00:49:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/ye_sh1thead  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Change Your Username and Nickname on Discord]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=483184</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15279267/change-username-on-discord"/>
        <updated>2022-05-07T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve been on Discord for a long time, you might feel that a username change is in order. If that’s the case, you should know that on Discord, unlike other social apps like Reddit, it’s easy to change your username whenever you want to. This tutorial shows how to change your username and nickname on Discord.
   

Content

How to Change Your Discord Username
How to Change Your Discord Tag without Nitro
How to Change Your Nickname on Discord
How to Change Other People’s Nicknames on a Server
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:9 Best Discord Gaming Bots You Must Add to Your Server
    
How to Change Your Discord Username
    
On Discord your username is made up of two components: the username per-se, the one you picked yourself when you first created your account on... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexandra Arici</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Partition too full]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujzmv9/partition_too_full/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujzmv9/partition_too_full/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T22:57:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I run pacstrap /mnt base base-devel linux linux-firmware vim
 an error appears, saying:
 error: Partition / too full: 131444 blocks needed, 60429 blocks free
 error: failed to commit transaction (not enough free disk space)
 Errors occurred, no packages were upgraded.
 ==> ERROR: Failed to install packages to new root
 Big newbie in here, so what do I do? 
 Edit: I tried remounting everything, now i have a different error
    submitted by    /u/VRDoesNotSuckPP  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Week in Ransomware - May 6th 2022 - An evolving landscape]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/the-week-in-ransomware-may-6th-2022-an-evolving-landscape/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/the-week-in-ransomware-may-6th-2022-an-evolving-landscape/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T22:27:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ransomware operations continue to evolve, with new groups appearing and others quietly shutting down their operations or rebranding as new groups. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Having trouble with uefi install on my thinkpad e580]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujyy8o/having_trouble_with_uefi_install_on_my_thinkpad/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujyy8o/having_trouble_with_uefi_install_on_my_thinkpad/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T22:22:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m trying to use Efistub, and if I understand correctly I have to use efibootmgr. I made to efibootmgr entries, because wanted to add microcode. Then I removed entry 1 because I figured I shouldn’t have both.
 I made a separate boot, var, home and swap partition.
 I’m able to boot, but I get dropped into an emergency shell.
 https://i.imgur.com/UIqUFN7.jpg
 Any help would be appreciated!
    submitted by    /u/Sleezebag  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wine 7.8 Released With More PE Conversion, WoW64 Sound Driver Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Wine-7.8-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Wine-7.8-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T22:22:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wine 7.8 is out today as the newest bi-weekly release of this software for enjoying Windows games and applications on Linux, macOS, and other platforms...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Questa settimana su TLI (07 maggio 2022)]]></title>
        <id>3569|20220507000001</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/newsletter-turbolab.it-1349/questa-settimana-tli-07-maggio-2022-3569"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T22:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Non hai tempo di leggerci tutti i giorni? nessun problema! ecco a te il riepilogo di quanto proposto da TurboLab.it nel corso della settimana in conclusione.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 13 best laptop docking stations of 2022]]></title>
        <id>a13a6ecd-f7f9-46dd-ab4a-af2b4ab8d417</id>
        <link href="https://www.zdnet.com/article/best-laptop-docking-station/#ftag=RSSbaffb68"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T21:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is the best laptop docking station? We've named the Plugable Thunderbolt 3 and USB-C docking station as our top laptop docking station after reviewing specs like price, connection type, power, video outputs, ports, audio input/output, and wired ethernet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest topics for ZDNet in Windows</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xbox is down worldwide with users unable to play games]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/xbox-is-down-worldwide-with-users-unable-to-play-games/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/xbox-is-down-worldwide-with-users-unable-to-play-games/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T21:36:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft says the Xbox Live services are currently down in a major outage, impacting customers worldwide and preventing them from launching or buying games. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Enable the Hidden Screen Recorder in Android]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=post-ideas&amp;p=355813</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/13761712/enable-hidden-screen-recorder-android"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For some unknown reason, Google decided once again to skip a built-in screen recorder for Android. In fact, it was a feature in the beta version but disappeared for the final release – mostly. While the process isn’t obvious, we show you here how to enable the hidden screen recorder in Android 10 and avoid having to download a third-party app. We show you  how to do the same on Android 11 and 12 as well, which is a much easier process.
   

Content

Why Enable the Hidden Screen Recorder in Android 10
Enable USB Debugging
Install the Android SDK Platform
Using ADB
Trying the Screen Recorder
Enable Hidden Screen Recorder in Android 11 and 12
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:10 Best Android Screen Recording Apps
    
Why Enable the Hidden Screen Recorder in Android 10
    
With so many apps available, why go through all... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Crystal Crowder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Search Comments on Reddit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=799977</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/799977/how-to-search-comments-on-reddit/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T21:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reddit users have been clamoring for the ability to search comments for years, and now the social media website has rolled out the feature site-wide. Filtering searches by comment means less time scrolling results and more efficient searches.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Watch the New 'Peanuts' Mother's Day Special]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117200/how-to-watch-the-new-peanuts-mothers-day-special/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117200/how-to-watch-the-new-peanuts-mothers-day-special/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T20:57:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The classic Peanuts characters are back with a new Mother’s Day special. Called Snoopy Presents: To Mom (and Dad) With Love, this special focuses on Peppermint Patty, who lives with a father but not a mother. But where can you watch the new Peanuts special?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Systemd suspends as soon as USB reconnects?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujwhx1/systemd_suspends_as_soon_as_usb_reconnects/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujwhx1/systemd_suspends_as_soon_as_usb_reconnects/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T20:27:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I posted this in the new people thread, and was told to make it a proper post, so I've copy-pasted my post there to here.
 So I recently installed arch, and am using sway. I also use a usb switch to share my keyboard/mouse with my laptop (which has arch) and my desktop. Additionally, I run my laptop in clamshell mode (laptop lid is closed while output goes to an external monitor).
 I've noticed that if I let the laptop idle long enough to turn off the external monitor, then switch my usb switch to my desktop, then switch back, the computer will suspend a few seconds after un-idling. I looked in the journal, and basically as soon as the usb switch reconnected systemd-logind suspends the computer. I was just wondering what exactly the issue is here, because it's rather annoying having to open the laptop lid to wake up the computer after being on my desktop for a little while.
 If more information is needed, I can provide it. I'm kinda new to arch, so I've provided what I thought was relevant.
 Recently, oddly enough, this pattern has seemed to stop, and I'm not sure why. If anyone has any insight, I would appreciate it, if not just to simply learn more.
    submitted by    /u/AjiBuster499  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[pacstrap does "nothing"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujwftq/pacstrap_does_nothing/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujwftq/pacstrap_does_nothing/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T20:25:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When i run pacstrap /mnt base base-devel linux linux-firmware vim, core appears and stays there, doing nothing.
 ​
 Btw im using virtual box 
 Edit: got it to work, just changed from NAT connection to bridge
    submitted by    /u/VRDoesNotSuckPP  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Your Next Keyboard Should Be Fully Split]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117164/why-your-next-keyboard-should-be-fully-split/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117164/why-your-next-keyboard-should-be-fully-split/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T20:21:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re like many people in the world, you spend at least part of every day typing on a keyboard. Chances are, you use whatever cheap keyboard you got on sale, and it’s the classic single strip QWERTY layout affair. But I’m here to say: it’s time to switch to a fully split keyboard.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Hendrickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Sort Google Sheets by Date]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=798264</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/798264/how-to-sort-google-sheets-by-date/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Sheets lets you sort your spreadsheets as well as the contents within those spreadsheets by date. You can use Sheets’ built-in functions to do that, and we’ll show you how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ferrari subdomain hijacked to push fake Ferrari NFT collection]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ferrari-subdomain-hijacked-to-push-fake-ferrari-nft-collection/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ferrari-subdomain-hijacked-to-push-fake-ferrari-nft-collection/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T19:56:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of Ferrari's subdomains was hijacked yesterday to host a scam promoting fake Ferrari NFT collection, according to researchers. The Ethereum wallet associated with the cryptocurrency scam appears to have collected a few hundred dollars before the hacked subdomain was shut down. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ax Sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraria stuttering]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujvj1j/terraria_stuttering/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujvj1j/terraria_stuttering/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T19:43:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey, I don't really know where to post this, so it's here and on r/Terraria. 
 I have a Lenovo ThinkPad L390 (i5-8265U, UHD620) running on Arch with bspwm. 
 The benchmarks I found online all show that I should be able to run it at stable 60 fps on 1920x1080, even with high settings. Steam built-in fps counter shows 60, but the game stutters so much it looks like 20 or less frames. It's like freezing for .x of a second every frame. I tried running it natively and through Proton, works the same. I can't really test it on Windows, because I'm not dual-booting. 
 I'm updating everything through pacman almost daily (-Syu), so there's no way I have obsolete drivers. 
 I really don't know what more I can do. 
 I have 1x8GB RAM, swap file of 8GB, running it with gamemode and turbo boost (Intel CPU) on without any unnecessary programs in the background (Discord, Spotify, etc.). Of course the CPU governor is set to performance and I'm playing with AC plugged in. I allocated the most RAM to the iGPU the BIOS let me (512MB). 
 I even found some launch options for Terraria on Steam and nothing seemed to work.
 Of course I tried lowering the settings in game, even to the lowest, and nothing changed. I lowered the resolution too, but it looks shitty even on 1600x900 and I wasn't able to move the cursor to the edge of my screen (the cursor space was 1600x900 even though the game was still rendering in fullscreen?).
 Help please, I don't want to play the mobile port:(
    submitted by    /u/palgume123  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch not resuming from hibernate]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujvbpf/arch_not_resuming_from_hibernate/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujvbpf/arch_not_resuming_from_hibernate/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T19:33:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I followed the arch wiki guide on setting up hibernation. Added boot parameters in grub (by editing etc/defaults/grub), did grub-mkconfig -o /boot/grub/grub.cfg, edited hooks in /etc/mkinitcpio.conf and did sudo mkinitcpio -p linux. When i try to hibernate my ThinkPad, it shuts down, instantly wakes up and does a clean boot "from scratch". It saves the state to disk but doesn't resume from it. When I did cat /proc/cmdline i can see that i lack the resume parameter. how to add it?
 EDIT: i fixed it by adding it using grub-customizer.
    submitted by    /u/Yellow_DMG  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Changing GTK theme on applications launched with gapplication?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujvar6/changing_gtk_theme_on_applications_launched_with/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujvar6/changing_gtk_theme_on_applications_launched_with/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T19:32:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I don't use a desktop environnment (i3wm) and I am having some problems with GTK themes in applications using libadwaita
 I can set the GTK_THEME environnment variable to Adwaita:dark, but this only affects applications direcly. Some applications, though, weirdly look differently when launched using gapplication (gnome-weather, gapplication launch org.gnome.Weather)
 In case it might be useful, these are the contents of my ~/.config/gtk-4.0/settings.ini:
 [Settings] gtk-cursor-theme-name=breeze_cursors gtk-application-prefer-dark-theme=true gtk-cursor-theme-size=24 gtk-decoration-layout=icon:minimize,maximize,close gtk-enable-animations=true gtk-font-name=Noto Sans, 10 gtk-icon-theme-name=Win11-dark gtk-primary-button-warps-slider=false gtk-theme-name=Adwaita 
 Is there any way to get gapplication to use a GTK theme? Thanks a lot in advance!
    submitted by    /u/alba4k  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get a Fire 7 Kids Pro Tablet for Under $50]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=298928</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/14951875/fire-7-kids-edition-tablet"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is such a great deal, it’s hard to ignore. You can set your child up with some summer learning and reading, as well as a little fun, with a Fire 7 Kids Pro Tablet for under $50. Note that the device is no toy – it’s 16 GB and works the same as any tablet, though it has parental controls to keep your child safe.
    
This full-featured Fire 7 Kids Pro Tablet has a 7″ display, 16 GB internal storage, dual cameras, up to 512 GB expandable storage, a micro USB port, and up to seven hours of battery life. The tablet comes with a Black, Sky Blue, Intergalactic, or Doodle case.
    
Purchase includes a one-year subscription to Amazon Kids+ to provide your child with more than 20,000 apps, games, books, videos, songs, and audiobooks. There are options for educational content from National Geographic, LEGO, and more with over 9,000 titles specifically for ages 6 and up. The subscription will automatically renew after one year, and if you choose to keep it, you’ll pay just $2.99 plus tax each month. But you aren’t roped in at all,... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Headphone disconnecting occasionally]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujusf0/headphone_disconnecting_occasionally/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujusf0/headphone_disconnecting_occasionally/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T19:08:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm using pulseaudio and in the past few weeks, my headphones have started randomly disconnecting. Pulseaudio can't detect them at all, but unplugging and replugging it works.
    submitted by    /u/Pay08  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple M1 NVMe Support Slated For Linux 5.19]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Apple-M1-NVMe-Linux-5.19</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Apple-M1-NVMe-Linux-5.19"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T19:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest Apple M1 excitement on Linux for the mainline kernel is the NVMe driver is slated for introduction in the upcoming Linux 5.19 merge window...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is a Whaling or Whale Phishing Attack Online?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=796978</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/796978/what-is-a-whaling-or-whale-phishing/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T19:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An online phishing attack typically involves a scammer attempting to impersonate a service you use in a bid to get credentials or money out of you. Another more targeted and potentially more lucrative version of this scam is called whaling or whale phishing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[grub editing 10_linux file not persist]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujuher/grub_editing_10_linux_file_not_persist/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujuher/grub_editing_10_linux_file_not_persist/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T18:54:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, I added --unrestricted to /etc/grub.d/10_linux
 CLASS="--class gnu-linux --class gnu --class os --unrestricted"
 each time i update /etc/default/grub and reload config it gets removed from 10_linux file.
 Is there any way to have my made config persist ?
    submitted by    /u/Spare_Prize1148  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Random (but frequent) Freezes in i3wm => stuck in last focused window]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujubkj/random_but_frequent_freezes_in_i3wm_stuck_in_last/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujubkj/random_but_frequent_freezes_in_i3wm_stuck_in_last/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T18:47:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today I did a full system backup. At first I had major problems with the new kernel which are now solved.
 Now a new problem appeared. My i3wm seems to be freezing at random so that I am locked inside the last focused window. I can't change focus or anything - not even reloading or using the mouse.
 ​
 The most likely cause as far as I read has been the kernel. So I switched to linux-lts. I also switched to linux-lts-header and nvidia-lts. I have run mkinitcpio for nvidia and grub-mkconfig -o /boot/grub/grub.cfg. Furthermore, I added another hook for nvidia-lts to pacman and reinstalled optimus-manager (to be on the safe side). To check whether my system complains I removed nvidia, optimus-manager is set to always start with nvidia atm. So far the transition seem to have run smoothly. Problem is the freezing remains. Everything else is absolutely fine so far.
 ​
 What else can cause this malicious behaviour. Which console outputs or logs are there keep hold of the error(s)?
    submitted by    /u/baxbear  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rare Apple 1 Computer Goes Up For Auction at $250,000]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=803742</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/803742/rare-apple-1-computer-goes-up-for-auction-at-250000/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T18:40:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Apple 1 (sometimes spelled as Apple-1 or Apple I) was the first computer built by the company know best known for the Mac and iPhone. There aren’t many Apple 1 boards left in existence, but one has now gone up for auction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Hide Windows 11’s Taskbar on Secondary Monitors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=798281</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/798281/windows-11-taskbar-hide-multiple-monitors/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T18:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 allows you to hide the taskbar on your additional monitors while keeping it enabled on the primary monitor. You’ll have to tweak the settings to do that, and we’ll show you how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lucid EVs Get a Huge Price Hike, and You Can Probably Guess Why]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117163/lucid-evs-get-a-huge-price-hike-and-you-can-probably-guess-why/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117163/lucid-evs-get-a-huge-price-hike-and-you-can-probably-guess-why/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T17:50:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lucid just published its first financial report of 2022, and the details are a bit disappointing. The company says it’s only delivered 360 vehicles this year, and more importantly, it’s cranking up the prices on all of its cars (minus the newly announced Lucid Air Grand Touring Performance).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ASpeed AST2600 BMC Support For DisplayPort Landing In Linux 5.19]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AST2600-DisplayPort-Linux-5.19</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AST2600-DisplayPort-Linux-5.19"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T17:30:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The "AST" DRM/KMS driver for ASpeed chips in Linux 5.19 is adding support for DisplayPort outputs... Leading to the era of hopefully seeing more servers with DisplayPort outputs to eventually replace VGA that is still very common on server platforms for display purposes...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Play Wordle on Your Commodore 64]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=803710</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/803710/you-can-play-wordle-on-your-commodore-64/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T17:01:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The word puzzle game Wordle might not be as popular now as it was a mere few months ago, but there are still countless clones and ports showing up. Perhaps one of the most unusual ports is a version for the Commodore 64, which just received an update.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Scan With Microsoft Defender Antivirus on Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=798753</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/798753/how-to-scan-with-microsoft-defender-antivirus-on-windows-11/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T17:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft’s Antivirus software has come a long way since the days of Microsoft Security Essentials.  Microsoft Defender goes toe to toe with the best third-party antivirus available. Here’s how you can use it to scan your PC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Lewis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Buy Slashes Laptop, Phone, Game, and TV Prices Through May 8th]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117161/best-buy-slashes-laptop-phone-game-and-tv-prices-through-may-8th/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117161/best-buy-slashes-laptop-phone-game-and-tv-prices-through-may-8th/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T16:42:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for a last-minute Mother’s Day gift? Best Buy is running a huge sale on phones, smart home devices, headphones, and more until May 8th. You could save $25 on a new Nintendo Switch game or go all-out on a discounted KitchenAid stand mixer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How can I upgrade an arch install from a small usb to a bigger one?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujrhji/how_can_i_upgrade_an_arch_install_from_a_small/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujrhji/how_can_i_upgrade_an_arch_install_from_a_small/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T16:36:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's say I have a 16gb usb with arch, and I want to upgrade to a 32gb usb. How can I do this?
 I've done something like this with raspbian, but never with arch and I'm not sure how. Searching online didn't really help.
    submitted by    /u/ItsZan3  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One Outlook: come si presenta il nuovo client di posta per Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=One-Outlook-come-si-presenta-il-nuovo-client-di-posta-per-Windows-11_24482</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=One-Outlook-come-si-presenta-il-nuovo-client-di-posta-per-Windows-11_24482"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T16:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft lo stava sviluppando ormai da più di un anno: conosciuto con il nome in codice di Project Monarch, si tratta di un client di posta elettronica per Windows che raccoglierà l'eredità di Outlook, disponibile in molteplici versioni.L'obiettivo del nuovo One Outlook è quello di presentare agli utenti un'applicazione che funziona nello stesso identico modo su qualunque dispositivo venga usata. Quasi sicuramente dovrebbe soppiantare le tradizionali applicazioni Posta e Calendario integrate in Windows.Durante le fasi di sviluppo di Project Monarch Microsoft ha preferito non mostrare alcuna anteprima e continuare a sviluppare internamente il nuovo Outlook.Il design complessivo riflette quello della versione Web di Outlook, al momento non sembra supportare account utente Microsoft di tipo personale (ma la cosa cambierà di sicuro da qui al momento del rilascio ufficiale) e non sembrano essere previsti particolari add-on.La novità più evidente a colpo d'occhio è che le principali funzioni dell'applicazione sono state posizionate nella parte superiore della finestra, a destra.

Le email si aprono invece in una finestra dedicata, similmente a quanto avviene oggi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US agricultural machinery maker AGCO hit by ransomware attack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-agricultural-machinery-maker-agco-hit-by-ransomware-attack/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-agricultural-machinery-maker-agco-hit-by-ransomware-attack/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T16:21:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AGCO, a leading US-based agricultural machinery producer, has announced it was hit by a ransomware attack impacting some of its production facilities. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Opzioni di Windows 10 da configurare dopo l'installazione]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2015/07/prime-opzioni-da-modificare-in-windows10.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2015/07/prime-opzioni-da-modificare-in-windows10.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T16:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft ha garantito un ottimo supporto per Windows 10, che resta il sistema operativo di riferimento per i computer non compatibili con TPM o con altri parametri necessari per far girare Windows 11. Con Windows 10 avremo un sistema veloce e ancora ben supportato, da installare su tutti i computer che hanno almeno 4 GB di RAM a disposizione.

 Se abbiamo deciso di rimanere con Windows 10 come...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sudden Screen Tearing with amdgpu on optimus laptop]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujqr6e/sudden_screen_tearing_with_amdgpu_on_optimus/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujqr6e/sudden_screen_tearing_with_amdgpu_on_optimus/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T16:02:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi all, I am suddenly facing screen tearing with amdgpu (which doesnt happen with nvidia, and also this issue doesnt happen before). Here's the specification of my laptop:
 OS: Arch Linux Kernel: 5.17.5-arch1-1 Laptop Model: Lenovo Legion 5 15ARH05 GPU 1: AMD ATI 06:00.0 Renoir GPU 2: NVIDIA GeForce GTX 1650 Ti Mobile 
 I am using optimus-manager to manage my gpus, and this issue only happens when I log into integrated mode. Here's the output of xrandr --listproviders:
 Providers: number : 1 Provider 0: id: 0x53 cap: 0xf, Source Output, Sink Output, Source Offload, Sink Offload crtcs: 4 outputs: 1 associated providers: 0 name:Unknown AMD Radeon GPU @ pci:0000:06:00.0 
 Here's my xorg configuration (created automatically by optimus-manager):
 ❯ cat /etc/X11/xorg.conf.d/10-optimus-manager.co…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does GPU Memory Matter? How Much VRAM Do You Need?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=794750</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/794750/does-gpu-memory-matter-how-much-vram-do-you-need/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T16:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data like rendered frames, textures, and shadows get stored in GPU memory, allowing your computer’s GPU to access this information quickly. But does it really matter how much GPU memory you have? Yes. Here’s why.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Georgie Peru</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ford Could Let You Rev Your Engine from a Phone or Key Fob]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117146/ford-could-let-you-rev-your-engine-from-a-phone-or-key-fob/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117146/ford-could-let-you-rev-your-engine-from-a-phone-or-key-fob/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T15:57:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla has a lot of fun with hidden features in its vehicles. Letting owners turn the car into a light show, romance mode, or even make fart noises. Now, it looks like Ford wants in on the fun, filing a new patent to let owners rev the engine remotely.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How best to keep archlinux-keyring updated?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujqlao/how_best_to_keep_archlinuxkeyring_updated/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujqlao/how_best_to_keep_archlinuxkeyring_updated/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T15:55:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I hate when commands fail. Normally I update my system with pacman -Syu but sometimes the archlinux-keyring package needs to updated in which case after it fails, I run pacman -S archlinux-keyring && pacman -Su (I don't need to refresh the database because I just did it and in the end my system is fully upgraded so it is not a partial upgrade).
 I could always just run pacman -Sy archlinux-keyring && pacman -Su but that seems like a waste if the keyring does not need to be updated. So in the Arch spirit of over engineering a solution, I was thinking I could write a script that calls pacman -Syup and does some regex foo to get a the list of packages that need to be updated. If the keyring is in that list, the script could then makes sure it is updated first.
 How do you keep the keyring package updated so pacman does not fail?
    submitted by    /u/AppointmentNearby161  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get Weekly Mosquito Forecasts with Google and OFF!'s New Tool]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117151/get-weekly-mosquito-forecasts-with-google-and-offs-new-tool/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117151/get-weekly-mosquito-forecasts-with-google-and-offs-new-tool/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T15:55:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Summer is just around the corner, and as always, the mosquitos will go bonkers. If you want to avoid running into a swarm of blood-sucking pests during your next camping trip, you may want to try OFF!’s new mosquito forecast tool, which tells you how bad the mosquitos will be in your area each week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QNAP fixes critical QVR remote command execution vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/qnap-fixes-critical-qvr-remote-command-execution-vulnerability/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/qnap-fixes-critical-qvr-remote-command-execution-vulnerability/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T15:38:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[QNAP has released several security advisories today to alert its customers about various fixes for flaws affecting its products. The one that stands out is a critical RCE (remote code execution) in QVR. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zink OpenGL-On-Vulkan Looking Quite Good & Shining With Mesa 22.1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31102</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31102"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T15:30:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently I carried out some tests looking at the performance of Zink for OpenGL implemented atop the Vulkan API in a generic manner that works across drivers. With the state of Mesa 22.1, all of Zink's recent improvements are paying off and here is a quick look at where the performance stands against using the RadeonSI OpenGL driver.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 Ways to Restore Deleted Files in Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=479970</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15278718/restore-deleted-files-windows"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You might have accidentally (or not) deleted files from your Windows PC at one point or another and wondered whether you can restore them from the Recycle Bin. The good news is that you can do so without much fuss.
    
Windows automatically places files from folders or external devices in the Recycle Bin when you delete them, so you can easily recover these with just a few clicks. If you’ve permanently deleted a file, however, you won’t be able to restore it through the Recycle Bin. Luckily, there are other advanced methods for recovering your files, as we shall see below. 
    
Note: the methods included in this article are compatible with Windows 10/11.
   

Content

1. From Recycle Bin
2. Bring Back Previous File Versions
3. With Command Prompt
4. Using Windows File Recovery Tool
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Disable Computer... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Claire Moraa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US sanctions Bitcoin laundering service used by North Korean hackers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-sanctions-bitcoin-laundering-service-used-by-north-korean-hackers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-sanctions-bitcoin-laundering-service-used-by-north-korean-hackers/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T15:17:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US Department of Treasury today sanctioned cryptocurrency mixer Blender.io used last month by the North Korean-backed Lazarus hacking group to launder funds stolen from Axie Infinity's Ronin bridge. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your New Nest Doorbell Works with Amazon TVs, but Not Google TVs!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117127/your-new-nest-doorbell-works-with-amazon-tvs-but-not-google-tvs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117127/your-new-nest-doorbell-works-with-amazon-tvs-but-not-google-tvs/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T15:15:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So, here’s something odd; your new Nest Doorbell can now stream live video to Amazon Fire TV devices, but this feature is still missing from the Chromecast with Google TV. It’s a strange situation, and it’s sure to disappoint customers who feel that Google is neglecting the Chromecast.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SSD scrivibile una sola volta: l'idea di Verbatim]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=SSD-scrivibile-una-sola-volta-l-idea-di-Verbatim_24481</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=SSD-scrivibile-una-sola-volta-l-idea-di-Verbatim_24481"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T15:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Siamo abituati ad acquistare unità SSD che, come tutti i dispositivi di memorizzazione, non sono 'immortali' e che con il tempo possono presentare problemi.Ci siamo chiesti in passato se la durata degli SSD sia un parametro di cui preoccuparsi sottolineando che le temperature di lavoro e il tempo hanno oggi un impatto negativo sul ciclo di vita di un dispositivo basato su memoria flash piuttosto che il numero di scritture.Parlando sempre di unità a stato solido, a febbraio 2022 un ricercatore aveva riportato in auge il problema della perdita di dati da alcuni modelli di SSD in seguito a un'improvvisa interruzione dell'alimentazione.Adesso Verbatim lancia l'idea dell'unità SSD scrivibile una volta sola: presentato come un dispositivo 'a lunga durata', SWOVA128G ha una capacità di 128 GB, utilizza storage flash NAND, interfaccia USB 3.2 Gen 1 e offre una garanzia di ben 10 anni (quando l'unità è utilizzata in ambienti a 55°C o meno).L'obiettivo è impedire la cancellazione accidentale dei dati: Verbatim SWOVA128G, infatti, accetta esclusivamente la memorizzazione di nuovi dati previa installazione su PC di un apposito software (compatibile con Windows 10 e Windows 11) ma in ogni caso non permette di eliminare quelli già scritti.La scrittura dei dati è consentita solamente da Windows 10 e 11 mentre tutti gli altri sistemi operativi compatibili con il file system exFAT (compresi macOS, Android, iOS,...) possono solo limitarsi a leggere e copiare i dati conservati nell'SSD.Il dispositivo di storage firmato Verbatim può essere un po’ considerato come l'evoluzione dei tradizionali DVD: nel caso di SWOVA128G, però, la 'sessione' resta sempre aperta nel senso che gli utenti autorizzati possono comunque aggiungere nuovi file e cartelle fino all'eventuale raggiungimento della capienza massima.In termini di dimensioni l'SSD è compatto: misura appena 46 x 108 x 9,5 mm e pesa 55 grammi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Highlight Part of an Image in Microsoft PowerPoint]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=802177</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/802177/highlight-part-of-an-image-powerpoint/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Images are common components in slideshows, adding visual flair to your presentations. So, what if you have a picture with a spot you want to focus on? With a little editing, you can highlight part of an image in PowerPoint.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Both "Miraclecast" and "gnome-network-displays" say that my wifi card is not supported, but it works if I try to cast via Windows on the same computer. Why? Does Windows use a different protocol different from Miracast? Or doesn't just my wifi card Linux driver support Miracast?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujp9v0/both_miraclecast_and_gnomenetworkdisplays_say/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujp9v0/both_miraclecast_and_gnomenetworkdisplays_say/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T14:54:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As title. Is there a way to fix?
 Here: https://wiki.archlinux.org/title/Miracast
 it says that if I do iw phy and iw dev I should say P2P but I don't, so it doesn't seem to be supported. But, again, if I use Windows in the same computer, screencasting works.
    submitted by    /u/allexj  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cannot pacman -Su to new kernel after failed update + downgrade to old kernel version]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujp98r/cannot_pacman_su_to_new_kernel_after_failed/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujp98r/cannot_pacman_su_to_new_kernel_after_failed/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T14:53:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Il can't update (pacman -Su) because then I get back to the start of: https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujio79/after_update_reboot_doesnt_work_failed_to_start/
 ...at which my system refuses to boot.
 Therefore, I tried to first downgrade my linux-headers. But still, I currently can't resolve problems from other packages like nvidia (I can't run mkinitcpio => ERROR: module not found: 'usbhid'), optimus-manager (doesn't start), ...
 After running startx it first works but doesn't set my monitor as primary even so the script enforces it (probably related to the problem since it worked before). I can do this later manually. But my i3 will stuck at some point at the last focused window...
 Summary:
  
Full System Upgrade but for unknown reasons boot wasn't updated/mounted (guess)
 Reboot - boot couldn't be mounted kernel modules couldn't be loaded
 Downgraded from linux-5.17.5.arch1-1 to linux-5.17.1.arch1-1
 Rebooted - was able to boot again normally - run pacman -Su - started from above
 Settled with the downgraded version in hope it works and also downgraded linux-headers to the same version due to complaints after reboots I reached the point where I figured some problems and created this thread
  
   submitted by    /u/baxbear  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 is Adding a “Controller Bar” for Opening Games]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=803634</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/803634/windows-11-is-adding-a-controller-bar-for-opening-games/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T14:45:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Xbox controllers are some of the best PC gaming controllers, thanks to their plug-and-play support in Windows and most games. Microsoft is now testing a new ‘Controller bar’ on Windows 11, which aims to make the experience even better.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come‌ ‌convertire‌ ‌video‌ ‌in‌ ‌audio‌ online gratis]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/05/come-convertire-video-in-audio-online.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/05/come-convertire-video-in-audio-online.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T14:33:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I video presenti sul computer o scaricati da Internet possono essere convertiti in comodi file audio, così da poter ricreare la colonna sonora della nostra vita o recuperare una precisa canzone che ci piace senza doverci per forza affidare ai servizi di streaming online o ai video musicali presenti su Internet. 
Invece di installare dei programmi sul computer (con il rischio di beccare qualche...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NVIDIA fined for failure to disclose cryptomining sales boost]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/nvidia-fined-for-failure-to-disclose-cryptomining-sales-boost/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/nvidia-fined-for-failure-to-disclose-cryptomining-sales-boost/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T14:30:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) announced Friday that it settled charges against multinational tech firm NVIDIA for "inadequate disclosures" of cryptomining's impact on its gaming business. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Work Out at Work: 6 Simple Exercises You Can Do at Your Desk]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lifesavvy.com/126584/work-out-at-work-six-simple-exercises-you-can-do-at-your-desk/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lifesavvy.com/126584/work-out-at-work-six-simple-exercises-you-can-do-at-your-desk/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T14:30:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Carving out the time for a full workout might not be possible for everyone’s schedule. If you spend your days sitting at a desk, though, there are plenty of simple exercises you can do while you work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karla Tafra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Encrypted external drive, boot slowed to a crawl]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujofov/encrypted_external_drive_boot_slowed_to_a_crawl/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujofov/encrypted_external_drive_boot_slowed_to_a_crawl/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T14:15:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I encrypted an external drive with luks and dmcrypt, added a crypttab and an fstab entry (with noauto) for easier mounting, now I see a lot of "USB device not responding to setup address" issues in the tty and my bios seems to take a lot longer to load and is very slow to respond when going through menus. I undid my fstab and crypttab changes and even wiped my boot and root partitionsl. No change. 
 Also, booting from my installation media takes much longer as well. Attempted a BIOS reset, but my laptop doesn't have a CMOS battery; took out the main battery, which I don't think did anything. The BIOS crawling and the usb errors might not be related, but I wanted to check here to see if anyone has seen this behavior.
 Computer is an HP 14-dq1033cl
    submitted by    /u/AblatedSprocket  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migliori app gratis per Android: la nostra selezione]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Migliori-app-gratis-per-Android-la-nostra-selezione_24480</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Migliori-app-gratis-per-Android-la-nostra-selezione_24480"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T14:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Il Google Play Store ospita oggi qualcosa come 3,5 milioni di applicazioni e ogni giorno vengono pubblicate 3.700 nuove app. Numeri scioccanti che di fatto rendono di fatto impossibile selezionare le migliori app gratis in assoluto.Nella disamina che presentiamo di seguito vogliamo concentrarci sulle app Android che abbiamo provato e che nel corso del tempo abbiamo utilizzato con soddisfazione, senza ovviamente alcuna ambizione di stilare un elenco adatto a tutti.Tralasceremo ovviamente applicazioni quali Chrome, WhatsApp, Telegram, Signal, Gmail, Google Drive, OneDrive, Dropbox, Google Foto, Calendar, Keep, Evernote, Android Auto, Spotify, Amazon Music, Google Contatti, Google Telefono, Google Messaggi, Google Duo, Google Home, TheFork, Tripadvisor, Waze, Moovit, Google Maps, YouTube, Google Pay, PayPal, Google One, Google Meet, Zoom, Microsoft Teams, TeamViewer, VLC, Microsoft To Do, Shazam, Snapseed, Gboard, SwiftKey, Google Documenti, Office e così via: le conoscono tutti, sono davvero onnipresenti e sarebbe quindi piuttosto inutile parlarne.
App gratis Android
 1) FRITZ!App WLANUn'applicazione utilissima per verificare la copertura delle reti WiFi e le loro prestazioni.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 5 Best Online Backup Services of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=790664</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/790664/best-online-backup-service/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T14:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Online backup services can help protect you from losing critical data during a catastrophe and provide you with workflow features that can help you in the day-to-day. Let’s look at the best ones to suit your needs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Albert Bassili</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google, Microsoft and Apple commit to passwordless sign-in standard]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178436</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/05/06/google-microsoft-and-apple-commit-to-passwordless-sign-ins-standard/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T13:50:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google, Microsoft and Apple have announced support for expanding passwordless sign-in support across major operating systems and devices. The three companies announced plans on May 5, 2022 to support a passwordless sign-in […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Google, Microsoft and Apple commit to passwordless sign-in standard appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Where can I find linux-5.17.1.arch1-1-x86_64.pkg.tar.zst ?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujnvlr/where_can_i_find_linux5171arch11x86_64pkgtarzst/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujnvlr/where_can_i_find_linux5171arch11x86_64pkgtarzst/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T13:48:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am trying to retrieve an old archlinux kernel version to fix my system and I just can't find it. I found some commit messages about the commit in github but wasn't able to retrieve the package.
 After, somebody provided the link - can I simply wget it and then do pacman -U pkg to downgrade to the old kernel?
    submitted by    /u/baxbear  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft's new Outlook email client is live (at least for now)]]></title>
        <id>d999f645-d4c2-4d9f-8966-f7fae798cbc6</id>
        <link href="https://www.zdnet.com/article/microsofts-new-outlook-email-client-is-live-at-least-for-now/#ftag=RSSbaffb68"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T13:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft's new Outlook mail client, codenamed 'Project Monarch,' seems ready to roll out in preview any time now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest topics for ZDNet in Windows</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 10 Best Stephen King Movies to Stream in 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=799139</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/799139/best-stephen-king-movies-to-stream-online/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stephen King’s vast catalog of novels and stories is nearly matched by the many movies that have been adapted from his work. From horror to drama, here are 10 of the best Stephen King movies to stream right now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Bell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[App per fare scatti rapidi di foto su Android e iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2015/09/app-per-fare-scatti-rapidi-di-foto-su.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2015/09/app-per-fare-scatti-rapidi-di-foto-su.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T13:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quante volte è capitato di perdere il momento perfetto per una foto perché ci abbiamo messo troppo tempo a prendere il telefonino per scattare la foto? Possiamo ridurre i tempi morti per gli scatti rapidi a pochissimi secondi utilizzando dei piccoli trucchi integrati sui moderni sistemi operativi o utilizzando delle app che, tramite scorciatoie o tasti macro, possono avviare la fotocamera e...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BenQ Mobiuz EX3410R 34-Inch Ultra-Wide Gaming Monitor Review: A Gamer's Paradise]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117030/benq-mobiuz-ex3410r-34-inch-ultra-wide-gaming-monitor-review-a-gamers-paradise/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117030/benq-mobiuz-ex3410r-34-inch-ultra-wide-gaming-monitor-review-a-gamers-paradise/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T13:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Monitors are a dime a dozen, but good gaming monitors that throw in features like HDR support, ultrawide dimensions, and controls that won’t drive you mad are much harder to find. You can look no further than BenQ’s Mobiuz EX3410R gaming monitor. It ticks just about all the boxes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Hendrickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are Gaming Mouse Pads Worth It?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=794984</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/794984/are-gaming-mouse-pads-worth-it/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T13:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gaming mouse pads are the highest quality options on the market that can drastically improve your gaming experience or general use on the computer. Let’s find out what they offer and whether they’re worth it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Nguyen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 DIY Kitchen Upgrades for People Who Love to Cook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lifesavvy.com/127688/six-diy-kitchen-upgrades-for-people-who-love-to-cook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lifesavvy.com/127688/six-diy-kitchen-upgrades-for-people-who-love-to-cook/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T13:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you love cooking for your family and friends, you likely spend a lot of time in your kitchen. If it could use some improvements, there are a lot of projects you can DIY, or that would be worth the investment to hire out. These six upgrades can give you the kitchen of your dreams and increase your resale value.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anne Taylor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is there a best week day to update Arch Linux?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujmpzh/is_there_a_best_week_day_to_update_arch_linux/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujmpzh/is_there_a_best_week_day_to_update_arch_linux/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T12:49:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Usually I update mine once at week, at friday. After making a backup with Clonezilla.
 The fact is that today an user reported here that /boot is not being mounted anymore at starting.
 So I wanted to know that inside the rolling system of arch linux, there are some days of the week where there are less activity or more stability.
 I did not find information about, so in case of this question does not make too much sense, I will just keep backups & updating routine the friday.
 Thanks!
    submitted by    /u/HansDCJ  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple, Google, Microsoft to Replace Passwords with “Passkey”]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=486640</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15278456/replace-passwords-with-passkey"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T12:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s no argument that passwords can be difficult to work with. They have been replaced in some key situations by biometric logins, such as fingerprint and facial identification. Apple, Google, and Microsoft have joined efforts to make this more universal and create an industry standard to replace passwords with a “passkey.”
   
Also read:The Best Two-Factor Authentication (2FA) Apps That Sync With Multiple Devices
    
Joing Efforts to Create Passkey
    
The FIDO Alliance was created by Apple, Google, Microsoft, and others in the industry to “address the lack of interoperability among strong authentication technologies and remedy the problems users face with creating and remembering multiple usernames and passwords.”
    
On May 5, 2022, the FIDO Alliance and World Wide Web Consortium pushed ahead the commitment to make a more secure Web by expanding support for a “common passwordless sign-in standard.” The vision is for websites and apps to offer a universal... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Is Legal Tender in El Salvador, Here’s How It’s Going]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=801982</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/801982/bitcoin-is-legal-tender-in-el-salvador-heres-how-its-going/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T12:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin has been legal tender in El Salvador since September 2021. It’s a bold financial experiment—so how’s that going? Data based on a survey by the National Bureau of Economic Research can help us understand how the process of Bitcoin adoption is going for everyday people.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Colin Brightfield</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AOMedia's "AVM" Repository Serves As Reference Implementation For Eventual AV1 Successor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AOMedia-AVM-Next-Gen-Repo</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AOMedia-AVM-Next-Gen-Repo"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T11:58:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Alliance for Open Media already has a public repository serving as the reference software implementation for "AVM" as the AOM Video Model as the next-generation codec from this alliance responsible for the excellent AV1...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NordVPN: le migliori caratteristiche per proteggere la navigazione online]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=NordVPN-le-migliori-caratteristiche-per-proteggere-la-navigazione-online_24463</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=NordVPN-le-migliori-caratteristiche-per-proteggere-la-navigazione-online_24463"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T11:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Il mercato dei servizi VPN è diventato col tempo davvero molto affollato tanto che è sempre più complesso orientarsi e scegliere il servizio che meglio si adatta alle proprie necessità.Abbiamo visto cos'è una VPN e come questo tipo di servizi permettano di superare le censure, accedere a risorse diversamente irraggiungibili, proteggere la privacy e scavalcare le limitazioni geografiche, comprese quelle imposte dalle varie piattaforme di streaming video online.Uno dei nomi più noti che vanta un'esperienza decennale nel settore è NordVPN: si tratta di una delle soluzioni VPN che sono cresciute di più nel corso degli anni in termini di infrastruttura, funzionalità, prestazioni e garanzie in termini di tutela della privacy. Una crescita talmente marcata che ha portato alla presentazione di NordLayer, VPN per la protezione di client, workstation e server aziendali.

Per un periodo di tempo limitato NordVPN viene proposto con uno sconto del 60% attivando il più economico piano di abbonamento biennale (solo 2,89 euro al mese).La politica applicata da NordVPN è 'soddisfatti o rimborsati': nel caso in cui il servizio non si rivelasse adatto alle proprie necessità, è possibile chiedere e ottenere un rimborso completo entro 30 giorni dall'ordine.Oltre alla VPN online NordVPN offre anche un completo ed efficace gestore delle password.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenCL 3.0.11 Released With Two New Extensions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=OpenCL-3.0.11-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=OpenCL-3.0.11-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T11:25:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overnight a new minor revision to the OpenCL 3.0 specification was published...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Much Download Speed Do You Really Need?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=799678</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/799678/how-much-download-speed-do-you-really-need/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your local internet service provider (ISP) likely has a variety of packages ranging from budget options to the fastest speeds available in the region. But how much download speed do you actually need?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Fitzpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Installare Windows 11 con un account locale]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Installare-Windows-11-con-un-account-locale_23762</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Installare-Windows-11-con-un-account-locale_23762"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T10:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Con il rilascio di Windows 11 l'azienda di Redmond ha deciso di spingere ancora di più l'acceleratore sull'utilizzo degli account utente Microsoft rendendo difficoltosa la creazione e l'uso di account locali.Riteniamo improbabile che Microsoft possa in futuro accantonare del tutto la possibilità di usare un account locale. Parlando delle differenze tra account Microsoft e locali in Windows abbiamo visto che ancora oggi, in molteplici circostanze, gli account locali restano di grande utilità e attualità.Quando ad esempio si devono condividere cartelle in rete permettendo l'accesso agli altri dispositivi collegati in LAN non è possibile prescindere dall'utilizzo di un account locale e assegnare le autorizzazioni corrette alle cartelle.Gli account Microsoft sono infatti protetti dalla password che si utilizza per accedere ai medesimi account: mica la si vorrà digitare sui vari dispositivi connessi in LAN per usare cartelle e risorse condivise?Un aspetto positivo dell'installazione di Windows 11 è che viene richiesto di assegnare un nome al PC senza generarne uno casuale come avveniva nelle precedenti versioni del sistema operativo.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GCC 12.1 Compiler Released With AVX-512 FP16, Better RISC-V Support, More C++23 Features]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=GCC-12.1-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=GCC-12.1-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T10:35:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GCC 12.1 is out today as the first stable release of GCC 12. It also marks 35 years already since the release of GCC 1.0...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Videos do not play]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujkg7m/videos_do_not_play/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujkg7m/videos_do_not_play/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T10:32:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For some reason, videos stopped playing all of a sudden I'm using MPV the audio is working fine but the video itself does not play, and the progress bar does not move as well.
 The same thing happens for web browser (Brave, Firefox, and Epiphany) the audio is playing while the video is frozen.
 The only thing that works is VLC.
 I mostly use Sway, but this issue also exists in i3.
 GPU: Radeon HD 8650G
 Kernel: 5.17.5-zen1-1-zen
 The video and audio works in ffplayer and vlc
    submitted by    /u/joezak1  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use local accounts on Windows 11 version 22H2 devices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178425</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/05/06/how-to-use-local-accounts-on-windows-11-version-22h2-devices/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T10:24:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft announced that it would extend the Windows 11 Home requirement of a Microsoft Account and Internet connection during setup to Windows 11 Pro in early 2022. The upcoming Windows 11 version […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post How to use local accounts on Windows 11 version 22H2 devices appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMDGPU Linux Driver Enabling New "LSDMA" Block]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMDGPU-LSDMA-Light-SDMA</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMDGPU-LSDMA-Light-SDMA"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T10:16:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As part of the increasing flow of AMD Radeon Linux graphics driver patches coming out ahead of the RDNA3 launch later this year, a new hardware block exposed by the latest patches is "LSDMA"...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gnome icon and theme issues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujk3ny/gnome_icon_and_theme_issues/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujk3ny/gnome_icon_and_theme_issues/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T10:08:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since a few days I'm having issues with Gnome. I use the default theme and icons, and have removed all extensions.
 First issue, weird icons for Firefox, Evolution, Terminal and Finder (and generally all Gnome applications):
 https://i.imgur.com/jHUGMsm.png
 Second issue, at start-up some applications like Firefox always launch bugged:
 https://i.imgur.com/ZwDRwMf.png
 I have to close and/or resize the window a few times using the super key to fix this.
 Third issue, dark mode is not working in Terminal:
 https://i.imgur.com/BY8vXd3.png
 Fourth issue, weird styling if I'm not mistaken. Also bluetooth is always disabled after reboot:
 https://i.imgur.com/dAbowfg.png
 I just removed everything I could from Gnome and reinstalled it completely, but that didn't fix it. Also reinstalled adwaita-…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 Popular Productivity Apps For Designers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/?p=43154</id>
        <link href="https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/popular-productivity-apps-designers/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T10:01:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Designers spend a significant amount of time trying to stay organized, juggling meetings and project deadlines, etc. which leaves them very little time]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Dagli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MSI Vigor GK71 Sonic Gaming Keyboard Review: Weightless Keys for the Win]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=799983</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/799983/msi-vigor-gk71-sonic-gaming-keyboard-review/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Professional Esports competitors and dedicated PC gaming hobbyists alike invest in premium gear to help consistently win games and climb leaderboards. The MSI Vigor GK71 Sonic Gaming Keyboard is one such accessory that can help you reach that level thanks to its lightning-fast keys.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arnold Carreiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel ISPC 1.18 Compiler Brings "Significantly Improved" Xe Graphics Performance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-ISPC-1.18-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-ISPC-1.18-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T09:16:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ahead of Intel's Vision event next week, open-source Intel engineers have released ISPC 1.18 as the newest update to their SPMD Program Compiler...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WhatsApp: ex direttore commerciale si dispiace di aver venduto a Facebook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=WhatsApp-ex-direttore-commerciale-si-dispiace-di-aver-venduto-a-Facebook_24479</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=WhatsApp-ex-direttore-commerciale-si-dispiace-di-aver-venduto-a-Facebook_24479"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T09:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Era il 19 febbraio 2014 quando pubblicammo la storica notizia dell'acquisizione di WhatsApp da parte di Facebook per la somma di 19 miliardi di dollari.Sono passati ormai quasi 10 anni da quando sono iniziati i primi colloqui tra Mark Zuckerberg e i vertici della piattaforma di messaggistica istantanea fondata a inizio 2009 da Jan Koum e Brian Acton (entrambi ex Yahoo!).Delle frizioni tra Koum-Acton e la dirigenza di Facebook in seguito all'acquisizione abbiamo parlato spesso in passato: i due hanno infatti rassegnato le loro dimissioni, rispettivamente, nel 2017 e nel 2018.Koum sbattè la porta perché in forte disaccordo con alcune scelte legate alla gestione della privacy e degli algoritmi crittografici mentre Acton lanciò addirittura la campagna DeleteFacebook.Uno dei dirigenti di WhatsApp all'epoca all'acquisizione era Neeraj Arora, direttore commerciale dell'azienda.In questi giorni Arora ha raccontato i fatti sul suo profilo Twitter dichiarandosi dispiaciuto per aver avallato la mossa di Facebook e la cessione della proprietà di WhatsApp a Zuckerberg.Dopo i primi tentativi di acquisizioni e una serie di rifiuti da parte di WhatsApp, Facebook tornò alla carica nel 2014 promettendo che l'applicazione sarebbe continuata ad esistere così com'era, non sarebbe stata inserita alcuna pubblicità, nessuna raccolta dei dati degli utenti e nessun tipo di tracciamento cross-platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[npm package with 1.4M weekly downloads ditches npmjs.com for own CDN]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/software/npm-package-with-14m-weekly-downloads-ditches-npmjscom-for-own-cdn/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/software/npm-package-with-14m-weekly-downloads-ditches-npmjscom-for-own-cdn/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T09:06:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a surprising move, the popular open source project, SheetJS aka "xlsx," has dropped support for the npm registry. Downloaded about 1.4 million times every week on npm, SheetJS is relied upon by NodeJS developers looking to craft and parse Excel spreadsheets using nothing but JavaScript. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ax Sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FreeBSD 13.1-RC6 Released Due To Lingering Bugs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=FreeBSD-13.1-RC6-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=FreeBSD-13.1-RC6-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T08:56:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FreeBSD 13.1-RELEASE was supposed to be out by the end of April but lingering bugs have yielded extra release candidates for this latest BSD operating system update...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[After Update - Reboot doesn't work: Failed to start Load Kernel Modules, Failed to mount /boot | how to fix / restore backup?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujio79/after_update_reboot_doesnt_work_failed_to_start/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujio79/after_update_reboot_doesnt_work_failed_to_start/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T08:19:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a complete system update that I have just installed I get after reboot:
  
[FAILED] Failed to start Load Kernel Modules. 
 [FAILED] Failed to mount /boot. 
 [DEPEND] Dependency failed for Local File Systems. 
 You are in emergency mode. After logging in, type ...
  
From the journal log the only additional information that catched my eye has been:
  
systemd-modules-load.service: Main process exited, code=exited, status=1/FAILURE 
 systemd-modules-load.service: Failed with result 'exit-code'. 
 Failed to start Load Kernel Modules
  
Is there a way to fix it?
 ​
 I have created a complete system backup before with:
 ... sudo rsync -qaAXv / --exclude={"/dev/*","/proc/*","/sys/*","/tmp/*","/run/*","/mnt/*","/media....} $DIR_PATH 
 on an external disk. How is the correct way to restore the backup?
 So, where and how do I mount (+ from which system) the backup correctly and from where to where do I copy the data?
    submitted by    /u/baxbear  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tor più veloce con il controllo della congestione: cos'è]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Tor-piu-veloce-con-il-controllo-della-congestione-cos-e_24478</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Tor-piu-veloce-con-il-controllo-della-congestione-cos-e_24478"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T08:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[La piattaforma che aiuta a combattere ogni censura e a raggiungere siti Web bloccati si aggiorna. Uno dei principali svantaggi, come spiegato nella nostra guida su Tor Browser, sono le prestazioni spesso non all'altezza delle aspettative.Il nuovo controllo della congestione permette di superare le attuali limitazioni di Tor sul piano delle prestazioni e contribuisce a ridurre la latenza con una gestione ottimizzata delle code sui singoli relay.I vantaggi per gli utenti di Tor saranno tangibili: si potrà così sfruttare meglio la banda disponibile e soprattutto la capacità della rete. È tuttavia necessario che gli operatori che si occupano della gestione degli exit relay, ovvero di quei sistemi che fanno da interfaccia Internet e la rete Tor, provvedano ad aggiornarli prima possibile.Il controllo della congestione è una caratteristica che è già parte integrante del protocollo TCP sul quale, ovviamente, anche la rete Tor si basa.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Docs crashes on seeing "And. And. And. And. And."]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/google-docs-crashes-on-seeing-and-and-and-and-and/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/google-docs-crashes-on-seeing-and-and-and-and-and/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T06:06:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A bug in Google Docs is causing it to crash when a series of words are typed into a document opened with the online word processor. BleepingComputer was able to reproduce the issue last night and reached out to Google. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ax Sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tor's Congestion Control feature promises improved performance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178422</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/05/06/tors-congestion-control-feature-promises-improved-performance/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T04:43:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tor Project released a new version of Tor, version 0.4.7.7, on May 4, 2022 to the public. Tor 0.4.7.7 is the first version of the service that supports congestion control, a new […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Tor's Congestion Control feature promises improved performance appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 Insider Preview Build 22616 brings a Controller bar and restores the option to rearrange icons in the System Tray]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178415</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/05/06/whats-new-in-windows-11-insider-preview-build-22616/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T04:06:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has rolled out Windows 11 Insider Preview Build 22616 to the Dev and Beta Channels. The latest build ships with a new way to launch games quickly, and fixes an annoying […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Windows 11 Insider Preview Build 22616 brings a Controller bar and restores the option to rearrange icons in the System Tray appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is systemd-homed ready for everyday use?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujcpj8/is_systemdhomed_ready_for_everyday_use/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujcpj8/is_systemdhomed_ready_for_everyday_use/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T01:51:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This may be a bit of an odd question, but what is the general consensus for systemd-homed? I am building a new computer soon, finally upgrading after about a decade, and I was thinking of making the switch to systemd-homed. 
 Is it ready for casual use? Or is there a not-insubstantial possibility of it blowing up in my face?
    submitted by    /u/archlinuxrussian  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[replacing grub with a tiny script !]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujc7ps/replacing_grub_with_a_tiny_script/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujc7ps/replacing_grub_with_a_tiny_script/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T01:23:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone, im seeking for help to remove grub and use a tiny script to boot into my os. I don't use anything other than arch on my laptop.So is it possible to replace grub with a Script to boot into my os? If so then how? Please send some help. 
 Regards Nabeen0x01
    submitted by    /u/Nabeen0x01  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[anyone know how to install redis insight gui on arch btw i found that it's only available on debian or ubuntu in thier offical website :)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujbqht/anyone_know_how_to_install_redis_insight_gui_on/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujbqht/anyone_know_how_to_install_redis_insight_gui_on/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T00:58:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/iamshubh69  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Laptop doesn’t use battery power when not plugged in]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujbmp6/laptop_doesnt_use_battery_power_when_not_plugged/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujbmp6/laptop_doesnt_use_battery_power_when_not_plugged/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T00:52:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The battery isn’t faulty, it charges when plugged in but when it’s not plugged in I want the laptop to use the battery it comes with. When I unplug the laptop it immediately turns off
 In Xfce4’s power settings my laptop battery appears to be 100 percent charged
 [SOLVED] silly me I forgot to put the screws on a year ago
    submitted by    /u/9934d  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How would i make my own local arch caching repo]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujbauz/how_would_i_make_my_own_local_arch_caching_repo/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/ujbauz/how_would_i_make_my_own_local_arch_caching_repo/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T00:28:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I would like to setup and make and arch repo that would cache packages automatically if it does not have them because multiple people in my house use arch and i want to limit the load on the repos and have faster updates at the same time but i dont want to manually download and set up each package every update so can i set up a self hosted repo such that if it is asked about a package that it does not have it would download and forward that the cache the package
    submitted by    /u/whypickthisname  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[9 Simple Ways to Open Device Manager in Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=483844</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15276969/ways-open-device-manager-windows"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a Windows user, you probably open the Device Manager quite frequently. After all, it’s the one-stop shop for managing all of the devices and hardware attached to your computer. It is also a critical part of troubleshooting. But despite the important role it plays, it’s somewhat hidden.
    
Fortunately getting into Device Manager is pretty easy. In this article, we’ll look at nine different ways to access Device Manager on your PC. The first two are the fastest and easiest methods. However, more tech-savvy users who don’t shy away from digging through extensive menu options or running commands might prefer the rest of the methods outlined. The techniques presented in this post are compatible with Windows 10, as well as Windows 11. 
   

Content

1. Use the Quick Access Menu
2. Via the Settings App
3. With Task Manager
4. Use the Run Command
5. With Control Panel
6. Use File Explorer
7. Give Command Prompt/Powershell a Try
8. Through the Computer Management Tool
9. Create a Shortcut

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Claire Moraa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mesa 22.2 Lands The Big Removal Of Old GLSL-To-TGSI Path, Now Always Going Through NIR]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Mesa-22.2-NIR-Always</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Mesa-22.2-NIR-Always"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T23:50:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Emma Anholt's perseverance the past year has paid off in freeing Mesa of the "glsl_to_tgsi" function with now all Mesa drivers going the route of from GLSL to the NIR intermediate representation. For Mesa drivers lacking native NIR consumption, there is then the NIR-to-TGSI path for going back to that traditional Gallium3D IR...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Krita g'mic plugin reliably crashes Krita 5.0.6]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uj8hmk/krita_gmic_plugin_reliably_crashes_krita_506/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uj8hmk/krita_gmic_plugin_reliably_crashes_krita_506/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T22:01:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Opening any image in Krita and trying to start the gmic plugin from the menubar's filter > Start G'MIC-Qt reliably crashes Krita.
 ​
 Running Krita from a terminal and doing this prints:
 *** stack smashing detected ***: terminated
 fish: Job 1, 'krita' terminated by signal SIGABRT (Abort)
 ​
 afaik my system is up to date and I don't have anything relevant to qt/gmic/krita installed from the AUR.
 ​
 Does anybody know what's going on here? Using G'MIC directly in Krita is useful to my workflow.
 Specifically the G'MIC tool to extract a foreground from a background by manually specifying foreground/background control points.
 I've tested it and I can do my G'MIC work in GIMP and load it into Krita as a workaround but oof. Since I already have a workaround I'm not really looking for another one, fixing this problem directly would be nice.
 ​
 package versions:
 gmic 3.1.0-1
 krita 5.0.6-1
 krita-plugin-gmic 3.0.2.2-2
 gimp 2.10.30-2
 gimp-plugin-gmic 3.1.0-1
    submitted by    /u/PreviousHighlight7  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come disattivare Snap Assist Flyout da Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>3555|20220506000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/manutenzione-156/come-disattivare-snap-assist-flyout-windows-11-3555"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Se con il mouse passate sopra al pulsante per ingrandire/rimpicciolire una schermata di Windows 11, quella di un browser, di Word o di esplora risorse, vi appare un menu dove potete scegliere un layout diverso per il vostro schermo. La cosa potrà essere utile per chi ha grandi schermi ed è magari abituato a suddividerli per gestire più cose sullo stesso monitor. A me questa funzione non serve, e non riesco ad abituarmi ad utilizzarla, quindi questa comparsa del menu la voglio eliminare.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is it possible to install Pacman on Busybox arch?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uj80gu/is_it_possible_to_install_pacman_on_busybox_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uj80gu/is_it_possible_to_install_pacman_on_busybox_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T21:39:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I want to replace gnu with busybox on my arch install, but gnu is needed for pacman. Is it possible to install pacman(or another package manager) on arch Linux with busybox? Also would yay work without gnutils and gnucore?
    submitted by    /u/Enter_The_Void6  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Raspberry Robin worm uses Windows Installer to drop malware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-raspberry-robin-worm-uses-windows-installer-to-drop-malware/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-raspberry-robin-worm-uses-windows-installer-to-drop-malware/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T21:36:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Canary intelligence analysts have discovered a new Windows malware with worm capabilities that spreads using external USB drives. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Turn Off Do Not Disturb While Driving]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=415798</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/14683758/turn-off-do-not-disturb-while-driving"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Often some services that are designed to help people can cause more annoyance rather than provide support. One such functionality is the Do Not Disturb mode while driving. I made the mistake of activating it by accident, and what followed was a barrage of missed notifications every time I was in the car. Fortunately, it’s easy to turn off Do not Disturb while driving on Android and iPhone, as we will demonstrate in this article. 
   

Content

How to Turn Off Do Not Disturb While Driving on iPhone in iOS15+
How to Turn Off Do Not Disturb While Driving on iOS 14 and Below
How to Turn Off Do Not Disturb While Driving on Android
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Get Bedtime Mode on Your Android Device
    
How to Turn Off Do Not Disturb While Driving on iPhone in iOS15+
... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mehvish Mushtaq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Triggering a script when a device connects to bluetooth?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uj7ehk/triggering_a_script_when_a_device_connects_to/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uj7ehk/triggering_a_script_when_a_device_connects_to/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T21:11:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have a logitech mouse that I use with logiops (logid). However, I've found that I have to manually run:
 sudo systemctl restart logid
 each time the mouse disconnects and reconnects. Is there a way that I can automate this? I'd also like to have the script trigger upon login.
    submitted by    /u/manafuzer  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Remove Malware Quickly with Malwarebytes’ Anti-Malware]]></title>
        <id>http://www.howtogeek.com/?p=2875</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/howto/2875/remove-malware-quickly-with-malwarebytes-anti-malware/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malwarebytes is one of the best anti-malware programs ever made. It has both free and paid versions, but even the free version is worth having around. Here’s how you can use it to remove malware from your PC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Lewis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fortnite Returns to iPhone and iPad With Xbox Cloud Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=803546</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/803546/fortnite-returns-to-iphone-and-ipad-with-xbox-cloud-gaming/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T20:54:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The popular online game Fortnite has been missing from iPhone and iPad ever since August 2020, when Apple removed it from the App Store over in-app purchase violations. Now the game is once again available for free on iOS devices, thanks to the magic of cloud gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memory slowly fills, process list gives no useful explanation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uj64xr/memory_slowly_fills_process_list_gives_no_useful/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uj64xr/memory_slowly_fills_process_list_gives_no_useful/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T20:12:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello,
 I've recently noticed that as my PC stays turned on for a while, the amount of free memory steadily decreases until it is around 97-98% full. This causes tabs to unload in Firefox and sometimes the whole system slows down.
 I've checked the process list, but nothing uses up even remotely enough memory to justify these numbers. Listing the processes under root doesn't help either. I use XFCE, have at most 4-5 programs running, the heaviest of these is Discord.
 Also I made sure that the memory is actually reported as "used" by free instead of "available" and the "cache" numbers are very low:
  total used free shared buff/cache available Mem: 15Gi 14Gi 762Mi 42Mi 743Mi 1.0Gi Swap: 14Gi 1.6Gi 13Gi 
 Is there anything I could do to figure out what's causing this?
    submitted by    /u/Nemin32  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[White House: Prepare for cryptography-cracking quantum computers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/white-house-prepare-for-cryptography-cracking-quantum-computers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/white-house-prepare-for-cryptography-cracking-quantum-computers/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T20:01:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[President Joe Biden signed a national security memorandum (NSM) on Thursday asking government agencies to implement a set of measures that would mitigate risks posed by quantum computers to US national cyber security. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Turn Off Lens Search in Google Chrome]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=797147</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/797147/turn-off-google-lens-chrome/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T20:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Chrome makes it easy to disable the Lens search feature and bring back the traditional “Search Google for This Image” context menu option. Here’s how you can do that in Chrome on desktop and Android.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dish’s Long-Awaited 5G Network Arrives As ‘Project Genesis’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=803512</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/803512/dishs-long-awaited-5g-network-arrives-as-project-genesis/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T19:27:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dish Network has been building its own cellular network in the United States, mostly with leftover wireless spectrum acquired from T-Mobile’s merger with Sprint. Now the network is starting to go live… in one city, anyway.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does the efibootmgr package do anything by itself?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uj55h8/does_the_efibootmgr_package_do_anything_by_itself/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uj55h8/does_the_efibootmgr_package_do_anything_by_itself/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T19:27:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I first learned how to install Arch I saw a youtuber installing it and he was doing an UEFI installation and he installed efibootmgr, but then he configured grub for efi. Since it was my first time doing it I did the same, but now I think efibootmgr is not doing anything in my system. I don't think it does anything if you are not using it to manage efi. Can this package be uninstalled with no downsides if you are not actively using it? It doesn't seem to be doing anything passively.
    submitted by    /u/nyvec  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get an Amazon Kindle, Ad-Supported, for Under $55]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=439314</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/14856197/amazon-kindle-ad-supported"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Getting ready for the summer reading season? Do it all from one device instead of making multiple trips to the library and book store. An Amazon Kindle will be your special beach buddy. While it may be ad-supported, that helps keep the cost down. Buy now and get it for a 39% discount.
    
The Kindle is designed just for reading rather than for multiple uses like smartphones and tablets. It has a 167 ppi glare-free display to make you feel like you’re reading on paper, even if you’re reading in direct sunlight. The adjustable brightness allows you to read comfortably, wherever you are, inside, at the beach, at the park, etc., regardless of the time of day.
    

    
Another difference from a tablet is that the Amazon Kindle will last for weeks on a single battery charge compared to just hours, making it the perfect vacation companion. It has 8GB of storage, allowing you to keep thousands of books at the ready, all on one device. You only have to pack one... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Systemd 251-rc2 Released With More Features]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=systemd-251-rc2</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=systemd-251-rc2"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T19:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just over one month after systemd 251-rc1 was released, a second release candidate to this next systemd installment is now available for testing. Systemd 251-rc2 brings yet more features to this Linux init system and service manager...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Pause Audio on Apple AirPods]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=797130</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/797130/how-to-pause-airpods/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T19:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you use Apple’s AirPods, you don’t have to reach for your phone to play or pause your music. You can use your AirPods’ built-in music controls to do that, and we’ll show you how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ukraine’s IT Army is disrupting Russia's alcohol distribution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ukraine-s-it-army-is-disrupting-russias-alcohol-distribution/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ukraine-s-it-army-is-disrupting-russias-alcohol-distribution/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T18:57:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hacktivists operating on the side of Ukraine have focused their DDoS attacks on a portal that is considered crucial for the distribution of alcoholic beverages in Russia. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your Nanoleaf Lines Are Begging for These Official Skins]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117078/your-nanoleaf-lines-are-begging-for-these-official-skins/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117078/your-nanoleaf-lines-are-begging-for-these-official-skins/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T18:22:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Out of the box, Nanoleaf Lines smart lights look a little plain. The lights themselves are colorful, for sure, but the hardware is just white. That’s why Nanoleaf now sells official matte black and pink skins for its Lines smart lights—prepare to drop $20 on these puppies; you definitely want them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Brings CGI Product Placement to Prime Video & Freevee]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=803476</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/803476/amazon-brings-cgi-product-placement-to-prime-video-freevee/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T18:19:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Product placement is nothing new for movies and TV shows, but Amazon is interested in pushing the idea a bit further with some content on Prime Video and Freevee (formerly IMDb TV).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NIST updates guidance for defending against supply-chain attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/nist-updates-guidance-for-defending-against-supply-chain-attacks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/nist-updates-guidance-for-defending-against-supply-chain-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T18:15:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST) has released updated guidance on securing the supply chain against cyberattacks. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Wi-Fi “Wardriving” and How Can You Protect Yourself?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=794732</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/794732/what-is-wi-fi-wardriving-and-how-can-you-protect-yourself/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T18:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[War, what is it good for? Well, when we’re talking about wardriving, it’s away to find unsecured Wi-Fi, sometimes with malicious intent. Wardriving is hard to detect, but with preparation you can protect your home network from being targeted.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sydney Butler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fedora Linux 36 Being Released Next Week]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Fedora-Linux-36-Next-Week</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Fedora-Linux-36-Next-Week"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After being delayed a few weeks from their original release target, Fedora 36 is now primed for release next week Tuesday...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTC to force ISP to deploy fiber for 60K users to match speed claims]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/ftc-to-force-isp-to-deploy-fiber-for-60k-users-to-match-speed-claims/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/ftc-to-force-isp-to-deploy-fiber-for-60k-users-to-match-speed-claims/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T17:43:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Federal Trade Commission (FTC) today proposed an order requiring Connecticut-based internet service provider Frontier Communications to stop "lying" to its customers and support its high-speed internet claims. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Problems connecting to MariaDB from Python (pyodbc)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uj2rm8/problems_connecting_to_mariadb_from_python_pyodbc/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uj2rm8/problems_connecting_to_mariadb_from_python_pyodbc/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T17:38:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been trying to connect to a database using this Python script but it gives me the folllowing error:
 pyodbc.connect('DRIVER=ODBC Driver for MySQL;User=user;Password=pass;Database=tareabd_1;Server=server;Port=3306;')
 error:
 pyodbc.Error: ('01000', "[01000] [unixODBC][Driver Manager]Can't open lib 'CData ODBC Driver for MariaDB' : file not found (0) (SQLDriverConnect)")
 ​
 If I chage the input to:
 pyodbc.connect(('DRIVER=/usr/lib/libmaodbc.so;User=user;Password=pass;Database=tareabd_1;Server=server;Port=3306;')
 the error changes to:
 pyodbc.Error: ('HY000', "[HY000] [ma-3.1.15]Unknown server host 'server' (-2) (2005) (SQLDriverConnect)")
 ​
 The output from "cat odbcinst.ini" is :
 [MySQL]
 Description = ODBC Driver for MySQL
 Driver = /usr/lib/libmaodbc.so
 FileUsage = 1
 ​
 The ouput from "cat /etc/odbc.ini" is:
 [CData MariaDB Source]
 Driver = CData ODBC Driver for MariaDB
 Description = Tarea 1 Bases de Datos
 User = user
 Password = pass
 Database = tareabd_1
 Server = server
 Port = 3306
 ​
 I followed the guide from the ArchWiki at first, but it doesn''t seem to work.
    submitted by    /u/LordMikeVTRxDalv  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can't get ArchLinux install flash drive to work.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uj2om5/cant_get_archlinux_install_flash_drive_to_work/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uj2om5/cant_get_archlinux_install_flash_drive_to_work/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T17:34:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I just can't get 2022.05.01 ArchLinux iso image to work as an install flash drive on HP EliteBook 840 G5. 
 I didn't find a way to get the text output, so I at least took a photo of it. https://imgur.com/tQGVNCg 
 Strange thing is that it works fine using 2021.01.01 iso. Did anyone experience similar problem? Is there even anything I can do about that?
    submitted by    /u/TheBCX  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NVIDIA Finally Offers 4K Cloud Gaming for Windows and Mac Users]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117068/nvidia-finally-offers-4k-cloud-gaming-for-windows-and-mac-users/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117068/nvidia-finally-offers-4k-cloud-gaming-for-windows-and-mac-users/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T17:28:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It took NVIDIA a few years to get here, but the company is finally offering its GeForce Now cloud gaming service at 4K and 120FPS for those on Windows and macOS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Acer Proves That Powerful Chromebooks Don't Need to Be Expensive]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117047/acer-proves-that-powerful-chromebooks-dont-need-to-be-expensive/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117047/acer-proves-that-powerful-chromebooks-dont-need-to-be-expensive/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T17:12:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Because Chromebooks run a lightweight operating system, they require far less horsepower than Windows or Mac computers. But power users are willing to pay out the nose for a speedy computer; they don’t care that $1,000 is “overpriced for a Chromebook.” So, Acer is giving those power users a much more affordable alternative.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can't install Spotify from the AUR]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uj21oo/cant_install_spotify_from_the_aur/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uj21oo/cant_install_spotify_from_the_aur/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T17:06:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When downloading Spotify using yay, I get the following error:
 ==> Validating source files with sha512sums...
 spotify.protocol ... Passed
 LICENSE ... Passed
 spotify-1.1.84.716-x86_64.deb ... FAILED
 spotify-1.1.84.716-1-Release ... Skipped
 spotify-1.1.84.716-1-Release.sig ... Skipped
 spotify-1.1.84.716-1-x86_64-Packages ... Skipped
 ==> ERROR: One or more files did not pass the validity check!
 -> error downloading sources: spotify
 context: exit status 1
 I've tried most of the solutions posted on https://aur.archlinux.org/packages/spotify, including importing a new GPG key, changing the sha512sums on the PKGBUILD file and deleting the yay and pacman cache, all resulting in the same error once again.
 Any help is highly appreciated.
    submitted by    /u/Sad-Mixture-1953  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lenovo Yoga 2022: la nuova serie di notebook, convertibili e all-in-one è sorprendente]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Lenovo-Yoga-2022-la-nuova-serie-di-notebook-convertibili-e-all-in-one-e-sorprendente_24477</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Lenovo-Yoga-2022-la-nuova-serie-di-notebook-convertibili-e-all-in-one-e-sorprendente_24477"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T17:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Il marchio Lenovo Yoga è da anni divenuto un vero e proprio punto di riferimento nel suo segmento. L'azienda ha iniziato con l'idea dei convertibili per poi ampliare la gamma con un ventaglio di portatili ultraleggeri, notebook gaming, Chromebook, tablet, 2-in-1 e anche desktop.Gli obiettivi della serie Yoga sono rimasti inalterati nel tempo ma l'ultima generazione convince ancora di più grazie all'adozione delle ultime piattaforme Intel e AMD, agli schermi PureSight e alle tecnologie di Lenovo come l'insieme di caratteristiche per aumentare le prestazioni X Power e il sistema A.I. Engine+ che sfrutta l'intelligenza artificiale per anticipare le esigenze dell'utente in termini di potenza e batteria sulla base dell'attività che si sta svolgendo.Lenovo ha svelato oggi la nuova generazione di…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Face ID?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=800426</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/800426/what-is-face-id/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T17:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Certain models of Apple iPhone and iPad include an authentication feature called “Face ID,” which uses a special camera on the front of your device to verify your identity. But why do we need Face ID, and how does it work? We’ll explain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced SystemCare per velocizzare Windows (gratuito)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2012/10/configurazione-pc-ottimale-con-systemcare.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2012/10/configurazione-pc-ottimale-con-systemcare.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T16:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced SystemCare di IOBit è uno dei programmi Windows più popolari per ottimizzare e ripulire Windows. Avviando questo programma potremo trovare la giusta configurazione del computer, correggendo automaticamente gli errori di sistema, ripulendo il disco da riferimenti e file non più validi o obsoleti e riconoscendo quali servizi disattivare per far andare il pc più veloce.

 Si tratta di una...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft, Apple, and Google to support FIDO passwordless logins]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-apple-and-google-to-support-fido-passwordless-logins/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-apple-and-google-to-support-fido-passwordless-logins/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T16:19:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft, Apple, and Google announced today plans to support a common passwordless sign-in standard (known as passkeys) developed by the World Wide Web Consortium (W3C) and the FIDO Alliance. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google fixes actively exploited Android kernel vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/google-fixes-actively-exploited-android-kernel-vulnerability/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/google-fixes-actively-exploited-android-kernel-vulnerability/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T16:11:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has released the second part of the May security patch for Android, including a fix for an actively exploited Linux kernel vulnerability. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla Drivers Discover an Unannounced Swivel Display Upgrade]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117040/tesla-drivers-discover-an-unannounced-swivel-display-upgrade/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117040/tesla-drivers-discover-an-unannounced-swivel-display-upgrade/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T16:06:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla could finally be ready to upgrade what many drivers and passengers interact with the most, the in-car infotainment display. New videos have confirmed that Tesla’s upgraded Model S and Model X displays will have a motorized swivel feature.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Help with CDM Install]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uj0rdh/help_with_cdm_install/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uj0rdh/help_with_cdm_install/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T16:04:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I followed the instructions on the wiki, but the wiki said a script in /etc/profile.d (called zzz-cdm.sh) should be generated, but when I check /etc/profile.d, nothing is there.
 Pacman says the package "cdm" is installed. I installed the AUR package from a non-root user because I'm not supposed to makepkg from root.
    submitted by    /u/Hefty_Ad2383  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Undo Typing on a Samsung Galaxy Phone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=800644</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/800644/how-to-undo-typing-on-a-samsung-galaxy-phone/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T16:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ability to “Undo” the last thing you typed is something we take for granted on PCs. The iPhone also happens to have a handy undo gesture—and, if you use a Samsung Galaxy phone, you do too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making This Coffee Switch Could Help Your Stomach]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lifesavvy.com/127742/making-this-coffee-switch-could-help-your-stomach/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lifesavvy.com/127742/making-this-coffee-switch-could-help-your-stomach/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T16:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coffee drinkers with sensitive stomachs are well aware that, sometimes, that morning cup doesn’t sit right. One change could make all the difference, though.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shea Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mesa's "Rusticl" Implementation Now Manages To Handle Darktable OpenCL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Rusticl-Darktable-Milestone</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Rusticl-Darktable-Milestone"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rusticl as what started out as a Rust language experiment for Mesa and has now matured into a working OpenCL 3.0 implementation for Mesa drivers is still making progress and on a path towards eventually being mainlined...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Working From Home? Boost Your Productivity With Setapp for Mac]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=798968</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/798968/working-from-home-boost-your-productivity-with-setapp-for-mac/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T15:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Working from home has become wildly popular over the past few years, but it has also introduced us to challenges we hadn’t considered. Pets, projects around the house, random distractions on the internet — all serve to deter focus and hamper productivity. Can a suite of work-focused apps help you get back on track? We’ll discuss how to stay productive while working from home with Setapp, a popular subscription service with more than 200 incredible apps for Mac.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sponsored</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Arch wants to mount my secondary hard drive at boot?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uj0e07/why_arch_wants_to_mount_my_secondary_hard_drive/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uj0e07/why_arch_wants_to_mount_my_secondary_hard_drive/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T15:47:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everytime that I boot, it appears this box ( https://imgur.com/a/ugYvoSW ) that asks the root password for mounting my hard drive (/dev/sda2). Why? How can I disabled this? it's so annoying.
 ​
 This is my /etc/fstab:
 ​
 [sh4ttered@arch-sh4ttered ~]$ cat /etc/fstab 
 # Static information about the filesystems.
 # See fstab(5) for details. 
 # <file system> <dir> <type> <options> <dump> <pass>
 # /dev/sdb2
 UUID=e8fce133-159e-4740-b4cd-7e56dfea74cd / ext4 rw,relatime 0 1 
 # /dev/sdb1
 UUID=DA0E-C048 /boot vfat rw,relatime,fmask=0022,dmask=0022,codepage=437,iocharset=ascii,shortname=mixed,utf8,errors=remount-ro 0 2
    submitted by    /u/lox689  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chromebooks Are Getting Super-Fast AMD Ryzen 5000 Processors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=803373</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/803373/chromebooks-are-getting-super-fast-amd-ryzen-5000-processors/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T15:42:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chromebooks don’t have the same options for hardware as traditional PCs, and more recently, many of the best Chromebooks have been behind on new processors. That’s now changing, with the introduction of AMD Ryzen 5000 C-Series chips for Chrome OS computers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[moving an existing arch install to a live usb drive]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uj072z/moving_an_existing_arch_install_to_a_live_usb/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uj072z/moving_an_existing_arch_install_to_a_live_usb/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T15:38:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, I have a fully working install of arch on my laptop but I could do with having a portable clone of it on a USB drive that I can boot to from any PC for work. I have looked on the wiki and can see steps to clone your install etc but I can't find a guide to clone the OS To a live usb. Can anyone point me in the right direction?
 I've seen guides on how to clone an install from usb to hdd but not the other way around
 Thanks!
    submitted by    /u/PWICHex  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google, Apple, and Microsoft Agree to Make Passwords a Thing of the Past]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117029/google-apple-and-microsoft-agree-to-make-passwords-a-thing-of-the-past/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117029/google-apple-and-microsoft-agree-to-make-passwords-a-thing-of-the-past/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T15:28:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Passwords are a hassle, and unfortunately, they’re often a security risk. Even when a password is nice and complicated (they usually aren’t), it may be compromised through brute-force attacks, leaks, or malware. That’s why Apple, Google, and Microsoft are now collaborating on our passwordless future through the FIDO standard.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[System doesn't boot completely after changing from NVIDIA to AMD]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uizyaj/system_doesnt_boot_completely_after_changing_from/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uizyaj/system_doesnt_boot_completely_after_changing_from/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T15:27:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[sry if anything here is weird to read but english isn't my first language (i'm from germany)
 I'm currently trying to get away from Windows (due to win11 being absolutely horrendous). After trying out a bunch of linux distros in virtual machines over several years, a portable Archlinux install on a flash drive and now also on my Steam Deck i actually installed Archlinux on my computer that i use for gaming and work.
 So far it worked great with sddm and KDE Plasma but the drivers for my NVIDIA GTX 1060 were awful to use. As i was already searching for a new GPU anyway i changed my plans a bit and purchased an AMD RX 6800 XT instead of another NVIDIA card.
 I thought that i could simply remove all nvidia drivers, install xf86-video-amdgpu and mesa and everything should work fine. Well, at boot i'm now stuck with:
 [ ok ] Reached Target Graphical Interface 
 By pressing Ctrl + Alt + F2 i've logged into the system and ran journalctl -b -p err to see what's wrong. Turns out systemd still tries to load the nvidia drivers:
 Failed to find module 'nvidia-uvm' 
 Besides that there seemed to be 3 errors regarding sddm not being able to launch because it couldn't connect to any display.
 I tried to look at the Arch Wiki systemd Article to tell it to not load the nvidia drivers but i honestly couldn't figure it out. Is there an way to fix that?
 Sidenote: My zsh ist configured to run neofetch at start (just for fun) but my GPU ist described as AMD RX 6800 / 6800 XT / 6900 XT. Does that mean it couldn't figure out which GPU is installed or am i overthinking things and this is normal?
 Edit: I had to delete the xorg.conf file from /etc/X11/ that was apparently also created by the nvidia drivers. Everything works now again.
    submitted by    /u/Jefson_Morinskey  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PS4/PS5 Controller Alternatives for Those Who Prefer the Xbox One Controller]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=340576</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/13491528/ps4-controllers-alternatives"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sorry Sony, but the DualShock and the DualSense controllers don’t hold a candle to the Xbox controller. Microsoft’s controller features a more comfortable offset analog stick layout and proper shoulder triggers instead of clunky bumpers. While it can be argued that the Sony consoles have a significantly better game library than the Xbox and despite both connecting through Bluetooth, there’s no way to use your Xbox One controller on your PlayStation natively. If you’re a PS4/PS5 fan but have always been envious of the Xbox One controller, there are a few third-party controller manufacturers that have answered your prayers.
   

Content

Do Any of these Controllers Work on PlayStation 5?
1. Hori ONYX
2. Nacon Asymmetric Wireless
3. Nacon Revolution Unlimited Pro
4. SCUF Vantage
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Connect a PS4/PS5 Controller to Your Android Phone
    
Do... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Lynch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Around A Paywall]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/?p=59613</id>
        <link href="https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/getting-around-paywall/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T15:01:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most blogs and online news outlets have paywalls in place to limit access to their content. Although these paywalls are put up by sites to get paid for]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hongkiat.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are Curved Monitors Worth It?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=794986</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/794986/are-curved-monitors-worth-it/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T15:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Curved monitors aren’t curved for a stylistic choice. They provide valuable benefits such as a wider field of view and wider display resolutions. However, they won’t benefit everyone. Let’s discuss whether curved monitors are right for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Nguyen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bonus Internet 300 euro senza limiti ISEE: cos'è e come funziona]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Bonus-Internet-300-euro-senza-limiti-ISEE-cos-e-e-come-funziona_24476</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Bonus-Internet-300-euro-senza-limiti-ISEE-cos-e-e-come-funziona_24476"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T14:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Con l'obiettivo di estendere la diffusione della connettività a banda ultralarga in Italia, il Ministero dello Sviluppo Economico (MISE) sta lavorando su un nuovo provvedimento con cui verranno erogati 300 euro di bonus alle famiglie che attiveranno abbonamenti capaci di assicurare in downstream, almeno commercialmente, non meno di 30 Mbps.A novembre 2020 avevamo parlato del bonus Internet, PC e tablet che metteva sul piatto un voucher da 500 euro per la 'digitalizzazione' delle famiglie italiane con ISEE non superiore a 20.000 euro.Attingendo ai fondi del PNRR (Piano nazionale ripresa resilienza), questa volta il MISE offre un bonus Internet da 300 euro ai richiedenti senza limiti di reddito. Attraverso Infratel Italia, società in-house del MISE, chiamata a gestire l'intera operazione, saranno stanziati poco meno di 410 milioni di euro suddivisi tra le varie regioni d'Italia.Come già avvenuto nel caso dei precedenti 'bonus', compreso quello di marzo 2022 destinato alla digitalizzazione delle imprese, anche in questo caso il voucher del valore di 300 euro sarà riconosciuto solo ed esclusivamente per l'attivazione di servizi di connettività ad almeno 30 Mbps di velocità massima in download, realizzati con qualsiasi tecnologia disponibile.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Se il Bluetooth del Amazon Echo non funziona, come risolvere]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/05/se-il-bluetooth-del-amazon-echo-non.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/05/se-il-bluetooth-del-amazon-echo-non.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T14:38:00.007Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I dispositivi Amazon Echo possono essere utilizzati come semplici casse Bluetooth: non dobbiamo far altro che lanciare il comando vocale "Alexa, accendi il Bluetooth" e utilizzare il menu Bluetooth del telefono o del computer per associarlo, così da poter riprodurre musica o suoni con una potenza maggiore rispetto alle casse integrate. Purtroppo non sempre l'associazione va a buon fine o, in...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMS truffa da Banca BPER: un dispositivo anomalo si è collegato alla vostra area privata]]></title>
        <id>3567|20220505163350</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/truffe-5953/sms-truffa-banca-bper-dispositivo-anomalo-si-collegato-area-privata-3567"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T14:33:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sta circolando con estrema velocità un SMS truffaldino inviato da furbetti che si fingono Banca BPER, il cui testo questa volta spicca per originalità. Vediamo di cosa si tratta
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New NetDooka malware spreads via poisoned search results]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-netdooka-malware-spreads-via-poisoned-search-results/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-netdooka-malware-spreads-via-poisoned-search-results/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T14:28:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new malware framework known as NetDooka has been discovered being distributed through the PrivateLoader pay-per-install (PPI) malware distribution service, allowing threat actors full access to an infected device. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Budget Smartwatches of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=794371</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/794371/best-budget-smartwatch/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T14:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Buying a budget smartwatch can feel daunting given the sheer number of options from both popular and relatively unknown brands. But we’re here to help. Here are our handpicked recommendations for the best budget smartwatches.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gaurav Shukla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don't Forget This Curb Appeal Task Before Selling Your Home]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lifesavvy.com/127735/dont-forget-this-curb-appeal-task-before-selling-your-home/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lifesavvy.com/127735/dont-forget-this-curb-appeal-task-before-selling-your-home/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T14:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to selling a home, there are a few things nearly everyone knows can increase the selling price. For example, you can upgrade fixtures or spruce up the lawn. However, there’s another exterior detail you might be forgetting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shea Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>