<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-05-19T02:00:54.703Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update grub config for Arch from another distro]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uss48o/update_grub_config_for_arch_from_another_distro/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uss48o/update_grub_config_for_arch_from_another_distro/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T01:31:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have a dual-booted system with Ubuntu and arch. Ubuntu is the default and controls grub, with os-prober used to add arch when changes are made. My arch os doesn't even have grub installed on it. How do I make changes to the grub config in Ubuntu so that they affect arch? So far any changes I make only affect Ubuntu.
    submitted by    /u/lovecraftedidiot  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mesa 22.1 Released With Many Vulkan Improvements, Kopper For Zink, Imagination Driver]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Mesa-22.1-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Mesa-22.1-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T00:40:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mesa 22.1 is out today as the newest, quarterly feature update to the open-source OpenGL/Vulkan graphics driver stack that also supports video acceleration and other GPU features on the Linux desktop...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Convert Legacy BIOS to UEFI in Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=284130</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/10906619/convert-legacy-bios-uefi-windows10"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In older versions of Windows, you were forced to reinstall the entire operating system if you wanted to convert legacy BIOS or Master Boot Record (MBR) to UEFI or GUID Partition Table (GPT). However, a new and simple tool called MBR2GPT was introduced in Windows 10. It lets you convert legacy BIOS to UEFI with just two commands. 
    
Here is how you can convert legacy BIOS to UEFI in Windows 10. If you’re a Windows 11 user, you shouldn’t do anything, as UEFI mode is enabled by default on your device.
    
Do not skip any of the prerequisites of legacy BIOS to UEFI conversion mentioned below, as it can lead to system failure and even hardware issues in some cases.
   

Content

Why Convert Legacy BIOS to UEFI?
Prerequisites for Legacy BIOS to UEFI Conversion
Do I Need to Convert Legacy BIOS to UEFI in Windows 11?
How to Check Whether You Are Using Legacy BIOS
How to Convert Legacy BIOS to UEFI
How to Fix the MBR2GPT "Disk Layout Validation Failed" Error
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sayak Boral</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How can I troubleshoot a wake from sleep issue?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/usqekl/how_can_i_troubleshoot_a_wake_from_sleep_issue/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/usqekl/how_can_i_troubleshoot_a_wake_from_sleep_issue/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-19T00:01:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a recent update my wake from sleep isn't working properly.
 On wake up the screen activates for 30seconds or so but SDDM login screen never appears and I have to hard power reset/reboot my system to get to a login screen. How can I troubleshoot this?
 Are logs saved from the previous boot somewhere?
 My gear as requested previously:
 5950x, 6700xt, asrock x570 m pro4, 5.17 kernel, kde desktop, SDDM. 
 Before the update sleep worked perfectly for 5+ months. . . 
 Thanks for any tips or ideas
    submitted by    /u/Im-Mostly-Confused  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Enterprise Linux 9.0 GA Now Officially Available]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=RHEL-9.0-GA-Official</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=RHEL-9.0-GA-Official"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T23:32:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week Red Hat announced at the Red Hat Summit that RHEL9 would be reach GA in the coming weeks while today it officially crossed that threshold...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secure Boot and archinstall via USB]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uspenc/secure_boot_and_archinstall_via_usb/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uspenc/secure_boot_and_archinstall_via_usb/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T23:10:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey all,
 Want to make a switch to Arch, but wondering if there is a uefi x64 shim I can place on the USB so that secure boot is used straight from the install?
 Is there any easy way to do this, or a guide anywhere?
 I don't want to get Arch running, then go through adding secure boot post-install, as there are a few machines I'd love to just get running quickly
    submitted by    /u/AussieAn0n  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stuck on Running Early Hook [udev] when I boot my pc]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uspcr0/stuck_on_running_early_hook_udev_when_i_boot_my_pc/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uspcr0/stuck_on_running_early_hook_udev_when_i_boot_my_pc/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T23:07:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently bought a pc but when I boot it opens up a page that says
 running early hook [udev]
 starting version 248.3-2-Arch
 my pc gets stuck on this page and when I restart it or power it off Then on again it brings me right back to this page. i have an option to open up bios except I have no idea what to do in bios to fix it or how to fix it in general
 Incase it matters my specs are EVGA RTX 2070 super, Ryzen 7 3800x, and 32gb of ram
 someone please help I have no idea how to fix this, Thanks!
    submitted by    /u/LucasNelson_25  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[meson.build returns error while installing packages with yay]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/usoqcp/mesonbuild_returns_error_while_installing/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/usoqcp/mesonbuild_returns_error_while_installing/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T22:37:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm new to Arch Linux, so I'm sorry if it's a dumb question.
 Recently I tried installing python-validity package using yay and every time I try it the build fails because of an error returned by meson.build:
 fprintd-clients/meson.build:1:0: ERROR: Unknown linker(s): [['gcc-ar'], ['ar'], ['gar']] The following exception(s) were encountered: Running "gar --version" gave "[Errno 2] No such file or directory: 'gar'" 
 Since it's the second package I encounter this error with (don't remember which one was the first one, though) I thought it hasn't something to do with the package itself but maybe with something on my PC, am I right? Is there something I can do to fix this?
 (I already tried uninstalling meson and reinstalling it first using pip and then using yay... it seems to be installed successfully, but I don't know)
    submitted by    /u/Elodran  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strange WiFi issues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/usoppg/strange_wifi_issues/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/usoppg/strange_wifi_issues/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T22:36:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, I have been having some confusing problems with my wifi.
 Network manager is often, but not always, unable to see any WiFi networks and there appears to be a correlation with this problem and the wifi networks my university provides, specifically eduroam. Occasionally I will be able to see all the networks that I should be able to, but, after an attempted connection timing out, the networks are no longer found by network manager. What is very odd it that this problem seems to be local to the wifi networks in use at my university. I was perfectly able to find and connect to networks in a cafe yesterday. It has crossed my mind that my credentials could have been blacklisted from the wifi (my torrenting is distros and copyright free material, obviously) but this can't be the case because my phone and other laptop connect fine with the same credentials.
 I should make clear that in some buildings of my university, I am able to see and connect to eduroam, so I'm pretty sure the problem isn't related to how I have the eduroam connection configured. 
 The hardware I am using is Qualcomm Atheros AR9285 Wireless Network Adapter (PCI-Express) and the ath9k kernel driver. I am running kernel version Linux 5.17.8-arch1-1.
 I can and would provide logs but because I am in the dark about what is going wrong I don't know which logs would be relevant as the ones I have looked through don't appear to show anything obviously wrong. I would greatly appreciate any pointers about what could be going on here. Thank you :)
    submitted by    /u/resvald  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft releases first ISO image for new Windows 11 Dev builds]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-releases-first-iso-image-for-new-windows-11-dev-builds/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-releases-first-iso-image-for-new-windows-11-dev-builds/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T22:27:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has released the first ISO image for the new Windows 11 Preview builds in the Dev channel, allowing Windows Insiders to perform clean installs of the operating system. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come modificare le dimensioni della barra di scorrimento di alcuni programmi in Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>3578|20220519000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/windows-10/come-modificare-dimensioni-barra-scorrimento-alcuni-programmi-windows-11-3578"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Da quando ho iniziato ad utilizzare Windows 11, una delle cose che mi creava dei problemi era la dimensione della barra di scorrimento laterale e inferiore che, in alcuni programmi che utilizzo, era notevolmente dimagrita. Dovendo io lavorare con un cursore del mouse piuttosto grande, quando la dovevo toccare per farla scorrere più velocemente, a volte, mi risultava difficile “catturarla”.
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spanish police dismantle phishing gang that emptied bank accounts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/spanish-police-dismantle-phishing-gang-that-emptied-bank-accounts/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/spanish-police-dismantle-phishing-gang-that-emptied-bank-accounts/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T21:36:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Spanish police have announced the arrest of 13 people and the launch of investigations on another 7 for their participation in a phishing ring that defrauded at least 146 people. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Secure Your Chromebook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=post-ideas&amp;p=278327</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/10706588/howto-secure-chromebook"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chromebooks are Google’s lightweight laptops that run on Chrome OS. These machines are designed to be used primarily while connected to the Internet. They are by design safe, durable, and secure, especially when compared with traditional computers. Google really has done its homework when it comes to Chromebook security. It offers interesting automated and customizable features to keep your information and laptop safe. Let’s check various ways to secure your Chromebook.
   

Content

1. Update Your Chromebook
2. Use a PIN Instead of a Password
3. Show Lock Screen After Waking Up From Sleep
4. Take Advantage of Guest Mode
5. Restrict Sign-in to Selected Users
6. Secure Chrome Browser
Lost Your Chromebook? Sign Out Remotely
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:6 Best Tips to Protect Your Gmail Account Security
    
1. Update Your Chromebook
    
As with any operating system, installing... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mehvish Mushtaq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to take a screenshot on Windows]]></title>
        <id>7878627f-5832-497e-a6c4-9590f8d1c2b3</id>
        <link href="https://www.zdnet.com/article/how-to-screenshot-on-windows/#ftag=RSSbaffb68"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T21:15:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We show you how to capture images on Windows with a free tool in this quick how-to. We'll also point you to a capture tool that costs a bit more but does just about everything you could possibly want.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest topics for ZDNet in Windows</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch firmware problems (?)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/usn04a/arch_firmware_problems/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/usn04a/arch_firmware_problems/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T21:14:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm trying to install Arch on a laptop that had its screen broken years ago, it worked fine with Ubuntu but I forgot the password. Now I wanted to try Arch but when entering the BIOS menu if I connect the laptop to a screen (that way I used and install Ubuntu) nothing appears on the screen, it is connected by HDMI. Could someone help me with any solution?
    submitted by    /u/sinnstral  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Jupiter WordPress plugin flaws let hackers take over sites]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/critical-jupiter-wordpress-plugin-flaws-let-hackers-take-over-sites/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/critical-jupiter-wordpress-plugin-flaws-let-hackers-take-over-sites/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T21:12:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress security analysts have discovered a set of vulnerabilities impacting the Jupiter Theme and JupiterX Core plugins for WordPress, one of which is a critical privilege escalation flaw. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Move Windows 11’s Taskbar to the Top of the Screen]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=759882</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/759882/how-to-move-windows-11s-taskbar-to-the-top-of-the-screen/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As of October 2021, Windows 11 doesn’t let you move your taskbar to the top of the screen with an official setting (unlike Windows 10). But we’ve figured out a way to make it happen by editing the Registry—and you can do it with just a few clicks. Here’s how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Issues installing xmobar-git]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/usmdyc/issues_installing_xmobargit/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/usmdyc/issues_installing_xmobargit/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T20:46:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello,
 I've recently successfully installed xmobar-git on my main VM and had fun tweaking it. I've now attempted a similar installation on a different VM, and I'm literally going insane with it.
 I get weird errors telling me that some package is broken. I've attempted to solve this by googling, reinstalling and doing the rain-dance. Can't get it to work, although it worked a couple days ago.
 Here is the error I get, note the fact the I check for installed packages in the end and they are identical to the packages on the working VM, yet it complains a bunch and won't let me install it. I can't think of how to proceed with this.
 Arch% sudo aura -A xmobar-git aura >>= Determining dependencies... aura >>= AUR Packages: xmobar-git aura >>= Continue? [Y/n] aura >>= Building xmobar-git... aura >>= Building failed. Would you like to see the error? [Y/n] xmobar-git ... Skipped Switched to a new branch 'makepkg' Error: The following packages are broken because other packages they depend on are missing. These broken packages must be rebuilt before they can be used. installed package dbus-1.2.22 is broken due to missing package lens-5.1-Ip0S0ojmIlP8S4rE2GWrUQ ==> ERROR: A failure occurred in build(). Aborting... aura >>= There was a makepkg failure. aura >>= Would you like to continue anyway? [Y/n] n aura >>= Building failed. Arch% pacman -Q | grep dbus dbus 1.14.0-1 haskell-dbus 1.2.22-53 Arch% pacman -Q | grep lens haskell-lens 5.1-37 Arch% 
    submitted by    /u/pink-skyline  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[National bank hit by ransomware trolls hackers with dick pics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/national-bank-hit-by-ransomware-trolls-hackers-with-dick-pics/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/national-bank-hit-by-ransomware-trolls-hackers-with-dick-pics/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T20:13:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After suffering a ransomware attack by the Hive operation, the Bank of Zambia made it clear that they were not going to pay by posting a picture of male genitalia and telling the hackers to s… (well, you can use your imagination). [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Edge Is Improving Your Installed Web Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=806088</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/806088/microsoft-edge-is-improving-your-installed-web-apps/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T20:02:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome has offered the ability to “install” web apps to your computer for a while now, and the feature is also available on the new Chromium-based Microsoft Edge. Now the Edge browser has an easier way to manage web apps, with more improvements on the way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add More Ethernet Ports to Your Router]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=753127</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/753127/how-to-add-more-ethernet-ports-to-your-router/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While most of us rely on wireless at home, wired internet is often a better choice. The only catch is that most home routers only have a handful of ports. Adding more ports is easy, but there are a few things to consider when setting things up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[fcitx5 empty system tray context menu]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/usl40h/fcitx5_empty_system_tray_context_menu/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/usl40h/fcitx5_empty_system_tray_context_menu/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T19:47:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey guys! For some reason, when I right click the fcitx5 system tray icon it pops up empty, I'm guessing it's a font problem. Does anyone know how to solve this?
 I have already installed the following fonts: ttf-dejavu ttf-liberation noto-fonts noto-fonts-cjk noto-fonts-emoji
 thanks in advance :D
 https://imgur.com/a/NbyxWeC 
 edit: not really solved, just uninstalled fcitx5 installed fcitx and everything is working fine now, apparently fcitx5 is just broken
    submitted by    /u/TR0V40_  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Take $100 Off a Samsung Galaxy A53 5G A Series Smartphone]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=490329</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15310965/samsung-galaxy-a53-5g-smartphone"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s no need to spend $1000 or more on a new smartphone. You can get the Samsung Galaxy A53 5G A Series Smartphone, released in 2022, for just $349.99. You won’t be skimping on features either, as this 6.5″ Android phone is unlocked and has 128GB, an FHD Super AMOLED screen, and a long battery life.
    
This super-fast charging 5,000mAh battery supports 25W charging and is long-lasting, whether you’re on a video call, bingeing your favorite shows, or catching up with social media. You’ll have smooth streaming as well with fast downloads, thanks to 5G.
    

    
This Samsung Galaxy A53 5G A Series Smartphone has the series’ biggest built-in storage with 6GB RAM, and you can expand it to 128GB with a microSD card so that you won’t be deleting photos trying to make more room. The intelligent camera allows you to record video and shoot pictures with just one tap, with all media being clear with image stabilization.
    
The 6.5″ display is meant for entertainment with clarity and... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Greek characters are not displayed right]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uskag1/greek_characters_are_not_displayed_right/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/uskag1/greek_characters_are_not_displayed_right/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T19:08:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello,
 Im using xprop to get the names of windows, and whenever there is greek text involed, it is displayed as follows:
 \316\221\316\273\316\273\316\267\316\273\316\277\316\263\317\201\316\261\317\206\316\257\316\261 
 I am thinking that it has to do with fonts but Im not sure. I have ttg-mgopen(TrueType fonts containing glyphs for the Latin and Greek alphabet) installed.
 The issue doesn't seem to be terminal emulator specific, as the same gibberish appear on my i3 status bar(I'm using a script that, using xprop, displays the window names in status bar).
 I don't know what other info to provide, that can be useful so write me in the comments and I will edit this post accordingly.
    submitted by    /u/that_guu  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Improve FaceTime Audio With Mic Modes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=805060</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/805060/how-to-improve-facetime-audio-with-mic-modes/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T19:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[iOS 15 and iPadOS 15 introduced a feature called “Microphone Mode” that can be used during FaceTime calls. You can choose from different modes to make yourself sound better to whoever you’re talking to. We’ll show you how easy it is to use.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel oneAPI Toolkits 2022.2 Released With ISPCRT, More Arc Graphics Preparations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-oneAPI-2022.2</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-oneAPI-2022.2"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intel today published their latest update (v2022.2) to the oneAPI Toolkits, their collection of open-source software components for empowering modern workloads across the growing world of CPUs/GPUs/XPUs...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Help, key mapping is making me cry ): Trying to map Right Alt to Enter/Return]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/usjpm5/help_key_mapping_is_making_me_cry_trying_to_map/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/usjpm5/help_key_mapping_is_making_me_cry_trying_to_map/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T18:41:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone,
 I've been trying to make some custom mapping on my keyboard with `xmodmap` and `setxkbmap` but it's just too much of a black box for me ): I read the arch wiki regarding Xorg keyboard configuration and other sources but most of the times they just give some commands but doesn't explain how things work. So far I'm just unable to debug anything at all.
 Regarding the mapping, I tried to `xmodmap -e keycode 108 = Return` and it works, but the behavior is slightly different, mainly the real Return key keeps sending the press while being hold, and the mapped Right Alt key just send it once, until release.
 Does someone have resources where I can read about how these things are handled ? Or do you have experience with it ? I'm totally lost right now.
    submitted by    /u/BabyAintBuffaloYoung  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla Says How Firefox Extensions Will Keep Up With Chrome]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=806063</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/806063/mozilla-says-how-firefox-extensions-will-keep-up-with-chrome/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T18:40:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Chrome 88 introduced the Manifest V3 API for extensions, which changes how extensions work in the browser. Mozilla has now outlined its plans for integrating those changes into Firefox.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US recovers $15 million from global Kovter ad fraud operation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-recovers-15-million-from-global-kovter-ad-fraud-operation/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-recovers-15-million-from-global-kovter-ad-fraud-operation/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T18:37:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US government has recovered over $15 million from Swiss bank accounts belonging to operators behind the '3ve' online advertising fraud scheme. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ProtonVPN & ProtonMail Get New Features (and Higher Prices)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=805971</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/805971/protonvpn-protonmail-get-new-features-and-higher-prices/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T18:35:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ProtonVPN and ProtonMail are two of the most popular privacy tools online, and the company behind them has been working to unify the two products. The pricing is also changing slightly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Acer Bets That Gamers Will Sacrifice FPS for Glasses-Free 3D]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118367/acer-bets-that-gamers-will-sacrifice-fps-for-glasses-free-3d/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118367/acer-bets-that-gamers-will-sacrifice-fps-for-glasses-free-3d/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T18:16:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The trend that nobody asked for is back. At least, that’s what Acer is betting on with its newest gaming laptops and monitors. Using advanced “SpatialLabs” technology, these new devices automatically convert 2D content into glasses-free 3D. But the immersion offered by this feature comes at a price.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel Linux Driver Wiring Up New "vRAM Self Refresh" Feature For Arc Graphics Cards]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-Linux-vRAM-SR</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-Linux-vRAM-SR"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T18:03:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the upcoming Linux 5.19 cycle appearing to be the point at which Intel's DG2/Alchemist Linux graphics driver support is settling down and may end up being the base version requirement for their forthcoming discrete graphics cards, we are seeing other non-core feature work happen for these Arc Graphics products. A new feature we've only seen mentioned today for the first time by Intel is "vRAM SR", short for vRAM Self-Refresh...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Condiment Could Be the Secret to Perfectly Grilled Meat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lifesavvy.com/129615/this-condiment-could-be-the-secret-to-perfectly-grilled-meat/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lifesavvy.com/129615/this-condiment-could-be-the-secret-to-perfectly-grilled-meat/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T18:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We can’t all be grill masters, but we can hack our way to delicious meals. One of the easiest ways for grilling novices to make juicy, flavorful meat might already be in your fridge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shea Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Buy Bitcoin With the Strike Mobile App]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=805424</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/805424/how-to-buy-bitcoin-with-the-strike-mobile-app/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T18:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the simplest ways to buy Bitcoin is by using the Strike mobile app. Thanks to its use of the Lightning Network, Bitcoin purchases on Strike have a much lower transaction cost. Here’s how to use it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>RJ Fulton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD Launches Xilinx + Linux Powered Robotics Starter Kit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMD-Kria-KR260-Robotics</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=AMD-Kria-KR260-Robotics"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T18:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AMD on Tuesday released the Kria KR260 Robotics Starter Kit featuring a Xilinx Kria K26 System-on-Module and tailoring it for robotics, machine vision, and industrial communication/control use-cases while running Ubuntu 22.04 LTS...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DHS orders federal agencies to patch VMware bugs within 5 days]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/dhs-orders-federal-agencies-to-patch-vmware-bugs-within-5-days/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/dhs-orders-federal-agencies-to-patch-vmware-bugs-within-5-days/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T17:38:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Department of Homeland Security's cybersecurity unit ordered Federal Civilian Executive Branch (FCEB) agencies today to urgently update or remove VMware products from their networks by Monday due to an increased risk of attacks. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VirtualBox On Linux Affected By Security Vulnerability Leaking Host Data To Guests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=VirtualBox-Leaky-Host-To-Guest</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=VirtualBox-Leaky-Host-To-Guest"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T17:36:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security researcher Jason Donenfeld who is known for leading the development of the WireGuard open-source software has outlined a new security vulnerability affecting the Oracle VM VirtualBox software...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[how to get the libpng15 dependecny to work?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/usi2tf/how_to_get_the_libpng15_dependecny_to_work/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/usi2tf/how_to_get_the_libpng15_dependecny_to_work/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T17:26:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[when i cloned the repo for the libpng15 and trying to build it i get this 
 one or more pgps cannot be verified. 
 so i read on the packages site that the key was expired and get it to work use this command gpg --keyserver pool.sks-keyservers.net --recv-keys 8048643BA2C840F4F92A195FF54984BFA16C640F 
 i tried this command but i get this gpg: keyserver receive failed: Server indicated a failure.well what should i do now? where to grab the libpng dependency to install autodesk maya?(i cloned maya from the aur and im missing libpng15 ncurses5-compat-libs adsklicensing=12.0.0.6537 libffi6 dependcies to build it)
    submitted by    /u/angryteapod  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thunderbird 102: support for multiple active spell checking dictionaries]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178653</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/05/18/thunderbird-102-support-for-multiple-active-spell-checking-dictionaries/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T17:15:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The open source email client Thunderbird will soon support multiple active spell checking dictionaries. Planned for Thunderbird 102, the feature enables users to have Thunderbird check for spelling mistakes using multiple dictionaries […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Thunderbird 102: support for multiple active spell checking dictionaries appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are Podcasts Hogging All Your iPhone Free Space?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=805942</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/805942/iphone-podcasts-free-space/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T17:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wondering where all your iPhone (or iPad) free space has gone? If you use Apple’s Podcasts app and have active subscriptions, it’s possible that your device has been downloading and holding onto episodes. Here’s how to check, and how to make sure it doesn’t happen in the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTG Deals: Save on Roborock Vacuums, Chromecasts, SD Cards, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=806008</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/806008/htg-deals-save-on-roborock-vacuums-chromecasts-sd-cards-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T17:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome back to another edition of How-To Geek Deals, the weekly series where we serve up the best discounts on the coolest gadgets known to humankind. This week, we’re shining a spotlight on Roborock’s newest pair of robot vacuums, plus the Chromecast with Google TV, one of our favorite Samsung SD cards of the year, and so much more. Let’s dive in!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zach Laidlaw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese ‘Space Pirates’ are hacking Russian aerospace firms]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/chinese-space-pirates-are-hacking-russian-aerospace-firms/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/chinese-space-pirates-are-hacking-russian-aerospace-firms/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T16:51:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A previously unknown Chinese hacking group known as 'Space Pirates' targets enterprises in the Russian aerospace industry with phishing emails to install novel malware on their systems. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Next-Gen Mercedes-Benz Battery Tech Could Take EVs Further]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118317/next-gen-mercedes-benz-battery-tech-could-take-evs-further/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118317/next-gen-mercedes-benz-battery-tech-could-take-evs-further/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T16:51:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week Mercedes-Benz announced that its partnership with Sila Nanotechnologies, a battery materials company, is about to pay off. That’s because Sila’s next-generation lithium-silicon battery technology is ready for primetime.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migliori App per fare foto con iPhone (alternative alla fotocamera)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2017/07/app-migliori-per-fotografare-con-iphone.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2017/07/app-migliori-per-fotografare-con-iphone.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T16:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anche se l'iPhone ha già un'ottima applicazione per fare foto, non è detto che non si possano realizzare scatti migliori scaricando altre app per fotografare con iPhone.

 Utilizzando altre app possiamo ottenere nuovi effetti, nuove funzioni da fotocamera professionale (come le linee dei terzi o il controllo dell'esposizione), aggiungere effetti e filtri live e molto altro ancora.

 In questa...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Weird "RUM" Microsite Appeared on Roku and No One Knows Why]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118309/a-weird-rum-microsite-appeared-on-roku-and-no-one-knows-why/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118309/a-weird-rum-microsite-appeared-on-roku-and-no-one-knows-why/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T16:33:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several Roku customers have opened support posts and Reddit threads asking why an app called “RUM” appeared on their home screen. This app is unremovable and doesn’t seem to do anything. Even weirder, Roku won’t explain what it is.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VMware patches critical auth bypass flaw in multiple products]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/vmware-patches-critical-auth-bypass-flaw-in-multiple-products/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/vmware-patches-critical-auth-bypass-flaw-in-multiple-products/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T16:01:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VMware warned customers today to immediately patch a critical authentication bypass vulnerability "affecting local domain users" in multiple products that can be exploited to obtain admin privileges. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Switch Sports Is an Upgraded Wii Sports for Nintendo Switch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=805687</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/805687/switch-sports-is-an-upgraded-wii-sports-for-nintendo-switch/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T16:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It feels like an age since the original Wii Sports launched alongside Nintendo’s 2006 console release, but the franchise finally has a spiritual successor on the Switch. The good news is that Switch Sports ticks all the boxes for those who still hold a candle for the original.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Skiff Mail is a new end-to-end encrypted email service, but should you use it?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178639</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/05/18/skiff-mail-end-to-end-encrypted-email-privacy-policy/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T15:55:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Skiff Mail has been launched to the public, it is a new end-to-end encrypted email service provider. The company says that it focuses on protecting the privacy of its users. The service […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Skiff Mail is a new end-to-end encrypted email service, but should you use it? appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Mac App Is Great for People With Short Attention Spans]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=798968</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/798968/working-from-home-boost-your-productivity-with-setapp-for-mac/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T15:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Working from home has become wildly popular over the past few years, but it has also introduced us to challenges we hadn’t considered. Pets, projects around the house, random distractions on the internet — all serve to deter focus and hamper productivity. Can a suite of work-focused apps help you get back on track? We’ll discuss how to stay productive while working from home with Setapp, a popular subscription service with more than 200 incredible apps for Mac.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sponsored</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Novità Acer: Chromebook, notebook OLED, convertibili, PC, monitor e tanti device che guardano alla sostenibilità]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Novita-Acer-Chromebook-notebook-OLED-convertibili-PC-monitor-e-tanti-device-che-guardano-alla-sostenibilita_24532</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Novita-Acer-Chromebook-notebook-OLED-convertibili-PC-monitor-e-tanti-device-che-guardano-alla-sostenibilita_24532"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In occasione dell'evento globale Next@Acer 2022 svoltosi oggi, Acer ha presentato un importante rinnovamento del suo catalogo di prodotti. Il 'piatto forte' sono i nuovi Chromebook Spin e il laptop Swift 3 OLED basato sui processori Intel Core serie H di dodicesima generazione (Alder Lake). L'azienda ha però svelato molti altri dispositivi: vediamoli in breve.Acer Chromebook Spin 714 è dotato di processori Intel Core di dodicesima generazione orientati alle prestazioni, presenta un design durevole e una penna USI integrata a ricarica rapida per trarre il massimo beneficio dai display da 14 pollici WQXGA (2560x1600) o WUXGA (1920x1200) con rapporto d’aspetto 16:10.Ottimizzato per il videoconferencing, Acer Chromebook Spin 714 è dotato di una webcam MIPI Full HD con tecnologia di riduzione del rumore e di doppio microfono, mentre i due altoparlanti rivolti verso l'alto con DTS Audio e amplificatore intelligente assicurano un'esperienza d'ascolto di alta qualità senza distorsioni.

Chromebook Acer Spin 714 offre connettività avanzata (compreso il supporto WiFi 6E e Bluetooth 5.2), una tastiera retroilluminata e numerose porte tra cui una HDMI e due Thunderbolt 4.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Finally Updates Its Fire 7 Tablet Adding a Much-Needed Feature]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118311/amazon-finally-updates-its-fire-7-tablet/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118311/amazon-finally-updates-its-fire-7-tablet/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T15:43:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon has finally updated its popular Fire 7 and Fire 7 Kids tablets, and wow, what a fantastic upgrade it is! Both tablets got a full suite of new hardware upgrades, improved battery life, smoother performance, and, best of all—they both have USB-C ports now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzanne Humphries</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Defrag Your Windows Hard Drive]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=post-ideas&amp;p=474426</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15309434/defrag-windows-hard-drive"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Due to the difference in technology, HDDs are inherently slower than their SSD counterparts, and their performance decreases over time as you store more and more data on them. This can be attributed to data fragmentation during the writing process. However, there is a simple fix for it called defragmentation. In this article, we will go over a few simple methods to help you defrag your Windows hard drive and get a significant performance boost.
   

Content

1. Use the Disk Optimization Tool
2. Schedule Optimization
3. Use the Command Line
4. Use a Third-Party Defragging Tool
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Format an Xbox One External Hard Drive for Use with a PC
    
What Is Defragmentation?
    
To understand what defragmentation is, you need to know how a hard... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ojash Yadav</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Garmin's Latest Cycling Accessory Combines Three Products Into One]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118301/garmins-latest-cycling-accessory-combines-three-products-into-one/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118301/garmins-latest-cycling-accessory-combines-three-products-into-one/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T15:24:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, Garmin announced a new 3-in-1 Varia radar system to help keep cyclists and bikers safe on the road. The Garmin Varia RCT715 is a radar-activated tail light with a built-in camera that’ll watch your back.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[steam suddenly more resource intensive?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/usff88/steam_suddenly_more_resource_intensive/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/usff88/steam_suddenly_more_resource_intensive/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T15:24:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I noticed one day that steam started to freeze up midgame when playing where 100% memory would be taken up. Even out of a game, just having the launcher open to login tacks on a fairly noticeable memory usage that I'm pretty sure it didn't do before.
 This only started happening-that I noticed-within the last few days.
 What could be going on here?
    submitted by    /u/reenmini  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA shares guidance to block ongoing F5 BIG-IP attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisa-shares-guidance-to-block-ongoing-f5-big-ip-attacks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisa-shares-guidance-to-block-ongoing-f5-big-ip-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T15:20:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a joint advisory issued today, CISA and the Multi-State Information Sharing and Analysis Center (MS-ISAC) warned admins of active attacks targeting a critical F5 BIG-IP network security vulnerability (CVE-2022-1388). [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung SmartThings Is the First Testing Ground for Matter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118294/samsung-smartthings-is-the-first-testing-ground-for-matter/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118294/samsung-smartthings-is-the-first-testing-ground-for-matter/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T15:15:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After an endless barrage of delays, Matter is finally coming together. The new standard promises to unify smart home products, allowing devices to work together regardless of their branding or smart assistant compatibility. And now, smart home companies can test Matter using Samsung’s SmartThings platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can I add non recursive mappings in zathura?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/usf266/can_i_add_non_recursive_mappings_in_zathura/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/usf266/can_i_add_non_recursive_mappings_in_zathura/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T15:07:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I remapped G to go the end of the last page instead of the beginning. However, this breaks [page number]G and I can no longer go to a particular page number I want. Is there a way to add non recursive mappings like noremap in vim?
    submitted by    /u/haca42  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Sort by Color in Microsoft Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=803167</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/803167/excel-sort-by-color/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T15:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using Microsoft Excel’s sorting feature, you can sort your cells that are either manually colored or conditionally colored by their color. This works for multiple colors and we’ll show you how to implement it in your spreadsheets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fake crypto sites lure wannabe thieves by spamming login credentials]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fake-crypto-sites-lure-wannabe-thieves-by-spamming-login-credentials/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fake-crypto-sites-lure-wannabe-thieves-by-spamming-login-credentials/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T14:54:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors are luring potential thieves by spamming login credentials for other people account's on fake crypto trading sites, illustrating once again, that there is no honor among thieves. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come creare un server FTP gratis]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/05/come-creare-un-server-ftp-gratis.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/05/come-creare-un-server-ftp-gratis.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T14:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chi lavora in azienda sa quanto è importante accedere ai file aziendali in ogni momento della giornata, così da poter verificarne il contenuto ed effettuare le modifiche necessarie anche senza accedere fisicamente al PC aziendale. Per l'accesso remoto dei file viene utilizzato il protocollo FTP, nato agli albori delle reti interconnesse ma ancora oggi molto utilizzato per la sua semplicità di...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bluetooth headset fails to connect]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/use5l9/bluetooth_headset_fails_to_connect/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/use5l9/bluetooth_headset_fails_to_connect/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T14:25:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trying to connect some wireless headphones to my laptop. They worked a couple days ago then stopped and I cant figure out why. Before that it would work for a few days then stop until I rebooted or just tried again after a few hours. Now it hasn't worked for almost 2 weeks.
 ``` $ neofetch Host: 20BU000AUS ThinkPad T450 Kernel: 5.17.7-zen1-2-zen 
 Installed
 bluez 5.64-2 bluez-firmware 1.2-9 bluez-hid2hci 5.64-2 bluez-libs 5.64-2 bluez-utils 5.64-2 hidapi 0.11.2-1 libldac 2.0.2.3-1 pulseaudio-bluetooth 15.0-4 sbc 1.5-2
 $ bluetoothctl show Powered: yes Discoverable: no Pairable: yes
 $ bluetoothctl info 8D:40:4C:C6:73:A4 Device 8D:40:4C:C6:73:A4 (public) Paired: yes Trusted: yes Blocked: no Connected: no LegacyPairing: no
 $ bluetoothctl connect 8D:40:4C:C6:73:A4 Attempting to connect to 8D:40:4C:C6:73:A4 Failed to connect: org.bluez.Error.Failed br-connection-profile-unavailable
 $ journalctl -u bluetooth bluetoothd[13782]: src/service.c:btd_service_connect() a2dp-sink profile connect failed for 8D:40:4C:C6:73:A4: Protocol not available
 $ systemctl list-unit-files | grep blue UNIT FILE STATE VENDOR PRESET bluetooth-mesh.service enabled disabled bluetooth.service enabled disabled dbus-org.bluez.mesh.service alias - dbus-org.bluez.service alias - bluetooth.target static -
 $ lsmod | grep bluetooth bluetooth 925696 31 btrtl,btmtk,btintel,btbcm,bnep,btusb crc16 16384 1 bluetooth rfkill 36864 6 iwlmvm,bluetooth,thinkpad_acpi,cfg80211 ecdh_generic 16384 2 bluetooth
 ```
    submitted by    /u/dominic_l  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Took My Money and Canceled My Nest Service]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118240/google-took-my-money-and-canceled-my-nest-service/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118240/google-took-my-money-and-canceled-my-nest-service/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T14:24:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve recommended the Nest Video Doorbell for years as the best premium option for smart doorbells. But that recommendation does require subscribing to Nest Aware to get the best features, and now I’m left considering abandoning Nest altogether after Google took my money and canceled my service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Hendrickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Epson compie 80 anni: la storia dell'azienda in breve]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Epson-compie-80-anni-la-storia-dell-azienda-in-breve_24531</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Epson-compie-80-anni-la-storia-dell-azienda-in-breve_24531"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T14:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Epson è una multinazionale giapponese tra i maggiori e più importanti produttori mondiali di stampanti e apparecchiature relative alla gestione dei dati e all'imaging.Ben 80 anni fa, nel mese di maggio 1942, fu fondata Daiwa Kogyo, l'azienda da cui è nata Epson. Anzi Seiko Epson, come si chiama oggi: nei primi anni di vita, infatti, gli elementi che hanno alimentato la crescita dell'azienda erano incentrati sul perfezionamento delle tecnologie di microlavorazione e di elaborazione ad alta precisione sviluppate per gli orologi e il loro impiego in altri campi applicativi.Daiwa Kogyo fu creata proprio da un negoziante di orologi locale, Hisao Yamazaki, e ricevette il supporto della famiglia di imprenditori che fondò il Gruppo Seiko.

L'Epson Museum Suwa, situato nella sede di Suwa (prefettura di Nagano, Giappone), è stato inaugurato oggi proprio con l'intento di descrivere l'intera storia della società, dalla fondazione ai giorni nostri.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch Linux stop working and sometimes restart automatically.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/usduu3/arch_linux_stop_working_and_sometimes_restart/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/usduu3/arch_linux_stop_working_and_sometimes_restart/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T14:11:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been using Arch Linux for like 6 months. I installed it with kde-plasma and recently moved into i3 window manager. Ever since I started using i3 my system halts unexpectedly. I mean I work like 2-3 hours and suddenly the computer halts and I have to restart it. And sometimes even weirder, it restart automatically. I have three questions?
  
Why does this happens?
 How to fix it?
 Am I hacked?
  
   submitted by    /u/NoMango101  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft’s New Outlook for Windows Is Missing Many Features]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=805914</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/805914/microsofts-new-outlook-for-windows-is-missing-many-features/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T14:04:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has been working on a new desktop Outlook application for a while now, and the company started testing it with work and education accounts earlier this month. Now it’s rolling out more widely for Office Insiders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Ergonomic Mice of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=796113</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/796113/best-ergonomic-mouse/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T14:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ergonomics mice come in a variety of shapes, sizes, and price tags. Whether you’re looking for a vertical layout, trackball design, or lightweight product, here are six of the best ergonomic mice currently on the market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Bitner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch Linux Installer Preparing FIDO2 Support For Handling Disk Encryption]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Arch-Linux-Archinstall-FIDO2</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Arch-Linux-Archinstall-FIDO2"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Arch Linux installer "Archinstall" that makes it simple to quickly and easily get this popular distribution installed has prepared a new release candidate where they are introducing FIDO2 support...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft warns of brute-force attacks targeting MSSQL servers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-warns-of-brute-force-attacks-targeting-mssql-servers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-warns-of-brute-force-attacks-targeting-mssql-servers/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T13:27:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft warned of brute-forcing attacks targeting Internet-exposed and poorly secured Microsoft SQL Server (MSSQL) database servers using weak passwords. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Huawei presenta Watch GT3 Pro, Watch Fit 2, Band 7 e Mate Xs 2: grande enfasi su salute e benessere]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Huawei-presenta-Watch-GT3-Pro-Watch-Fit-2-Band-7-e-Mate-Xs-2-grande-enfasi-su-salute-e-benessere_24530</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Huawei-presenta-Watch-GT3-Pro-Watch-Fit-2-Band-7-e-Mate-Xs-2-grande-enfasi-su-salute-e-benessere_24530"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T13:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Milano ha fatto quest'oggi da cornice al lancio dei nuovi prodotti Huawei dedicati alla salute, alla nutrizione e al fitness.Huawei Watch GT3 Pro, Watch Fit 2, Band 7 e Mate Xs 2 mirano a semplificare ulteriormente la vita quotidiana dei consumatori. Si tratta infatti di una nuova generazione di prodotti a supporto dell'health management che integrano il tracciamento e il monitoraggio dell'attività fisica, il tracciamento e l'analisi dettagliata dell'alimentazione, le soluzioni per il benessere mentale.Con l'evento HOUSE OF HUAWEI, la società ha voluto sottolineare il suo impegno nella progettazione, sviluppo e realizzazione di dispositivi e strumenti che aiutano e semplificano la vita quotidiana degli utenti in molteplici occasioni.Si parla di 'fashion-tech' ossia dell'uso sempre più trendy della tecnologia e dei materiali industriali nella moda insieme all'immancabile supporto dell'e-commerce e dei dispositivi tecnologici.'Ogni giorno gli utenti sono circondati da numerosi device con le più disparate funzioni, ma è il modo in cui prodotti di diverse categorie comunicano tra loro a fare la differenza', ha dichiarato Pier Giorgio Furcas, Deputy General Manager Huawei Consumer Business Group Italia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to List Users in Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=803907</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/803907/linux-list-users/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T13:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linux is a multiuser operating system, so creating numerous user accounts is easy. Over time, it’s easy to lose track of which accounts are required. Listing user accounts helps you manage them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKay</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ZOWIE Mouse Fitting Kit Review: Every PC Gamer Needs This]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117003/zowie-mouse-fitting-kit-review-every-pc-gamer-needs-this/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117003/zowie-mouse-fitting-kit-review-every-pc-gamer-needs-this/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T13:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are a ton of gaming mice out there, and it can be tough to find The One without buying all of them and trying them out one by one. However, with the ZOWIE Mouse Fitting Kit, you can do just that. With it, you’ll be sent 10 gaming mice to try in the comfort of your home for two weeks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzanne Humphries</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kdump and Crash utility confusion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/usc45r/kdump_and_crash_utility_confusion/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/usc45r/kdump_and_crash_utility_confusion/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T12:48:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So, the wiki states that when compiling the crash kernel for kdump one should change the package base name to "linux-kdump" or similar to distinguish it from the normal kernel. A consequence of this is that my vmlinux file has, according to crash, version "5.17.8-arch1-1-kdump".
 The problem is that my system kernel is of version "5.17.8-arch1-1" and so when running "crash vmlinux crash.dump" it tells me that there is an inconsistency between kernel versions of the vmlinux file and the crash dump:
 'WARNING: kernel version inconsistency between vmlinux and dumpfile
 WARNING: cannot find matching kernel version in vmlinux file:
 verify_namelist:
 dumpfile /proc/version:
 Linux version 5.17.8-arch1-1 (linux@archlinux) (gcc (GCC) 12.1.0, GNU ld (GNU Binutils) 2.38) #1 SMP PREEMPT Mon, 16 May 2022 20:45:27 +0000
 vmlinux:
 Linux version 5.17.8-arch1-1-kdump (linux-kdump@archlinux) (gcc (GCC) 12.1.0, GNU ld (GNU Binutils) 2.38) #2 SMP PREEMPT Wed, 18 May 2022 00:42:02 +0000'
 Am I misunderstanding the instructions about naming the kernel, or am I misunderstanding how to use crash? Never used the utility before so any help would be appreciated. One thing that I tried was using my system's vmlinux file, but Arch does not ship them with debug info, so it cannot be used with crash.
    submitted by    /u/ContentMammoth  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Se il segnale Wi-Fi è debole, da cosa dipende]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2016/12/se-il-segnale-wifi-e-debole-da-cosa.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2016/12/se-il-segnale-wifi-e-debole-da-cosa.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T12:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Non riuscire ad ottenere una buona connessione wireless in varie zone di casa può dipendere da vari fattori, ma nella maggior parte dei casi il segnale Wi-Fi debole è provocato da impedimenti fisici o da interferenze. Questo segnale debole genera anche una velocità di internet non adeguata o la perdita costante del collegamento, rendendo impossibile navigare su Internet o ottenendo errori durante...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What to Know About the Skittles, Starburst, and Life Savers Recall]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lifesavvy.com/129561/what-to-know-about-the-skittles-starbursts-and-life-saver-recall/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lifesavvy.com/129561/what-to-know-about-the-skittles-starbursts-and-life-saver-recall/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T12:30:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you or your little ones have a real sweet tooth, you might want to check your pantry. Three popular candies are currently under voluntary recall.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shea Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alternative to Gnome Boxes for KVM virtual machines]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/usbqq3/alternative_to_gnome_boxes_for_kvm_virtual/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/usbqq3/alternative_to_gnome_boxes_for_kvm_virtual/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T12:28:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I ran into this year old bug on Gnome Boxes while trying to clone a Windows VM and now Boxes crashes on start every time. 
 https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/gnome-boxes/-/issues/678
 Frankly, I'm not all that impressed with Boxes in the first place, but I like having a gui manager for VMs for the time being. I actually like the interface for Virtualbox but it does not use KVM and the core promise of KVM is achieving near-native performance. 
 Does anyone have a suggestion for a good KVM manager?
    submitted by    /u/Taste_of_Based  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 Mesh Router Placement Mistakes to Avoid]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=802562</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/802562/mesh-router-placement-mistakes-to-avoid/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T12:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Purchasing a mesh router system is only half of the upgrade process. If your mesh node placement is poor, you’ll never realize the full benefits of a mesh system. Here are common mistakes you want to avoid.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Fitzpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux Kernel Patches Posted For USB Support With Realtek RTW88 WiFi Driver]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-Patches-RTW88-WiFi-USB</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-Patches-RTW88-WiFi-USB"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in 2019 Realtek contributed the open-source "RTW88" WiFi driver to the Linux kernel for supporting their newer wireless chipsets on Linux. To date the mainline driver has just supported their PCI-based WiFi adapters while a patch series now out for review extends the driver to supporting their newer USB-specific chipsets...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel Releases SVT-AV1 v1.1 As It Continues Advancing Open-Source AV1 Encoding]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=SVT-AV1-1.1</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=SVT-AV1-1.1"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T11:03:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was just shy of one month ago that Intel and AOMedia released SVT-AV1 v1.0 and now Intel engineers have released SVT-AV1 v1.1 as the newest feature update to this CPU-based, open-source AV1 video encoder...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 Ways to Ruin Your Smartphone’s Battery]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=803942</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/803942/4-ways-to-ruin-your-smartphones-battery/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s a lot of information out there about how to treat smartphone batteries. We can argue about the best practices, but there are some clearly bad things that can ruin batteries quickly. Let’s make sure you’re avoiding them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows: come aprire più volte lo stesso programma]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-come-aprire-piu-volte-lo-stesso-programma_24529</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-come-aprire-piu-volte-lo-stesso-programma_24529"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T10:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Può capitare di avere la necessità di usare più istanze di uno stesso programma Windows, ad esempio per usare contemporaneamente due diversi account utente, per aprire in modalità affiancata più documenti, per effettuare dei test e altro ancora.Indipendentemente dalla necessità, aprire più volte lo stesso programma Windows in alcuni casi è possibile in maniera molto semplice (si pensi al browser Web o ai componenti delle suite per l'ufficio come Microsoft Office e LibreOffice), in altri non è permesso.Per aprire una seconda istanza di un programma in esecuzione basta tenere premuto il tasto MAIUSC quindi cliccare una volta sull'icona mostrata nella barra delle applicazioni di Windows.Si possono anche avviare i programmi rapidamente usando le scorciatoie di Windows: ad esempio utilizzando Windows+MAIUSC+1 si apre una nuova finestra del primo programma mostrato sotto forma di icona nella barra delle applicazioni.Il trucchetto del tasto MAIUSC, purtroppo, non funziona per tutte le applicazioni perché gli sviluppatori non permettono l'utilizzo contemporaneo di più istanze.
Avviare più volte lo stesso programma in Windows, anche per le applicazioni che non lo permettono
 Quando si avvia un qualunque programma in Windows, questo viene aperto utilizzando l'account correntemente in uso: è immediato verificarlo aprendo il Task Manager di Windows (CTRL+MAIUSC+ESC), cliccando eventualmente su Più dettagli quindi sulla scheda Dettagli in alto.I processi che riportano il nome dell'utente corrente sono quelli avviati usando l'account in uso; dove figura SYSTEM generalmente si tratta di processi di sistema.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[G Suite Legacy Free Edition Users Get Some Breathing Room]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=490193</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15308786/g-suite-legacy-free-edition-users-personal"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T10:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[G Suite legacy free edition users have been panicking since January. Google’s announcement made it seem as if those who used the service for personal use would either have to start paying or export all their data. However, a further clarification shows that personal users of the G Suite legacy free edition have a more palatable option.
   
Also read:Google Pay vs Samsung Pay vs Apple Pay: The Best Apps for NFC Mobile Payments and More
    
Google Clarifies the G Suite Plan
    
In October 2020, Google rebranded G Suite as Google Workspace. There wasn’t anyone confused about Google’s motive – obviously, this move would benefit the Alphabet subsidiary in some way. Left in the lurch again were the users who had lost the free services and sent to the G Suite legacy free edition in 2012.
    
In January... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Touchpad not working]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/us9lh0/touchpad_not_working/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/us9lh0/touchpad_not_working/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T10:16:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[after updating my laptop today my touchpad stopped working.
 i tried install xf86-input synaptics but still couldn't get my touchpad to work
    submitted by    /u/Wambug  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lenovo ThinkPad P16: prima workstation mobile con processore Alder Lake HX]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Lenovo-ThinkPad-P16-prima-workstation-mobile-con-processore-Alder-Lake-HX_24528</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Lenovo-ThinkPad-P16-prima-workstation-mobile-con-processore-Alder-Lake-HX_24528"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T09:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nei giorni scorsi abbiamo parlato dei processori Intel Alder Lake HX, i top di gamma di ultima generazione progettati per i notebook di fascia più alta.Il primo sistema a farne uso è Lenovo ThinkPad P16, una workstation mobile che oltre ai nuovi Alder Lake HX utilizza grafica dedicata NVidia e configurazioni davvero generose in termini di memoria RAM e storage.Lenovo ThinkPad P16 nasce per venire incontro alle esigenze dei professionisti che hanno necessità di un PC ultraperformante quando si trovano in viaggio o comunque lontano dall'ufficio. Il sistema utilizza un telaio in alluminio per un peso complessivo di 2,95 kg.

Questo notebook di casa Lenovo è equipaggiato con uno schermo da 16 pollici: il cliente può scegliere tra diverse tipologie di pannelli.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lars Knoll Leaving The Qt Company, Starting New Chapter Outside Qt]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Lars-Knoll-Leaving-Qt</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Lars-Knoll-Leaving-Qt"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T09:47:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After 25 years being heavily involved in the Qt toolkit development, Lars Knoll announced today he is leaving The Qt Company where he currently serves as CTO and also largely departing from active work within the Qt community to "try out something else" moving forward...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Valve's Gamescope Compositor Merges NVIDIA Image Scaling Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Gamescope-Lands-NVIDIA-Scaling</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Gamescope-Lands-NVIDIA-Scaling"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T09:35:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Valve's Vulkan-powered Gamescope Wayland compositor has merged support for NVIDIA Image Scaling...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qualcomm Exploring Bootloader-Based Hibernation For Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=QuIC-Bootloader-Based-Hibernate</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=QuIC-Bootloader-Based-Hibernate"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T09:25:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Qualcomm engineers are exploring bootloader-based hibernation in order to improve the user experience when restoring from a hibernated state...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My computer always beeps five times at 11am and I have no idea why.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/us8veh/my_computer_always_beeps_five_times_at_11am_and_i/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/us8veh/my_computer_always_beeps_five_times_at_11am_and_i/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T09:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey everyone,
 I have this really weird annoyance. Every day, at exactly 11am (or 10am during winter time), my laptop goes "beep beep!" 5 times in a row. Now that I get to do in-person meetings more again, that joke gets old and embarrassing fast. I'm using Gnome.
 Here are some things I checked:
  
Gnome Calendar, Todo and Alarms - nothing should trigger a sound there
 Having a look at Gnome Audio Settings at 11am to see what program causes the beeps, nothing listed there
 Checking all systemd timers
  
Does anybody have an idea what could cause this?
 Thanks so much!
    submitted by    /u/krmax44  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11: Microsoft Designer permette di creare immagini per post sui social e presentazioni]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-11-Microsoft-Designer-permette-di-creare-immagini-per-post-sui-social-e-presentazioni_24527</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Windows-11-Microsoft-Designer-permette-di-creare-immagini-per-post-sui-social-e-presentazioni_24527"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T09:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Uno dei più apprezzati strumenti per la progettazione grafica da usare in alternativa a PhotoShop dovrà confrontarsi con un nuovo software che presto debutterà in Windows 11.Conosciamo Canva, strumento per creare presentazioni, biglietti e poster, utilissimo per produrre contenuti grafici accattivanti da pubblicare sui principali social network.

Bene, a breve Windows 11 si arricchirà con Microsoft Designer, uno strumento che permetterà di accedere a un vasto database di modelli, foto, grafiche e caratteri per creare immagini di qualità da utilizzare online ed eventualmente stampare.Della novità si è accorto WalkingCat, uno dei più noti leaker responsabile della scoperta in anteprima di tante funzionalità in arrivo in Windows e negli altri software Microsoft.

Esaminando le immagini condivise in anteprima su Twitter, Microsoft Designer si presenta come un'applicazione simile a Publisher, tranne per il fatto che sembra più focalizzata sul Web.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to properly set up amd radeon graphics card?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/us5nim/how_to_properly_set_up_amd_radeon_graphics_card/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/us5nim/how_to_properly_set_up_amd_radeon_graphics_card/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T05:27:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey, I have recently bought a new rx 6600 xt because nvidia just sucks on linux. I have already installed mesa, 32lib mesa, xf86 video amdgpu, vulkanradeon and lib32 vulkanradeon. 
 Is there anything that I missed? I noticed worse performance than I had on my 2060 for example in forza horizon 5 ( now it works stable with amd), detroit become human etc. 
 Thanks in advance
    submitted by    /u/efoxpl3244  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[`Good News: non-business legacy Google G Suite customers may keep their accounts after all]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178636</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/05/18/good-news-non-business-legacy-google-g-suite-customers-may-keep-their-accounts-after-all/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T04:53:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google revealed plans to shut down the G Suite legacy free edition in January 2022. The company gave customers only two options at the time: sign-up for a paid plan to continue […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post `Good News: non-business legacy Google G Suite customers may keep their accounts after all appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating additonal bootloader for bios systems.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/us21ir/creating_additonal_bootloader_for_bios_systems/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/us21ir/creating_additonal_bootloader_for_bios_systems/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T01:52:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi. So I have Arch installed on my external SSD in UEFI mode. But there are still some systems around me that do not support uefi boot and therefore I am not getting advantage of portability.
 ​
 I was wondering whether can I install another grub for bios systems? What is the process to do so?
    submitted by    /u/fumaxin  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gnome xrdp issue]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/us1mqb/gnome_xrdp_issue/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/us1mqb/gnome_xrdp_issue/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T01:30:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just got out from trying to fix my arch install for hours after a gnome update, maybe someone else had the same problems.
 Been using Arch in HyperV Enhanced session mode with the same config for years with no problem, but among the last updates of gnome it just broke. The xrdp login shows like always, but after login the HyperV window says the connection dropped.
 Gnome was configured to start in .xinitrc in X11 mode. Xrdp sesman log just says the window manager exited with code 255 and signal 5, and that it exited quickly immediately.
 Tried fresh install in new VM with default xrdp and xorgxrdp. Config changed to use vsock and to not use encryption in rdp. Issue persists. Changed from gnome to xfce4 and everything works without issue
 Decided to stick with xfce4 after that, but thought maybe someone could shed some light on it. Or just to prevent someone else to waste time fixing their install
    submitted by    /u/TodHeartbreaker  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Lands VA-API To Direct3D 12 H.264 Video Encode/Decode In Mesa]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Mesa-22.2-D3D12-Video</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Mesa-22.2-D3D12-Video"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T00:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has made a lot of interesting developments and maneuvers over the past number of months for leveraging open-source Mesa for use by Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSL) and supporting various Khronos APIs atop Direct3D 12 for use when native drivers are lacking on Windows. This work so far has been focused on OpenGL, OpenCL, and Vulkan but Microsoft has now even implemented Direct3D 12 video API support within Mesa and leverages the VA-API state tracker support within Mesa...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Pay vs Samsung Pay vs Apple Pay: The Best Apps for NFC Mobile Payments and More]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=459453</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15307507/best-nfc-digital-wallet"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tired of carrying around a bulky wallet filled with credit, debit, and loyalty cards? Then switch to mobile payments and a digital wallet. While you have a growing number of options here, Google Pay, Samsung Pay, and Apple Pay are three of the top choices available. They’re similar services, but each offers very distinct features. All three let you pay for purchases online and in-store (where available).
    
To figure out which is best for your needs, see how each option fares in terms of features, ease of use, and availability.
    
By itself, Apple Pay is a contactless mobile payment solution. When combined with Apple Wallet and Apple Cash, it matches the digital wallet feature set provided by Google Pay and Samsung Pay. However, we refer to Apple Pay as a digital wallet here to avoid confusion.
   

Content

Availability
Security
Reach and Flexibility
Types of Cards and Banks
Perks
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Crystal Crowder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[tap to click on wayland sway]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/us05m1/tap_to_click_on_wayland_sway/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/us05m1/tap_to_click_on_wayland_sway/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-18T00:10:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Does anyone know how i can configure my track pad to enable tap to click I tried installing libinut but all I can do is device list and see the configuration of them I am new to Linux in general and I read all I could online
    submitted by    /u/Akira-Arch  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Ubuntu Preview" Makes It Easy To Try The Bleeding-Edge Ubuntu Experience On WSL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Ubuntu-Preview-WSL</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Ubuntu-Preview-WSL"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T22:36:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Canonical continues investing a lot in ensuring a first-rate Ubuntu experience when using Microsoft's Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSL/WSL2) with Windows 10 and newer. Rather than needing to wait longer to see the fruits of that work in the next Ubuntu releases, Canonical has now made "Ubuntu Preview" available from the Microsoft Store to have a daily-updated, bleeding-edge Ubuntu experience...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean devs pose as US freelancers to aid DRPK govt hackers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/north-korean-devs-pose-as-us-freelancers-to-aid-drpk-govt-hackers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/north-korean-devs-pose-as-us-freelancers-to-aid-drpk-govt-hackers/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T22:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. government is warning that the Democratic People's Republic of Korea (DPRK) is dispatching its IT workers to get freelance jobs at companies across the world to obtain privileged access that is sometimes used to facilitate cyber intrusions. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Ilascu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean devs pose as US freelancers and aid DRPK govt hackers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/north-korean-devs-pose-as-us-freelancers-and-aid-drpk-govt-hackers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/north-korean-devs-pose-as-us-freelancers-and-aid-drpk-govt-hackers/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T22:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. government is warning that the Democratic People's Republic of Korea (DPRK) is dispatching its IT workers to get freelance jobs at companies across the world to obtain privileged access that is sometimes used to facilitate cyber intrusions. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Ilascu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come ripristinare il pulsante + (Nuova Scheda) in Firefox]]></title>
        <id>3573|20220518000000</id>
        <link href="https://turbolab.it/browser-455/come-ripristinare-pulsante-nuova-scheda-firefox-3573"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leggendo una richiesta su un forum di Firefox, sulla scomparsa del pulsante + che permette l’apertura di una nuova scheda del browser, mi sono messo a cercare una risposta e il problema sembra essere piuttosto diffuso. In alcuni casi era dovuto all’applicazione di un tema, o di una personalizzazione, di colore particolare che nascondeva il pulsante, nonostante fosse sempre presente nello stesso punto. Quindi se avete appena fatto una modifica del genere non vi resta che annullarla e vedere se il pulsante ricompare. Dopo qualche ricerca sono riuscito a riprodurre il problema togliendo, e poi rimettendo, il pulsante +
›› Leggi tutto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@turbolab.it (TurboLab.it)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Websites to Find Images with a Transparent Background]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=371514</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15307227/best-websites-find-images-with-transparent-background"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you spend a lot of time in Photoshop, you probably often have the need for images with a transparent background. Unfortunately, tracking them down can be frustrating. One would think that using Google Image Search to find images with a transparent background would be easy. Unfortunately, this is far from the truth. Thankfully, there are a number of websites that host images with a transparent background, making sourcing images for your next project a breeze.
   

Content

What is a transparent image and why would I want one?
1. IMGBIN
2. CleanPNG
3. StickPNG
4. PNGTree
5. FavPNG
6. FreePNGs
7. removebg
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Make an Image Transparent without Photoshop
    
What is a transparent image and why would I want one?
    
Transparent images are pictures that are partially transparent or see-through. Most often, transparent images refer... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Lynch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Stop Your Mac’s Mail App From Wasting Gigabytes of Space]]></title>
        <id>http://www.howtogeek.com/?p=209517</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/209517/how-to-stop-your-macs-mail-app-from-wasting-gigabytes-of-space/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using Apple’s Mail app on a Mac? You may be losing gigabytes of space from attachments that you could be putting to better use. Here’s what you can do about it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft: Windows Server 20H2 reaches end of service in August]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-windows-server-20h2-reaches-end-of-service-in-august/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-windows-server-20h2-reaches-end-of-service-in-august/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T20:22:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has reminded customers today that Windows Server, version 20H2 will be reaching the end of service (EOS) on August 9, 2022. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[YouTube Music on Wear OS is Less Terrible Now]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=805887</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/805887/youtube-music-on-wear-os-is-less-terrible-now/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T20:20:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[YouTube Music was one of the first major apps introduced alongside Google Wear OS 3 (coming soon to some of the best smartwatches), but it had one major problem: it couldn’t stream music. Now that has finally been fixed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s How Disney+’s Cheaper Ad-Supported Tier Will Work]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=805851</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/805851/heres-how-disneys-cheaper-ad-supported-tier-will-work/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T20:14:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Disney revealed a few months ago that it was working on a cheaper Disney+ plan that would be supported with advertisements, expanding options for one of the best streaming services. Now we have more details about how it will work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fix “Wi-Fi Doesn’t Have a Valid IP Configuration” on Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=804796</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/804796/how-to-fix-wi-fi-doesnt-have-a-valid-ip-configuration/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T20:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wi-Fi is a wonderful thing when it works correctly. You can probably carry a device around and still get high-speed access to the internet. But when it misbehaves, fixing Wi-Fi configuration errors on Windows can be a pain. Here are some things you should try.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Lewis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How can I find and uninstall unused packages?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/urujh6/how_can_i_find_and_uninstall_unused_packages/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/urujh6/how_can_i_find_and_uninstall_unused_packages/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T19:42:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey, so uhhh, I have over 2,2K packages installed and I definitely don't use them all, can I somehow find them and remove them? thanks!
    submitted by    /u/DominiCzech  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get an Amazon Fire TV Stick Lite for Under $20]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=377200</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/14142017/amazon-fire-tv-stick-lite"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re interested in dipping your toe into the streamed media space – or even more specifically, Fire TV – this is a great product to do it with. For less than $20, you can get the Amazon Fire TV Stick Lite. This little streaming device will stream your favorite TV shows and movies using Alexa voice support.
    
Despite being a budget Fire TV Stick, you can still stream in Full HD. Just use your voice with the Alexa Voice Remote Lite to search for your favorite movies, TV shows, videos, music, and more.
    

    
Included in t. he tens of thousands of available channels, Alexa skills, and apps are Netflix, Hulu, YouTube, Prime Video, Disney+, Apple TV+, and HBO Max. You’ll never run out of things to watch with more than 500,000 movies and TV episodes.
    
The Fire TV Stick Lite even airs live TV so that you can watch news and sports with subscriptions to Sling TV, YouTube, TV, and more. You don’t have to subscribe to... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This HyperX Headset Lasts 300 Hours on a Charge, but How?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118249/this-hyperx-headset-lasts-300-hours-on-a-charge-but-how/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118249/this-hyperx-headset-lasts-300-hours-on-a-charge-but-how/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T19:22:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We could hardly believe our ears when HyperX announced the Cloud Alpha Wireless headset. Not only does it come at the low price of just $200, but it lasts 300 hours on a charge—something we verified in our detailed review. Still, HyperX hasn’t explained this battery wizardry. But iFixit may have an answer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NVIDIA fixes ten vulnerabilities in Windows GPU display drivers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/nvidia-fixes-ten-vulnerabilities-in-windows-gpu-display-drivers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/nvidia-fixes-ten-vulnerabilities-in-windows-gpu-display-drivers/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T19:12:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NVIDIA has released a security update for a wide range of graphics card models, addressing four high-severity and six medium-severity vulnerabilities in its GPU drivers. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fix “Last Line No Longer Available” on iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=804155</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/804155/last-line-no-longer-available/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T19:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[iPhone users with an eSIM may see an error that notifies complaining “last line no longer available” when trying to place a call. So what does this mean, and what can you do about it?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Defender for Endpoint gets new troubleshooting mode]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-defender-for-endpoint-gets-new-troubleshooting-mode/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-defender-for-endpoint-gets-new-troubleshooting-mode/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T18:47:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft says Defender for Endpoint now comes with a new 'troubleshooting mode' that will help Windows admins test Defender Antivirus performance and run compatibility scenarios without getting blocked by tamper protection. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do EVs Need Special Tires?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118218/do-evs-need-special-tires/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118218/do-evs-need-special-tires/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T18:44:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Buying an electric vehicle is different from buying a regular gas car. You don’t have to worry about maintenance or stopping for gas, but you will have to keep an eye on the battery. And like any vehicle, you’ll eventually need new tires for your EV.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Problem with kernel directories]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/urt6vu/problem_with_kernel_directories/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/urt6vu/problem_with_kernel_directories/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T18:40:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi all,
 I want to load the vboxdrv kernel, when I run "modprobe vboxdrv" the result is : "modprobe: FATAL: Module vboxdrv not found in directory /lib/modules/5.17.4-arch1-1". I found the kernel in "/usr/lib/modules/5.17.7-arch1-2/extramodules/vbox.ko.xz" . How can I solve this ?
    submitted by    /u/Zealos707  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dolphin file previews stopped & /var/tmp/pamac-build-yamo/electron9 is taking alone 8.9 Gb]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/urszr6/dolphin_file_previews_stopped/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/urszr6/dolphin_file_previews_stopped/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T18:31:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For some reason the previews stopped in the Dolphin browser, however I found that it is working in the home directory but not on the other directories I couldn't find a fix for that.
 And while I was looking for a fix I found in filelight that /var/tmp/pamac-build-yamo/electron9 is taking 8.9 Gb So what is this and can I remove it?
    submitted by    /u/KDA_Yamo  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VP9 Encoder & Other Media Functionality Of Tesla's FSD Chip To Be Upstreamed In Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Tesla-FSD-Chip-MFC-Patches</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Tesla-FSD-Chip-MFC-Patches"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T18:20:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the Linux 5.18 kernel reaching stable in the next week or two there is basic support for Tesla's FSD chip. That Samsung-based SoC for powering Tesla's full-self driving technology has the basic support pieces in place for this kernel while Samsung engineers are working on ironing out other portions of the SoC support for future kernel releases...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is VPS? What a Virtual Private Server Can Do for You]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=799511</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/799511/what-is-vps-what-a-virtual-private-server-can-do-for-you/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T18:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to get server space of some kind you don’t necessarily need to rent an entire physical server, there are plenty of other options available. One of the more interesting is using a virtual private server, or VPS. Let’s take a look at how these work and what they can do for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fergus O'Sullivan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD Radeon RX 6750 XT Linux Gaming Performance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31122</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/vr.php?view=31122"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week AMD launched the Radeon RX 6650 XT / RX 6750 XT / RX 6950 XT models as RDNA2 refreshed for 2022 with higher clock speeds as an interim launch until RDNA3 graphics cards debut later in 2022. Up for Linux benchmarking today is a look at the Radeon RX 6750 XT open-source driver performance using an ASRock Challenger Pro Radeon RX 6750 XT 12GB.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Handling custom arch repo with aurutils]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/urs7j6/handling_custom_arch_repo_with_aurutils/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/urs7j6/handling_custom_arch_repo_with_aurutils/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T17:56:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello
 I cannot build packages with aurutils:
 [doskanoness@archlinux paczuchy]$ aur sync -c numix-icon-theme-git ==> Using [spacev7] repository -> numix-icon-theme-git (none) -> 21.10.31.r0.g7a28092dd-1 ==> Retrieving package files Cloning into 'numix-icon-theme-git'... remote: Enumerating objects: 75, done. remote: Counting objects: 100% (75/75), done. remote: Compressing objects: 100% (64/64), done. remote: Total 75 (delta 10), reused 71 (delta 10), pack-reused 0 Receiving objects: 100% (75/75), 15.18 KiB | 15.18 MiB/s, done. Resolving deltas: 100% (10/10), done. 78c3476 (bump 21.10.31, 2021-11-03) /tmp/aurutils-1000/view.pC6Ziuv is a directory [doskanoness@archlinux paczuchy]$ aur sync -c numix-circle-icon-theme-git ==> Using [spacev7] repository -> numix-circle-icon-theme-git (none) -> 21.10.31.r0.gfccd3b9-1 -> numix-icon-theme-git (none) -> 21.10.31.r0.g7a28092dd-1 ==> Retrieving package files POST git-upload-pack (155 bytes) From https://aur.archlinux.org/numix-icon-theme-git = [up to date] master -> origin/master Cloning into 'numix-circle-icon-theme-git'... remote: Enumerating objects: 102, done. remote: Counting objects: 100% (102/102), done. remote: Compressing objects: 100% (84/84), done. remote: Total 102 (delta 14), reused 100 (delta 14), pack-reused 0 Receiving objects: 100% (102/102), 19.11 KiB | 1.59 MiB/s, done. Resolving deltas: 100% (14/14), done. f03f189 (bump 21.10.31, 2021-11-03) /tmp/aurutils-1000/view.KxaMWiz is a directory 
 Do you know what's the cause of it?
    submitted by    /u/doskanoness  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How do you add persistent kernel arguments that apply to all current and future releases?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/urs63p/how_do_you_add_persistent_kernel_arguments_that/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/urs63p/how_do_you_add_persistent_kernel_arguments_that/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T17:54:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm trying to add "button.lid_init_state=open" as a kernel parameter which keeps my laptop from going haywire when I open the lid and resume from suspend. When I go to /boot/loader/entries I see two .conf files, one for the linux kernel and one for the lts, both named after the release version.
 My question is, is it possible to create a configuration where certain arguments are passed to whatever kernel is requested by systemd-boot?
 Thanks in advance.
    submitted by    /u/2BitNick  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ad-Supported Disney+ Is Ad-Free for Kids]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118221/ad-supported-disney-is-ad-free-for-kids/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118221/ad-supported-disney-is-ad-free-for-kids/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T17:43:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Disney+ charges just $8 a month for its service, making it one of the cheapest streaming platforms available today. Still, the company plans to launch an even cheaper ad-supported plan later this year. The company promises that this plan will go light on the ads, and in an odd twist, some viewers won’t see any ads!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulkan 1.3.214 Released With New AMD Vendor Extension]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Vulkan-1.3.214</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Vulkan-1.3.214"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T17:40:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just one week after Vulkan 1.3.213 released with its four new extensions, which included an update to the ray-tracing support, Vulkan 1.3.214 is out today with various fixes while introducing just one new extension...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Switching to Arch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/urr8vn/switching_to_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/urr8vn/switching_to_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T17:12:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm not on Linux for a long time, but I like it a lot. I'm currently using Linux Mint and even tho I like it I think it's just too user-friendly. I like challenges and learning and on Linux Mint there is nothing really to learn. And that's why I'm considering switching to Arch, I think it will give me a better understanding of Linux and hopefully teach me something. You know, it's a little different when you just flash Linux Mint into your PC, and when you have to build the whole operating system from scratch, even with the instruction. But I know Arch is not easy, especially for someone who is not on Linux for a long time. I will learn a bit first, try to install it on my other PC which is basically for testing things and then after some time of learning switch to Arch entirely. But still I would love to hear from more advanced and experienced users some tips or general advice. Even the stupidest shit might be useful for me. So that's basically what I'm asking for, general advice, maybe some not that obvious information about how things work on Arch, no noes, things that would make the switch easier, things that you wish you would know before you have switched to Arch etc.
 Thanks in advance for every reply :)
    submitted by    /u/korupcja  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is a DEX? Decentralized Exchanges Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=800261</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/800261/what-is-a-dex-decentralized-exchanges-explained/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T17:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A decentralized exchange (DEX) has distinct advantages over centralized exchanges. However, before using a DEX for all of your cryptocurrency transactions, you should be aware of the limitations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>RJ Fulton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch Dual Boot W10]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/urqi6i/arch_dual_boot_w10/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/urqi6i/arch_dual_boot_w10/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T16:38:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey guys, hope i won't get blasted too hard for this xD, i'm trying to run archinstall script to dualboot Arch and W10 (coming from Ubuntu), and after reading the wiki i understood almost everything, the only thing i'm worried about is the partitioning which isn't clear at all to me, i'm afraid of wiping my windows partitions somehow and i don't really get how the scripts partition system works. Any safe way to dual boot that with the script? Ty in advance!
    submitted by    /u/TeoXXIX  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TP-Link Brings Its Crazy-Affordable Smart Home Devices to the US]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118210/tp-link-brings-its-crazy-affordable-smart-home-devices-to-the-us/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118210/tp-link-brings-its-crazy-affordable-smart-home-devices-to-the-us/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T16:34:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[First available in Europe, the popular and outrageously affordable TP-Link Tapo lineup is now available in the United States. TP-Link is kicking things off with four security cameras and a smart LED strip, all of which $60 or less.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migliori App Scanner per fare scansioni dal telefono (Android e iPhone)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2012/07/scansione-di-documenti-in-pdf-da-iphone.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2012/07/scansione-di-documenti-in-pdf-da-iphone.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T16:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Se il nostro scanner o la stampante sono fuori uso o non funzionano come dovrebbero, possiamo utilizzare la fotocamera del nostro telefono per realizzare la versione digitale dei documenti e dei libri scritti su fogli di carta, come se fosse uno scanner digitale.

 Sono disponibili numerose app che acquisiscono i documenti come fa uno scanner, sfruttando la fotocamera del cellulare e convertendo...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Font issues in gnome]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/urpztk/font_issues_in_gnome/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/urpztk/font_issues_in_gnome/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T16:15:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been having some issues in gnome, specifically in GTK 4 applications here's a screenshot does anyone know what could be happening?
 EDIT: Resolved. it was an issue with mesa-git. Everything came back to normal after updating.
    submitted by    /u/Dani9oo  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[System-wide screen blank (no X)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/urpysy/systemwide_screen_blank_no_x/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/urpysy/systemwide_screen_blank_no_x/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T16:14:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m running into conflicting or unclear instructions so came here for help. In a modern systemd based system, Arch specifically, where X is not normally running, how does one implement a system-wide setting to blank the display after n minutes?
 Currently I’m using ‘setterm —blank=2’ in my .profile, but obviously that only works when I’m logged in. I’d like the display to do this regardless of login state.
    submitted by    /u/doa70  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Burrata Has Been Dubbed the Charcuterie Star of Summer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lifesavvy.com/129411/why-burrata-has-been-dubbed-the-charcuterie-star-of-summer/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lifesavvy.com/129411/why-burrata-has-been-dubbed-the-charcuterie-star-of-summer/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T16:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks to their no-heat-required, easy prep, charcuterie boards are an easy dinner solution as temperatures rise. While they’ve been popular for quite a while, a new addition is putting charcuterie back in the spotlight.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shea Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Adaptive Charging Saves Your Android Battery]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=803245</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/803245/how-adaptive-charging-saves-your-android-battery/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bad battery life can ruin your Android experience. But even a big battery probably still needs nightly charging. On top of that, batteries degrade over time. “Adaptive Charging” is a feature that aims to help all of these problems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Early Bird Sale: Roborock’s New Allergy-Busting Vacuums Are Here]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=805194</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/805194/early-bird-sale-roborocks-new-allergy-busting-vacuums-are-here/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T15:58:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While you’d expect allergens to run rampant outside your home during spring and summer, plenty of dust mites, pollen grains, pet dander, and other irritants also make it into your hallowed halls. Your home’s air filtration system gets a lot of these out of the air, but what about all the debris that gets left behind in your carpet? Roborock has the solution with its new Q series robot vacuums, which go on sale starting today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zach Laidlaw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung Could Finally Ditch Snapdragon for Its Own Mobile Chipset]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118200/samsung-could-finally-ditch-snapdragon-for-its-own-mobile-chipset/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118200/samsung-could-finally-ditch-snapdragon-for-its-own-mobile-chipset/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T15:39:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New rumors suggest Samsung could finally be ready to ditch the Qualcomm Snapdragon processor that’s powered many of its mobile devices over the years. Instead, it’ll design a custom in-house chipset built specifically for the Galaxy S line.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity agencies reveal top initial access attack vectors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cybersecurity-agencies-reveal-top-initial-access-attack-vectors/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cybersecurity-agencies-reveal-top-initial-access-attack-vectors/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T15:33:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A joint security advisory issued by multiple national cybersecurity authorities revealed today the top 10 attack vectors most exploited by threat actors for breaching networks. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The LimeWire Name Returns From the Dead to Sell Music NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=805773</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/805773/the-limewire-name-returns-from-the-dead-to-sell-music-nfts/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T15:29:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LimeWire was one of the most popular torrenting applications in the early 2000s. The original app was discontinued over a decade ago, but now the name is back to sell music-based NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eve Launches the First HomeKit Secure Video Floodlight Camera]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118187/eve-launches-the-first-homekit-secure-video-floodlight-camera/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118187/eve-launches-the-first-homekit-secure-video-floodlight-camera/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T15:25:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Outdoor security cameras are among our favorite bits of smart home tech, so we’re excited to learn about the latest devices, like Eve’s new Outdoor Cam. This is the first floodlight camera designed exclusively for Apple HomeKit Secure Video, and it’s full of smart and convenient features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzanne Humphries</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Android Launchers for Senior and Visually Impaired Users]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=199020</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/6290242/best-android-launchers-for-senior-visually-impaired-users"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With smartphones being omnipresent in today’s world, it’s easy to take them for granted. Unfortunately, there are a number of people who find modern smartphones either too confusing or too difficult to use. Elderly people are prone to being left behind as they find it hard to adapt to rapidly changing technology. Similarly, visually-impaired folks may have difficulty operating a device that relies on hand-eye coordination.
    
Fortunately, there are ways to combat these problems.
    
Some may find that specially-designed smartphones are the way to go. Alternatively, if you already have a phone, you can tweak the appearance of your Android phone with apps called launchers. Launchers can change the entire look and feel of your Android device, making them easier to use. The following Android launchers are designed with seniors and the visually-impaired in mind.
   

Content

1. Grand Launcher
2. Help Launcher
3. BIG Launcher
4. Elementique Senior Launcher
5. Simple Launcher
6. Senior Safety Phone
7. Simple Mode
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Megan Glosson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What games would you see benchmarked in a kernel roundup?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/urolcl/what_games_would_you_see_benchmarked_in_a_kernel/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/urolcl/what_games_would_you_see_benchmarked_in_a_kernel/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T15:10:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following this post about whether the linux-zen kernel is still viable for gaming I'd like to do some benchmark. I want to compare Arch's default kernel, linux-zen, linux-xanmod and linux-tkg.
 I'm asking myself which game's I should benchmark for a good overview, so I'm asking you. What game's should I benchmark?
 I guess I'm only going to benchmark three to five games and they should have an in-game benchmark to have consistent results. For now I settled with the following, but let me know if you want to see any other game.
 I choose those games because they're quite popular and I own all of them.
  
Red Dead Redemption 2
 Cyberpunk 2077
 Watch Dogs: Legion
 GTA 5
 Assassin's Creed: Odyssey
 Shadow of the Tomb Raider
 Far Cry 5
  
EDIT: I'll definitely add CS:GO and Civilization 6, because both games are especially heavy on the CPU. In terms of the other games I suggested I guess I'll go with GTA 5 because it's still pretty popular, as well as Cyberpunk 2077 because it's also popular and Shadow of the Tomb Raider because it is or was a well-established game for benchmarks.
 So the selection for now looks like this:
  
Counter-Strike: Global Offensive
 Civilization VI
 Grand Theft Auto 5
 Cyberpunk 2077
 Shadow of the Tomb Raider
  
   submitted by    /u/Arjab  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NVidia Studio e Canvas: cosa sono e come funzionano]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=NVidia-Studio-e-Canvas-cosa-sono-e-come-funzionano_24525</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=NVidia-Studio-e-Canvas-cosa-sono-e-come-funzionano_24525"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T15:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[La tecnologia sta rapidamente evolvendo e grazie ad essa è possibile migliorare il processo attraverso il quale i creatori di contenuti realizzano le loro idee trasformandole in progetti concreti. NVidia, come altre aziende, ha scelto l'intelligenza artificiale per far risparmiare tempo prezioso grazie all'accelerazione di un'ampia gamma di attività.NVidia Studio è una piattaforma che aiuta i creatori a lavorare meglio e più velocemente. Si tratta di una piattaforma end-to-end che spazia cioè dall'hardware sul quale è basato il PC al software: l'obiettivo è fornire le migliori prestazioni, la massima affidabilità e nuove funzionalità che accelerano il loro flusso di lavoro.A supportare l'idea della piattaforma end-to-end, il fatto che NVidia Studio è un ecosistema formato da:- GPU NVIDIA R…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Withings Debuts the Most Stylish Smartwatch to Date]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118174/withings-debuts-the-most-stylish-smartwatch-to-date/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118174/withings-debuts-the-most-stylish-smartwatch-to-date/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T15:03:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I reviewed the original Withings ScanWatch, I called it a “smartwatch for people who don’t like smartwatches.” That’s because it looks like an analog watch but still offers powerful health and fitness features. Now, Withings is taking things even further with the ScanWatch Horizon, the most stylish smartwatch I’ve ever seen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Android Factory Reset Not Working? Try These Fixes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/?p=59714</id>
        <link href="https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/android-factory-reset-not-working-try-these-fixes/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T15:01:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're having trouble resetting your Android device using the Factory Reset function, don't worry - you're not alone. It is a common issue many Android]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Muhammad Junaid Khalid</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add, Edit, and Remove Tab Stops in Microsoft Word]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=803061</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/803061/how-to-add-edit-and-remove-tab-stops-in-microsoft-word/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T15:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tab stops in Microsoft Word give you quick and easy ways to move your cursor to certain spots. This is handy for indents or specific spacing. Here, we’ll show you how to add, edit, and remove tab stops in Word.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come personalizzare LibreOffice]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/05/come-personalizzare-libreoffice.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/05/come-personalizzare-libreoffice.html"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T15:00:00.006Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LibreOffice è una suite d'ufficio gratuita rilasciata con licenza open source e, come tutti i programmi rilasciati con questa licenza, esso è altamente personalizzabile. Rispetto ad Office infatti possiamo cambiare la disposizione di qualsiasi tasto o barra presente nell'interfaccia, cambiare colori e icone presenti nelle applicazioni e personalizzare i menu, così da rendere la suite d'ufficio su...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers can steal your Tesla Model 3, Y using new Bluetooth attack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-can-steal-your-tesla-model-3-y-using-new-bluetooth-attack/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-can-steal-your-tesla-model-3-y-using-new-bluetooth-attack/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T14:30:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security researchers at the NCC Group have developed a tool to carry out a Bluetooth Low Energy (BLE) relay attack that bypasses all existing protections to authenticate on target devices. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Audio-Technica ATH-CKS50TW Review: Solid Sound, Amazing Battery Life]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/117313/audio-technica-ath-cks50tw-review/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/117313/audio-technica-ath-cks50tw-review/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T14:24:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Audio-Technica, a company with a familiar name to even the most casual listeners, created a great sounding set of buds that, unfortunately, chooses function over form. The ATH-CK550TW have top-of-the-line specs and versatility that should put these earbuds near the top of any buyer’s list.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chazz Mair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Help getting FIDO2 and systemd-cryptenroll working]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/urnj8x/help_getting_fido2_and_systemdcryptenroll_working/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/urnj8x/help_getting_fido2_and_systemdcryptenroll_working/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T14:20:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So I'm in the process of trying to add (rudimentary) FIDO2 support to archinstall (hidden behind --advanced as it's clearly very unfinished and I'm still figuring this out).
 The way that I've done it is by following these three resources: * https://wiki.archlinux.org/title/Universal_2nd_Factor#Data-at-rest_encryption_with_LUKS * https://wiki.archlinux.org/title/Trusted_Platform_Module#systemd-cryptenroll * https://wiki.archlinux.org/title/dm-crypt/System_configuration#Using_sd-encrypt_hook
 And long story short, after encrypting a partition with a password, unlocked it, formatted it and closed the partition I do the following:
 (/dev/sda1 being boot, and /dev/sda2 being the crypt device)
  
systemd-cryptenroll --fido2-device=auto /dev/sda2
 Modifying {target}/etc/mkinicptio.conf to contai…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple App Store: per gli aumenti di prezzo varrà il silenzio assenso]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Apple-App-Store-per-gli-aumenti-di-prezzo-varra-il-silenzio-assenso_24524</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Apple-App-Store-per-gli-aumenti-di-prezzo-varra-il-silenzio-assenso_24524"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T14:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gli aumenti dei canoni di abbonamento sono ammessi: è tuttavia necessario che l'utente sia preventivamente informato della variazione contrattuale. Dopo aver correttamente informato il cliente il fornitore del servizio può applicare modifiche peggiorative per l'utente applicando anche il meccanismo del silenzio assenso.Lo sanno bene tutti coloro che dispongono di un'utenza mobile o fissa e si sono dovuti confrontare, nel corso del tempo, con varie rimodulazioni tariffarie.Nel caso delle applicazioni pubblicate sull'Apple App Store quando viene aumentato il prezzo di un abbonamento con rinnovo automatico, fino ad oggi erano chiamati ad acconsentire all'applicazione dell'aumento di prezzo.L'abbonamento non si rinnova automaticamente allorquando fossero applicati dei ritocchi al rialzo sul valore del canone mensile o annuale prelevato attraverso il metodo di pagamento specificato.Talvolta capita che gli utenti ignorino le email, le notifiche push e i messaggi in-app che informano circa la modifica delle condizioni economiche dell'abbonamento.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is ISO 27001 and Why it Matters for Compliance Standards]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/what-is-iso-27001-and-why-it-matters-for-compliance-standards/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/what-is-iso-27001-and-why-it-matters-for-compliance-standards/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ISO 27001 may seem like a big undertaking, but the certification can pay off in more ways than one—including overlap with compliance regulations. Read about the benefits of ISO 27001 and how to get started. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sponsored by Specops</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>