<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-06-03T01:45:26.567Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://sovy666.github.io/informatica/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Atlassian Confluence zero-day actively used in attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/critical-atlassian-confluence-zero-day-actively-used-in-attacks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/critical-atlassian-confluence-zero-day-actively-used-in-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T01:41:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers are actively exploiting a new Atlassian Confluence zero-day vulnerability tracked as CVE-2022-26134 to install web shells, with no fix available at this time. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ip link says I have no IP address]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3n3g5/ip_link_says_i_have_no_ip_address/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3n3g5/ip_link_says_i_have_no_ip_address/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T00:31:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I connected to my wireless network using iwctl however, i do not have an ip adress. Is there a way to get an IP address in the live install?
    submitted by    /u/NotSheltr  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Legally Download a Windows Virtual Machine]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=490562</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15346647/legally-download-windows-virtual-machine"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to run a copy of Windows in a virtual machine on your computer, you need to pay for a Windows license, right? But did you know that you can actually legally get a pre-made Windows Virtual Machine directly from Microsoft? These are meant for software developers, but they aren’t locked behind any sort of paid program or login page. You can have your own copies within a few minutes of reading this.
   

Content

Why Use a Windows VM?
Where to Get Your Free Windows VM?
What's the Catch?
How to Use Your VM with VirtualBox
Can You Run These VMs on an Apple Silicon Computer?

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Share Files Between Host PC and Virtual Machines
    
Why Use a Windows VM?
    
These pre-made VMs aren’t a permanent solution, but they offer a reliable... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sydney Butler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch hard freezing on AMD hardware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3l1mu/arch_hard_freezing_on_amd_hardware/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3l1mu/arch_hard_freezing_on_amd_hardware/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T22:45:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi all! I've been trying to install Arch, but I'm having issues with it.
 During installation the Live OS will freeze. Using Arch itself, a GUI installer, and other Arch based distros. I did get an Arch based distro to install, but it freezes also minutes after booting. I would rather use vanilla Arch instead of a distro anyways. I've used Linux before, and even got my Linux+ certification in 2011. I haven't used Linux in a while and want to play around again.
 I want to use Arch since it's what SteamOS is based on, but I don't want to use SteamOS.
 My hardware is as follows Ryzen 5 3600x ASRock Fatal1ty B450 Gaming-ITX/ac 32GB crucial 3200 ram AMD Radeon 5700xt
 I've tried searching and using different commands but either I'm doing it wrong or it's not working for me.
 Thank you for your time!
    submitted by    /u/LooseGas  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 10 KB5014023 update fixes slow copying, app crashes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-10-kb5014023-update-fixes-slow-copying-app-crashes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-10-kb5014023-update-fixes-slow-copying-app-crashes/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T21:50:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has released optional cumulative update previews for Windows 10 versions 20H2, 21H1, and 21H2, with fixes for slow file copying and applications crashing due to Direct3D issues. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why are there only headers, and no actual source files, for various packages?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3jrt3/why_are_there_only_headers_and_no_actual_source/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3jrt3/why_are_there_only_headers_and_no_actual_source/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T21:45:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arch is supposed to bundle all development files in with the standard packages, yet it seems like half of the packages only include the headers, and no actual source files.
 Specifically, I'm trying to compile something using libsensors. /usr/include/sensors/sensors.h exists, but the linker is throwing a fit because the equivalent sensors.c file is nowhere to be found when searching in /usr.
 Am I missing something here? Why are these files not included in the packages?
    submitted by    /u/BassChaser710  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wake from sleep magically fixed. Thank You Arch Devs!!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3jha4/wake_from_sleep_magically_fixed_thank_you_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3jha4/wake_from_sleep_magically_fixed_thank_you_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T21:32:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm just throwing it out there for the people that have been having issues with wake from sleep since late 5.17 kernel. My issue magically resolved itself with my latest update. So if you have been having issues with waking from sleep maybe updating will get it working for you again.
 P.S. Any tips to troubleshoot this in the future would be cool, I never got it figured as powering off just worked.
    submitted by    /u/Im-Mostly-Confused  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Which drive should I install Arch on?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3jd7c/which_drive_should_i_install_arch_on/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3jd7c/which_drive_should_i_install_arch_on/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T21:27:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was wondering which drive should I install Arch on; nvme0n1 which is 223.6G or sda which is my hard drive which is 931.5G. (I'm a newbie so I don't know that much :D).
    submitted by    /u/frOSystem  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add Screenshots and Animation to GitHub Pull Requests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=336059</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15346476/add-screenshots-animation-github-pull-requests"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub programmers often add screenshots or animated GIFs to their repository pull requests. These techniques are definitely more eye-catching than making someone read several lines of plain text. Adding static screenshots is helpful if you want to insert visual changes or photographs inline. To demonstrate process flows and mouse-cursor motion, you can use MP4 videos and GIF animation. The following tutorial shows you how to add screenshots and MP4/GIF animation in GitHub pull requests. 
   

Content

1. Add a New Repository and Branch
2. Create Screenshots for GitHub
3. Create Videos and GIF Animation for GitHub
4. Add Screenshots or Animations to GitHub Pull Requests
5. Display Screenshots and GIF Images on a GitHub Page
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:The Beginner’s Guide to Git
    
1. Add a New Repository and Branch
    
Even if you have never used GitHub before, you can use the below steps... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sayak Boral</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 10 Android banking trojans target apps with 1 billion downloads]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/top-10-android-banking-trojans-target-apps-with-1-billion-downloads/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/top-10-android-banking-trojans-target-apps-with-1-billion-downloads/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T21:09:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ten most prolific Android mobile banking trojans target 639 financial applications that collectively have over one billion downloads on the Google Play Store. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make Your Taskbar Larger or Smaller on Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=759589</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/759589/how-to-make-your-taskbar-larger-or-smaller-on-windows-11/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As of October 2021, the taskbar size in Windows 11 can’t be adjusted with the Settings app. Luckily, we’ve discovered a registry hack that can make the taskbar larger or smaller. Here’s how to do it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benj Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evil Corp switches to LockBit ransomware to evade sanctions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/evil-corp-switches-to-lockbit-ransomware-to-evade-sanctions/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/evil-corp-switches-to-lockbit-ransomware-to-evade-sanctions/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T20:35:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Evil Corp cybercrime group has now switched to deploying LockBit ransomware on targets' networks to evade sanctions imposed by the U.S. Treasury Department's Office of Foreign Assets Control (OFAC). [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel Issues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3hwj7/kernel_issues/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3hwj7/kernel_issues/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T20:19:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Error! Bad return status for module build on kernel: 5.18.1-arch1-1 (x86_64) 
 what does this mean and what can be done about it?
    submitted by    /u/Sea-End9327  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cannot wrap my head around Filesystems and partitions, HELP REQUIRED]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3hhlb/cannot_wrap_my_head_around_filesystems_and/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3hhlb/cannot_wrap_my_head_around_filesystems_and/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T20:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So I want to install arch on my main BIOS machine and would like to avoid the archinstall.
 The only problem I got up until now is to find the BEST partition method for my system. I could go easy and simple and just repeat whatever guide or tutorial out there in Youtube like I've done so far but I really find myself in the need of step up.
 I know this depends on lots of factors and I would like some guidance.
 Some of my questions:
 should I go with btrfs or xfs? 
 why some partitions require one filesystem or another?
 should I allocate the swap at the beginning or at the end?
 ​
 Right now my tab looks like this:
 sda1 - ext4 - 8M
 sda2 - swap - 8G
 sda3 - xfs - 100G (root)
 sda4 - btrfs - 580G (home)
 ​
 Any help would be much appreciated
    submitted by    /u/cnovoa15  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Insert a Handwritten Signature in Google Docs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=755404</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/755404/how-to-insert-a-handwritten-signature-in-google-docs/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While digital signatures have become a popular way to sign documents, you may have a document of your own where you just want to handwrite your signature. Using Google’s drawing tool, you can create and insert your signature easily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save 21% on a Garmin Forerunner 245 Music Running Smartwatch]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=399290</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/14466607/garmin-forerunner-music-running-smartwatch"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you like to completely let go when you work out, you’ll like the Garmin Forerunner 245 Music Running Smartwatch. While getting advanced running dynamics during your training, you can listen to your favorite tunes.
    
Sync the smartwatch with your favorite playlists on Spotify or various other music streaming services for ad-free listening. You can store up to 500 songs on the device. Transfer music from your computer, add headphones via Bluetooth and listen while you train for your next marathon.
    

    
The Garmin Forerunner 245 Music Running Smartwatch will allow you to make smarter training decisions to help you prepare for your next race. Watch your VO2 max and erase your concerns about heat and altitude, as the watch will analyze the impacts on your performance. Your exercise history and performance indicators are evaluated to help you maintain productivity. Get feedback from your aerobic and anaerobic training.
    
Join the Garmin Connect online fitness community to create custom workouts with the available tools or download free workouts. Need a coach?... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Microsoft Store on Windows Is About to Get Much Better]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=809010</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/809010/the-microsoft-store-on-windows-is-about-to-get-better/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T19:19:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Microsoft Store is the main app store on Windows 10 and 11, and it received an overhaul last year in time for the first version of Windows 11. Now even more improvements are on the way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apps for recording audio on ArchLinux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3ghm8/apps_for_recording_audio_on_archlinux/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3ghm8/apps_for_recording_audio_on_archlinux/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T19:14:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What audio recording app do you use on ArchLinux?
 I've been using gnome-sound-recorder but I want to switch to something less bloat. I guess ffmpeg might help but I'm not sure if I could get a good audio quality using only ffmpeg.
 I use this command in my script to record my screen along with my voice but my voice is not usually recorded properly. For example, my last words [at the end of the recording] usually are cut off and I don't know why.
 ffmpeg -video_size ${SCREEN_WIDTH}x${SCREEN_HEIGHT} -framerate 16 -f x11grab -i :0.0 -f pulse -ac 2 -i default ~/Videos/$(date +%Y-%m-%d_%T).mp4
    submitted by    /u/i8ad8  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setting up WiFi on Arch.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3ghbc/setting_up_wifi_on_arch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3ghbc/setting_up_wifi_on_arch/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T19:14:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, I'm a newbie to Arch and Linux in general so please excuse me if my knowledge is a little bit underwhelming. I was wondering how to properly set up WiFi on Arch. I already know how to use IWCTL and how to connect to WiFi but is there anything else needed for a working WiFi so it connects when I boot and is there anything to set up with NetworkManager. Unfortunately I don't have access to ethernet so using that and going the easy route is out of the picture. Thanks in advance!
    submitted by    /u/frOSystem  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Your Next Car Needs Adaptive Cruise Control]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119885/why-your-next-car-needs-adaptive-cruise-control/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119885/why-your-next-car-needs-adaptive-cruise-control/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T19:07:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s nothing better than turning on cruise control and relaxing to some music during a road trip. And while cruise control is useful, the latest premium feature you’ll want in your next vehicle is adaptive cruise control (ACC), and here’s why.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ransomware gang now hacks corporate websites to show ransom notes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ransomware-gang-now-hacks-corporate-websites-to-show-ransom-notes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ransomware-gang-now-hacks-corporate-websites-to-show-ransom-notes/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T19:01:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A ransomware gang is taking extortion to a new level by publicly hacking corporate websites to publicly display ransom notes. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Loop a Video on iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=806998</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/806998/how-to-loop-a-video-on-iphone/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T19:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using just the built-in features in iPhone’s Photos and YouTube app, you can make your videos play in a loop for as long as you want. This eliminates the need to manually re-play your videos, and we’ll show you how to do that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox Nightly Tries For VA-API Video Acceleration For Mesa Users]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Firefox-103-Nightly-VA-API</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Firefox-103-Nightly-VA-API"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T18:28:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Potentially for the Mozilla Firefox 103 release we could see VA-API video acceleration for Linux users finally enabled by default while as of today has been flipped back on again in Firefox Nightly builds...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[why is this package still installed?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3f247/why_is_this_package_still_installed/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3f247/why_is_this_package_still_installed/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I had installed wine earlier, and I uninstalled it. I uninstalled all dependencies along with it.
 pacman -Qdtq and pacman -Qdttq do not list lib32-attr, and lib32-libogg. (These commands list nothing)
 pacman -Qe does not list it either.
 When I try to uninstall them, they give no error or warning.
 They are not an explicitly installed package. Neither a normal or an optional dependency.
 Why are they still installed?
    submitted by    /u/abrattic  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trying to install on ThinkPad T61 on ethernet, can’t import PGP keys]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3ezzp/trying_to_install_on_thinkpad_t61_on_ethernet/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3ezzp/trying_to_install_on_thinkpad_t61_on_ethernet/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T18:07:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am trying to install Arch Linux (kernel 5.18.1) onto my T61, however, whenever I run pacman -Syyu or use the archinstall script, it asks me to manually import PGP keys, and then fails, telling me the required key is missing from the keyring. Any clue as to what is going on?
    submitted by    /u/1kelpy  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Disable the “These Files Might Be Harmful to Your Computer” Warning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=807905</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/807905/how-to-disable-the-these-files-might-be-harmful-to-your-computer-warning/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows can be pretty aggressive with security warnings, to the point that it warns you about your own files on your own home network. Here’s how to calm Windows down so you can use network shares and your NAS in peace.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Fitzpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BMW and Ford Just Announced More Electric Cars]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=808999</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/808999/bmw-and-ford-just-announced-more-electric-cars/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T17:45:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are now more options than ever for all-electric and hybrid vechicles, and now two more are on the way: an electric version of BMW’s X1 SUV, and a commercial vehicle from Ford.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[System76 & HP Formally Launch The HP Dev One AMD Ryzen Laptop With Pop!_OS Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=HP-Dev-One-Launches</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=HP-Dev-One-Launches"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T17:39:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last month System76 and HP began teasing an HP developer laptop with AMD Ryzen SoC and running Pop!_OS while today that HP Dev One laptop has formally launched...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft blocks Polonium hackers from using OneDrive in attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-blocks-polonium-hackers-from-using-onedrive-in-attacks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-blocks-polonium-hackers-from-using-onedrive-in-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T17:36:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft said it blocked a Lebanon-based hacking group it tracks as Polonium from using the OneDrive cloud storage platform for data exfiltration and command and control while targeting and compromising Israelian organizations. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smartproxy Review: The Reliable, High-Quality Proxy]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?p=489231</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15346221/smartproxy-review"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T17:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gathering data is critical for building businesses, but web scraping manually is tiresome and often leads to IP blocks and bans. Sadly, many proxy services only have limited options and aren’t always trustworthy, even after paying high fees to use them. I recently had the opportunity to test Smartproxy, which promises to not only be trustworthy but also offers high-quality services for a fair price. 
    
This is a sponsored article and was made possible by Smartproxy. The actual contents and opinions are the sole views of the author who maintains editorial independence even when a post is sponsored.
    
Overview of Smartproxy
    
Smartproxy doesn’t just specialize in one type of proxy service or tool. Between a a variety of proxies, tools, and user resources/tutorials, users get everything they need to scrape the web efficiently. In fact, Smartproxy actually won the 2021 Best Value Provider by Proxyway for their dedication to meeting customer needs. 
    
Some of the main features the service offers include:
    
Intuitive dashboard with a quick account setup
Free geo-targeting
Unlimited connections and threads
Advanced proxy rotation
Numerous informative resources that are... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Crystal Crowder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Select LEGO Sets Will See a Price Hike This August]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119886/select-lego-sets-will-see-a-price-hike-this-august/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119886/select-lego-sets-will-see-a-price-hike-this-august/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T17:09:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As if LEGO sets weren’t expensive enough, a new price hike is coming later this year. It seems that increased material and operating costs are finally getting the best of LEGO, as the company plans to increase prices on “around a quarter” of its catalog this August.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What to Look for in a Gaming Headset]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=797570</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/797570/what-to-look-for-in-a-gaming-headset/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T17:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to take your gaming up a notch? A gaming headset will help give you the competitive advantage you need to come out on top. Here are all the main factors to consider when shopping for a gaming headset.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Nguyen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Opens a PS5 and Xbox Waiting List for Real People, Not Bots]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119873/amazon-opens-a-ps5-and-xbox-waiting-list-for-real-people-not-bots/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119873/amazon-opens-a-ps5-and-xbox-waiting-list-for-real-people-not-bots/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T16:39:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a (at this point, noble) effort to evade bots and scalpers, Amazon is creating a by-request waiting list for purchasing the highly sought after PlayStation 5 and Xbox Series X gaming consoles after a recent restock. Users can request an invitation on the Amazon product page.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzanne Humphries</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese LuoYu hackers deploy cyber-espionage malware via app updates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/chinese-luoyu-hackers-deploy-cyber-espionage-malware-via-app-updates/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/chinese-luoyu-hackers-deploy-cyber-espionage-malware-via-app-updates/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T16:36:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Chinese-speaking hacking group known as LuoYu is infecting victims WinDealer information stealer malware deployed by switching legitimate app updates with malicious payloads in man-on-the-side attacks. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another Pixel 7 Prototype Ended Up In Someone's Pocket]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119876/another-pixel-7-prototype-ended-up-in-someones-pocket/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119876/another-pixel-7-prototype-ended-up-in-someones-pocket/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T16:29:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the end of May, we reported on Google’s unreleased Pixel 7 popping up on eBay. Now, it looks like another Pixel 7 prototype, the flagship Pixel 7 Pro, ended up on Facebook marketplace and in someone’s pocket.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BMW Reveals Its First Affordable EV]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119874/bmw-reveals-its-first-affordable-ev/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119874/bmw-reveals-its-first-affordable-ev/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T16:27:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The newly-revealed BMW X1 lineup is all about functionality, style, and affordability, with ICE cars starting at $35,000. But more notably, this lineup includes BMW’s first affordable electric car—the BMW iX1 xDrive30.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Experimenting With "NVK" Nouveau Open-Source Vulkan Driver]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Red-Hat-NVK-NVIDIA-Vulkan</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Red-Hat-NVK-NVIDIA-Vulkan"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T16:09:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following the recent news about Nouveau shifting code around so their shader compiler can be used outside of Nouveau Gallium3D, Red Hat's Karol Herbst who has been a longtime Nouveau developer has been posting patches for his new "NVK" Nouveau Vulkan driver effort...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Fastest Way to Type a Period on iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=808317</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/808317/the-fastest-way-to-type-a-period-on-iphone/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T16:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The iPhone keyboard is one of the most popular keyboards on the planet, but it’s not without its quirks. Strangely, the period key is buried in the secondary layout. There’s a much faster way to use it, though.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Social media’s ‘Doomscrolling Reminder Lady’ on her favorite corners of the internet]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.mozilla.org/?p=69042</id>
        <link href="https://blog.mozilla.org/en/internet-culture/interviews/karen-ho-twitter-doomscrolling-reminder-lady/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T15:55:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here at Mozilla, we are the first to admit the internet isn’t perfect, but we are also quick to point out that the internet is pretty darn magical. The internet opens up doors and opportunities, allows for people to connect with others, and lets everyone find where they belong — their corners of the internet. […]
The post Social media’s ‘Doomscrolling Reminder Lady’ on her favorite corners of the internet appeared first on The Mozilla Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kristina Bravo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[dropped into emergency shell, arch no longer boots]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3bxxp/dropped_into_emergency_shell_arch_no_longer_boots/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3bxxp/dropped_into_emergency_shell_arch_no_longer_boots/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T15:51:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I don't know what's going on. I've been experiencing a multitude of problems lately and have suspected something wrong with my system overall and then it finally stopped working on me.
 This is the screen I get now. https://ibb.co/s9Szc5r
 At first, it wasn't recognizing the kernel images that I had installed. I removed and reinstalled my kernels as well as my boot manager-refind-and that changed it to what you see now.
 The bootmanager pulls up fine. The normal options are all there. I can load into recovery media perfectly fine and see that everything is still there just the way it was before it stopped booting. It just won't boot into arch.
 It appears that, for some reason, the system cannot locate the file systems.
 Please help.
    submitted by    /u/reenmini  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unable to log-in on after installing nvidia drivers on laptop (fresh installs)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3bxhv/unable_to_login_on_after_installing_nvidia/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3bxhv/unable_to_login_on_after_installing_nvidia/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T15:50:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is what my screen looks like when i try to log in. This issue appears only after I install proprietary nvidia drivers via: sudo pacman -S nvidia-dkms nvidia-utils lib32-nvidia-utils nvidia-settings vulkan-icd-loader lib32-vulkan-icd-loader lib32-opencl-nvidia opencl-nvidia libxnvctrl
 Methods tried so far: • reinstalled arch few times • tried both kde and gnome • added nvidia related modules to /etc/mkinitcpio.conf • blacklisted iGPU modules (source: arch wiki)
    submitted by    /u/mmj0299  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is it worth encrypting my disk using LUKS if I'm the only person who has physical access to it ?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3bsst/is_it_worth_encrypting_my_disk_using_luks_if_im/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3bsst/is_it_worth_encrypting_my_disk_using_luks_if_im/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T15:44:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The title explains it all, i'm an Arch user, and I have it installed in my Desktop PC. I do trust my family members and I'm literally the only person who would ever have physical access to it. My question here is: Is it worth encrypting the disk in my case ? Cause I have to backup all my data + dotfiles before doing a clean install of Arch.
 Thanks in advance! I'm all ears to hear out ur opinions.
    submitted by    /u/1_7xr  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Pay e Google Pay sono sicuri per i pagamenti?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/06/apple-pay-e-google-pay-sono-sicuri-per.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/06/apple-pay-e-google-pay-sono-sicuri-per.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T15:40:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tra i metodi di pagamento digitale in rapida diffusione troviamo sicuramente Apple Pay e Google Pay, due app che si comportano in maniera del tutto simile a dei portafogli di nuova generazione. Con esse infatti è possibile inserire i dati della propria carta di credito (ma anche Bancomat o carte prepagate) e "virtualizzarla", così da poter pagare nei negozi abilitati semplicemente avvicinando il...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Newbie Question: Is there an arch installation guide within the arch iso?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3bjni/newbie_question_is_there_an_arch_installation/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3bjni/newbie_question_is_there_an_arch_installation/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T15:32:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I want to know if there is something like an installation guide within the arch iso that I can look up while I'm in the installation process without having to look for it on another device. 
 I hope I made myself clear. Thanks in advance.
    submitted by    /u/cnovoa15  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Safari Not Working on Your iPhone? Here’s How to Fix It]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=post-ideas&amp;p=243361</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/8302860/safari-not-working-iphone"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Although iPhones and iPads support other apps to reach the Web, Safari remains the most favored and frequently used browser for iOS users. Troubleshooting on Safari can be frustrating, especially if its issues prevent you from searching for a solution online. Here are a few common reasons why Safari may not be working on your iPhone and how to fix the problems.
   

Content

Turn on Mobile Data for the Safari App
Disable Experimental Features
Change Your Network Settings

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Make Mobile Safari Save Your Passwords on iOS
    
Test Your Internet Connection
    
To begin with, ensure that the problem is with Safari and not with your internet connection. For this, open, say, a non-Apple app like Facebook or Chrome, and see whether the website or the feed loads. If it does, then Safari is at fault.... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ojash Yadav</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Steam Deck Accessory Just Got Delayed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119869/the-best-steam-deck-accessory-just-got-delayed/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119869/the-best-steam-deck-accessory-just-got-delayed/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T15:24:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in April, I predicted that the Steam Deck Docking Station would launch in late June, “barring any last-minute delays.” And it seems that I jinxed everyone, because the Steam Deck Dock just got delayed indefinitely. We have no clue when it will launch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla releases local machine translation tools as part of Project Bergamot]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.mozilla.org/?p=69082</id>
        <link href="https://blog.mozilla.org/en/mozilla/local-translation-add-on-project-bergamot/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T15:23:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In January of 2019, Mozilla joined the University of Edinburgh, Charles University, University of Sheffield and University of Tartu as part of a project funded by the European Union called Project Bergamot. The ultimate goal of this consortium was to build a set of neural machine translation tools that would enable Mozilla to develop a […]
The post Mozilla releases local machine translation tools as part of Project Bergamot appeared first on The Mozilla Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rebecca Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Audio and video drivers?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3ay7d/audio_and_video_drivers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3ay7d/audio_and_video_drivers/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T15:05:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello,I'm trying to install video drivers for my system. I'm running arch off of a USB onto a Dell G15 laptop. It has a NVIDIA 3060 GPU and I think it has integrated Intel graphics. To log into my system I just use tty1 and then start X on login. I use i3.
 I've tried installing the NVIDIA package a couple times but it always leads to some sort of issue where my system completely stalls whenever I start X. Because of this, I'm pretty sure some sort of configuration is wrong, but it could be that I'm installing the wrong driver or even something else entirely.
 I'd be fine with only using the integrated Intel graphics, but for some reason, xrandr doesn't recognize my 2 external monitors that I connect via usbc dock.
 I've read through a a bunch of the wiki and done a decent amount of googling. Its entirely possible that I've missed something though. Any pointers in the right direction would be really really helpful. 
 Edit: I know the title says Audio and video, but I've decided to work on things one at a time haha.
    submitted by    /u/SyntaxAerror  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TCL Picks Up Where the LG Stylo Left Off]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119850/tcl-picks-up-where-the-lg-stylo-left-off/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119850/tcl-picks-up-where-the-lg-stylo-left-off/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T15:02:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After LG decided to stop selling smartphones, it left a huge gap in the “this phone is kinda weird” market. Most notably, the death of LG Stylo meant that only Motorola would sell affordable stylus-equipped smartphones. But the universe is correcting itself with the launch of TCL’s Stylus 5G.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Goal Seek in Microsoft Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=805858</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/805858/goal-seek-excel/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T15:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever had a financial goal you sought but weren’t exactly sure how to get there? Using Goal Seek in Microsoft Excel, you can determine what you need to accomplish your goal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Steam Deck’s Official Docking Station Is Now Delayed (Again)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=808977</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/808977/steam-decks-official-docking-station-is-now-delayed-again/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T14:40:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Valve originally promised a docking station would be available for the Steam Deck at the console’s release, but it has been delayed. Now Valve has confirmed it has been delayed, again.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iOttie Velox Wireless Charging Dash & Windshield Mount Review: Not Quite Wireless]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119089/iottie-velox-magnetic-wireless-charging-dash-and-windshield-mount-review/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119089/iottie-velox-magnetic-wireless-charging-dash-and-windshield-mount-review/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T14:24:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[iOttie’s Velox Magnetic Wireless Charging Dash & Windshield Mount does little to stand out among the ever-growing crowd of vehicle chargers and mounts. It solves just enough minor inconveniences to stand above the pack, but its bulky size means it’s only for cars with space to spare.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chazz Mair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video on websites are freezing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3a040/video_on_websites_are_freezing/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3a040/video_on_websites_are_freezing/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T14:22:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, today I discovered an issue on my Arch. I rarely watch videos on my laptop, so I am not sure since when this issue has been there.
 When I try to play a video, the video just freeze. I can seek the bar on the player, but it will only change the frame shown. The video will keep freezing.
 Not only on Reddit, but on youtube as well.
 You can see the issue in action here: https://i.imgur.com/XbSlmfv.mp4
 Hopefully someone can give me an idea to try. Thanks!
  
Os: Arch
 kernel: linux 5.18.1.arch1-1
 Browser: Occur on Firefox and Chrome
 GPU: Occur on both AMDGPU and Nvidia
  
   submitted by    /u/tom_yacht  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best VR Headsets of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=754839</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/754839/best-vr-headset/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Virtual reality prices are down, and the quality of games is up, so it’s a great time to jump in if you’ve been holding off on taking the plunge. While we aren’t quite in The Matrix yet, modern VR headsets are shockingly good. Here’s the best VR headset you can buy right now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sydney Butler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some users are reporting printing issues in Microsoft Edge 102]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178909</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/02/some-users-are-reporting-printing-issues-in-microsoft-edge-102/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T13:57:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft released a new stable version of the company's Edge web browser a few days ago. Microsoft Edge 102 fixed several security issues in the browser, including three that were specified to […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Some users are reporting printing issues in Microsoft Edge 102 appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cannot install Arch: error: key "9D4C5AA15426DA0A" could not be looked up remotely]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v38zcu/cannot_install_arch_error_key_9d4c5aa15426da0a/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v38zcu/cannot_install_arch_error_key_9d4c5aa15426da0a/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T13:33:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm trying to install Arch using a custom ISO built for my specific system, but the pacstrap command it fails with a bunch of key errors just like:
 error: key "9D4C5AA15426DA0A" could not be looked up remotely 
 The full command:
 pacstrap /mnt base base-devel nano zsh grml-zsh-config tlp dialog openssl-1.0 
 Is there any way to make Arch ignore signatures, or some other way to work around this problem?
    submitted by    /u/ScandicMinecraft  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conti ransomware targeted Intel firmware for stealthy attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/conti-ransomware-targeted-intel-firmware-for-stealthy-attacks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/conti-ransomware-targeted-intel-firmware-for-stealthy-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T13:22:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers analyzing the leaked chats of the notorious Conti ransomware operation have discovered that teams inside the Russian cybercrime group were actively developing firmware hacks. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deal With Difficult and Problematic Clients]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/?p=14628</id>
        <link href="https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/deal-with-clients/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T13:01:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The longer you stay in the freelancing trade, the more you will encounter a particular type of client, one of the 'difficult' variety. They are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajiv Sighamony</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Funzioni speciali del menu Start su Windows 11 e 10]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/06/funzioni-speciali-del-menu-start-su.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/06/funzioni-speciali-del-menu-start-su.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T13:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Il menu Start di Windows non è un semplice raccoglitore di applicazioni, ma può essere utile anche per accedere ad alcune impostazioni avanzate di Windows, senza doverle cercare all'interno del Pannello di controllo o dell'app Impostazioni. Per accedere  queste voci è sufficiente premere con il tasto destro del mouse sopra il menu Start o premere la scorciatoia WIN+X e selezionare la voce...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 7 Best Wireless Keyboards for Chromebooks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/116832/the-best-wireless-keyboards-for-chromebooks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/116832/the-best-wireless-keyboards-for-chromebooks/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T13:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chromebooks combine a simple, secure operating system with a sleek design, but the built-in keyboard isn’t for everyone. Investing in a wireless keyboard can add some extra oomph to your Chromebook setup and make using it even more enjoyable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Chaney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s the Difference Between a MacBook Air and Pro?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=806807</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/806807/difference-between-macbook-air-and-pro/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So you want to buy a MacBook, but you’re not sure whether to go Air or Pro. The most important question to ask yourself is: do you need extra power, or is portability more important to you?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What goes into maintaining an Arch system?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v384xb/what_goes_into_maintaining_an_arch_system/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v384xb/what_goes_into_maintaining_an_arch_system/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T12:48:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So, basically, I've had two issues with Ubuntu so far that are enough to annoy me off the platform, so I'm looking at other options. I'm not intimidated at all by the Arch installation process because it's literally just a set of instructions. 
 What I am concerned with is maintaining the machine. By that, I mean the following:
  
When I want to download something for "Linux," Ubuntu is always listed at the top. It's very easy. I sudo apt install or whatever else, and boom, I've got the program up and running. Is it equally easy to get software on Arch? Is there any branch of software at all (gaming, etc.) that will be even mildly annoying to get compared to Ubuntu?
 Will drivers work out of the gate or is that something that will need to be setup manually? I can list my specs if necessary, but that seems a bit presumptuous of me. The short version is: can I expect that if my machine/peripherals all run on Ubuntu, that they'll run on Arch?
 Is maintaining/updating my system easy? I straight up don't have to think about it on Ubuntu. I hit apt update, then sudo apt upgrade and I'm good to go.
  
Basically: the following scenario:
 I want to grab Lutris. Then I want to install League of Legends. After that, I want to get Rust setup. Then get Nitrogen for my wallpapers. Get Discord. Then, after leaving my computer up for a week like an idiot, I want to completely update my system (drivers, apps, git, whatever). Any chances for drivers/apps to brick because the latest update isn't good?
 Is any part of that more complicated than Ubuntu?
 Is there any part of the daily driving experience that will be more annoying on Arch or is everything post-installation streamlined and easy?
    submitted by    /u/directedgraphs  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clipminer malware gang stole $1.7M by hijacking crypto payments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/clipminer-malware-gang-stole-17m-by-hijacking-crypto-payments/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/clipminer-malware-gang-stole-17m-by-hijacking-crypto-payments/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T12:08:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat analysts have discovered a large operation of a new cryptocurrency mining malware called Clipminer that brought its operators at least $1.7 million from transaction hijacking. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Does Cold Weather Affect Electric Car Battery Life?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=804709</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/804709/cold-weather-electric-car-battery/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T12:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A chief concern about electric vehicles (EVs)—right up there with range anxiety and cost—is cold weather. We know the cold takes a toll on EV battery life, but why? Let’s look at what happens to an EV’s battery in cold weather, and the steps you can take to mitigate adverse effects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Bogna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[alsa/sound problems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v36xb0/alsasound_problems/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v36xb0/alsasound_problems/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T11:42:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[been having issues with every sound server and getting audio going on my ryzen system. everyything suggests it should work, thati s the wall i run into, theres nothing else to try or troubleshoot i know of.
 ​
 what happens when i aplay
 aplay foo.wav
 ALSA lib pcm_dmix.c:1032:(snd_pcm_dmix_open) unable to open slave
 aplay: main:831: audio open error: No such file or directory
 ​
 but when i aplay -l
 aplay -l
 **** List of PLAYBACK Hardware Devices ****
 card 0: HDMI [HDA ATI HDMI], device 3: HDMI 0 [HDMI 0]
 Subdevices: 1/1
 Subdevice #0: subdevice #0
 card 1: Generic [HD-Audio Generic], device 0: ALC892 Analog [ALC892 Analog]
 Subdevices: 1/1
 Subdevice #0: subdevice #0
 ​
 it lists my audio devices fine. it sees card 0, card 1. it can see the pcms.
 ​
 aplay -L
 null
 Discard all samp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux 5.19 Perf Changes Bring Three Notable AMD Features]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-Perf</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-Perf"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The perf events changes that landed last week for the Linux 5.19 kernel bring some exciting platform PMU updates on the AMD side while also supporting newer CPUs on the Intel side...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here is how to protect Windows PCs from Protocol vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178901</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/02/here-is-how-to-protect-windows-pcs-from-protocol-vulnerabilities/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T11:13:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two days ago, security researchers disclosed a vulnerability in the Microsoft Support Diagnostic Tool that affects all client and server versions of the Windows operating system. The tool, designed as a tool […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Here is how to protect Windows PCs from Protocol vulnerabilities appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Should You Buy a VR Headset?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=794893</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/794893/should-you-buy-a-vr-headset/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T11:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re looking to broaden your gaming horizons, you might be tempted to invest in a virtual reality headset. But VR isn’t simply an extension of the games you may already enjoy, it’s a whole new medium that comes with its own pros and cons.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Brookes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coreboot 4.17 Brings New Motherboards, AMD PSB, Doom Game Ported To Run As A Payload]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Coreboot-4.17</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Coreboot-4.17"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coreboot developers are releasing Coreboot 4.17 today with various new motherboards supported, support for GRUB2 atop SeaBIOS as a payload, and various low-level code improvements too. Plus Coreboot 4.17 brings the "coreDOOM" payload -- yes, it's possible to get the game Doom running atop this system firmware. There is also AMD Platform Secure Boot (PSB) support introduced to Coreboot too...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migliori ricevitori AirPlay per trasmettere da iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/06/migliori-ricevitori-airplay-per.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2022/06/migliori-ricevitori-airplay-per.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T10:07:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lo schermo degli iPhone vanta un livello di dettaglio decisamente molto elevato rispetto agli altri telefoni sul mercato, ma non può sicuramente competere con la qualità di uno schermo TV di ultima generazione. Anche dal punto di vista dell'audio la cassa speaker integrata nell'iPhone non offre la stessa resa sonora di un impianto home theater, di una soundbar o di un impianto Hi-Fi. 
Per poter...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Mine FLUX Coin Using GPU]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/?p=59977</id>
        <link href="https://www.hongkiat.com/blog/mine-flux-coin/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T10:01:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Flux is a GPU-mineable coin that is completely decentralized thanks to FluxNodes, which is located worldwide on enterprise-class hardware. Like other]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikita</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Surfshark VPN Review: Blood in the Water?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=808578</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/808578/surfshark-vpn-review/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T10:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Surfshark has grown in popularity following its acquisition by NordVPN and then with its announcement of the Nexus VPN standard. Product announcements aside, though, how good is Surfshark really, and are there noticeable traces of the takeover by NordVPN? I’ll take a look in this full review.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fergus O'Sullivan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fragment Shading Rate Extension Comes To OpenGL ES]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=OpenGL-ES-Fragment-Shading-Rate</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=OpenGL-ES-Fragment-Shading-Rate"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T09:46:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since 2020 the Vulkan API has offered a fragment shading rate extension for allowing games to provide higher levels of detail in a scene compared to other less important areas of the screen. Desktop OpenGL has also offered a fragment shading rate extension while this week a similar extension has been added for OpenGL ES...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NTFS-3G Driver For FUSE-Based NTFS Support Updated For Security Fixes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=NTFS-3G-2022.5.17</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=NTFS-3G-2022.5.17"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T09:32:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tuxera has issued its first new release of the NTFS-3G FUSE driver for NTFS read/write support on Linux and other platforms since last August's prior stable release. This new version was issued last week in order to ship security fixes...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PCI Changes Land In Linux 5.19 - Including Power Management Quirk For Intel DG2 Graphics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-PCI</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Linux-5.19-PCI"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T09:14:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The PCI subsystem changes have landed for the in-development Linux 5.19 kernel...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gettings key exists in xml but doesn't actually show up in gsettings after compiling.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3477q/gettings_key_exists_in_xml_but_doesnt_actually/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3477q/gettings_key_exists_in_xml_but_doesnt_actually/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T08:33:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My gnome is crashing because it can't find 'privacy-screen' in org.gnome.desktop.privacy. 
 Following this post I have verified that they key exists in /usr/share/glib-2.0/schemas/org.gnome.desktop.privacy.gschema.xml, and I ran sudo glib-compile-schemas /usr/share/glib-2.0/schemas. But gnome still crashes with the same error, and when I run gsettings get org.gnome.desktop.privacy sure enough there's no privacy-screen. I'm not familiar with gsettings, so I'd really appreciate any help.
 SOLVED: apparently there was something overwriting my XDG_DATA_DIRS so it was using different schemas
    submitted by    /u/revohour  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Foxconn confirms ransomware attack disrupted production in Mexico]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/foxconn-confirms-ransomware-attack-disrupted-production-in-mexico/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/foxconn-confirms-ransomware-attack-disrupted-production-in-mexico/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T08:20:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Foxconn electronics manufacturer has confirmed that one of its Mexico-based production plants has been impacted by a ransomware attack in late May. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitwarden's username generator now supports SimpleLogin, AnonAddy, and Firefox Relay email alias services]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178891</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/02/bitwardens-username-generator-now-supports-simplelogin-anonaddy-and-firefox-relay-email-alias-services/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T04:52:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitwarden has updated its browser extensions and Web Vault to improve its username generator. The cloud-based password manager introduced the feature in April 2022. What's new in Bitwarden 2022.05.0 Update Bitwarden now […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Bitwarden's username generator now supports SimpleLogin, AnonAddy, and Firefox Relay email alias services appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google is turning Meet and Duo into one voice and video calling application]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ghacks.net/?p=178892</id>
        <link href="https://www.ghacks.net/2022/06/02/google-is-turning-meet-and-duo-into-a-one-voice-and-video-calling-application/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T04:45:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google announced plans to merge the company's applications Meet and Duo into a single voice and video calling application. The company plans to keep the Google Meet name and the Google Duo […]
Thank you for being a Ghacks reader. The post Google is turning Meet and Duo into one voice and video calling application appeared first on gHacks Technology News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Brinkmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The microphone and Bluetooth are not working on an Acer laptop]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v30els/the_microphone_and_bluetooth_are_not_working_on/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v30els/the_microphone_and_bluetooth_are_not_working_on/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T04:10:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello \o
 Today, I installed the Arch with the latest ISO and, on the first boot, noticed I didn't have any sound whatsoever. I was able to get the audio output working by creating the /etc/modprobe.d/dsp.conf file and appending options snd_intel_dspcfg dsp_driver=1. Even so, the microphone is not detected. All I get in both alsamixer and pavucontrol is a monitor device, but not the micro.
 Also, my Bluetooth device isn't working. I installed bluez and even bluez-hid2hci, but the device is not detected. If I run bluetoothctl power on, I get the message No default controller available.
 The Bluetooth device does appear in dmesg logs:
 sudo dmesg | grep -i blue
 [ 1.480240] Bluetooth: Core ver 2.22
 [ 1.480255] NET: Registered PF_BLUETOOTH protocol family
 [ 1.480256] Bluetooth: HCI device a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ditching the Intel driver for modesetting: why? how? What about Wayland?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3079i/ditching_the_intel_driver_for_modesetting_why_how/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v3079i/ditching_the_intel_driver_for_modesetting_why_how/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T03:58:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm preparing a new Linux install on a Lenovo X1 Fold with a i5-L16G7 CPU: it's essentially a mobile 10th generation Ice Lake core without AVX512 called Sunny Cove.
 My goal is a Wayland install, mostly for the foot terminal: I want to do terminal things with a wireless keyboard outside Msys2/Windows Terminal. I also want to try how touchscreen stuff works on Gnome.
 I started by reading a bit about what to do as the X1 Fold (with a weird CPU, OLED touchscreen no physical mouse or keyboard...) is a bit exotic. This may have caused a few issues in Ubuntu 22.04, like no backlight control, i915 not being able to claim the display in lshw -C video...
 Still, it's such a cool device I still want to try to make it work on Linux.
 I've tried a lot of different kernel cmdline flags. They helped a bit for various things, but while waiting for my custom kernel to compile I've decided a best use of my time would be to try returning to Arch to do things the right way from the start!
 I found this post from libcg (account now deleted) which is very interesting given my i915 problems: https://web.archive.org/web/20160714232204/https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/4cojj9/it_is_probably_time_to_ditch_xf86videointel/
 In practice, on a new install for a 10th gen Ice Lake, would you chose to use modesetting over Intel driver? Even on Wayland?
 I understand you must still use drm+i915, but what else should I keep or install for video acceleration say on youtube?
    submitted by    /u/csdvrx  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pacman invalid or corrupted database (PGP Signature)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2zyad/pacman_invalid_or_corrupted_database_pgp_signature/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2zyad/pacman_invalid_or_corrupted_database_pgp_signature/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T03:44:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, trying to do "sudo pacman -Syu" on my desktop running arch returned :
 error: GPGME error: No data
 error: GPGME error: No data
 error: GPGME error: No data
 error: GPGME error: No data
 :: Synchronising package databases...
 core 155.5 KiB 219 KiB/s 00:01 [####################################] 100%
 extra 1729.6 KiB 361 KiB/s 00:05 [####################################] 100%
 community 6.6 MiB 364 KiB/s 00:19 [####################################] 100%
 multilib 172.6 KiB 336 KiB/s 00:01 [####################################] 100%
 error: GPGME error: No data
 error: GPGME error: No data
 error: GPGME error: No data
 error: GPGME error: No data
 error: failed to synchronize all databases (invalid or corrupted database (PGP signature))
 ​
 After searching around for a solution, what worked was either removing the <*.db.sig> files from /var/lib/pacman/sync or deleting the sync folder and letting it regenerate WITHOUT the .sig files by running pacman -Syu.
 However, editing de Siglevel to Required (removing the DatabaseOptional option), this no longer works. For this reason and from the research I had done, I was worried this solution leaves my system vulnerable so I decided to check if the arch install on my laptop, which was pretty much a fresh install only a couple of weeks old, had those .sig files.
 To my surprise, not only were those files missing, but I got the exact same error from "sudo pacman -Syu" as I did on my desktop, despite the fact that removing those same files on the desktop had been the solution there.
 Could anyone help me make sense of this, and help me fix the issue without leaving my systems vulnerable? Thank you very much
    submitted by    /u/IdontPlayTheTrombone  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Need help debugging a curl/SSL/Plexamp issue]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2we0d/need_help_debugging_a_curlsslplexamp_issue/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2we0d/need_help_debugging_a_curlsslplexamp_issue/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T00:44:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At some point in May, the Plexamp Appimage stopped working entirely. Checking Plexamp's logs, it says:
 [Javascript] INFO - Auth: Requesting PIN. [0x0513ba40] DEBUG - Networking: Create request 2: (POST https://plex.tv/api/v2/pins?strong=true). [0xf61fb640] DEBUG - Networking: Completed request 2: (POST https://plex.tv/api/v2/pins?strong=true) with code -59 (have 0 bytes) in 146 ms. [Javascript] ERROR - Auth: Could not get PIN HTTP status -59 
 cURL's manual states code 59 means it cannot use the selected SSL cipher (whatever that may be). 
 The Plexamp Appimage doesn't seem to be at fault as it hadn't been updated before it broke and it works without issue on an xUbuntu 21.10 machine I have. Additionally, although I'm running Arch, I grabbed the latest Manjaro daily build as well as a build from April and threw them into a VM for testing. Plexamp had no issues with the build from April but the daily build exhibited the same behavior as Arch, cURL code -59.
 Worth noting the Flatpak version of Plexamp works as expected, but Plexamp by default doesn't have a titlebar and I only had success force enabling it with the Appimage version.
 Tried downgrading OpenSSL and cURL but had no luck. I'm not sure where to go from here, especially since I thought Appimages contained all the required dependencies and wouldn't rely on system packages. Any suggestions would be appreciated.
    submitted by    /u/CarelessSpark  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch Linux Hits Top Linux Spot Over Ubuntu In May's Steam Survey]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Steam-Survey-May-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Steam-Survey-May-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T00:40:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Steam Survey results are in for May 2022 and while it shows Linux slightly down on a percentage basis, it shows a new top-spot for the most popular Linux distribution unseating Ubuntu LTS...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Is Activity Status Not Showing on Instagram?]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=pitch&amp;p=489573</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15344575/activity-status-not-showing-instagram"/>
        <updated>2022-06-02T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just like on Facebook, it’s possible to view when someone was last active on Instagram. The feature was introduced back in 2018 and proved quite popular with users on the network. However, as you might have noticed yourself, sometimes a user’s “Activity Status” can be hidden or unavailable. This post examine all the reasons you can’t see when someone was last active on Instagram and offers a few tips to fix it.
   

Content

How to Tell When Someone Was Last Active on Instagram
1. They Are Not Following You
2. They Don’t Have Activity Status Turned On
3. You Don’t Have the Activity Status Enabled
4. You’ve Never Sent Them a Direct Message
5. The 25 Conversations Rule
6. You’ve Been Restricted
7. You’ve Been Blocked
What to Do If You Can’t See “Activity Status” on Instagram
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Rearrange Photos in an... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexandra Arici</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mesa 22.1.1 Released With Many Open-Source Graphics Driver Fixes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Mesa-22.1.1-Released</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Mesa-22.1.1-Released"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T23:58:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last month marked the debut of Mesa 22.1 as the newest quarterly release to this open-source Linux graphics driver stack. For those that prefer waiting until the first point release before upgrading, today is the day with Mesa 22.1.1 now available...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Windows Search zero-day added to Microsoft protocol nightmare]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-windows-search-zero-day-added-to-microsoft-protocol-nightmare/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-windows-search-zero-day-added-to-microsoft-protocol-nightmare/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T22:06:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new Windows Search zero-day vulnerability can be used to automatically open a search window containing remotely-hosted malware executables simply by launching a Word document. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Abrams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use S Pen Like a Pro on Samsung Galaxy Phones]]></title>
        <id>http://maketecheasier.com/?p=63743</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15344400/tips-and-tricks-to-using-the-s-pen-stylus"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[S Pen can be incredible useful accessory for your Samsung Galaxy phone or tablet. Whether you’re using the S Pen as a remote control, copying text, taking handwritten notes, or creating GIFs, the stylus can significantly enhance your experience while using your device. This post aims to help you get most of the S Pen on Samsung Galaxy phones and tablets.
   

Content

1. Open Air Command Menu in Multiple Ways
2. Scroll Using S Pen
3. Preview Image or Videos
4. Read Notifications and Messages
5. Select and Copy Text
6. Select Multiple Items Using S Pen
7. Take Notes on Lock Screen
8. Pin Notes to Always-on Display
9. Create a Note When You Remove S Pen
10. Take Notes on Any Screen
11. Write on Screenshot
12. Annotate a PDF
13. Write Using S Pen in Any App
14. Take Advantage of Smart Select
15. Extract Text
16. Create GIFs Using S Pen
17. Use S Pen to Translate Text
18. Listen to Text
19. Use the Glance Tool
20. Magnify Text Using S Pen
21. Search for Similar Images
22. Launch Camera Quickly
23. Use S Pen as... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mehvish Mushtaq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Import Data From a PDF to Microsoft Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=770474</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/770474/how-to-import-data-from-a-pdf-to-microsoft-excel/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you have a PDF document such as a bank statement or financial report, you may want to pull this information into Microsoft Excel. With a built-in feature, you can easily import and automatically convert a PDF to Excel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8bitdo controller issues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2r6tv/8bitdo_controller_issues/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2r6tv/8bitdo_controller_issues/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T20:55:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey I just bought an 8bitdo pro 2 wired gamepad, and I cannot get steam, or retroArch to detect it. when I do "Lsusb" it shows up, but nothing detects it, I've been looking online for solutions but I havent found anything. Thanks!
    submitted by    /u/Tetlus  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Is Raising Prices on Ring Protect Basic Subscriptions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=808929</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/808929/amazon-is-raising-prices-on-ring-protect-basic-subscriptions/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T20:49:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon-owned Ring sells some of the most popular video doorbells, and the Ring Protect Basic subscription offers video storage in the cloud and other features. Now prices for the subscription are going up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Glitchy/Corrupt Desktop after the last update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2qyj6/glitchycorrupt_desktop_after_the_last_update/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2qyj6/glitchycorrupt_desktop_after_the_last_update/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T20:45:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi. After I updated my arch installation today and restarted, I started to get a very strange glitching effect on my desktop. It happens at random but consistent places, like my panel and on application previews. The glitch is not visible on screenshots. I've tried reinstalling the Nvidia drivers, but that didn't help. Dmesg and the journal report no problem. Iv'e also reset my Xorg config, but that also didn't help. It's also not related to gnome extentions.
 https://imgur.com/a/sMbY24R
 The problem is not hardware related, as it is completely fine in console and bios.
 I'm running GNOME 42.1 on X11 with nvidia proprietary drivers 515.43.04. 
 Edit: Forgot to mention OpenGL applications are also broken with the message:
  
X Error of failed request: BadWindow (invalid Window parameter) 
 Major opcode of failed request: 156 (NV-GLX) 
 Minor opcode of failed request: 4 () 
 Resource id in failed request: 0x3800002 
 Serial number of failed request: 45 
 Current serial number in output stream: 45
  
​
    submitted by    /u/IndependentCrow-448  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MESA-LOADER - Problem to run flatpak app]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2qrjf/mesaloader_problem_to_run_flatpak_app/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2qrjf/mesaloader_problem_to_run_flatpak_app/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T20:36:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am getting this error when I try to run Frog, an Flatpak app.
 ​
 ​
 $ flatpak run com.github.tenderowl.frog
 libEGL warning: MESA-LOADER: failed to retrieve device information
 ​
 libEGL warning: DRI2: could not open /dev/dri/card0 (Arquivo ou diretório inexistente)
 libGL error: MESA-LOADER: failed to retrieve device information
 Cache downloaded codes: ['eng']
 No provider of glGetShaderiv found. Requires one of:
 Desktop OpenGL 2.0
 OpenGL ES 2.0
 ​
 Someone can help me to fix it?
 ​
    submitted by    /u/anderson_szr  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former OpenSea head of product charged with NFT insider trading]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/former-opensea-head-of-product-charged-with-nft-insider-trading/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/former-opensea-head-of-product-charged-with-nft-insider-trading/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T20:21:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nathaniel Chastain, a former product manager at OpenSea, the largest online non-fungible token (NFT) marketplace, has been arrested and charged by the U.S. Department of Justice (DOJ) with NFT insider trading. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Google Pixel Watch Won't Outlast Your Fitbit's Battery]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119790/the-google-pixel-watch-wont-outlast-your-fitbits-battery/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119790/the-google-pixel-watch-wont-outlast-your-fitbits-battery/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T20:10:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People are really overestimating the Pixel Watch’s capabilities, likely because it’s backed by several years of rumors and hype. And while we don’t really know all of the Pixel Watch’s specs, it probably doesn’t have a crazy battery life. Yeah, I’m making an educated guess, but it’s backed by a recent 9to5Google report.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stop Closing Apps on Your Android Phone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=771413</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/771413/stop-closing-apps-on-your-android-phone/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since its birth, Android has had to deal with one big misconception. Some phone makers have even helped perpetuate this myth. The truth is you do not need to kill Android apps. In fact, closing apps can make things worse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Where should I report this Bug?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2prmx/where_should_i_report_this_bug/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2prmx/where_should_i_report_this_bug/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T19:54:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Title says it all: I've found a bug and im unsure where to report it.
 When in install gdm, gnome-terminal, gnome-themes-extra and gnome-control-center, restart into gnome and open the control center, i cannot change any settings...
 I managed a few installes where I install the packages one by one and everything works fine. Maybe it's a gnome issue, maybe it's only on arch, where should i go to report this?
    submitted by    /u/Zacki_404  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Is Mixing up Its Video Chat Apps Again]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=808900</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/808900/google-is-mixing-up-its-video-chat-apps-again/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T19:45:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google currently has two apps for video and audio calls, Meet and Duo, but soon the company will combine them into a new Google Meet application.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iwd can't see my home Wi-Fi network.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2payc/iwd_cant_see_my_home_wifi_network/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2payc/iwd_cant_see_my_home_wifi_network/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T19:35:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My internet was working fine, connecting automatically through iwd and whatnot.
 Then, out of nowhere, my AP stopped showing when I scan and get-networks, other SSIDs do show, but my home one doesn't. 
 I can, by the way, connect to it through my phone, a laptop, and other phones in the house, just not my Linux client.
 Being able to see other SSIDs means that the problem isn't iwd, nor is it my Wi-Fi dongle, but my router/modem/ap, but I'm not sure, because it works fine with every other device.
    submitted by    /u/BraveWinner  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save 33% on a YOREPEK Travel Backpack, Extra Large, with USB Port]]></title>
        <id>https://admin.maketecheasier.com/?post_type=deal&amp;p=494272</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/15344260/yorepek-travel-backpack"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re planning on taking your laptop and other devices with you during your summer plans, you’ll want the YOREPEK Travel Backpack. This extra-large bag has a USB port, fits a 17″ laptop, and is TSA approved. Buy it now for 33% off, and if you do it soon enough, Prime members can still get it delivered today.
    
Inside the 18″ x 13.5″ x 6.5″ large capacity bag, there are three spacious sections, with one of them roomy enough for a 17″ laptop. Another one will fit your daily needs, such as a change of clothes, portable charger, etc. The front section has small pockets to hold pens, a stylus, and cords, with a special spot for your keys as well so that these items are always at hand. There are also two side mesh pockets for water bottles and similar items.
    

    
The YOREPEK Travel Backpack is TSA approved and can be fully unfolded 90 to 180 degrees, which allows it to pass through security quickly while still keeping everything... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Command to show usage of apps?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2oyng/command_to_show_usage_of_apps/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2oyng/command_to_show_usage_of_apps/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T19:19:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi,
 Is there a command/application to show the frequence/usage of installed programms?
 Something like, "spent 20h in firefox"
 Thanks in advance
    submitted by    /u/len1315  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GM's 2023 Chevy Bolt EV Gets a Massive Price Cut]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119782/gms-2023-chevy-bolt-ev-gets-a-massive-price-cut/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119782/gms-2023-chevy-bolt-ev-gets-a-massive-price-cut/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T19:16:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These days EV manufacturers like Tesla and Rivian are raising the prices of vehicles at an alarming rate, but GM decided to do the complete opposite. The already affordable Chevy Bolt EV and EUV just received a massive price cut for the 2023 models.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Which Smart TV Should You Buy: Roku, Fire, or Google]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119734/which-smart-tv-should-you-buy-roku-fire-or-google/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119734/which-smart-tv-should-you-buy-roku-fire-or-google/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T19:15:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When talking about TVs, we tend to only focus on specs and pricing. But a smart TV’s operating system is also quite important. For most people, this operating system is the springboard for streaming content, discovering new shows, or even controlling a smart home. But with so many options to choose from, which smart TV OS is best?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hundreds of Elasticsearch databases targeted in ransom attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hundreds-of-elasticsearch-databases-targeted-in-ransom-attacks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hundreds-of-elasticsearch-databases-targeted-in-ransom-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T19:13:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A campaign targeting poorly secured Elasticsearch databases has deleted their contents and dropped ransom notes on 450 instances, demanding a payment of $620 to give them back their indexes, totaling a demand of $279,000. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Yield Farming in DeFi?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=804073</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/804073/what-is-yield-farming-in-defi/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T19:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi promises to eliminate the need for banks almost entirely. Known as yield farmers, holders of a cryptocurrency can earn yields by serving the same role that banks traditionally did. Here’s how it works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>RJ Fulton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IO_uring Continues Advancing In 2022 With New Features For Pushing Linux I/O]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=KR2022-IO_uring</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=KR2022-IO_uring"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Kernel Recipes 2022 conference kicked off today in Paris, France. Kicking off the event was Linux block subsystem maintainer and lead IO_uring developer Jens Axboe to talk about all of the recent and ongoing work around this major advancement to Linux I/O in recent years...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[keeping user accounts in sync across multiple btrfs root subvolumes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2odm9/keeping_user_accounts_in_sync_across_multiple/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2odm9/keeping_user_accounts_in_sync_across_multiple/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T18:54:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m looking for advice on how to keep the user accounts in sync across multiple btrfs subvolumes on the same ssd—usernames, passwords, etc. I’ve read about LDAP configuration, but since this would all be local, I was wondering if LDAP was the right way forward.
 My use case is I have a “recovery” subvolume for “ / “that I leave unaltered, and a “system” subvolume for “ / “ that’s for regular use. However, changes to the user on one are not reflected in the other.
    submitted by    /u/wohnonono  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This issue has bested me]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2ocdl/this_issue_has_bested_me/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2ocdl/this_issue_has_bested_me/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T18:52:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I bought a clone wireless x360 controller and I couldn't get my laptop to see it as a wireless x360 controller. Usb_modeswitch didn't work no matter what I did. Xpad, xpadneo, xow, xone were tested and none of those worked too. The computer thinks it's a goddamn nintendo switch pro controller through the dongle but it's seen as a generic x360 controller when connected with the cable. I am completely stumped it's been at least painful 1.5 months trying to fix this. I had it working as it should on Ubuntu and Linux Mint. But I can't make it work on arch.
 Edit: thank you, you beautiful bastards, I tried what worked on mint live boot and it works on arch now
    submitted by    /u/crippl3r  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FBI seizes domains used to sell stolen data, DDoS services]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fbi-seizes-domains-used-to-sell-stolen-data-ddos-services/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fbi-seizes-domains-used-to-sell-stolen-data-ddos-services/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T18:46:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) and the U.S. Department of Justice announced today the seizure of three domains used by cybercriminals to sell personal info stolen in data breaches and to provide DDoS attack services. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[systemd-udev throwing a ton of errors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2ntww/systemdudev_throwing_a_ton_of_errors/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2ntww/systemdudev_throwing_a_ton_of_errors/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T18:30:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm running archlinux with nvidia drivers. When I look at journalctl, I find that systemd-udev is throwing a ton of errors. Can someone please help me debug this. I can use my system just fine. There is no noticeable impact of these errors, but I would still like to clear these out if I can.
 ​
 # uname -a Linux acerarch 5.17.9-arch1-1 #1 SMP PREEMPT Wed, 18 May 2022 17:30:11 +0000 x86_64 GNU/Linux # pacman -Qs local/cuda 11.6.2-1 NVIDIA's GPU programming toolkit local/cuda-tools 11.6.2-1 NVIDIA's GPU programming toolkit (extra tools: nvvp, nsight, samples) local/egl-wayland 2:1.1.9+r3+g582b2d3-1 EGLStream-based Wayland external platform local/libvdpau 1.5-1 Nvidia VDPAU library local/libxnvctrl 515.43.04-1 NVIDIA NV-CONTROL X extension local/nvidia 515.43.04-7 NVIDIA drivers for linux local/nvidia-lts 1:515.43.04-8 NVIDIA drivers for linux-lts local/nvidia-prime 1.0-4 NVIDIA Prime Render Offload configuration and utilities local/nvidia-settings 515.43.04-1 Tool for configuring the NVIDIA graphics driver local/nvidia-utils 515.43.04-2 NVIDIA drivers utilities local/opencl-nvidia 515.43.04-2 OpenCL implemention for NVIDIA # journalctl -p 3 -xb Output link below since it was too big for this post. # systemctl --failed UNIT LOAD ACTIVE SUB DESCRIPTION 0 loaded units listed. 
 Journalctl output at https://pastebin.com/RSTfujfS
 My machine is an Acer Predator Helios 300 laptop. Also I am using auto-cpufreq. Also, I'm dual booting archlinux with Windows 11.
    submitted by    /u/pr0_Disappointment  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[how to make sure kde plasma splash screen runs for a specific number of seconds before desktop starts up]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2nrj9/how_to_make_sure_kde_plasma_splash_screen_runs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2nrj9/how_to_make_sure_kde_plasma_splash_screen_runs/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T18:27:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is there any way to configure my start up via sddm in such a way that the splash screen animation gets completed atleast by setting some user defined time intervals. Currently I am unable to see what goes on in the splash screen as the desktop loads really fast. It's a not super important factor but I would love to know if it's possible in some way.
    submitted by    /u/Kknsr  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Etcher now needs sudo privileges?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2nfkl/etcher_now_needs_sudo_privileges/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2nfkl/etcher_now_needs_sudo_privileges/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T18:13:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've written many iso USB sticks (I do the Arch Linux one every month just so I have a up to date USB stick handy). Well, last month and this month I have been unable to write to USB sticks without becoming sudo. Did something change with etcher or is it something in Arch? I'm not sure. I'm thinking it's something with etcher. I installed imagewriter just to try that one out but nope, I have to run that as sudo too. 
 Did something change with user permissions or something? I know I had no issues in April when I mad 4 USB sticks for friends who wanted to try Arch (They love it BTW). I'm confused as to what happened. 
 Why am I no longer able to write iso files to USB sticks without becoming sudo?
    submitted by    /u/Phydoux  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unable to edit /etc/locale.gen]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2n9zc/unable_to_edit_etclocalegen/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2n9zc/unable_to_edit_etclocalegen/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T18:06:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, I am following the arch installation guide: https://wiki.archlinux.org/title/Installation_guide and I am at the step where I need to edit the locale.gen file. I have chroot'ed into the new system and used pacman -S vim and it says it installed correctly however when I try use vim to edit locale.gen I get the error: 
 vim: error while loading shared libraries: libperl.so: cannot open object file: no such file or directory
    submitted by    /u/Glum_Ad7879  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Twitter Circle, and Should You Use It?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=808813</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/808813/what-is-twitter-circle-and-should-you-use-it/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T18:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter makes it easy to blast your thoughts out for everyone to see. However, you may not always want all your followers to see every single tweet. That’s where a feature called “Twitter Circle” comes in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Launches New Silicon Design Portal For Open-Source Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Google-Open-Silicon-Portal</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Google-Open-Silicon-Portal"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has been helping small open-source projects get started in chip fabrication with Google covering the costs and partnering with SkyWater Technology using their open-source process design kit (PDK). While the chip manufacturing is done on a 130nm process (SKY130), this effort has proven to be a big success for open-source hardware projects with limited funding and Google today announced a new silicon design portal...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch Linux STM32 SDK & IDE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2mxnx/arch_linux_stm32_sdk_ide/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2mxnx/arch_linux_stm32_sdk_ide/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T17:53:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone, is there an SDK and IDE for STM32 development for Linux. Currently now I use arm-none-eabi GCC toolchain and openocd for firmware upload. Is there any thing like SDK? It would be good but if there isn't any, I would write my one via documentation
    submitted by    /u/nikolaytihonov  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Surface Laptop Go 2 Is Microsoft’s New Budget Windows 11 PC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=808888</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/808888/surface-laptop-go-2-is-microsofts-new-budget-windows-11-pc/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T17:22:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The original Surface Laptop Go was one of the best laptops for students and anyone else not interested in dropping $1,000 or more on a PC. Now the laptop has received a much-needed upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US govt: Paying Karakurt extortion ransoms won’t stop data leaks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-govt-paying-karakurt-extortion-ransoms-won-t-stop-data-leaks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-govt-paying-karakurt-extortion-ransoms-won-t-stop-data-leaks/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T17:09:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several U.S. federal agencies warned organizations today against paying ransom demands made by the Karakurt gang since that will not prevent their stolen data from being sold to others.  [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTG Deals: Get Our Favorite Earbuds for Just $28, Plus More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=808883</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/808883/htg-deals-get-our-favorite-earbuds-for-just-28-plus-more/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T17:09:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the first day of June! To kick off the new month, we’ve assembled an awesome array of deals for your buying pleasure. Enjoy savings on Apple Watch Series 7, Microsoft Surface Duo 2, an Amazon eero 6 mesh Wi-Fi 6 router, our Editor’s Choice UGREEN HiTune T3 Earbuds, and one of our favorite Amazon Fire TV televisions of 2022. Continue on for details!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zach Laidlaw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Buick Teases Stunning Wildcat EV Concept As it Shifts to Electric]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119740/buick-teases-stunning-wildcat-ev-concept-as-it-shifts-to-electric/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119740/buick-teases-stunning-wildcat-ev-concept-as-it-shifts-to-electric/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T17:09:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Buick, the well-known American automaker owned by General Motors, just unveiled its Wildcat EV concept to help tease its all-electric future. The stunning Fastback coupe certainly doesn’t look like an old person’s car, something many think of when hearing the Buick name.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Upgrade to latest Nextcloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2lr83/upgrade_to_latest_nextcloud/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2lr83/upgrade_to_latest_nextcloud/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T17:02:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone. I've been running an old version of Nextcloud (20.x.x) because it wouldn't work with php8. So I stuck my head in the sand and now I've come up for air and noticed that the dependencies for nextcloud 23 in the repositories has php8. I've currently have this line in my pacman.conf:
 IgnorePkg = nextcloud php php-apache php-apcu php-cgi php-dblib php-igbinary php-imagick php-imap php-intl php-memcached perl
 If I remove this line am I going to mess up everything?
    submitted by    /u/PhantomNomad  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up Voice Access on Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=806979</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/806979/how-to-set-up-voice-access-on-windows-11/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Voice controls are everywhere now. They’re ubiquitous in TVs, smartphones, and cars, and they’re increasingly common in household appliances. Windows 11 also includes the ability to control your computer with your voice. All you need is a microphone and some practice. Here’s how to set up Windows Speech Recognition.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Lewis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lampada LED smart da soffitto con ventilatore integrato: si comanda via Bluetooth]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Lampada-LED-smart-da-soffitto-con-ventilatore-integrato-si-comanda-via-Bluetooth_24594</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Lampada-LED-smart-da-soffitto-con-ventilatore-integrato-si-comanda-via-Bluetooth_24594"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T16:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Il mercato offre un numero sempre crescente di dispositivi per la smart home che possono essere gestiti a distanza utilizzando lo smartphone o i comandi vocali.La lampada LED smart da soffitto con ventilatore è in offerta fino al prossimo 30 giugno a soli 69,99 euro con spedizione dai magazzini europei.Si tratta di un oggetto circolare installabile a soffitto, di diametro pari a 54 cm e spessore di circa 18 cm, che permette di illuminare l'ambiente grazie alla lampada LED integrata e alla possibilità di scegliere tra tre diverse temperature di colore: 3000K, 4500K e 6000K. In questo modo si può ottenere una luce calda, un bianco neutro o oppure una luce più fredda.

Tutti i parametri sono regolabili mediante l'app su smartphone: la connessione con la lampada smart avviene infatti via Bluetooth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RuneScape phishing steals accounts and in-game item bank PINs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/runescape-phishing-steals-accounts-and-in-game-item-bank-pins/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/runescape-phishing-steals-accounts-and-in-game-item-bank-pins/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T16:39:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered a new RuneScape-themed phishing campaign, and it stands out among the various operations for being exceptionally well-crafted. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Toulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft's Affordable Surface Laptop Go 2 Promises Repairability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119714/microsofts-affordable-surface-laptop-go-2-promises-repairability/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119714/microsofts-affordable-surface-laptop-go-2-promises-repairability/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T16:21:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The original Surface Laptop Go launched in 2020 as a sort of Chromebook competitor. And while it looked really pretty for a $550 device, the pricing was actually a bit awkward. Now, Microsoft is back with the $600 Surface Laptop Go 2, a repairable laptop with specs that more appropriately match the MSRP.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel Makes Another Exciting Software Acquisition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-Acquires-Codeplay</id>
        <link href="https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=Intel-Acquires-Codeplay"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T16:12:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in February Intel announced it was acquiring Linutronix as the folks maintaining real-time Linux (PREEMPT_RT) and other prominent Linux contributions. Today Intel announced another exciting software acquisition for bolstering their open ecosystem...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phoronix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google TV Arrives on iPhone to Help You Find Your Next Show]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=808826</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/808826/google-tv-arrives-on-iphone-to-help-you-find-your-next-show/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T16:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google TV is the new(ish) brand for all of Google’s entertainment offerings, but the old ‘Google Play Movies & TV’ name was sticking around on the iPhone and iPad. At long last, Apple devices can use the newer Google TV app.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Switching Between iPhone and Android Is Easier Than You Think]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=805224</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/805224/switching-between-iphone-and-android-isnt-a-big-deal/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T16:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[iPhone vs. Android is one of the biggest rivalries in the tech world. Switching between the platforms is not something people take lightly. I recently made the switch, and you know what? It’s really not that big of a deal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Fedewa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Mac App Is Great for People With Short Attention Spans]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=798968</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/798968/working-from-home-boost-your-productivity-with-setapp-for-mac/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T15:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Working from home has become wildly popular over the past few years, but it has also introduced us to challenges we hadn’t considered. Pets, projects around the house, random distractions on the internet — all serve to deter focus and hamper productivity. Can a suite of work-focused apps help you get back on track? We’ll discuss how to stay productive while working from home with Setapp, a popular subscription service with more than 200 incredible apps for Mac.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sponsored</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows MSDT zero-day vulnerability gets free unofficial patch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/windows-msdt-zero-day-vulnerability-gets-free-unofficial-patch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/windows-msdt-zero-day-vulnerability-gets-free-unofficial-patch/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T15:31:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A free unofficial patch is now available to block ongoing attacks against Windows systems that target a critical zero-day vulnerability known as 'Follina.' [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergiu Gatlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung Galaxy Z Fold 4 Leak Teases Huge Camera Upgrades]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119712/samsung-galaxy-z-fold-4-leak-teases-huge-camera-upgrades/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119712/samsung-galaxy-z-fold-4-leak-teases-huge-camera-upgrades/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T15:29:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we draw closer to a release date for Samsung’s next foldable phone, the Galaxy Z Fold 4, we’re getting new rumors about the device. And while we know plenty about it already, the latest Galaxy Z Fold 4 leaks suggest some huge camera upgrades—both inside and out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Beginner’s Guide to Using Cron in Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maketecheasier.com/?p=276787</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.maketecheasier.com/link/12555/10892137/beginner-guide-use-cron-linux"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T15:25:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cron is a simple UNIX utility that manages and schedules the execution of commands in your computer. It was first developed in 1987 by Paul Vixie and it has since become an invaluable tool in Linux-based operating systems for both administrators and users alike.
    
Nowadays, there are a number of cron implementations and rewrites that you can easily install in your Linux system. Despite the differences, these programs all share the same Vixie Cron lineage.
    
As such, this article aims to provide a basic overview of how the original Vixie cron works, its syntax, and how you can use it to schedule tasks in your Linux system.
   

Content

How Does Cron Work?
Crontab: The Heart of Cron
System Crontabs
Reviewing cron activity
Frequently Asked Questions

.toc{background-color:#f3f4f6;font-size:16px;font-weight:500;padding:1em;}.toc h4{text-align:center;text-transform:uppercase;font-size:0.9375rem;margin-bottom:1rem;}.toc ul{margin:0;padding:0;font-size:15px;}.toc-content{overflow-y:auto;max-height:600px;}.toc-content li{list-style:none!important;margin-bottom:1em;}.toc-content a{color:rgba(74,85,104,var(--text-opacity));text-decoration:none;}.toc-content a:hover{color:#C72F29;}.toc-content li.active a{color:#C72F29;font-weight:bold;}@media (min-width:1340px){.toc-wrap{position:absolute;float:left;margin-left:-9rem;top:0;left:-90px;height:100%;width:200px;background-color:white;}.toc{position:sticky;top:50px;font-size:14px;padding:0.5em;}.toc-content li{margin-bottom:0.5em;}}   
Also read:How to Easily Create Cron jobs in Linux with... Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramces Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xbox Steals PlayStation's Best Trophy Feature]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119703/xbox-steals-playstations-best-trophy-feature/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119703/xbox-steals-playstations-best-trophy-feature/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T15:06:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gamers get hyped! Microsoft just revealed a long-awaited (and highly demanded) achievement feature for its Xbox consoles in its June 2022 update, and we’re certain gamers of all varieties, especially achievement hunters, will be incredibly excited about it!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzanne Humphries</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make a Bubble Chart in Microsoft Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=804965</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/804965/bubble-chart-excel/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T15:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you want to display three data series on a type of scatter plot, then a bubble chart is the ideal choice. We’ll show you how to organize your data and create a bubble chart in Microsoft Excel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandy Writtenhouse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix's Anti-Account Sharing Test Is Confusing Customers and Employees]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/119694/netflixs-anti-account-sharing-test-is-confusing-customers-and-employees/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/119694/netflixs-anti-account-sharing-test-is-confusing-customers-and-employees/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T14:50:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix wants to crack down on password sharing. And to prepare for this unpopular new policy, it’s running an anti-account sharing “pilot program” in Chile, Costa Rica, and Peru. But the test is going about as well as you’d expect. Neither customers nor employees seem to understand what’s going on.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Heinzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Murena One, smartphone Android senza i servizi Google. Un valore aggiunto per gli ideatori del progetto]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Murena-One-smartphone-Android-senza-i-servizi-Google-Un-valore-aggiunto-per-gli-ideatori-del-progetto_24593</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Murena-One-smartphone-Android-senza-i-servizi-Google-Un-valore-aggiunto-per-gli-ideatori-del-progetto_24593"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T14:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Huawei è l'azienda che forse più di tutti ha investito sulla creazione di un ecosistema alternativo a quello di Google: con HMS Core l'azienda ha proposto una valida alternativa lasciando comunque agli sviluppatori la facoltà di creare applicazioni Android compatibili anche con i servizi dell'azienda di Mountain View.L'ideatore della nota distribuzione Mandrake Linux, Gaël Duval, ha presentato il suo Murena One, uno smartphone che vuole distinguersi per l'impegno sul piano della tutela della privacy e dei dati degli utenti.Duval racconta di aver sviluppato il sistema operativo sul quale si basa Murena One stanco del duopolio Android-iOS e della massiccia raccolta di dati che viene posta in essere.Non aspettatevi però di trovare Linux all'interno di Murena One: lo smartphone poggia il suo funzionamento su un fork di Android chiamato /e/ che abbina buona parte del codice sorgente del progetto Google AOSP (Android Open Source Project) con quello di LineageOS, una delle ROM più apprezzate.

Nel sistema /e/ la maggior parte dei servizi Google (non tutti) vengono sostituiti con delle implementazioni open source totalmente svincolate dal lavoro dell'azienda di Mountain View.Ci sono ad esempio librerie e app che forniscono servizi di mappe, geolocalizzazione, messaggistica, uno store basato sul repository non ufficiale Clean APK e così via.Gli utenti possono ovviamente installare la maggior parte delle app di Google e le migliaia di quelle esistenti per Android.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[App per il Rooting di quasi tutti gli smartphone Android (Samsung, Xiaomi e altri)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.navigaweb.net/2014/03/root-are-quasi-tutti-gli-smartphone.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.navigaweb.net/2014/03/root-are-quasi-tutti-gli-smartphone.html"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T14:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Il Root di Android è la procedura di sblocco dei permessi del sistema operativo per usarlo come amministratore. Usare come amministratore uno smartphone o un tablet Android significa poterlo usare come un vero computer, senza limitazioni. Questo permette di personalizzare il sistema a proprio piacimento, di installare le app che sfruttano il root e installare una Custom ROM, ossia cambiare...


Continua a leggere su Navigaweb.net (clicca sul titolo)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navigaweb.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anker 757 PowerHouse Battery Review: Crazy Fast and Powerful]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reviewgeek.com/118973/anker-757-powerhouse-battery-review-crazy-fast-and-powerful/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reviewgeek.com/118973/anker-757-powerhouse-battery-review-crazy-fast-and-powerful/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T14:24:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you go on outdoor adventures and camping trips or live somewhere with frequent power outages, having a way to recharge all your gadgets is essential. And while Anker is a well-known brand for charging accessories, its new massive 757 PowerHouse portable power station is another beast entirely.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cory Gunther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best USB Flash Drives of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=795657</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/795657/best-usb-flash-drive/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T14:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shopping for a new flash drive? There are tons out there. They may all look the same at a glance, but they’re not. We’ve highlighted some of the best USB flash drives you can buy today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Max Buondonno</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What to Know About the Strawberry Recall]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lifesavvy.com/131281/what-to-know-about-the-strawberry-recall/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lifesavvy.com/131281/what-to-know-about-the-strawberry-recall/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T14:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You probably read about the recent Jif peanut butter recall, but unfortunately, another one is now dominating the news. Here’s what you might want to check in your pantry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shea Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple WWDC 2022: How to Watch and What to Expect]]></title>
        <id>https://www.howtogeek.com/?p=808733</id>
        <link href="https://www.howtogeek.com/808733/apple-wwdc-2022-how-to-watch-and-what-to-expect/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T13:56:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple holds a Worldwide Developers Conference (WWDC) every year, and WWDC 2022 is quickly approaching. Here’s how to watch it, and what Apple might reveal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corbin Davenport</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[can I force password prompt using popup for GPG?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2hkwg/can_i_force_password_prompt_using_popup_for_gpg/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/archlinux/comments/v2hkwg/can_i_force_password_prompt_using_popup_for_gpg/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T13:55:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[on my laptop using BSPWM everytime I have to enter my GPG passphrase there's this little popup thing asking me for my password
 on my desktop running kde plasma I got this curses interface instead. 
 how do I make it so that GPG asks for password using popup prompt like on my laptop? since I sign my git commits, this makes me unable to commit my changes using fugitive plugin in neovim, I have to exit neovim, commit my changes, then open neovim again, which is very inconvenient
 I'm using the exact same dotfiles, so I doubt it has anything to do with this (shell config, env variables and all that)
    submitted by    /u/shkspr_  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch Linux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chiavi crittografiche RSA deboli recuperate con un algoritmo di 380 anni fa]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Chiavi-crittografiche-RSA-deboli-recuperate-con-un-algoritmo-di-380-anni-fa_24592</id>
        <link href="https://www.ilsoftware.it/articoli.asp?tag=Chiavi-crittografiche-RSA-deboli-recuperate-con-un-algoritmo-di-380-anni-fa_24592"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T13:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gli algoritmi crittografici sono essenziali per proteggere i dati scambiati attraverso un mezzo di comunicazione intrinsecamente insicuro qual è la rete Internet.La crittografia asimmetrica in particolare permette a due soggetti o due entità di comunicare a distanza in modo sicuro senza bisogno di essersi prima scambiati reciprocamente 'un segreto' (come può essere una password di decodifica dei dati).Gli sviluppatori, quando realizzano un software o implementano qualunque funzione in hardware che deve gestire dati riservati, sono soliti ricorrere all'utilizzo di algoritmi crittografici oggi considerati affidabili e robusti.In un altro articolo abbiamo visto quanto è davvero sicuro un algoritmo crittografico come RSA e abbiamo chiarito qual è il ruolo dell'operazione di fattorizzazione qua…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IlSoftware.it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>